<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>2003 on JFO Library</title>
    <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/tags/2003/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 2003 on JFO Library</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2003 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://jorjafox.net/library/tags/2003/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Los Angeles Magazine</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2003/los-angeles-magazine/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2003/los-angeles-magazine/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The fight against cancer is a team effort. Nowhere is that more evident than at the annual Komen Las Angeles County Race for the Cure, at the Pasadena Rose Bowl on November 2. Jorja Fox of CBS&amp;rsquo; &lt;em&gt;CSI: Crime Scene Investigation&lt;/em&gt;, who is serving as spokesperson for the cause [&amp;hellip;] felt passionate about joining the fight after losing both her mother and a friend to cancer. &amp;ldquo;One of the keys to having a great life is to get involved in things that you care about.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Remembering her own experiences as the loved one of a cancer victim, Fox is enthusiastic about what funds raised at the Race can accomplish. &amp;ldquo;The Komen Foundation has a tremendous amount of empathy, wisdom and guidance to offer people,&amp;rdquo; says Fox. &amp;ldquo;They&amp;rsquo;re an incredible resource.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>National Examiner</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2003/national-examiner/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2003/national-examiner/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;There&amp;rsquo;s a battle royal going on behind the scenes at CSI: Crime Scene Investigation &amp;#8212; should Gil Grissom leap into the sack with Sara Sidle?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fans of TV&amp;rsquo;s top-rated show, now in its fourth season, think it&amp;rsquo;s a pretty hot drama. But backstage fights over what should happen between the characters played by William Petersen and Jorja Fox make the on-screen happenings seem like winter in Antarctica, say insiders.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;The production team has been torn apart,&amp;rdquo; a source says.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;One group believes workaholic Grissom is so emotionally stunted that he could never have an affair and that&amp;rsquo;s the way he should be played.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;But the rival faction is campaigning for some action between the sheets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;They point out that after all, it&amp;rsquo;s unrealistic to believe that when two available people flirt so much it won&amp;rsquo;t lead to an affair.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;To have them flirt without a sexy outcome is like kissing your sister, and the viewers will start to yawn, they say.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The stars who play the two characters involved can&amp;rsquo;t agree on how far to take things, either.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Petersen, 50, wants the pair to explore their growing attraction, as long as it doesn&amp;rsquo;t turn the show into a soap opera, say insiders.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But Fox, 35, believes that although their constant flirting is a great dynamic for creating tension, a segue into sex would detract from the show&amp;rsquo;s strong stories.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She admits she&amp;rsquo;ll be making goo-goo eyes at Grissom for the foreseeable future.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;I think we&amp;rsquo;re going to have a very personal year for the characters,&amp;rdquo; she reveals, &amp;ldquo;more-so that we&amp;rsquo;ve ever done.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The backstage bickering over the steamy issue has spilled onto the Internet, where fans are airing their opinions online. And now that the new CSI season is in full swing, the debate is healing up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One group of fans even posted an open letter to the shows producers, urging them to press ahead with the Grissom-Sara love match.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;We feel that a relationship would provide a human element to the show,&amp;rdquo; the petition says.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Other online fans agreed, licking their lips at the prospect of the two stodgy characters getting intimate for a change.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But some viewers are squarely against pairing up the investigators in the bedroom.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;It does nothing for the show,&amp;rdquo; one disappointed fan complains.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>93.7 The Buzz</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2003/93.7-the-buzz/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2003/93.7-the-buzz/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;93.7 BZZ is a top-40 station with all of today&amp;rsquo;s new music.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bubba:&lt;/strong&gt; Has it hit you yet that you&amp;rsquo;re on, like, the number one television show in the world?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; No, absolutely not. I don&amp;rsquo;t know if it&amp;rsquo;ll ever really hit me. I don&amp;rsquo;t really know, I mean it&amp;rsquo;s kind of like fantastically overwhelming to think of.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bubba:&lt;/strong&gt; And it&amp;rsquo;s not like you&amp;rsquo;re a bit player in the show, that you like are taking credit for the whole show, you&amp;rsquo;re actually are the show.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; Well that&amp;rsquo;s very nice of you to say that. There&amp;rsquo;s like 140 of us that make the show.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bubba:&lt;/strong&gt; Well I know but you are- you&amp;rsquo;re one of the key elements of that show.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; I get to be there every week, you know. I always have something to do and I got to be there almost from the very, very beginning, which is something new for me. You know I was lucky enough I got to be on two other shows that did really well but I came in- They were already runaway, huge hits by the time I came on and this was the like big wildcard risk, who knew what was gonna happen kind of thing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dave:&lt;/strong&gt; With the popularity of CSI, and your being so busy, that- I would guess that would be enough to make it so you didn&amp;rsquo;t know even how popular the show was or anything. You&amp;rsquo;re so busy doing&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; Yeah, you know, it&amp;rsquo;s very ethereal, you know. It comes out in the newspaper and the ratings and, and everyone&amp;rsquo;s very happy. And I&amp;rsquo;ve never really been a ratings watcher but we shoot up in this very small rural sort of area north of Los Angeles and you&amp;rsquo;re sorta up there. It&amp;rsquo;s almost like being on location every day. And you&amp;rsquo;re just kinda doing what you do and you hear about it and you know, it&amp;rsquo;s??? it&amp;rsquo;s like, you know, being on a magic carpet ride. It&amp;rsquo;s been just incredible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bubba:&lt;/strong&gt; And you&amp;rsquo;re great, by the way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; Well, thank you very much.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bubba:&lt;/strong&gt; Which- which helps.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; It doesn&amp;rsquo;t happen, you know? I mean this doesn&amp;rsquo;t happen to anyone. The odds of this happening to anyone are like one in a billion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dave:&lt;/strong&gt; Someone ??? who was it? &amp;#8212; said you have better odds of getting colon cancer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bubba:&lt;/strong&gt; What a horrible way to think of that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; Yeah, I know.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dave:&lt;/strong&gt; It is kind of a weird analogy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; There are better odds of anything almost happening to you probably than this.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dave:&lt;/strong&gt; So you film an hour and a half north of L.A.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; Yeah.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dave:&lt;/strong&gt; And you drive there every day?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; Well we drive. It&amp;rsquo;s about 45 minutes, it&amp;rsquo;s about 90 minutes round trip. I mean we all usually drive there. Every once in awhile we&amp;rsquo;ll stay up there if we&amp;rsquo;ve got a big grind or sometimes you&amp;rsquo;re just beat and you know. I stayed up there just last week.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bubba:&lt;/strong&gt; Why ??? why do you tape all the way up there?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; Well, originally, you know, there wasn&amp;rsquo;t a lot of money for the show, and we really wanted to focus most of it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bubba:&lt;/strong&gt; Well, that&amp;rsquo;s changed!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; Yeah. Maybe, I don&amp;rsquo;t know. That&amp;rsquo;s focused a lot on the special effects. They really wanted the effects to be good. And also, it&amp;rsquo;s a good master of Vegas. Like up there it&amp;rsquo;s high desert country, and at least the exterior area. If you can&amp;rsquo;t do the city Vegas, which we come down, we shoot in downtown L.A. for that, sometimes or we go to Vegas to get that. But we can do the deserts, and we can do the mountains and a lot of stuff.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dave:&lt;/strong&gt; They always remind me of old Barnaby Jones.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; Nice, thanks, excellent!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dave:&lt;/strong&gt; I think it&amp;rsquo;s cool. I love that area.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bubba:&lt;/strong&gt; I remember the first time I watched CSI. A friend of mine said, &amp;ldquo;You&amp;rsquo;ve gotta watch this show.&amp;rdquo; We work weird hours and we don&amp;rsquo;t get a chance to watch it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; You guys are morning guys, right? Yeah, so that&amp;rsquo;s late for you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bubba:&lt;/strong&gt; But I remember I sat down and watched it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; Thank you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bubba:&lt;/strong&gt; And I was hooked. Immediately. It&amp;rsquo;s one of those shows that if anybody listening knows about it, hears about it, the popularity of it, all you have to do is watch it once. And the one show that stands out in my mind is the show with the uh- the little people. You remember that show?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; That was last year, yeah.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bubba:&lt;/strong&gt; It was the little people convention. How much research went into every single show because-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; Phenomenal amounts done on every show.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bubba:&lt;/strong&gt; There are things in that I never thought about. It was great.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; It was cool. It was sort of the largest assembly of little people actors since Over the Rainbow and before that The Wizard of Oz. So it was really fun and you know a lot of ??? you know a ton of those actors knew each other and it was really cool to work with all those guys. They were great people.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dave:&lt;/strong&gt; The opening song is that the thing that uh you can hear from anywhere in the house, wherever you are, and you hear that, the opening from The Who, and you know, boom!, it&amp;rsquo;s begun.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; That&amp;rsquo;s still, you know, my favorite part of the show. Every week is the song with the credits.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dave:&lt;/strong&gt; Me too! Same thing! Because the way it&amp;rsquo;s edited, with the ??? they do the opening of the show with whatever the scene is or whatever.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; The teaser.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dave:&lt;/strong&gt; And then, boom!, man, right into that. And that song was just so perfect for that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; So compelling. It was unbelievable that we were able to get that song. And it was Billy&amp;rsquo;s idea. Billy Peterson was like, &amp;ldquo;No, this song. This song.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dave:&lt;/strong&gt; No way!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; And everybody&amp;rsquo;s like, &amp;ldquo;We don&amp;rsquo;t have the money for this. No way we&amp;rsquo;re gonna get this song.&amp;rdquo; And then they talked to Pete Townsend and it happened and it was a coup. I mean, it was really an amazing moment to get that song.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bubba:&lt;/strong&gt; Have you ever had a scene where there&amp;rsquo;s a body and obviously it&amp;rsquo;s either an actor.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; I have a lot of scenes where there&amp;rsquo;s a body.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bubba:&lt;/strong&gt; I know. But my point is, it was so realistic looking, so gross looking, that you almost got sick?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; It happens all the time to me. It still happens. I&amp;rsquo;m going into four years of this and that still happens to me on a regular basis.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bubba:&lt;/strong&gt; And I mean even though you know it&amp;rsquo;s either an actor with all kinds of makeup on or a dummy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; Yeah, a live, a real live actor.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bubba:&lt;/strong&gt; And you&amp;rsquo;re like gaaak?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; Yeah, it&amp;rsquo;s pretty gnarly. The special effects guys&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bubba:&lt;/strong&gt; They&amp;rsquo;re amazing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; I think we have the best special effects guys in the business. They&amp;rsquo;re really fantastic between the makeup and the effects that we do and &amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bubba:&lt;/strong&gt; I think the coolest thing is like when they&amp;rsquo;ll show like the scene of someone getting shot but then the bullet hits the body and then they follow the bullet into the body and threw the heart and into the lung.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; Sick and crazy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bubba:&lt;/strong&gt; And you&amp;rsquo;re like, ugh!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dave:&lt;/strong&gt; And you&amp;rsquo;ll sit here and tell us with a straight face that there&amp;rsquo;s nothing erotic about that. *laughter all around* We&amp;rsquo;re talking to Jorja Fox.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; Wait, I&amp;rsquo;m sorry, is that about the dead body or about the bullet that, uh ???&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bubba:&lt;/strong&gt; Jorja, I don&amp;rsquo;t work with him.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dave:&lt;/strong&gt; The new season of CSI starts tonight, 8 PM. Thank you, Jorja Fox.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; Thank you guys so much, and take it easy.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E Online</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2003/e-online/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2003/e-online/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;From copssister: Any scoop on CSI?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The scuttlebutt going around is that producers are planning for Grissom and Sara to hookity-hook it, but that stars William Petersen and Jorja Fox have conflicting opinions on whether they want to. She does; he doesn&amp;rsquo;t.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;From copssister: Have you been able to scrape up info on Without a Trace. It&amp;rsquo;s so good, it made me tape ER and watch it!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
I hear there are office romances on Without a Trace, CSI and CSI: Miami this year.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Living TV</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2003/living-tv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2003/living-tv/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Living TV is &amp;ldquo;Women orientated entertainment&amp;rdquo; and is available on Sky, Telewest and NTL.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Marc:&lt;/strong&gt; Looking quite glamorous is Jorja from CSI.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; Thank you very much.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Marc:&lt;/strong&gt; Chewing gum on the red carpet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; Well it&amp;rsquo;s better than a cigar right?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Marc:&lt;/strong&gt; Ok, you heard it here first, this is a fashion statement, gum chewing, as they say. No let&amp;rsquo;s face it. CSI, the runaway hit, everyone&amp;rsquo;s talking about it, you guys have gotta be feeling pretty good about yourselves.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; Thank you, I think we&amp;rsquo;re, we&amp;rsquo;re the luckiest people we know, ya know, we&amp;rsquo;re just riding the tail of a comet right now, very humble, hungry, excited, I mean it, it doesn&amp;rsquo;t happen to people, this doesn&amp;rsquo;t happen to people.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Marc:&lt;/strong&gt; Have you learned anything now that you&amp;rsquo;re a brainiac in the lab? Have you learned anything about a little forensic pathology and so on?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; What&amp;rsquo;s &amp;lsquo;forensic&amp;rsquo; mean? laughter&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Marc:&lt;/strong&gt; If ya can&amp;rsquo;t spell the word, ya can&amp;rsquo;t be on the show, that&amp;rsquo;s the rule. Jorja chuckles No, do you ya take any of the information and sit there at cocktail parties and go &amp;#8216;do you know?&amp;rsquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; Yeah, but ya know, people get up and leave usually, I don&amp;rsquo;t know why&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Marc:&lt;/strong&gt; That&amp;rsquo;s the story of my career darling, story of my career.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; Usually I don&amp;rsquo;t talk much.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Marc:&lt;/strong&gt; Thank you very much for stopping by, best of luck on the show and the season, and I think she can loosen up a little, that&amp;rsquo;s my vote.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Guide</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2003/tv-guide-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2003/tv-guide-5/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Question:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I enjoy your column, but I had to throw my two cents in on the&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;CSI&lt;/em&gt; romance issue. I think you were hasty in saying that a pairing&lt;br /&gt;
would be disastrous. The show already deals with a tremendous amount of&lt;br /&gt;
non-case driven material &amp;mdash; just look at how Catherine Willows is&lt;br /&gt;
portrayed: single mother (as is mentioned almost every episode), former&lt;br /&gt;
stripper, has a murdered, violent ex-husband, her possible father may be a&lt;br /&gt;
killer&amp;hellip; I think you see my point. &lt;em&gt;CSI&lt;/em&gt; would never become a soap,&lt;br /&gt;
but a relationship between the two most interesting characters (in my&lt;br /&gt;
opinion), Sara Sidle and Gil Grissom, could flesh the characters out more&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;mdash; when given, as &lt;strong&gt;Anthony Zuiker&lt;/strong&gt; has said, in doses. I know I&lt;br /&gt;
would love to see it, just as I also love the cases. To me, it is all about&lt;br /&gt;
balance, and the show is not balanced right now. We know much more about&lt;br /&gt;
Catherine than any other character, and last season seemed too weighed down&lt;br /&gt;
by her melodramas. I would love to see more of the rest of the team,&lt;br /&gt;
especially Sara Sidle. &lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; is a wonderful, radiant actress who&lt;br /&gt;
deserves more and better stories, as I think she is vastly underused.&lt;br /&gt;
Thanks for letting me rant. I feel better now. &amp;mdash; Michelle&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Matt:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Glad to oblige. And I should say for the record that after the column&lt;br /&gt;
ran noting I had heard more from Grissom-Catherine fans than from&lt;br /&gt;
Grissom-Sara fans, the other side weighed in. I was also informed that fan&lt;br /&gt;
sites and fan fictions also favor Grissom and Sara. So be it. I just watch&lt;br /&gt;
TV, and am rarely able to indulge detours into the deeper depths of online&lt;br /&gt;
fandom. I still think &lt;em&gt;CSI&lt;/em&gt; would be wise parceling out these doses of&lt;br /&gt;
implied romance in very small and cautious doses.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Guide</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2003/tv-guide-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2003/tv-guide-4/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Question:&lt;/strong&gt; Okay, what is up with CSI? In the beginning it was no romance,&lt;br /&gt;
strictly science. Well now, all the hype is that Gil and Sara are going to&lt;br /&gt;
fall in love, or whatever they&amp;rsquo;re saying. I mean, what about the finale?&lt;br /&gt;
Why didn&amp;rsquo;t they have Gil tell Sara about his surgery, if the master plan is&lt;br /&gt;
to have them together? Why would he tell Catherine if really he wants to be&lt;br /&gt;
with Sara? It makes no sense, and they are just blowing the finale off like&lt;br /&gt;
it never happened. Everyone makes a big deal that Sara wiped chalk off&lt;br /&gt;
Gil&amp;rsquo;s cheek, yet Catherine hugs him, and not a word is said. I am just so&lt;br /&gt;
confused. Can you maybe clarify what exactly the writers are trying to&lt;br /&gt;
accomplish? ? Janine&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Matt:&lt;/strong&gt; From what little I know of the situation, the producers will admit to&lt;br /&gt;
a sexual tension between Gil and Sara, and maybe even between Gil and&lt;br /&gt;
Catherine. But if this is why you&amp;rsquo;re tuning in CSI, I think you&amp;rsquo;re destined&lt;br /&gt;
to be disappointed no matter who you want Gil to lean on, hug, kiss,&lt;br /&gt;
whatever. (My mail favors Gil and Catherine, no question about it. Very&lt;br /&gt;
little support for Gil and Sara.) But I&amp;rsquo;m all for CSI being all science, no&lt;br /&gt;
romance. A laboratory liaison on this show would be as disastrous a mistake&lt;br /&gt;
as showing Jack McCoy actually hitting on any of his lovely ADAs on Law &amp;amp;&lt;br /&gt;
Order. I can understand why the writers would add little hints of&lt;br /&gt;
on-the-job attraction in an otherwise just-the-facts show just to shake&lt;br /&gt;
things up a little, but in this case it has become a real distraction for&lt;br /&gt;
CSI fans. Which makes me think it&amp;rsquo;s dangerous territory they&amp;rsquo;re all better&lt;br /&gt;
off just avoiding. I tune in for the weird cases, the fascinating gadgets,&lt;br /&gt;
and the pleasure of watching some good actors play detective. If I want a&lt;br /&gt;
soap opera, I&amp;rsquo;ve got plenty of other places to go.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New York Post</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2003/new-york-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2003/new-york-post/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;ONE question romantically inclined TV audiences never tire of asking is &amp;ldquo;Will they or won&amp;rsquo;t they?&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These days, the most unlikely TV couple who&amp;rsquo;s keeping them guessing is &amp;ldquo; CSI: Crime Scene Investigation &amp;ldquo; &amp;rsquo;s Sara Sidle and her boss, Gil Grissom, played by Jorja Fox and William Petersen.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you&amp;rsquo;ve been focusing on the series&amp;rsquo; parade of autopsies rather than its more subtle relationship dynamics, you missed one of last season&amp;rsquo;s most heartbreaking below-the-radar attempts at pairing off.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;I don&amp;rsquo;t think we&amp;rsquo;ve seen the end of that story line,&amp;rdquo; Fox told The Post.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;I think we&amp;rsquo;re going to have a very personal year for the characters this year, more so than we&amp;rsquo;ve ever done.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Online chat rooms were ablaze with opinions of the budding romance, with one fan summing it up as follows: Either get together or not, but stop the big tease.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The chatter was obviously unaware that it&amp;rsquo;s the big tease that rachets up interest and makes imaginations race overtime.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Billy [Petersen] and I both love the fact that people have different takes on it,&amp;rdquo; she said.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;It&amp;rsquo;s kind of a little bit controversial. It takes on its own substance. People read into it what they want to.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The fictional Sidle, who has pretty much buried her feelings for Grissom, got rebuffed toward the end of last season when she tentatively expressed her wish that they take it further.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fox says Grissom responds by basically telling Sidle, &amp;ldquo;She &amp;lsquo;wouldn&amp;rsquo;t have the chance of going out with him,&amp;rsquo; ever! He didn&amp;rsquo;t know what to do with it.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, is Grissom a simpleton or does he suspect he might have a heart?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;I think he&amp;rsquo;s very much aware of it,&amp;rdquo; Fox said.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not that these two characters are paragons of relationship savvy. As one online fan wrote, they&amp;rsquo;re &amp;ldquo;two workaholics with poor social skills,&amp;rdquo; which prompted Fox to explain that &amp;ldquo;the show lends itself to that - so much of what they do is thinking.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fox, 35, who made her mark playing &amp;ldquo; ER &amp;rdquo; &amp;rsquo;s feisty Dr. Maggie Doyle, concedes that this past season her CSI character has become a much more vulnerable character.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;I suffered a couple of really big blows for her personally,&amp;rdquo; she said, referring to betrayals by a boyfriend and another friend, not to mention the explosion at the lab. And her feelings for Grissom.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Outside of &amp;ldquo;CSI,&amp;rdquo; Fox is one of the core members of Honeypot Productions, a theater group that puts up shows in the open air during California summers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The group has been putting its efforts into an original musical they&amp;rsquo;re considering adapting as a film. But right now, it&amp;rsquo;s back to the crime lab and new scripts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;We&amp;rsquo;re leaving it to the writers to follow their hearts, because they&amp;rsquo;re always going to be annoying someone, so you can&amp;rsquo;t win,&amp;rdquo; she said.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Herald Sun TV Guide</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2003/herald-sun-tv-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2003/herald-sun-tv-guide/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;They have an expression that&amp;rsquo;s so popular among the producers, writers and cast of CSI that they made it the title of a two part episode that will open the show&amp;rsquo;s next season: Assume nothing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mainly it concerns the scientific unravelling of the most minute clues left in the wake of murders, when the CSI team moves in with its hi-tech equipment. But if you want to know about something that appears to be far more simple, say a personal relationship between the CSI team&amp;rsquo;s aloof boss, Gil Grissom and TV&amp;rsquo;s sexiest scientist Sara Sidle you can apply the same rule.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Danny Cannon a series executive producer and frequent director, says Grissom will &amp;ldquo;become more engaged with the world&amp;rdquo; as the show continues.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;You keep hearing that from writers, right?&amp;rdquo; Petersen, 50, responds when asked to explain the phrase. &amp;ldquo;I dont know what that means either, but I heard it, too. I think one thing Grissom has learned is that he either has much to learn or much to forget. I think he&amp;rsquo;s very strong but he has his limitations and he focuses on what he&amp;rsquo;s good at. It&amp;rsquo;s not that he&amp;rsquo;s never been out with a woman, it&amp;rsquo;s just that he&amp;rsquo;s never been in love with a woman, so that&amp;rsquo;s not a priority for him.There&amp;rsquo;s some change going on in him, some midlife situation he&amp;rsquo;s going to have to address, but how he addresses it I have no idea.&amp;rdquo; Petersen means, of course, that we should assume nothing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;If he&amp;rsquo;s smart he&amp;rsquo;ll chase me, right?&amp;rdquo; quips 35 year old Fox.&amp;ldquo;I came in originally as a love interest for Grissom and there is a back story then they changed their minds on that. So we know there&amp;rsquo;s some history between them but we dont really know what it is. Still I think the dance will be played out.&amp;rdquo; Then Fox pauses and adds &amp;ldquo;But I dont know for sure.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To Anthony Zuiker, who created CSI a romantic interlude between two of his main characters is a moot point anyway.&amp;ldquo;We&amp;rsquo;re a forensic procedural drama at heart,&amp;rdquo; he says, a description which in itself would be likely to drain the romance out of anyone quicker than you can say &amp;ldquo;scapel&amp;rdquo;. When we go into personal relationships in doses- I stress the word doses- it&amp;rsquo;s so much richer when Jorja Fox wipes chalk off Billy Petersen&amp;rsquo;s cheek, or he might call her &amp;lsquo;honey&amp;rsquo;. It cames totally out of left field and when you hear those things it really gets everybody talking and excited versus us doing those beats constantly from page 0ne to page 60. It just wouldnt have the impact.&amp;rdquo; So the balance between lab and love is likely to remain skewed heavily towars lab, althogh Zuiker of course adds: &amp;ldquo;But in short, assume nothing.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Love the &#39;70s</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2003/i-love-the-70s/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2003/i-love-the-70s/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;I Love the 70s&amp;rdquo; is a television mini-series shown on VH1, and was created after the success of &amp;ldquo;I Love the &amp;lsquo;80s&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;##Appearances##&lt;br /&gt;
Jorja appeared in 5 episodes of the miniseries:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1970 - Original Airdate 08.18.2003&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1973 - Original Airdate 08.19.2003&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1974 - Original Airdate 08.20.2003&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1976 - Original Airdate 08.21.2003&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1977 - Original Airdate 08.21.2003&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;##See Also##&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.vh1.com/shows/dyn/i_love_the_70s/series.jhtml&#34;&gt;VH1 - I Love the &amp;lsquo;70s&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Sierra Club</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2003/the-sierra-club/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2003/the-sierra-club/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The scene: the Utah desert, 35 miles from Salt Lake City. Tons of nuclear waste could soon be rumbling toward the Skull Valley Indian Reservation, whose band of Goshutes is already beset by nearby nerve-gas storage and hazardous-waste incinerators. Enter James Cromwell, who played the U.S. president in the nuclear-weapons thriller The Sum of All Fears. In 2002, the actor addressed senators in Utah and traveled to Washington, D.C., to fight a proposed storage facility for 44,000 tons of high-level nuclear waste on Goshute land. &amp;ldquo;The hazardous materials will be transported on trains and trucks through highly populated areas,&amp;rdquo; he said at a press conference at the Capitol. &amp;ldquo;The storage land is on an earthquake fault line and subject to flooding. The whole process must be flawless-or there could be dire consequences.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another Hollywood green group, Earth Communications Office, was founded in 1989 by entertainment attorney Bonnie Reiss, who discovered that many of the biggest stars were willing to bring some high gloss to the realm of the tree-hugger. Boasting a member roster that includes Cromwell, Pierce Brosnan, and Kevin Bacon, ECO made its mark with emotional public-service announcements shown before the main features in movie theatres all over the globe. Footage of pristine waters, roiling clouds, leaping dolphins, and time-lapsed sunsets with Willie Nelson singing &amp;ldquo;What a Wonderful World&amp;rdquo; as soundtrack encouraged viewers to &amp;ldquo;reduce, reuse, and recycle.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;ECO&amp;rsquo;s current campaign addresses global warming and the steps we can take to change our fossil-fueling ways. Click on climatestar.org and up pops a muscular Kevin Bacon who pronounces, &amp;ldquo;Six degrees can make a world of difference. Not separation-temperature.&amp;rdquo; Bacon has played troubled kids and bad guys and commands big bucks for his work. But he and Joshua Jackson (TV&amp;rsquo;s Dawson&amp;rsquo;s Creek), Jacqueline Obradors (NYPD Blue), and Jorja Fox (CSI) have volunteered their names and faces to this Web site&amp;rsquo;s worthy cause, easing the transition to the site&amp;rsquo;s somewhat unglamorous &amp;ldquo;Climate Facts&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Carbon Footprint Calculator.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>USA Today Weekend</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2003/usa-today-weekend-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2003/usa-today-weekend-2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;With all the comic book-inspired movies out lately, we asked super celebrities which hero they&amp;rsquo;d most like to play.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s a lineup&lt;/strong&gt; that would leave even Doctor Doom shaking in his steel booties. Spurred by the success three years ago of &amp;ldquo;X-Men&amp;rdquo; and last year&amp;rsquo;s smash hit &amp;ldquo;Spider-Man&amp;rdquo;, which spun its way to being one of the highest-grossing movies of all time, comic-book films are enjoying a golden age. &amp;ldquo;Daredevil&amp;rdquo; premiered in February with a $42.5 million opening weekend, &amp;ldquo;X2&amp;rdquo; has raked in more than $200 million so far, and as of press time &amp;ldquo;The Hulk&amp;rdquo; was set for a monstrous opening June 20 &amp;#8212; all of which bodes well for next weekend&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;The League of Extraordinary Gentlemen&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There&amp;rsquo;s more where those came from: Projects in development or production include sequels to &amp;ldquo;Spider-Man&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Daredevil&amp;rdquo; (plus an Elektra spinoff) and features starring icons such as Batman, Superman and the Fantastic Four as well as lesser-known do-gooders like the Punisher, Hellboy, Catwoman, Iron Man, Namor the Sub-Mariner, Ghost Rider, Luke Cage and Iron Fist. And comic companies such as Marvel and DC are laughing &amp;#8212; like the Joker &amp;#8212; all the way to the bank.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So why are guys and girls with superpowers ruling Hollywood?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;We call it &amp;lsquo;comics,&amp;rsquo; and it&amp;rsquo;s sort of self-deprecating, because this is really great literature,&amp;rdquo; says Avi Arad, president of Marvel Studios. &amp;ldquo;No one will wonder why they make movies based on Tom Clancy [books], but they&amp;rsquo;re trying to figure this one out. What&amp;rsquo;s really interesting is if you&amp;rsquo;re a filmmaker or an actor or a studio exec, you can open a comic book and you&amp;rsquo;ve got storyboards, probably the most detailed storyboards you&amp;rsquo;ll ever see. Then, you can see the movie.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, in an effort to help scads of casting directors trying to fit the right celebrity to the right crime fighter (Britney Spears as a singing She-Hulk, perhaps?), we asked stars: If you could be in a movie based on a comic book, whose brightly colored tights would you most like to slip on?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox (&amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo;):&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;ldquo;I wasn&amp;rsquo;t allowed to read comic books when I was a kid. My well-meaning mother didn&amp;rsquo;t consider them &amp;lsquo;literature.&amp;rsquo; Instead, I read a lot of Stephen King novels and any other horror [and] suspense stuff I could get my hands on. So I don&amp;rsquo;t know &amp;hellip; but it would be really cool to play somebody&amp;rsquo;s hero.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WTEV CBS Flordia</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2003/wtev-cbs-flordia/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2003/wtev-cbs-flordia/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The producers of hit TV drama CSI: Crime Scene Investigation are stepping up security on the show&amp;rsquo;s California set after cast members received a barrage of death threat mail and calls.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sickos claiming to be fans have been getting too close to stars like Marg Helgenberger and Jorja Fox - uncovering personal phone numbers and addresses, and demanding to meet them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A set insider says, &amp;ldquo;Producers didn&amp;rsquo;t take the threats lightly. They immediately brought in a private security firm to work on the set and then warned everyone associated with the show about the dangers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;The show is a huge hit, but it has also caught the attention of some real sickos who are obsessed with autopsies.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CSI Season 3 DVD extras</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2003/CSI_Season_3_Dvd_Extras_%282003%29/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2003/CSI_Season_3_Dvd_Extras_%282003%29/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;crash-and-burn:bc34ae24366084c3a1c1117294a3d832&#34;&gt;Crash and Burn&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; You know, Sara Sidle had a very dark year in season 3; she had a tough one, she really had a tough one. It really started, uh, I would say, in January, about midway through the season. Ah, the first thing that happens is, is, a very good friend of hers betrays her very personally. And the next time we see Sara, her boyfriend, it turns out, has a girlfriend and he also betrays her.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; And I think for her, you know, the type of person that she is and what she does for a living, she&amp;rsquo;s so sure that she knows the truth about everyone, and to find out that two people she was very very close to were, were lying to her all along is a pretty hard thing for her to digest. You know, just above and beyond the fact that these relationships both go sour but then &amp;#8216;wow, that somebody, she was fooled, she was tricked&amp;rsquo; by people she was close to. Then, ah, we see her again in another episode and the lab blows up and she, she walks away from the explosion, her and Greg Sanders get blown up together, and that was a very hard thing, I think for her, you know, personally, and, and the episode ends with-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;play-with-fire:bc34ae24366084c3a1c1117294a3d832&#34;&gt;Play With Fire&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;ndash; a pretty certain refusal from Grissom that anything will ever happen between the two of them, so, that was, that season 3 for Sara was &amp;ldquo;hard&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; [Director] Danny [Cannon] is fast, he&amp;rsquo;s like the lightning bolt director, and everybody loves, you know, just starting out with him they know that they&amp;rsquo;re gonna get, they&amp;rsquo;re gonna have a shorter day with him and that things are going to move very quickly and people really like that, you know, it&amp;rsquo;s, it&amp;rsquo;s, when you&amp;rsquo;re on show 12 and you&amp;rsquo;ve been working for five months the idea of having a short day is really good.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Star Magazine</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2003/star-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2003/star-1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;CSI star Jorja Fox is tired of looking like a dowdy stiff. She thinks her lab-tech character Sara should be able to show as much skin as the cadavers in the Las Vegas morgue. What prompted this sudden change? The single star was horrified when she began getting calls from pals asking if she was pregnant - because she looks so heavy on TV in lab coats and baggy shirts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She immediately had her handlers place a call to the show&amp;rsquo;s honchos demanding that next season she get a makeover so she can show off her stuff. A pal tells Star that after three years of hiding under lab coats as Dr. Doyle on ER and another three years on CSI, foxy Jorja is itching to slip into some belly-baring outfits like her competing CSI:Miami beauty Emily Proctor gets to wear.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>