<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Company on Fans of Le Fox Library</title>
    <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/tags/company/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Company on Fans of Le Fox Library</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://jorjafox.net/library/tags/company/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Honeypot Productions</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/honeypot/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/honeypot/</guid>
      <description>Honeypot Productions (also known as HoneyPot Productions) is an independent theater company in Los Angeles.
Jorja Fox and many of her friends are the founders, and through the company they write, produce and star in many of their own works. According to what she said a TV Guide interview, HoneyPot was formed in either 1998 or 1999; she met fellow Honeypot members Katherine Kendall and Suzanne Mara during the filming of Food for the Heart in 1998.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seafox Productions</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/seafox/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/seafox/</guid>
      <description> Seafox Productions is an independent film, television and theater company based in Los Angeles, California. It is owned by Sea Turtle Inc.
Currently, Seafox Productions focuses on documentary and biographical projects that highlight the critical inter-connectedness between humans and the natural world.
Staff  Jorja Fox - President Jonathan Grant - Chief Operating Officer  Projects  Extinction Soup Lion Ark How I Became An Elephant Stay Forever: The Life and Music of Dusty Springfield  See Also  Seafox Productions  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>