<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>2015 on JFO Library</title>
    <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/tags/2015/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 2015 on JFO Library</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 24 Oct 2015 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://jorjafox.net/library/tags/2015/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Extra at the EMA Awards Green Carpet</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2015/ema-awards/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Oct 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2015/ema-awards/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Renee Bargh:&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;hellip; Ah but first up we&amp;rsquo;ve got Jorja Fox from &lt;em&gt;CSI&lt;/em&gt;. Hi, how are you?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; You look amazing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Renee:&lt;/strong&gt; You love wonderful.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; Thank you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Renee:&lt;/strong&gt; You look great. So tell me, why is it so important to be at this event?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; I think it&amp;rsquo;s one of the most important events that you could attend in Los Angeles. Bringing attention to environmental awareness, which is at such a critical, frightening stage right now. I&amp;rsquo;m super excited to celebrate &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://jorjafox.net/library/library/advocacy/racing-extinction/&#34;&gt;Racing Extinction&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt; tonight, I&amp;rsquo;ve had the pleasure of seeing it already. It&amp;rsquo;s one of the greatest films I&amp;rsquo;ve ever seen.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Renee:&lt;/strong&gt; Really?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; Yeah.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Renee:&lt;/strong&gt; Why so?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; There&amp;rsquo;s a context that the filmmakers are able to sort of just put everything in perspective, and share it in such a way that you feel it cerebrally. You feel it in your heart, you feel it through your body. You just want to get up and do something. It&amp;rsquo;s also a hopeful film, believe it or not. You don&amp;rsquo;t leave the theater going &amp;lsquo;Oh well. Everything&amp;rsquo;s lost.&amp;rsquo; Which is great.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Renee:&lt;/strong&gt; That&amp;rsquo;s amazing. That you so much for being here. We&amp;rsquo;re gonna let you get down the carpet, &amp;lsquo;cause everyone wants to talk to you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; Thank you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Renee:&lt;/strong&gt; But we&amp;rsquo;ll see you inside. Thank you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; Thank you.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Insider</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2015/tvinsider/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Oct 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2015/tvinsider/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;in-praise-of-csi-s-happy-ending:ae6661f2a439b56472bd0f6031fa6455&#34;&gt;In Praise of CSI&amp;rsquo;s Happy Ending&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Question:&lt;/strong&gt; Several years ago, I wrote to you regarding my extreme disappointment in &lt;em&gt;CSI&lt;/em&gt; for divorcing Grissom and Sara, the series&amp;rsquo; &amp;ldquo;long ship&amp;rdquo; known as GSR. Well, you were the voice of reason, saying that you hoped William Petersen would be back for the end. Thankfully, you were right. Although I still think they should not have been separated, the end of the finale was oh so satisfying. Grissom and Sara sailing off into the sunset was a much-welcomed cliché. The finale was good, old-school &lt;em&gt;CSI&lt;/em&gt; with lots of throwbacks to the past, and the ending was absolutely beautiful. Nicely done for a show about death. The onscreen magic of Petersen and Jorja Fox will be missed, but the memories now are all good ones. Thanks to the cast and crew, and to Anthony Zuiker, for making it happen. — &lt;em&gt;Jen&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Matt Roush:&lt;/strong&gt; Even if the sailing off into the sunset fadeout was a bit corny, it seemed appropriate, and most important, satisfying to the fans. When wrapping up a show with this much history and baggage, giving the faithful viewer a payoff should be a top priority. (Are you listening, &lt;em&gt;Castle&lt;/em&gt;?) If Grissom hadn&amp;rsquo;t come back for the final chapter, it would have been much more disappointing for everyone. So kudos for sure.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lylapalooza</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2015/lylapalooza/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2015/lylapalooza/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;CSI star Jorja Fox takes time out to chat with Lyla about dogs, insects, and ice cream. Special guest appearance by Belle the puppy.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lyla:&lt;/strong&gt; This is Lylapalooza and we have Jorja Fox on our show today. Hello, Jorja, how are you today?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; I am very good, Lyla, how are you doing?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lyla:&lt;/strong&gt; Good. This is my shnuffler. Shnuffle. Do you have anything to say?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Belle the Puppy:** *silence*&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lyla:&lt;/strong&gt; Okay! So.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; Profound.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lyla:&lt;/strong&gt; Yes. For our first question. Jorja, what would your favorite color be?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; I think my favorite color, and it changes a lot but right now it&amp;rsquo;s blue. Cuz it reminds me of the ocean and sky and the nighttime.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lyla:&lt;/strong&gt; Yes. The same with me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; Oh really? Profound.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lyla:&lt;/strong&gt; I also really like orange right now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; Me too! Cuz it&amp;rsquo;s like the sun.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lyla:&lt;/strong&gt; Mmm hmm! And the sand.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; Yes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lyla:&lt;/strong&gt; For our second question today, with Jorja Fox. Jorja &amp;hellip; Hmm. What&amp;rsquo;s your favorite insect?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; My favorite insect is dragonflies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lyla:&lt;/strong&gt; I personally like bumblebees.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; Bumblebees are amazing. And you know what else? Maybe fireflies too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lyla:&lt;/strong&gt; Oh yes! And ladybugs!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; Ladybugs, of course! It&amp;rsquo;s hard to- you can&amp;rsquo;t maybe pick one favorite.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lyla:&lt;/strong&gt; This is hard! What is your favorite animal?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; My favorite animal has to be my dog, Bexar. She&amp;rsquo;s like a poodle mix. But her full name is Bexar County Rodeo Princess. She&amp;rsquo;s from Texas.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lyla:&lt;/strong&gt; That makes a lot of sense.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; Thank you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lyla:&lt;/strong&gt; Okay. What is your favorite article of clothing?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; My favorite article of clothing is sunglasses.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lyla:&lt;/strong&gt; I like sweatshirts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; Sweatshirts are good.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lyla:&lt;/strong&gt; What is your favorite &amp;hellip; hmm &amp;hellip; way to help animals?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; My favorite way to help animals is to &amp;hellip; not eat them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lyla:&lt;/strong&gt; My favorite way to help animals is &amp;hellip; I don&amp;rsquo;t like to litter. I never litter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; You don&amp;rsquo;t do it?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lyla:&lt;/strong&gt; I don&amp;rsquo;t litter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; Me either. No, that&amp;rsquo;s terrible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lyla:&lt;/strong&gt; So bad for the earth.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; Bad for the seals and the sea turtles and the dolphins.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lyla:&lt;/strong&gt; And everything that can eat stuff off the ground.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; Yes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lyla:&lt;/strong&gt; And the sea.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; Like Belle!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lyla:&lt;/strong&gt; Like Belle! Like baby. Okay. For our sixth question, what&amp;rsquo;s your favorite type of music?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; I love all music. Like every kind, it&amp;rsquo;s my favorite thing in the whole world. But if I had to pick a favorite style it would probably be &amp;hellip; like &amp;hellip; Jazz. Maybe?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lyla:&lt;/strong&gt; Jorja! What&amp;rsquo;s your favorite type of ice cream?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; Well, Lyla. I think my favorite kind of ice cream is called Kind Cream. And it&amp;rsquo;s the cookies&amp;rsquo;n&amp;rsquo;cream flavor. Classic cookies&amp;rsquo;n&amp;rsquo;cream. And they used the cookies they get them from Baby Cakes Bakery in New York City. What about you?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lyla:&lt;/strong&gt; I like &amp;hellip; Hmmm &amp;hellip; So my three favorites would probably be- I just have three favorites because I can&amp;rsquo;t choose.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; You can&amp;rsquo;t choose!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lyla:&lt;/strong&gt; So I have cotton candy, chocolate, aaaaand &amp;hellip; So there&amp;rsquo;s an ice cream store on Fire Island, it&amp;rsquo;s called Unfriendly&amp;rsquo;s Ice Cream, and one of their flavors is called Play-doh. It&amp;rsquo;s vanilla ice cream dyed yellow, with little bits of cookie chunks in it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; Wow!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lyla:&lt;/strong&gt; And they&amp;rsquo;re dyed blue and orange and red to look like play-doh. This is Lylapalooza signing out! Good bye! Goodbye!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; Bye!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shark Allies</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2015/shark-allies/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2015/shark-allies/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Jorja Fox talks about her personal connection to the ocean and her perception of trophy hunting and the misrepresentation of sharks in the media.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Our Connection to the Ocean&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I spend as much time on the water as I can. I&amp;rsquo;ve been bodyboarding since I was about six and surfing for about the last fifteen years. So I&amp;rsquo;m there, you know, several times a week if I can be.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A long time ago, when you think of how mankind kind of evolved on earth, it was this battle&lt;br /&gt;
between man and nature. Man needed to dominate nature in order to survive. And we won that battle a long time ago. Now, you know, our job and and our kids&amp;rsquo; job is to figure out the balance on the planet. I guess at the end of the day, it&amp;rsquo;s really important to know that that without the ocean, human survival will end. We need fish for our own survival and we need water and oxygen for out own survival. The ocean makes the bulk of the world&amp;rsquo;s oxygen. If the oceans are sick, then the balance of the entire planet will fall apart.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We cannot survive without a healthy ocean.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sharks and the Media&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The shark programing, I think it&amp;rsquo;s been very, very unfortunate you know in the last twenty or thirty years. On one hand, we know more about sharks than we ever did, and we&amp;rsquo;ve been exposed to sharks more than we could have ever imagined. But so much of that information has been negative information or kind of information that&amp;rsquo;s more for to instill fear in people or to instill cheap kinda thrills, action packed thrills.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The media, whether it&amp;rsquo;s been intentional or not, often focuses on stories that are gonna have a shock value for people, that are going to get people&amp;rsquo;s attention. So, often, that&amp;rsquo;s what sharks have have done inadvertently to people, or how people have been harmed by sharks. But I think what would be really important piece of this puzzle is if the media could start focusing on on how we are affecting short survival.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Trophy Hunting&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sport fishing, in my opinion, and hunting for sport is kind of something that should go the way the history books. Something that people did. We don&amp;rsquo;t do that anymore. Now we&amp;rsquo;re actually trying to create sustainable habitat for wildlife and for sea life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There was a time where lead paint was a great idea and where asbestos was a great idea. And both of them are sort of human ingenuity and we kind of&lt;br /&gt;
realized &amp;ldquo;Okay, well that was then and let&amp;rsquo;s build things differently now and and and do things differently now because that&amp;rsquo;s not sustainable for us anymore.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well me, personally, I&amp;rsquo;m not a fan of any kind of hunting and that would include commercial and sport fishing. It&amp;rsquo;s just not something that I really understand and &amp;hellip; I think I would invite anybody who does enjoy that activity to take a few moments and ask themselves what about killing is so satisfying for them. I&amp;rsquo;m not really sure where the the sport or the fun is in that and I would encourage people just ask that question to themselves.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Channel Guide Magazine</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2015/channel-guide-magazine/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2015/channel-guide-magazine/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At some point in the episode, another woman blows herself up, this time, it&amp;rsquo;s a Lady Heather doppleganger outside of the mistresses&amp;rsquo; house. When the lookalike&amp;rsquo;s car explodes, Brass catches on fire, but once he&amp;rsquo;s extinguished by a fast-acting Sara, he stands there like a total bad-ass, proving once again that the former captain&amp;rsquo;s cajones are made of â¦ well, brass.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Gil&amp;rsquo;s in Vegas, sees his ex-wife Sara (#Awkward), and runs into a chipper redhead who flummoxes him to no end. Gil acts like an old, confused man.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lady Heather is older, and I still want to slap her smug mug SOoooo hard, which is a testament to the sexy, complex and challenging character that actress Melinda Clarke has played intermittently throughout the series.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sara still hates Lady Heather. Me too. I&amp;rsquo;m totally #TeamSara.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sara and Gil are divorced, but Sara still loves the bug-loving lug. And finally, we get to see Gil talk to some bugs, because it&amp;rsquo;s just not a Gil-centric episode if we don&amp;rsquo;t&amp;rsquo; get to see him 1) Talk to bugs, 2) use the Latin name for a bug, 3) turn his head quizzically and look at something/ someone. Ding! Ding! Ding! Three for three! Bonus: Gil got to wear lots of goofy looking-hats in this episode. And, he seemingly trained bees in a matter of minutes, like the bug-whisperer he&amp;rsquo;s always been.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The bees tell Gil where the murder is (in a scary, yet technologically awesome, shack!). Lo and behold! It&amp;rsquo;s the Green Mile guy. Called it. He&amp;rsquo;s got a bomb vest, and he&amp;rsquo;s set up a bunch of bombs in a Las Vegas parking structure; requiring Catherine, Greg and Morgan to do some fancy wire-cutting. And even though she&amp;rsquo;s been on the show since Season 11, when she was in a L.A/Las Vegas crossover episode, Morgan&amp;rsquo;s hands still have the shakes. Once they&amp;rsquo;re not dead, Morgan and Greg hug and I hope for a moment that they&amp;rsquo;ll make out, because when has Greg ever gotten any action? He&amp;rsquo;s always been in friend zone.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Gil convinces the mad bomber/ murderer not to blow himself up, because he deduces that the bomb vest isn&amp;rsquo;t even activated. Murder man hates Gil because he blames Gil for Lady Heather leaving her role as a dom, and then stopping the boning her therapy patients, and then stopping her psychiatry practice altogether. Guy really loves his Lady Heather time. Gil tells a story about a whale whose mate can&amp;rsquo;t hear his song, which makes no sense even though I think it&amp;rsquo;s supposed to be about the man&amp;rsquo;s unrequited love for LH, but is sad, nonetheless.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Catherine wants out of the FBI and wants to gank the Director&amp;rsquo;s job that Sara wants. What mom doesn&amp;rsquo;t want to be her daughter&amp;rsquo;s boss?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Gil wraps everything up with Lady Heather (I don&amp;rsquo;t care if she&amp;rsquo;s a doctor, she&amp;rsquo;ll always be a dominatrix to me) and he thanks her for making able to love someone like Sara. It&amp;rsquo;s sweet, but he&amp;rsquo;s also giving her some police procedural info, which makes me scratch my head: Why are they letting the consultant run the case?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But Sara gets the director&amp;rsquo;s position, and even takes photos with her new badge so that&amp;rsquo;ll be #Awkward due to Catherine&amp;rsquo;s conversation of about 20 seconds ago.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And for a few seconds, you think that the Sara and Gil ship has sailed, but with a gentle nudge from newbie Lindsay, Sara watches Lady Heather&amp;rsquo;s statement interview with Gil where he admits his love for Miss Sidle. Suddenly, Sara arrives at Gil&amp;rsquo;s San Diego boat dock in a taxi, because clearly Sara&amp;rsquo;s rather call a cab than ask her longtime pak Nick Stokes for a ride. (Another missed chance for George Eads to do something in this ep.). Gil is wearing yet-another hat, this time it&amp;rsquo;s one that he stole from Ernest Hemmingway. Sarah boards Gil&amp;rsquo;s ship and when they embrace, you know that it&amp;rsquo;ll be Gil + Sara forever. While they sail away from San Diego, I can&amp;rsquo;t help wonder why Sara brought only her small messenger bag with her, and I hope they didn&amp;rsquo;t run that picture of her shaking hands with the commish in the newspaper because she&amp;rsquo;s gone. I guess Catherine gets the job as CSI director by default. Because really, with Sara gone, it&amp;rsquo;s the inmates running the asylum with Morgan, Greg and Hodges (and now newbie Lindsay) left in the department.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CinemaBlend</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2015/cinemablend/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2015/cinemablend/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Despite Lady Heather&amp;rsquo;s rivalry with Sara Sidle over the years, I don&amp;rsquo;t think anyone wanted her to be a true terrorist, and &lt;em&gt;CSI&lt;/em&gt; obliges. It&amp;rsquo;s a frame job, and when the real terrorist shows up&amp;ndash;he&amp;rsquo;s played by frequent baddie Doug Hutchinson&amp;ndash;we know immediately where the episode is going. Regardless, it doesn&amp;rsquo;t matter, as this was an episode about bringing together the original team and sending them off in a way that pleased fans who showed up earlier in the show&amp;rsquo;s run as well as the fans who stuck around for the series over the long term.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Although Ted Danson and the new players&amp;ndash;minus Elisabeth Shue and George Eads&amp;rsquo; characters&amp;ndash;are players in the new episode, it really is an episode that is about the original characters, many of whom left at some point but came back for the movie. Willows, Grissom and Sidle get the most screentime (there&amp;rsquo;s even a bees-oriented scene!). And when Lady Heather eventually does show up, she helps with the case but also helps the tension between Grissom and Sidle to subside.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Which leads us to the lovely final few minutes of the series, when Grissom tells the bomber that he understands bombs as much as he understands oceans, talking to the criminal about a whale and comparing the whale to the bomber&amp;rsquo;s ultimate love for Lady Heather. Catherine Willows decides to put her &amp;lsquo;hat in the ring&amp;rsquo; for a director&amp;rsquo;s position, and D.B. Russell packed up and got ready to go. While we got closure for many of the main characters, the best moment was when Sara decided to come with him on his boat to try a relationship again.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E! Online</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2015/e-online-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2015/e-online-1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Full disclosure: I haven&amp;rsquo;t watched &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; in years, but that didn&amp;rsquo;t mean tonight wasn&amp;rsquo;t a total emotional roller coaster for me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I watched every single episode for the first nine seasons at least, and even stuck around for a couple more after Grissom left (and broke my heart in the process).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I loved CSI, and I never really stopped loving it. I just kind of grew up and apart from the show, just as the original characters grew apart from each other (looking at you, Grissom and Sara).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, tonight&amp;rsquo;s two-hour finale, which reunited Gil Grissom (&amp;ldquo;&amp;lsquo;William Petersen&amp;rdquo;&amp;rsquo;), Sara Sidle (&amp;ldquo;&amp;lsquo;Jorja Fox&amp;rdquo;&amp;rsquo;), Catherine Willows (&amp;ldquo;&amp;lsquo;Marg Helgenberger&amp;rdquo;&amp;rsquo;), Jim Brass (&amp;ldquo;&amp;lsquo;Paul Guilfoyle&amp;rdquo;&amp;rsquo;), David Hodges (&amp;ldquo;Wallace Langham&amp;rdquo;), the aforementioned Greg, and even Grissom&amp;rsquo;s ridiculous dominatrix friend/foe Lady Heather (&amp;ldquo;&amp;lsquo;Melinda Clarke&amp;rdquo;&amp;rsquo;), felt like a trip back to my teen years in a way I should have expected but totally didn&amp;rsquo;t.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was like no time had passed at all, both for me and for the show. In fact, I&amp;rsquo;m pretty sure I have social studies homework due tomorrow, and that I should go to bed (as soon as I&amp;rsquo;m finished updating my LiveJournal with all my Grissom/Sara thoughts).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The emotional through-line of the finale was obviously Sara and Grissom reuniting since getting divorced however long ago that was. They both ended up admitting separately to Lady Heather that they were still in love with each other, but it took Lindsey hinting to Sara that she should watch Grissom&amp;rsquo;s interrogation of Lady Heather for her to get that. In the end, she and Grissom sailed off into the sunset on his little boat, which is just as things should be.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From a fan standpoint, I loved everything about everything that I just saw.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If I&amp;rsquo;m looking at the episode with a more critical eye, that was totally and completely ridiculous. Obviously, the bomber was Doug Hutchison. Obviously, Sara and Grissom were destined to be together again. Obviously, all bombs (and there were a lot of bombs) that endangered anyone we cared about were diffused at the very last second. Obviously, bees.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E! Online (News)</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2015/e-online-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2015/e-online-2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Confession: I have never purposefully watched an episode of CSI. Or any of its spinoffs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sarah and Catherine, are they frenemies? I feel tension? I feel history? Tempted to Google, but that feels like cheating.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Wait, Sarah and Petersen were MARRIED?! Is that why there was tension with her and Marg&amp;rsquo;s character?! Love it.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sarah and Gil&amp;rsquo;s (I&amp;rsquo;ll call him that from now on, not Petersen) first encounter. Tension&amp;rsquo;s so thick you can cut it with a shark fin. Ted Danson also meets him for the first time and I had no idea there wasn&amp;rsquo;t ever any crossover with them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thanks for all the exposition, Sarah. Caught up on their relationship drama. &amp;ldquo;Seeing you again left me a little speechless,&amp;rdquo; is a pretty good line.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Oh, so I guess Catherine and Gil were NOT a thing? So my Gil shipping order currently is 1. Lady Heather. 2. Catherine. 3. Sarah. Sorry, not sorry.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sarah getting the swabs from the suspects&amp;rsquo; mouths is the most I&amp;rsquo;ve liked her.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sarah still loves Gil. Lady Heather doesn&amp;rsquo;t love Gil. I guess I have to update my ranking. Sigh.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ha, Gil is reprimanding the bees. He&amp;rsquo;s a wonderful weirdo. Sarah interrupts and they have A MOMENT.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;And Gil&amp;rsquo;s wearing another hilarious hat, albeit this is for bee-keeping. And Sarah is wearing one, too. Bow-chicka-wow-wow. Also, how are bees now an integral part of this case? I&amp;rsquo;m confused.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Vegas is lucky to have you.&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;The oceans are lucky to have you.&amp;rdquo; Deep. &amp;ldquo;I hope you find what you are looking for out there!&amp;rdquo; BUT HE&amp;rsquo;S ALREADY FOUND IT.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gil and Lady Heather have quite the goodbye. Why he loves Sarah? &amp;ldquo;She helped me with my crossword puzzles.&amp;rdquo; True love right there, people. But he says he&amp;rsquo;s going to miss her for the rest of his life. Or you could just be together? Why do you need to be such a drama queen, you can be with her!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sarah went to him! I love that they chose not to have the actors say anything. So much more powerful with no words.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;And then they rode off into the sunset.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LA Times</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2015/la-times-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2015/la-times-2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jorja Fox, one of the show&amp;rsquo;s original cast members, has said in previous interviews that she didn&amp;rsquo;t think anyone would watch the series when it first premiered in 2000. She could not have been more wrong. The drama about a forensics investigation division in Las Vegas was an instant smash.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;During its 15-year run, &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; spawned three spinoffs and became one of TV&amp;rsquo;s most popular series, in the U.S. and internationally.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Like other cast member, Fox, who played investigator Sara Sidle, was extremely appreciative that the show was given a final bow: &amp;ldquo;It was such a great gift. I was thrilled. And the finale was truly a love letter to our fans.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fox added that working again with William Petersen, who played investigator Gil Grissom, and Marg Helgenberger, who played Catherine Willows, was exciting. &amp;ldquo;Us all being back together felt like the most natural thing in the world. It was such a joy to have them.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of the main attractions for fans of the series was the romance between Grissom and Sidle. And the finale featured them in a tough situation. After getting married years ago, things started to go wrong and they divorced.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;See the most-read stories in Entertainment this hour &amp;gt;&amp;gt;&lt;br /&gt;
A fatal explosion in a casino brings the retired Grissom back to Vegas, where he has a tense reunion with his ex.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;My character is really thinking, &amp;lsquo;How can I work with him again?&amp;rsquo; and it&amp;rsquo;s pretty awkward,&amp;rdquo; Fox said. &amp;ldquo;It&amp;rsquo;s uncomfortable and messy.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, by the end of the episode, the two discover that they are still in love with each other.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Said Fox: &amp;ldquo;I always knew I was part of this weird love story. For all the violence and darkness in the show, there&amp;rsquo;s still this love story, and that&amp;rsquo;s such a terrific way to end up. No matter how black things seem, &amp;lsquo;CSI&amp;rsquo; is a love story; there is long and lasting love.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The couple is seen at the end literally riding off into the sunset, where Grissom has relocated. But there&amp;rsquo;s still the matter of Sidle&amp;rsquo;s job in Las Vegas, where she&amp;rsquo;s been promoted to the head of the CSI unit. The future of Grissom and Sidle is still a mystery as the credits close.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;On one hand, maybe they&amp;rsquo;ll just ride around in the boat for an hour and then call it quits,&amp;rdquo; Fox said with a chuckle. &amp;ldquo;Or maybe they&amp;rsquo;ll stay together and become CSIs for the ocean and the environment. There&amp;rsquo;s no talk of a spinoff, but that would make a great idea for a show.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the meantime, Fox is looking forward to the next chapter of her life and career.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;I have no idea what&amp;rsquo;s next,&amp;rdquo; Fox said. &amp;ldquo;In some ways, the end of the show caught me by surprise. It&amp;rsquo;s the first time in 19 years I&amp;rsquo;ve been between jobs. I&amp;rsquo;m just going to decompress a little bit. It&amp;rsquo;s been nice just hanging out with my dog and just letting go. I can&amp;rsquo;t wait to see what the next thing is.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LA Times (Review)</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2015/la-times-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2015/la-times-3/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In the end, &amp;lsquo;CSI: Crime Scene Investigation&amp;rsquo; died as it lived: fun, flabby, and altogether too invested in the undying love of two deeply sexless characters.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Though Petersen&amp;rsquo;s return for the series finale gave the show a badly needed jolt of original &amp;lsquo;CSI&amp;rsquo; magic, it also meant that the love story of Gil Grissom and Sara Sidle returned to center stage.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sidle, played by Jorja Fox, was another of the show&amp;rsquo;s originating characters. She initially was Grissom&amp;rsquo;s subordinate but eventually became friend, lover, wife, estranged wife, ex-wife &amp;#8212; in the most uninteresting ways possible. Fox and Petersen always existed within the show&amp;rsquo;s universe without an ounce of chemistry, so when the series opted to make the two its &amp;lsquo;one true pairing,&amp;rsquo; it went all in on the show&amp;rsquo;s least interesting relationship.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sadly, there was plenty of Grissom-and-Sidle relationship drama in the finale, as we quickly learn that the two have divorced and it becomes clear, when Grissom returns to Las Vegas to help investigate a string of suicide bombings, that they are still in love with each other. It&amp;rsquo;s this misguided commitment to its own worst tendencies that made &amp;lsquo;Immortality, Parts 1 and 2&amp;rsquo; such a fitting sendoff for &amp;lsquo;CSI.&amp;rsquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Though the show finally had the luminous Helgenberger back as Catherine Willows, it trapped her in a one-dimensional storyline that underlined how the series only knew how to view the character through the fact that she was a mother.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even worse than the investment in Grissom and Sidle is the fact that the show brought back Lady Heather, a popular recurring character, played by Melinda Clarke, who had a deep and complex relationship with Grissom, who, despite having the entire plot seemingly revolve around her, functions only as a red herring, only useful to drive Sidle and Grissom back together.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But perhaps the most egregious misstep the finale makes is in its conclusion when, after finally taking over as CSI director, Sidle leaves the career she&amp;rsquo;s built to wander around the oceans with Grissom. True love is one thing; it&amp;rsquo;s two people meeting in the middle and each giving ground so they can find a place where they can each thrive. But that&amp;rsquo;s not what &amp;lsquo;CSI&amp;rsquo; does. It breaks Sara&amp;rsquo;s back and sends her on her way, and the implication is clear: If her relationship only works by following Grissom to the ends of the Earth, then her true calling is following Grissom to the ends of the Earth.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s a weird and contrary message, the opposite of what love is, and, in a way, the perfect summation of a relationship that never really worked. Sidle and Grissom sail off into the sunset, something the show believes is a happy ending but reality makes less clear.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LostRemote</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2015/lostremote/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2015/lostremote/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;While CSI has been one of the longest-running shows of the decade, its series finale drew almost no digital buzz. Amobee Brand Intelligence analyzed the engagements around the finale and found that just a few fans were called to action last night, which either means that CSI is more a of a VOD hit than anything else or that everyone was watching ABC, which premiered Quantico and Once Upon a Time last night.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Most interest spun around original cast members returning for the finale. Between Sept. 27-28, &lt;strong&gt;William Petersen&lt;/strong&gt;, who hadn&amp;rsquo;t been a series regular since season 9 had the most CSI related digital content engagement; while &lt;strong&gt;Marg Helgenberger&lt;/strong&gt; who hadn&amp;rsquo;t been a series lead since season 12, had 81 percent as much CSI related digital content engagement. &lt;strong&gt;Ted Danson&lt;/strong&gt;, who&amp;rsquo;d been on the show between seasons 12-15 had 74 percent as much CSI related digital content engagement as Peterson between Sept. 27-28; with &lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; who&amp;rsquo;d been with the show for every season other than seasons 9-10; having 54 percent as much CSI related digital content engagement as Peterson in the same time period.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Equals</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2015/tv-equals/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2015/tv-equals/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Still, it was hard to complain about that, when the show not only brought back Catherine Willows (Marg Helgenberger) and Jim Brass (Paul Guilfoyle), but the long-since-gone Grissom (William Peterson) and- be still my heart- even Lady Heather, aka Dr. Kessler (Melinda Clarke). I certainly wasn&amp;rsquo;t. Grissom was as wonderfully grizzled and nerdy as ever, (Sara) sidling back into the role as if no time whatsoever had passed. As such, it was probably inevitable that he would get the most screen time, but I suppose that&amp;rsquo;s as it should be.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Besides, if they hadn&amp;rsquo;t taken that approach, we wouldn&amp;rsquo;t have gotten what were, by far, the tenderest moments in the entire series between Grissom and Sara (Jorja Fox), culminating in an implied boat ride off into the sunset together, with Sara seemingly forgoing her new job as director to be with him and Catherine stepping up to the plate in her stead, which was a nice touch.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While part of me- the more feminist part- was a bit miffed that Sara would give up her plum gig for a guy that was clearly married to his own work, I get it. The show, and perhaps more than a few viewers, wanted these two to ride off- or sail off, as the case was- into the sunset together, and that&amp;rsquo;s what we got. Hey, at least they gave the job to another woman, so there&amp;rsquo;s that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think my favorite moments of the episode were the quieter ones: Sara and Grissom speaking volumes in the silence as they waited for color-coded bees to return; the look on Grissom&amp;rsquo;s face when the &amp;lsquo;Syndaver&amp;rsquo; opened its eyes in that open-aired warehouse, itself a quintessential &amp;lsquo;CSI&amp;rsquo;-type location; the last sighting of those hyper-bright flashlights in the darkness; the other oddball clues, like the thumbprint &amp;lsquo;face&amp;rsquo; D.B. (Ted Danson) discovered or the &amp;lsquo;X-Marks the Spot&amp;rsquo; one Willows&amp;rsquo; daughter found; and the requisite so-bad-it&amp;rsquo;s-good one-liner, fittingly given to Grissom at the beginning: &amp;lsquo;Looks like somebody jumped the shark.&amp;rsquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I did like that there were nods to the show&amp;rsquo;s illustrious past in the commercial breaks, i.e. the &amp;lsquo;furries,&amp;rsquo; for instance; and the show could have done worse in terms of the overall plot- I liked that they not only brought back Lady Heather, but answered a few burning questions a lot of us had about her- that she and Grissom were never intimate and she never was truly in love with him, he just helped her come to terms with certain facets of herself. Good to know, and even better for Sara to know. Definitely a nice touch.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Washington Post</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2015/washington-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2015/washington-post/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;rdquo;&amp;lsquo;Grissom and Sara ended up together &amp;ndash; for good this time, we assume.&amp;ldquo;&amp;rsquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For a moment it seemed like the on-again, off-again lovers might go their separate ways, but come on. There&amp;rsquo;s no way that was happening. Instead, Sara left Vegas and flew to San Diego to join Gil on his boat. The pair literally sailed off into the sunset.&amp;lsquo;CSI&amp;rsquo; was never the subtlest show.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zap2It</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2015/zap2it/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2015/zap2it/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;After 15 years, 335 episodes and countless grisly death scenes, &amp;lsquo;CSI&amp;rsquo; said goodbye with a TV movie entitled &amp;lsquo;Immortality.&amp;rsquo; It was a chance to bid adieu to old friends, wrap up some loose ends, and watch a television institution ride off into the sunset.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But in true &amp;lsquo;Crime Scene Investigation&amp;rsquo; fashion, it was also an opportunity to bring some grisly drama. With Las Vegas itself under attack, would the return of Gil Grissom, Catherine Willows and Jim Brass help save the day? What does the future hold for D.B. and Sara? And what about the return of Lady Heather? Read on for all the answers but beware: Spoilers ahead.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The episode was largely dominated by Grissom, which seems only right since the character was the driving force of the show for nine seasons. &amp;lsquo;Looks like somebody jumped a shark,&amp;rsquo; Grissom joked at one point, very tongue-in-cheek. Ted Danson had a handful of scenes, and Elizabeth Shue was killed off rather unceremoniously. Professional dominatrix and fan favorite Lady Heather also had a memorable return, as she was at the center of multiple twists and turns that had viewers buzzing on social media &amp;ndash; even if Jorja Fox&amp;rsquo;s Sara Sidle wasn&amp;rsquo;t in the mood.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Grissom had a lot of great lines, including a poem: &amp;lsquo;Evidence may bear, even if rare,&amp;rsquo; he said. &amp;lsquo;It&amp;rsquo;s what&amp;rsquo;s not there that gives you a scare.&amp;rsquo; But ultimately a lot of it came down to terrorism, Catherine&amp;rsquo;s box and a lonely 52-Hertz whale. And although some may not love Gil&amp;rsquo;s happy ending that had him and Sara boating off together (many consider their romance as the moment when &amp;lsquo;CSI&amp;rsquo; jumped its own shark), it was a beautiful farewell to a beloved character.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With &amp;lsquo;CSI&amp;rsquo; gone for good, fans will undoubtedly be sad that they&amp;rsquo;re losing a landmark show that some feared had hung on too long. Then again, as Gil said in one of his final moments: &amp;lsquo;You can&amp;rsquo;t lose something you never had.&amp;rsquo;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deadline</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2015/deadline/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2015/deadline/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DEADLINE&lt;/strong&gt;: Let&amp;rsquo;s start with the final scene of Gil and Sara sailing off into the sunset. How did that ending come about?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ZUIKER&lt;/strong&gt;: SixteenÂ years ago, William Petersen, (executive producers) Cindy Chvatal and Jonathan Littman and myself sat down at the Beverly Wilshire, that was the first time we got together.Â We actually met there 16 years later, same table, same party of four. And William Peterson pulled out this research folder that dealt with sea shepherd. This is a gentleman that goes along the ocean and does things in terms of keeping the ocean safe. That was the beginning of me thinking of the Gil Grissom&amp;rsquo;s character being a CSI at sea. We knew we wanted to start with him on a boat. Then we started to think about ending with him on the boat. And it just organically happened. Once he&amp;rsquo;d gotten in touch with his heart and when he really understood that Sara was the only person for him, it was only fitting as a closure for the series that Gil Grissom and Sara Sidle would drive off into the sunset.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DEADLINE&lt;/strong&gt;: Was there any alternativeÂ endingÂ you considered?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ZUIKER&lt;/strong&gt;: No, there wasn&amp;rsquo;t. We knew right away that if we were going to grab (Gil) on a boat to start his arc it only was fitting to end there. The one thing that wasn&amp;rsquo;t planned, it hit me during the running, was them actually driving off into the sunset,Â only this time it was on water. The metaphor of them driving off into the sunset happened in the moment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DEADLINE&lt;/strong&gt;: The Gil-Sara romance has been aÂ very popular storyline for many seasons but also divided some fans. Why did you make it the centerpiece of the finale? Did you always know that the two of them would end up together or you did it for the fans?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ZUIKER&lt;/strong&gt;: This one really was for the fans. I&amp;rsquo;d put some feelers out early on Twitter about what were some things the hardcore Twitttersphere wanted to accomplish. And overwhelmingly it really was a sufficient closure between Grissom and Sara. We knew that we would be going that route. We had to complicate that fantasy, and that was the reason to put Lady Heather in the middle because she suddenly became this other option that Grissom had been wrangling with over the course of many seasons, much to the point where a lot of the audience was convinced, and maybe even Grissom himself, that Lady Heather is the one that actually has his heart. As it turns out, Grissom has to make a choice by the end of the show, and I think the audience would be happy he chooses SaraÂ and we finally put them together.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DEADLINE&lt;/strong&gt;: If there is a &lt;em&gt;CSI: 10 Years Later&lt;/em&gt; special a decade from now, where will we see the main characters? Will Gil and Sara still be roaming the seas?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ZUIKER&lt;/strong&gt;: I believe so. I believe in my heart 10 years from now that Grissom and Sara not only are conquering the seas and sailing the oceans but they are also probably saving the environment on land and sea. They would probably have children and they would dedicate their lives to the betterment of humanity. In terms of the other characters, probably Catherine would still be running the crime lab, Bass probably would retire, living somewhere in Hawaii, and DB probably is working in the private sector in Washington DC. And I think that all these characters would still have their toe in the crime water.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>