<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Producer on Fans of Le Fox Library</title>
    <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/producer/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Producer on Fans of Le Fox Library</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://jorjafox.net/library/producer/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Dear Bernard</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/producer/dear-bernard/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/producer/dear-bernard/</guid>
      <description>Overview New York City - 1973. The city is awash in excess, playing host to the hottest parties and people of the moment. &amp;ldquo;Dear Bernard&amp;rdquo; tells the timeless tale of a small town English girl seeking fame and glamour in in America - with a twist.
Chelsea Mills - our exuberant English import - arrives in New York and is quickly discovered by the Liberace of fashion photographers, who propels her to the top of the &amp;ldquo;body part model&amp;rdquo; biz.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Extinction Soup</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/producer/extinction-soup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/producer/extinction-soup/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Extinction Soup&amp;rdquo; follows documentary filmmaker Philip Waller on his quest for adventure as he sets out to tell the story of his larger-than-life friend and extreme sports legend, Jimmy Hall. The film quickly takes a surprise turn when Waller finds himself consumed with exposing to the world an environmental catastrophe in the making - the extinction of the oceans&amp;rsquo; shark population through the mass slaughter of these magnificent animals for their fins.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How I Became an Elephant</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/producer/how-became-elephant/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/producer/how-became-elephant/</guid>
      <description>How I Became An Elephant is more than just a film. It&amp;rsquo;s one girl&amp;rsquo;s story&amp;hellip; which led to a movement, which led to a continuing plan, to save a species.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lion Ark</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/producer/lion-ark/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/producer/lion-ark/</guid>
      <description>More action adventure than traditional documentary, Lion Ark follows the world’s most ambitious and daring animal rescue, with a narrative compiled from film, interviews, conversations and reactions as events unfolded. How attitudes to animals were changed in Bolivia, illegal circuses pursued and closed, and 25 lions airlifted to freedom.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Producer</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/producer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/producer/</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;!DOCTYPE html&amp;gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stay Forever: The Life and Music of Dusty Springfield</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/producer/stay-forever/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/producer/stay-forever/</guid>
      <description>Originally shown at the L.A. Gay &amp;amp; Lesbian Center’s Lily Tomlin/Jane Wagner Cultural Arts Center, Jorja Fox produced this with Bunnyhop Productions in 2008.
In 2012, the show was revived off-Broadway.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>