<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Official on Jorja Fox Library</title>
    <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/tags/official/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Official on Jorja Fox Library</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="http://jorjafox.net/library/tags/official/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Official Biography</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/biographies/official/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/biographies/official/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;With a variety of memorable roles filling up her resume, it would not be cliched for one to hum a few bars of &amp;ldquo;Jorja On My Mind.&amp;rdquo; Actress JORJA FOX currently stars on the highest-ranked drama of the new television season, CSI: Crime Scene Investigation for CBS. Fox stars as a member of the autopsy team who heads-up the gritty drama series that is executive produced by Jerry Bruckheimer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No stranger to television, Fox also stared on NBC&amp;rsquo;s top-rated series ER as resident intern Dr. Maggie Doyle prior to her segue as Secret Service Agent Gina Toscano on Aaron Sorkin&amp;rsquo;s Emmy Award-winning drama THE WEST WING. Additional credits include guest turns on LAW AND ORDER and the historic &amp;ldquo;coming out&amp;rdquo; episode of ELLEN.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fox has also managed to carve out some impressive film credits that includes this year&amp;rsquo;s Sundance Film Festival dramatic competitor MEMENTO in which she portrays the wife of lead Guy Pearce. This marks Fox&amp;rsquo;s third foray into Sundance. She has previously made the trip in conjunction with her roles as sister to Clea Duvall in the quirky comedy HOW TO MAKE THE CRUELEST MONTH and as the town-gossip in THE KILL-OFF which was based on the book by renowned author Jim Thompson (&amp;ldquo;The Grifters&amp;rdquo;). More recent feature credits include the comedy FOREVER FABULOUS with Jean Smart and DOWN WITH THE JONESES opposite Joshua Leonard (&amp;ldquo;The Blair Witch Project&amp;rdquo;).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Having appeared in numerous stage productions, Fox continues to work tirelessly in conjunction with the theater company which she co-founded, Honeypot Productions. Honeypot has put up three plays to date, two of them scribed by Fox. The fourth play, &amp;ldquo;Loving Stanley,&amp;rdquo; which she also penned, offers up a comedic romp about the women&amp;rsquo;s bowling circuit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Born in New York City, Fox moved to the small costal town of Melbourne Beach, FL with her French Canadian parents. Upon completion of high school, she moved back to New York to pursue her career in acting. Now residing in Los Angeles, Fox enjoys travelling, playing guitar, singing and has an affinity for the ocean which dates back to her childhood.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>