<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Transcripts on Fans of Le Fox Library</title>
    <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/categories/transcripts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Transcripts on Fans of Le Fox Library</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 Jul 2001 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://jorjafox.net/library/categories/transcripts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Animal Planet Radio</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2001/animal-planet-radio/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jul 2001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2001/animal-planet-radio/</guid>
      <description>Introduction [&amp;hellip;] TV star Jorja Fox of &amp;ldquo;Crime Scene Investigation: CSI&amp;rdquo; talked about how she plays with her pooch while she has time between scenes. She also talked about her roles on &amp;ldquo;The West Wing&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;E/R.&amp;rdquo; Jorja says her dream job would be appearing on TV on Animal Planet. Were the bosses listening that day?
Animal Planet Radio - (10 min) Steve Dale We&amp;rsquo;ll be right back with Jorja Fox on Animal Planet Radio!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CSI Season 1 DVD extras</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2001/csi-dvd-extras/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jul 2001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2001/csi-dvd-extras/</guid>
      <description>Jorja Fox Ah, my character&amp;rsquo;s name is Sara Sidle, and she&amp;rsquo;s come in from San Francisco, ah, the character of Grissom has called her up and said there&amp;rsquo;s, you know, there&amp;rsquo;s a major problem happening down in Vegas, would you come down and help out for a while. So that&amp;rsquo;s what I&amp;rsquo;ve done, I&amp;rsquo;ve sort of just come off an airplane and like everybody else I haven&amp;rsquo;t slept in like two days, came right in.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Transcripts</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/main/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/main/</guid>
      <description>Interviews, press announcements, and live chat transcripts are presented, in whole or in part, with as much accuracy as can be found in the source media. Even in the case that an interview is grossly inaccurate, information will be presented honestly in reference to its source. There has been no attempt to correct grammar and while every best effort is put forth, assume no responsibility over the accuracy or validity of any transcripts you may read in this section of the website.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>