<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>1998 on Fans of Le Fox Library</title>
    <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/tags/1998/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 1998 on Fans of Le Fox Library</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 Feb 1998 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://jorjafox.net/library/tags/1998/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Variety</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/1998/variety/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 1998 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/1998/variety/</guid>
      <description>A Fugue State/Magnet Prods. presentation. Produced by Alison Dickey, Mark Lipson. Executive producer, James R. Hedges. Co-producer, Caitlin Abramoritz.
Directed, written by Kip Koenig. Camera (color), Julian Whatley; editor, Chris Figler; music, Jeff Martin; production design, Jodi Ginnever; set decoration, Melissa K. Frankel; costume design, Agnes NaDene Baddoo, Dalhia Schuette; sound (Dolby), Larry Blake; associate producers, Scott Kennedy, Luis Barajas, Alberto Gieco; assistant director, Marie O&amp;rsquo;Keefe; casting, Joseph Middleton. Reviewed at Sundance Film Festival (competing), Jan.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BTinternet</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/1998/btinternet/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 1998 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/1998/btinternet/</guid>
      <description>Written for the screen &amp;amp; directed by Maggie Greenwald.
Starring Loretta Gross, Jackson Sims, Cathy Haase, Steve Monroe, Andrew Lee Barrett and Jorjan Fox.
Cinematography by Declan Quinn.
Grim but Worthy &amp;#8212; Low-Life Study
Maggie Greenwald&amp;rsquo;s dark, low-budget adaptation of The Kill-Off is considered one of the finest translations of a Jim Thompson novel from page to screen. Completed in 1989 the movie documents the sleazy lowlife of an East Coast nowheresville and its inhabitants who share a common hatred of monstrous bed-ridden gossip Luane (played by Loretta Gross) who terrorizes the town with her tales and accusations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Checkout</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/1998/checkout/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 1998 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/1998/checkout/</guid>
      <description>Kip Koenig wrote and directed this comedy, set in a small college town, about neurotic Bell Bryant (Clea DuVall) who explains her problems directly to the camera: her older sister Sarah (Jorja Fox) has a happy marriage plus a baby on the way. Her other sister, beautiful Dot (Amy Smart), is involved in an affair with Bell&amp;rsquo;s ex, Leonard (Gabriel Mann). In a remote location, Bell makes love to Leonard and then departs, abandoning the nude Leonard who makes his way to the house of a married couple (Dennis Haysbert, Marianne Jean-Baptiste).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>News Articles (1998)</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/1998/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 1998 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/1998/</guid>
      <description>  Date Source    January 01 BTinternet   January 01 Checkout   February 02 Variety    </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>