<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Dvd on Jorja Fox Library</title>
    <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/tags/dvd/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Dvd on Jorja Fox Library</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Jul 2007 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://jorjafox.net/library/tags/dvd/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>CSI season 7 DVD extras</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2007/csi-season-7-dvd-extras/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jul 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2007/csi-season-7-dvd-extras/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;ldquo;(on Billy Petersen leaving the show for four weeks in November of 2006)&amp;rdquo; I wasn&amp;rsquo;t disappointed at all, I think, you know, obviously as I met Billy he had come almost directly out of this excitement of theater he was doing in Chicago and he&amp;rsquo;s very famous for that theater that he&amp;rsquo;s done. I think that it&amp;rsquo;s been the heart of his work over the time of his career, he&amp;rsquo;s done some films that are ground-breaking and memorable and everybody, those, that&amp;rsquo;s probably the way that the most people know Billy Petersen, but I think that people who know Billy Petersen &amp;ldquo;know&amp;rdquo; that his heart and his soul has always been in the theater, so, and it&amp;rsquo;s almost as if in a sense odd that it took him six years to find his way into one, you know, and I think that it&amp;rsquo;s a testament to the show, how much &amp;ldquo;CSI:&amp;rdquo; has all this passion that he hasn&amp;rsquo;t felt like he could go do a play at the same time. Cause he&amp;rsquo;s also fairly multi-faceted, much more so than I am and I think some of us are on the show.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; From the very beginning of the inception of my character coming on to the pro- the show of &amp;ldquo;CSI:&amp;rdquo; and them deciding to add this character, there&amp;rsquo;s this little piece of paper that you get when you go to audition for these roles, and, and , I think the first sentence said &amp;#8216;love interest for Grissom&amp;rsquo;. So from like day one of me kind of going for the audition this was a story that hung there in the ethers and then, you know, as we started to go into season 1 and season 2 and started to realize that we were going to have a season 3 I think there was interest on everybody&amp;rsquo;s part not to, so to speak, &amp;#8216;blow our wad&amp;rsquo; too soon, you know &amp;ldquo;(laughs)&amp;rdquo;. You tell this story then where do you go from there and it could be, you know, if we were lucky enough which it &amp;ldquo;seemed&amp;rdquo; might be happening, there&amp;rsquo;d be years of awkwardness after the break-up or stuff that you know &amp;ldquo;(laughs)&amp;rdquo; we didn&amp;rsquo;t want to play for three seasons. So I think that it, it was kind of wise to hold back on it and, and then we got to a point where we thought that maybe the fans were not interested in it any more.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;ldquo;(voiceover)&amp;rdquo; We&amp;rsquo;d already begun shooting the last episode of season 6, the script had been out, there was an ending set, and I got a call from Carol Mendelsohn suggesting &amp;lsquo;hey, what do you think about this and would you want to do this&amp;rsquo; and is this interesting to you. Which is also something that&amp;rsquo;s great about this show and I think very unique is I don&amp;rsquo;t know how often actors get those calls. I was shocked, very surprised, and, and, and very very intrigued. I thought it could make season 7 extremely interesting for my character and certainly a storyline that I had always been gearing up to play and wanted to play, and I&amp;rsquo;ve always loved the dynamic between Grissom and Sara, I love that it&amp;rsquo;s a &amp;ldquo;little&amp;rdquo; bit sort of scandalous, it&amp;rsquo;s untraditional in, in a couple of respects, and I love those kinds of love stories. So&amp;hellip; I was thrilled.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; It&amp;rsquo;s a complete and utter shock and surprise. First of all I can&amp;rsquo;t believe it&amp;rsquo;s been seven years. One of the reasons I &amp;ldquo;hate&amp;rdquo; doing interviews like this is &amp;lsquo;cause I&amp;rsquo;m reminded that it&amp;rsquo;s been seven years, &amp;ldquo;(laughs)&amp;rdquo; because it doesn&amp;rsquo;t feel like seven years. It&amp;rsquo;s like &amp;#8216;yeah, a couple of years&amp;rsquo;, you know, it&amp;rsquo;s the coolest thing ever, I never could have even wished for this, to be a part of a show this long and never would have expected that it would ever happen and I can&amp;rsquo;t believe that it has, in many respects, we still have a gazillion cool stories left to tell. So&amp;hellip; yeah, it&amp;rsquo;s pretty weird.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CSI Season 5 DVD extras</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2005/csi-season-5-dvd-extras/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2005/csi-season-5-dvd-extras/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; All bets are off, and on at the same time. Anything can happen to anybody, there&amp;rsquo;s lines that have been drawn, and uh, it does make it really fascinating.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; It, we&amp;rsquo;re split almost down the middle, 50 percent of the people who watch &amp;ldquo;CSI:&amp;rdquo; want more character stuff, and 50 percent of the people who watch the show don&amp;rsquo;t want that much of it, they really like the stories and the science. So the writers are sort of always letting down somebody, and I think that they&amp;rsquo;ve done a really good job of, of just deciding to follow their hearts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; I knew probably by season 3 that the writers thought there might be something personal in Sara&amp;rsquo;s past that, uh, really prompted her to go into this line of work, but, uh, had no idea what that might be.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; I was hoping, &amp;#8216;wow, I was hoping we can pull this off in a way that it&amp;rsquo;s good&amp;rsquo; and it&amp;rsquo;s dark and it&amp;rsquo;s funny but you also don&amp;rsquo;t end up making somebody, you know, sort of seem like the exhibit at the zoo or something like that, and I think Richard Lewis {director} pulled that off brilliantly.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CSI Season 3 DVD extras</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2003/CSI_Season_3_Dvd_Extras_%282003%29/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2003/CSI_Season_3_Dvd_Extras_%282003%29/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;crash-and-burn:bc34ae24366084c3a1c1117294a3d832&#34;&gt;Crash and Burn&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; You know, Sara Sidle had a very dark year in season 3; she had a tough one, she really had a tough one. It really started, uh, I would say, in January, about midway through the season. Ah, the first thing that happens is, is, a very good friend of hers betrays her very personally. And the next time we see Sara, her boyfriend, it turns out, has a girlfriend and he also betrays her.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; And I think for her, you know, the type of person that she is and what she does for a living, she&amp;rsquo;s so sure that she knows the truth about everyone, and to find out that two people she was very very close to were, were lying to her all along is a pretty hard thing for her to digest. You know, just above and beyond the fact that these relationships both go sour but then &amp;#8216;wow, that somebody, she was fooled, she was tricked&amp;rsquo; by people she was close to. Then, ah, we see her again in another episode and the lab blows up and she, she walks away from the explosion, her and Greg Sanders get blown up together, and that was a very hard thing, I think for her, you know, personally, and, and the episode ends with-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;play-with-fire:bc34ae24366084c3a1c1117294a3d832&#34;&gt;Play With Fire&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;ndash; a pretty certain refusal from Grissom that anything will ever happen between the two of them, so, that was, that season 3 for Sara was &amp;ldquo;hard&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; [Director] Danny [Cannon] is fast, he&amp;rsquo;s like the lightning bolt director, and everybody loves, you know, just starting out with him they know that they&amp;rsquo;re gonna get, they&amp;rsquo;re gonna have a shorter day with him and that things are going to move very quickly and people really like that, you know, it&amp;rsquo;s, it&amp;rsquo;s, when you&amp;rsquo;re on show 12 and you&amp;rsquo;ve been working for five months the idea of having a short day is really good.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CSI season 2 DVD extras</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2002/csi-season-2-dvd-extras/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2002/csi-season-2-dvd-extras/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;ldquo;(shot of the characters viewing a &amp;lsquo;corpse&amp;rsquo;; Jorja walks away holding her stomach)&amp;rdquo; Uh. It&amp;rsquo;s too early. &amp;ldquo;(to &amp;lsquo;corpse&amp;rsquo;)&amp;rdquo; I mean, I&amp;rsquo;m sure you&amp;rsquo;re a really nice guy&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CSI Season 1 DVD extras</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2001/csi-dvd-extras/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jul 2001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2001/csi-dvd-extras/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; Ah, my character&amp;rsquo;s name is Sara Sidle, and she&amp;rsquo;s come in from San Francisco, ah, the character of Grissom has called her up and said there&amp;rsquo;s, you know, there&amp;rsquo;s a major problem happening down in Vegas, would you come down and help out for a while. So that&amp;rsquo;s what I&amp;rsquo;ve done, I&amp;rsquo;ve sort of just come off an airplane and like everybody else I haven&amp;rsquo;t slept in like two days, came right in. So that idea is that, ah, I&amp;rsquo;ll just sort of see if I can help out getting to the bottom of this disaster and then go on home to San Francisco.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; I&amp;rsquo;m a CSI 2 and I&amp;rsquo;m a forensic scientist who also does some investigative work. So I think that science is my specialty, but I&amp;rsquo;ll be doing a lot of investigating.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; A lot of people attracted to the show will be puzzle solvers and will be very interested in getting to the, the truth of the matter and getting to the depth of the matter, so&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; I can only say that my biggest concern about being so excited to do the show was the day to day of being in the gore and how I deal with that, you know, like &amp;#8216;would that be fun&amp;rsquo; or would that be like I wasn&amp;rsquo;t quite sure and&amp;hellip; I think it&amp;rsquo;s going to be&amp;hellip; okay, you know, I still know like if there&amp;rsquo;s something particularly disturbing I probably will skip lunch until we shoot it, finish it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; I have so much respect and admiration, actually, for the folks who do this, you know, who can, who can show up every day and kind of try and figure out what has happened.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; Sara Sidle is not squeamish. I think she&amp;rsquo;s, you know, she&amp;rsquo;s very cerebral, and she really, she lives for what she does, and I think, uh, she, she can become emotionally affected by what she&amp;rsquo;s experiencing, but it doesn&amp;rsquo;t get in the way of her ability to, to be there and be present in it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; The intent is not to be gratuitous, you know, but at the same time, ah, because the show is so visual, and, and we can go places with that. There&amp;rsquo;s moments like, you know, we can show this pulsing heart, we have the technology, you know, so you want to have that opportunity if you can.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>