<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>2000 on Fans of Le Fox Library</title>
    <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/tags/2000/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 2000 on Fans of Le Fox Library</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2000 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://jorjafox.net/library/tags/2000/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>USA Today</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2000/usa-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2000/usa-today/</guid>
      <description>12/21/00- Updated 07:16 PM ET
VALENCIA, Calif. &amp;#8212; Harsh sunlight burst through the ceiling of a burned-out house, turning the CSI criminalists into shadows against the charred walls. Smoke particles hung in the air, but, three months after an arson, the crime scene appeared cold.
&amp;ldquo;There&amp;rsquo;s nothing left, Gris,&amp;rdquo; Warrick Brown (Gary Dourdan) said to his boss, Gil Grissom.
&amp;ldquo;More than you think,&amp;rdquo; the cerebral Grissom (William Petersen ) responded, already rooting out clues.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Guide</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2000/tv-guide-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2000/tv-guide-2/</guid>
      <description>Through its exploration of anal swabs and poisoned nipples, CSI: Crime Street Investigation - the CBS drama that has been described as Quincy meets Seven - has quickly become one of this season&amp;rsquo;s biggest hits. A large part of the show&amp;rsquo;s success can be chalked up to its stomach-churning shock value, an element that required its plucky cast - including actress Jorja Fox - to develop an extra layer of thick skin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dallas Morning News</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2000/dallas-morning-news/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Nov 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2000/dallas-morning-news/</guid>
      <description>Question: I&amp;rsquo;m interested in the actress Jorja Fox on the new show &amp;ldquo;CSI (Crime Scene Investigation).&amp;rdquo; Haven&amp;rsquo;t I seen her on &amp;ldquo;ER&amp;rdquo;? - C.C.L., Dallas
Answer: You have. She played Dr. Maggie Doyle on &amp;ldquo;ER.&amp;rdquo; After her exit in 1999 from &amp;ldquo;ER,&amp;rdquo; she joined The West Wing as secret service agent Gina Toscano. After appearing in &amp;ldquo;West Wing&amp;rsquo;s&amp;rdquo; second season premiere in October, she moved on again to the new CBS drama &amp;ldquo;CSI,&amp;rdquo; one of the highest rated new shows of the season.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Guide</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2000/tv-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2000/tv-guide/</guid>
      <description>9-10PM, CBS
PREMIERES October 6
STARRING: Jorja Fox, Marg Helgenberger, William Petersen, George Eads, Gary Dourdan, Paul Guilfoyle
PREMISE: It&amp;rsquo;s the evidence, stupid. This slick crime drama focuses on &amp;ldquo;crime scene investigation,&amp;rdquo; the specialty of the forensic team in the Las Vegas police department&amp;rsquo;s Criminalistics Bureau. By relentlessly analyzing every detail at the scene of the crime, no matter how seemingly irrelevant or grotesque in nature, these sleuths have science and experience on their side to solve the case.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Las Vegas Review Journal</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2000/las-vegas-review-journal/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2000/las-vegas-review-journal/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s a Strip-to-strip week for &amp;ldquo;C.S.I.&amp;rdquo;
The new prime-time crime drama about Las Vegas forensic investigators, which debuted last Friday on CBS, visits its small-screen hometown for three days starting Thursday.
And the whole &amp;ldquo;C.S.I&amp;rdquo; starring crew will be along for the ride &amp;#8212; one of them literally.
Series star William L. Petersen, who plays Criminalistics Bureau chief Gil Grissom, will brave the Manhattan Express roller coaster atop New York-New York for one scene.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Post-Gazette</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2000/post-gazette/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2000/post-gazette/</guid>
      <description>Who&amp;rsquo;s been shot?
It&amp;rsquo;s the question fans of NBC&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;The West Wing&amp;rdquo; have been asking all summer following the show&amp;rsquo;s season finale shooting attack on the president and his staff. Tonight viewers will get their answer.
NBC refused to send critics tapes of new episodes out of fear that some unthinking clod would lend the tape to his brother&amp;rsquo;s girlfriend&amp;rsquo;s cousin who might post revelations to a Web site, spoiling the surprise for everyone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Newsday</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2000/newsday/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2000/newsday/</guid>
      <description>C.S.I. (CBS, 9 p.m.): Weird, wild and witty. And in Vegas! You&amp;rsquo;d have to be strange to scrutinize crime there, so we have police crime scene investigators (as in the title) serving up chocolate-covered grasshoppers, synching &amp;ldquo;Dark Side of the Moon&amp;rdquo; to &amp;ldquo;The Wizard of Oz&amp;rdquo; and feeling &amp;ldquo;like King Kong on cocaine.&amp;rdquo; Their buzz comes from catching the baddies by &amp;ldquo;concentrating on what cannot lie: the evidence,&amp;rdquo; says sage boss William Petersen (&amp;ldquo;The Beast&amp;rdquo;), whose forensics team includes competitive hotshots Gary Dourdan and George Eads, single mom Marg Helgenberger and gung-ho newbie Jorja Fox.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zetnet</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2000/zetnet/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2000/zetnet/</guid>
      <description>After the promise of the no-budget London thriller *Following, *all eyes were on what Nolan would do with a little Hollywood cash. And he certainly hasn&amp;rsquo;t taken the easy road. **Memento **is told with an even more unconventional narrative that keeps your brain in high gear from the very first shot. And it&amp;rsquo;s absolutely brilliant-a terrific little thriller that takes the genre and turns it inside out.
Leonard (Pearce) has a memory disorder: Ever since his wife (Fox) was raped and murdered, he can&amp;rsquo;t create new memories, so he must use a series of Polaroids, notes and tattoos to remind himself where he is, who the people around him are and what he should be doing as he seeks revenge.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Student Advantage</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2000/student-advantage/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2000/student-advantage/</guid>
      <description>Scoop: In Entertainment Weekly&amp;rsquo;s February cover story, director Aaron Sorkin discussed his plans for this year&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;The West Wing.&amp;rdquo; The most dramatic change is in the cast, since Moira Kelly is leaving.
&amp;ldquo;Moira is a terrific actress,&amp;rdquo; Sorkin said. &amp;ldquo;But we just weren&amp;rsquo;t the right thing for her. She expressed that she felt the same way, and as a result, story lines haven&amp;rsquo;t been invested in that character, because we knew that at the end of the year, we&amp;rsquo;d be shaking hands and parting company.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alliance-Atlantis</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2000/alliance-atlantis/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2000/alliance-atlantis/</guid>
      <description>Starring William Petersen (To Live and Die in L.A.) and Marg Helgenberger (China Beach)
Series Executive Produced by Action Feature Film Producer Jerry Bruckheimer (Pearl Harbour, Con Air)
August 9, 2000 - Toronto &amp;#8212; ALLIANCE ATLANTIS COMMUNICATIONS INC. announced today a co-production deal with CBS Productions and Jerry Bruckheimer Films Inc. to produce the one-hour crime drama CSI: Crime Scene Investigation. Twelve one-hour episodes began filming in Los Angeles on August 2, 2000, to premiere on the CBS Television Network this fall on Friday nights at 9 p.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Post-Gazette</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2000/post-gazette-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2000/post-gazette-2/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
Jorja Fox, who played Maggie Doyle on &amp;ldquo;ER&amp;rdquo; and the Secret Service agent assigned to the president&amp;rsquo;s daughter on &amp;ldquo;West Wing,&amp;rdquo; said she has watched every episode of &amp;ldquo;Survivor.&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;I really love Gervase and I love Richard,&amp;rdquo; she said at a CBS &amp;ldquo;Survivor&amp;rdquo;-themed party. Fox was there to promote her new CBS crime drama &amp;ldquo;C.S.I.&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;I was really hoping some of the cast would be here.&amp;rdquo;
[&amp;hellip;]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Post-Gazette</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2000/post-gazette-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2000/post-gazette-3/</guid>
      <description>Last season on &amp;ldquo;The West Wing,&amp;rdquo; actress Jorja Fox played a Secret Service agent willing to take a bullet for the president&amp;rsquo;s daughter. Turns out she suffered a different injury while filming the assassination attempt scene in the show&amp;rsquo;s season finale.
&amp;ldquo;We accidentally ran over her leg with a limousine &amp;#8212; and she was great about it,&amp;rdquo; said &amp;ldquo;West Wing&amp;rdquo; writer/creator Aaron Sorkin.
Fox was filming on location in front of the Newseum in Arlington, Va.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Entertainment Weekly</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2000/entertainment-weekly/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Feb 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2000/entertainment-weekly/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
Another Sorkin mistake was casting Moira Kelly as a political consultant who began the series as Josh&amp;rsquo;s ex-girlfriend but whose scowly, abrasive role has evaporated into a series of background grimaces. &amp;ldquo;Moira is a terrific actress,&amp;rdquo; says Sorkin diplomatically. &amp;ldquo;[But] we just weren&amp;rsquo;t the right thing for her. She expressed that she felt the same way, and as a result, story lines haven&amp;rsquo;t been invested in that character, because we knew that at the end of the year, we&amp;rsquo;d be shaking hands and parting company.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dish This</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2000/dish-this/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Feb 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2000/dish-this/</guid>
      <description>President Bartlett heads out of Los Angeles for a big fundraiser this week on &amp;ldquo;The West Wing&amp;rdquo; (Wednesday, NBC, 9 p.m.). Look for Jorja Fox, who was so underused as Maggie Doyle on &amp;ldquo;ER,&amp;rdquo; to show up as the President&amp;rsquo;s daughter&amp;rsquo;s new Secret Service agent.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Georgia</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2000/georgia/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jan 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2000/georgia/</guid>
      <description>Pharr House Productions&amp;rsquo; The Hungry Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s Club, a romantic comedy, opened at selected theaters nationwide on November 12. The feature film, which stars Atlanta&amp;rsquo;s Bill Nunn and Jorga Fox, was written by Georgia screenwriters Fred Dresch and Ron Ratliff, adapted frm a novel of the same name by Atlanta novelist Lynn Scott Myers, sister of Atlanta DP Ed Myers. Currently in development by Atlanta&amp;rsquo;s Pharr House Productions is the next novel written by Myers entitled Susceptible Terrain, another quirky romantic comedy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nerdslut</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2000/nerdslut/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2000/nerdslut/</guid>
      <description>This is the new favorite show around the Nerdslut Electronic Hearth. Focusing on a group of Forensic Scientists and Technicians in Las Vegas, Nevada, you get to watch two or three different crimes get solved every episode. The science is primary &amp;#8212; and that&amp;rsquo;s what makes it so great. While occasional diversions are inserted into the scripts (e.g., Marge Heckelberger&amp;rsquo;s ex-husband, a gambling problem gone awry,) for the most part it&amp;rsquo;s good solid geek fun, and some mystery to boot.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>News Articles (2000)</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2000/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2000/</guid>
      <description>  Date Source    January 01 Nerdslut   January 02 Georgia   February 21 Dish This   February 25 Entertainment Weekly   July 26 Post-Gazette   July 29 Post-Gazette   August 09 Alliance-Atlantis   August 24 Student Advantage   September 11 Zetnet   September 24 Newsday   October 04 Post-Gazette   October 09 Las Vegas Review Journal   November 24 TV Guide   November 25 Dallas Morning News   December 08 TV Guide   December 22 USA Today    </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>