<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>1997 on Fans of Le Fox Library</title>
    <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/tags/1997/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 1997 on Fans of Le Fox Library</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Sep 1997 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://jorjafox.net/library/tags/1997/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Gay TV</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/1997/gay-tv/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 1997 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/1997/gay-tv/</guid>
      <description>FUN FACTOID
Jorja Fox is also the actress known as Jorjan Fox. They&amp;rsquo;re the same person, but when she joined the cast of ER, Jorjan shortened her name to Jorja. Oh, those showbiz types.
All of America will be watching ER tomorrow night as TV&amp;rsquo;s top-rated show is broadcast live for its fourth season premiere! Will Dr. Ross and Nurse Hathaway rekindle their romance? Will Dr. Greene finally get over his assault from last season?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Washington Post</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/1997/washington-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 1997 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/1997/washington-post/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
With all the publicity when &amp;ldquo;Ellen&amp;rdquo; stepped out of the closet on ABC last spring, apparently no one noticed that the Maggie Doyle doctor character also came out on &amp;ldquo;ER&amp;rdquo; &amp;ndash; &amp;ldquo;There was absolutely no response to that story line,&amp;rdquo; [John] Wells [Executive Producer] said &amp;ldquo;&amp;hellip; She&amp;rsquo;ll be back in the fall, he said. &amp;ldquo;She is a doctor and a character who we like, who just happens to be gay &amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Advocate</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/1997/the-advocate/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 1997 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/1997/the-advocate/</guid>
      <description>*ER* gets a lesbian
Prime-time TV just got it&amp;rsquo;s 24th gay character. ER&amp;rsquo;s Dr. Maggie Doyle, played by Jorja Fox, came out to fellow first-year resident, Dr. John Carter, played by Noah Wyle, on the Feburary 6 episode of the hit NBC drama. To coproducer Dr. Neal Baer, who wrote the script, Maggie&amp;rsquo;s lesbian revelation is no big deal. &amp;ldquo;We also found out that she&amp;rsquo;s a vegetarian in that episode and that she collects guns,&amp;rdquo; Baer told The Buzz.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GLAAD</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/1997/glaad/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 1997 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/1997/glaad/</guid>
      <description>On &amp;ldquo;Whose Appy Now?,&amp;rdquo; the February 6 episode of NBC-TV&amp;rsquo;s hit show E.R., the newly arrived Dr. Maggie Doyle (Jorjan Fox) came out to her sometimes nemesis and co-worker Dr. John Carter (Noah Wyle). Over this past season, the two characters have slowly made the transition from fighting over turf and authority to becoming friends. Near the end of the episode, Carter asks Maggie if she wants to go out that evening, but she declines, saying she already has plans.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>News Articles (1997)</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/1997/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 1997 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/1997/</guid>
      <description>  Date Source    February 07 GLAAD   March 18 The Advocate   September 26 Gay TV   September 26 Washington Post    </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>