<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>2012 on Jorja Fox Library</title>
    <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/tags/2012/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 2012 on Jorja Fox Library</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Dec 2012 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://jorjafox.net/library/tags/2012/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Heeb Magazine</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2012/heeb-magazine/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Dec 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2012/heeb-magazine/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How long have you been working on this show&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;About 7 years ago, I started to listen heavily to her music, watching videos and reading anything I could get my hands on. I wrote monologues in her voice and sang her songs at an open mic night at The Gardenia Club in West Hollywood. I won a screenwriting grant at University of Southern California and used that to get some musical charts in order and prototype a show. We performed the show once at USC and Jorja Fox from CSI was there and decided she wanted to be involved. She helped bring the idea to The Lily Tomlin/Jane Wagner Cultural Arts Center, part of the Gay and Lesbian Center in LA. We had a small successful run there but I knew the final frontier was New York. We&amp;rdquo;ve overcome some incredible obstacles; it is a dream come true to be running FOREVER DUSTY at New World Stages.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Fanatic</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2012/tv-fanatic/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Dec 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2012/tv-fanatic/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Santa visited &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; fans early this year, as we received the unexpected gift of a Sara-centered episode on &amp;ldquo;Risky Business Class.&amp;rdquo; It was based on a former colleague of Sara&amp;rsquo;s, Doug Wilson from the NTSB, asking for the help from the crime lab.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First, I&amp;rdquo;m thrilled that we got an episode that focused on this team member, specifically her marriage to Grissom. Many fans have wondered why there isn&amp;rsquo;t more mention of Grissom or why Sara doesn&amp;rsquo;t seem to acknowledge that she&amp;rdquo;s even hitched.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I do have a couple of questions, though:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;# How long ago was she in San Francisco to work with Wilson? Their conversation gave clear indication it had been several years, but if it was before she came to Las Vegas that would be more than 13 years ago. Talk about carrying a flame for someone for a long time.&lt;br /&gt;
# The preview teased &amp;ldquo;An old lover of Sara&amp;rsquo;s.&amp;rdquo; Did anyone get the feeling they had been lovers?!? I sensed an attraction, but not that sort of vibe. Then again, Jorja Fox can be a bit tough to read, so maybe the crooked smile meant lover.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Either way, I hope we get more of Sara and her relationship; I would like to see it go somewhere. It just seems like a boat anchor around her neck; she can&amp;rdquo;t date because she married to a ghost, she can&amp;rdquo;t hold bidirectional conversations because William Petersen isn&amp;rsquo;t really on the show, we only get one side if she talks to him at all.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rdquo;s just frustrating watching the character float in limbo!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the other hand, you can tell it&amp;rsquo;s December as Donna Hoppe (Pamela Reed) made a return visit approximately one year after her last visit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rdquo;m not sure if they are trying Reed out to see if she would work as a series regular or frequent visitor, but she was great. She fills in a gap in research and knowledge that helped when she was here before and she certainly helped this week.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Overall I&amp;rdquo;m giving the episode 4.2 family trees for a fun return of Reed and a much needed revisit to the Grissom family line. I hope everyone has a safe and happy holidays and we will see you all back here with the return of CSI in January.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TVEquals</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2012/tvequals/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Dec 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2012/tvequals/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Now that all of my fellow GSR fans have breathed a collective sigh of relief, although it might be a bit premature, I can honestly say that &amp;lsquo;Risky Business Class,&amp;rsquo; this week&amp;rdquo;s episode of CSI, will only ever be memorable as the episode that clearly exposed the rift in Grissom and Sara&amp;rdquo;s marriage.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There have been signs that the long distance arrangement is wearing on her all season, but it usually takes something big to make us wake up and realize there&amp;rdquo;s a problem in our lives, and for Sara it took the appearance of Doug Wilson, an NSTB investigator and former fling from San Francisco, who arrived in Vegas to investigate the crash of a small charter plane just off the Strip.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;By the way, has CBS tightened the show&amp;rdquo;s budget? How come we never actually saw the crash site? That kind of threw me a little. It might have even done the episode a disservice, as not seeing the scope of the crash meant that we never formed a visceral attachment to the victims, so it was harder to get into the story of their deaths.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Seeing Doug definitely threw Sara for a loop, but while she ignored a call from Grissom, she never crossed any lines. Even the hug she gave Doug before he left town was less about wanting to connect him with him and more about just wanting to hold someone since she couldn&amp;rdquo;t hold her husband. He brought up some great memories for her, but Sara is not a cheater, and had things gone any further, I probably wouldn&amp;rdquo;t be writing these reviews anymore.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It begs the question, thoughâ¦how is this story going to end? And should we even get our hopes up for a Grissom cameo by the end of the year?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CSI Files</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2012/csi-files-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Dec 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2012/csi-files-01/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;There&amp;rsquo;s a fine line to ride when doing interviews with folks from the &lt;em&gt;CSI: Crime Scene Investigation&lt;/em&gt; franchise. Obviously, I am a huge fan of the shows (otherwise I would not be here), so there’s always a bit of excitement and nostalgia when doing promotional material. But there’s always a reminder in the back of my head that CSI Files is a very professional outlet, and I have to be somewhat on guard as to how ‘geeky’ I get. However, this week’s interview subject is someone I consider to be a vital and important part to the &lt;em&gt;CSI&lt;/em&gt; franchise and her knowledge and history from the early days of &lt;em&gt;CSI&lt;/em&gt; is so enlightening and special. &lt;em&gt;CSI: Miami&lt;/em&gt; producer &lt;strong&gt;Corey Miller&lt;/strong&gt; first introduced me to &lt;strong&gt;Elizabeth Devine&lt;/strong&gt; in 2006, and we had scheduled an interview that never quite worked out (on my end). We reconnected a few years ago much to my delight and I feel like professionally, from a career standpoint, she has changed the direction of the path I take for the better. Devine, who is one of the nicest people you will ever meet, started out at a real-life CSI before segueing into an entirely different career: a writer at &lt;em&gt;CSI&lt;/em&gt;. More often than not I find myself increasingly frustrated by how impatient I can be by my pursuits to engage in a television career as well, but Devine gives one hope that, no matter what the job is now, engaging in other professional endeavors is likely to happen.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here below the consulting producer previews the final episode of 2012, Sara&amp;rsquo;s unhappiness in her life, and looks back on the history of two &lt;em&gt;CSI&lt;/em&gt; classics.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CSI Files&lt;/strong&gt;: Having been on set for some of &amp;ldquo;Risky Business Class,&amp;rdquo; I get the feeling that the Grissom/Sara pot is being stirred a little bit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Elizabeth Devine&lt;/strong&gt;: Yes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CSI Files&lt;/strong&gt;: With Doug Wilson (&lt;strong&gt;Josh Randall&lt;/strong&gt;) entering the picture does it seem on first blush that he is a threat to their marriage?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Devine&lt;/strong&gt;: We&amp;rsquo;re not playing it as that right &lt;em&gt;now&lt;/em&gt;, but it&amp;rsquo;s more of a realization that she&amp;rsquo;s not getting what she needs out of the relationship with Grissom [&lt;strong&gt;William Petersen&lt;/strong&gt;] being so far away. This is a person that she had a relationship before coming to the crime lab in Vegas and it went well, and we don&amp;rsquo;t know why they didn&amp;rsquo;t pursue it but some probably think it&amp;rsquo;s because she moved to Vegas to work at the Las Vegas Crime Lab. He comes back in the picture and she sees that she can be attracted to somebody and deserves to have someone to be around. Grissom&amp;rsquo;s not there and she&amp;rsquo;s very lonely. I think it&amp;rsquo;s pretty obvious in her expressions that this has been a hard time apart for her.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CSI Files&lt;/strong&gt;: I have a feeling that this is not the way Sara (&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt;) had envisioned her marriage to go.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Devine&lt;/strong&gt;: Right. There&amp;rsquo;s no question that she loves him, it&amp;rsquo;s not about that; it&amp;rsquo;s how they&amp;rsquo;re apart so much that I think whenever she hears about being married, I think she feels so separate from him that it&amp;rsquo;s got to be impacting the way she feels about their relationship.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CSI Files&lt;/strong&gt;: Doug comes from San Francisco and Sara&amp;rsquo;s whole history and back-story originates from that city. Is Sara&amp;rsquo;s mother mentioned in this episode, or any of her back-story at all?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Devine&lt;/strong&gt;: No, we don&amp;rsquo;t talk about that at all. We really just mention that she worked an assist for the NTSB when she was in San Francisco. They had a plane crash there and that&amp;rsquo;s how she met him. They worked together and became close. That&amp;rsquo;s about as much detail as you&amp;rsquo;re going to get from Sara, but their body language is pretty obvious that they had a relationship. He does try to pursue it a bit in the episode.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CSI Files&lt;/strong&gt;: And how does Sara react to that?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Devine&lt;/strong&gt;: She obviously says no. [Laughs.] But I think you can see that she&amp;rsquo;s torn in the fact that not him specifically, but just she&amp;rsquo;s very lonely and she&amp;rsquo;s sad; it&amp;rsquo;s wearing on her. They&amp;rsquo;re playing phone-tag, which we start the episode with, and it&amp;rsquo;s hard for her. She doesn&amp;rsquo;t get to talk to him when she wants to and they have to squeeze time in to talk to each other. They make quick flights to see each other but it&amp;rsquo;s not a consistent situation and she&amp;rsquo;s not happy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CSI Files&lt;/strong&gt;: You&amp;rsquo;ve been involved with &lt;em&gt;CSI&lt;/em&gt; since the beginning, so you most certainly know Grissom and Sara to a T. From your own point of view, what would your ideal situation for this couple be?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Devine&lt;/strong&gt;: Well if I had my way, we&amp;rsquo;d have him have a fear of losing her and get him back, but that&amp;rsquo;s not going to happen. [Laughs.] We love Grissom and everybody loves Grissom; it&amp;rsquo;s impossible not to. But is he a good husband? I think he does the best he can. I think their separation is easier on him than it is for her, I&amp;rsquo;ll just say that. I don&amp;rsquo;t think it has to do with how they feel about each other, I really want to stress that. I think it&amp;rsquo;s more it&amp;rsquo;s hard to maintain a long-distance relationship and retain the intimacy that you need when you&amp;rsquo;re married to somebody. She&amp;rsquo;s finding that to be difficult and he must too. We&amp;rsquo;re very sensitive about Grissom. We want to protect that character because everyone loves him, but we also have Sara here and she is the character that we see, so we also feel that we have to protect her as well. It&amp;rsquo;s very hard to figure out what to do because this character is basically talking on the phone to her husband and that&amp;rsquo;s all we see. In a perfect world we&amp;rsquo;d get Billy back, have him shoot some scenes, and we&amp;rsquo;d all be happy. But we don&amp;rsquo;t know if that&amp;rsquo;s going to happen. Right now we&amp;rsquo;re playing that it&amp;rsquo;s wearing on them and there will be developments from that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CSI Files&lt;/strong&gt;: Donna Hoppe (&lt;strong&gt;Pamela Reed&lt;/strong&gt;) also makes a return. Her involvement here is more with Morgan (&lt;strong&gt;Elisabeth Harnois&lt;/strong&gt;). What can you tease about their connection?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Devine&lt;/strong&gt;: We know that Morgan has been establishing a closer relationship with her father [Conrad Ecklie, &lt;strong&gt;Marc Vann&lt;/strong&gt;] after really being estranged from him for so long. Now that she&amp;rsquo;s in Vegas, and especially after him being shot, they have become closer and it&amp;rsquo;s a perfect opportunity to play with the genealogy a bit. She is looking into Ecklie&amp;rsquo;s history because she&amp;rsquo;s been a Brody, and now she wants to learn a little more about the Ecklies. That&amp;rsquo;s how we get into the Donna Hoppe story, but she&amp;rsquo;s also close with Doc Robbins [&lt;strong&gt;Robert David Hall&lt;/strong&gt;]. Doc Robbins expressed a lot of excitement about everything Donna and her group were able to do in &amp;ldquo;Genetic Disorder&amp;rdquo; for him, so he suggested to her that it might be a great way to connect with that side of her family. Donna also helps us solve this case.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CSI Files&lt;/strong&gt;: How does &amp;ldquo;Risky Business Class&amp;rdquo; compare to Season One&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Unfriendly Skies&amp;rdquo;?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Devine&lt;/strong&gt;: They&amp;rsquo;re completely different.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CSI Files&lt;/strong&gt;: How was it reuniting with &lt;strong&gt;Mark Moses&lt;/strong&gt;?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Devine&lt;/strong&gt;: It was great. I was so so new when he was on the show in Season One [&amp;ldquo;Sex, Lies, And Larvae&amp;rdquo;], it was early for me in terms of working on a set, so I was a little intimidated by actors. He is such a nice man and I&amp;rsquo;m a huge fan of his work on &lt;em&gt;Mad Men&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;Desperate Housewives&lt;/em&gt;. I enjoyed having him in the episode.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CSI Files&lt;/strong&gt;: You&amp;rsquo;re working more on development in the coming months, but are you going to be writing an additional episode this season?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Devine&lt;/strong&gt;: I do not know. It could be, but maybe not. We have a big staff and we have some new kids we want to give opportunities to. I&amp;rsquo;m happy to just jump in and help out and hopefully share some of my experience and help them make a great episode. A lot of this job is helping them mentor people coming up and we have some great young writers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CSI Files&lt;/strong&gt;: Now that this particular actress is free you know what storyline I&amp;rsquo;d like you to revisit?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Devine&lt;/strong&gt;: What?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CSI Files&lt;/strong&gt;: &amp;ldquo;Organ Grinder.&amp;rdquo;&lt;strong&gt;Devine&lt;/strong&gt;: Aaaaah!&lt;strong&gt;CSI Files&lt;/strong&gt;: Since &lt;strong&gt;Marcia Cross&lt;/strong&gt; isn&amp;rsquo;t doing anything, I think that would make for a great sequel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Devine&lt;/strong&gt;: That was right before she hit big with Desperate Housewives. I remember &lt;strong&gt;Carol&lt;/strong&gt; [&lt;strong&gt;Mendelsohn&lt;/strong&gt;], of course, was involved with writing the great &lt;em&gt;Melrose Place&lt;/em&gt; episode where the shock and awe of when she took that wig off and you saw those scars… do you remember that?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CSI Files&lt;/strong&gt;: I haven&amp;rsquo;t seen it, no.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Devine&lt;/strong&gt;: Oh my God! Anyone that watched &lt;em&gt;Melrose Place&lt;/em&gt; it was just shocking. So Carol was involved with that and it had a great deal to do with Marcia Cross being cast in &amp;ldquo;Organ Grinder.&amp;rdquo; That would be fun. I would have to watch the episode again to remind myself how we left that. I think she went to jail, did she?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CSI Files&lt;/strong&gt;: No! Remember Sara got really peeved by them getting away, and Grissom reminded her that there&amp;rsquo;s no statute of limitations on murder.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Devine&lt;/strong&gt;: That&amp;rsquo;s right! I love her. I would love to have her back.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CSI Files&lt;/strong&gt;: I was also watching &amp;ldquo;The Accused Is Entitled&amp;rdquo; is still a classic to this day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Devine&lt;/strong&gt;: Yeah, I really wanted to do that episode. It&amp;rsquo;s such a big thing for cops in Vegas and California, so that was kind of a fun thing to explore where all these cops come to Vegas for a race, someone dies, and all our suspects could be cops.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Televizier</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2012/televizier/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2012/televizier/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;[Translated from Dutch by Google &amp;amp; Corrected by Volunteers.]&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;rdquo;&amp;lsquo;In the new season of CSI, Russel has to save his granddaughter. Sara finds an important lead. If he hadn&amp;rdquo;t had herâ¦&amp;rdquo;&amp;rsquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A corrupt officer of the LAPD appears to be working closely with the kidnappers. He leads CSI-investigator Finn (Elisabeth Shue) to where D.B. Russell&amp;rdquo;s (Ted Danson) granddaughter Katie is being held. The girl is allowed to call her grandfather to show she is still alive. The head of the laboratory gets very angry: who targets his family, targets him. The kidnappers demand a ransom of two million dollar. In the meantime, Nick Stokes starts drinking because he wants to quit and deputy sheriff Conrad Ecklie is in the hospital. He was shot in the season finale of the last season of the still popular crime show. Sara Sidle (Jorja Fox) finds evidence at the crime scene, Russell&amp;rdquo;s house that can possibly lead them to the kidnappers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;rdquo;&amp;lsquo;Calmness and wisdom&amp;rdquo;&amp;rsquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sara is starting to take Catherine Willows, the former right hand of the boss of the nightshift, place on CSI: a &amp;ldquo;mother hen&amp;rdquo; with experience who radiates calmness and wisdom. As of 2011,Jorja Fox is playing the role again on a weekly basis, after a break of a few seasons. &amp;ldquo;Sara has become more mature and wiser,&amp;rdquo; admits the 43-year-old actress. &amp;ldquo;She had to get away for a while, to regain her balance after a few shocking cases. During that time she buried some demons from her past, so she could start over with a clean slate.&amp;rdquo; Her marriage to Gil Grissom is also something that has been good for Sara: &amp;ldquo;Because of that she has become a lot more stable. I do have to admit that they haven&amp;rdquo;t seen each other for a long time. This could mean that there is some tension between Sara and Gil. But what exactly is going on, I don&amp;rdquo;t know. I&amp;rdquo;m not on the writers team.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;rdquo;&amp;lsquo;Season 13&amp;rdquo;&amp;rsquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;About the thirteenth season of CSI, which starts tonight on RTL 4, we can say that Sara and het colleagues will be personally involved with the cases. The son of CSI Warrick Brown, who was murdered four years ago, comes back into the picture, which brings back some painful memories. After the discovery of a mass grave, Finn gets to deal with an unsolved case from het past and het ex-husband. And D.B. Russel will again be having a hard time, when his son Brandon gets accused of murder.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CSI Files</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2012/csi-files-09/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2012/csi-files-09/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;CSI: Crime Scene Investigation&lt;/em&gt; is preparing for some heavy character development in the second stretch of Season Thirteen.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sources close to the show tell CSI Files exclusively that Sara Sidle (&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt;), Nick Stokes (&lt;strong&gt;George Eads&lt;/strong&gt;), and Morgan Brody (&lt;strong&gt;Elisabeth Harnois&lt;/strong&gt;) will be dealing with some significant character development during the remainder of this season, and also potentially set the stage for a visit from returning characters.&amp;lsquo;We want to more completely address the issue of Sara and Grissom; the challenge of that for her, certainly,&amp;rsquo; one source tells CSI Files. That particular storyline will gain traction in this season&amp;rdquo;s tenth episode, &amp;lsquo;Risky Business Class,&amp;rsquo; which is scheduled to air December 12. &lt;em&gt;Ed&lt;/em&gt; star &lt;strong&gt;Josh Randall&lt;/strong&gt; will appear (in what is being eyed as a recurring role) as a NTSB investigator that Sara previously worked with in San Francisco, the city she was employed in prior to joining Grissom&amp;rdquo;s (&lt;strong&gt;William Petersen&lt;/strong&gt;) team in &amp;lsquo;Cool Change.&amp;rsquo; Randall&amp;rdquo;s Doug Wilson character comes at a time where Sara and Grissom&amp;rdquo;s marriage is going through a difficult and straining time, and mere seconds after the couple try yet again to connect on the phone. &amp;lsquo;We have big plans for Sara,&amp;rsquo; another source shares. &amp;lsquo;The audience is going to be very interested in a turn that she takes.&amp;rsquo; Though not able to elaborate on what direction the character will be taking, CSI Files has learned exclusively that &lt;strong&gt;Adam J. Harrington&lt;/strong&gt;, who played Ronald Basderic in this season&amp;rdquo;s &amp;lsquo;Code Blue Plate Special,&amp;rsquo; will return and quite possibly reignite some of Sara&amp;rdquo;s anger and frustration seen earlier this year. &amp;lsquo;That&amp;rdquo;s going to be an interesting adventure.&amp;rsquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To fill the rest of the season out: an episode that has some Latin music flavor, an odd forensics murder mystery at an all-female poker tournament that has a unique murder weapon, and maybe another visit or two from some of &lt;em&gt;CSI&lt;/em&gt;&amp;ldquo;s iconic characters from the past. &amp;lsquo;There&amp;rdquo;s a possibility of a Lady Heather [&lt;strong&gt;Melinda Clarke&lt;/strong&gt;] and Sofia Curtis [&lt;strong&gt;Louise Lombard&lt;/strong&gt;], but the writers have stories they&amp;rdquo;re working on and it all depends on a case and story basis.&amp;rsquo;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CSI Files</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2012/csi-files-03/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2012/csi-files-03/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CSI Files&lt;/strong&gt;: Who of the original team is most affected by this episode?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mularz&lt;/strong&gt;: I&amp;rdquo;d say Nick and Sara. Nick and Sara, I feel like, take it the hardest. Brass has a really nice moment where he talks about how he actually hasn&amp;rdquo;t been to the cemetery since Warrick&amp;rdquo;s funeral, but he has his own ways of remembering him. Brass likes to think about how much energy Warrick had. He says a little piece about Fight Nights, those are the nights that he thinks of Warrick. He has a feeling that there&amp;rdquo;s no way he would be missing all of that electric energy on the Strip. So they each have their own ways of remembering him, but I think Nick and Sara are the two who the weight is most apparent on their shoulders as they&amp;rdquo;re dealing with this case.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CSI Files&lt;/strong&gt;: I was watching the pilot the other day for what seems like the 700th time. From the onset, Brass and Warrick had a very tumultuous relationship.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mularz&lt;/strong&gt;: Brass and Warrick had an adversarial relationship at the start, and so did Sara and Warrick at the very start. Sara kind of blames Warrick&amp;rdquo;s gambling for Holly Gribbs&amp;rdquo; incident, and she is skeptical of him until a little ways into that season when there&amp;rdquo;s a misunderstanding about whether Warrick was leaving on duty again to go gamble, and it turns out he was actually going to pick up money to help out this boy he was helping support, so they grew much closer. At the start of the show, both of those relationships, Brass and Warrick and Sara and Warrick, were pretty rocky.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ming Lo (25 October 2012)</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2012/ming-lo/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Oct 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2012/ming-lo/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From time to time, the music we play and with all the noise, we&amp;rdquo;d have to take a break from shooting. For example, they played Queen&amp;rdquo;s &amp;lsquo;We will rock you&amp;rsquo;, and the crowd got into it, dancing and waving their hands. Meanwhile, the crew and cast would walk around and record video of everyone. On another one of these breaks, Jorja Fox did an impressive little dance in a little hidden space behind video village. When she came out for the next take, I said to her, &amp;lsquo;I caught your little dance. You got some moves, I was very impressed.&amp;rsquo; For the record, I thought she was quite good. &amp;lsquo;You should do a musical. In fact, you should do a musical version of CSI, where everyone sings and dances.&amp;rsquo; Now I have to admit, I have always found Jorja Fox to be likeable on screen. Even back on West Wing, where she played a Secret Service agent, I wanted to see more of her and hoped that her storyline would get extended. And it turns out in real life, she&amp;rdquo;s actually exactly that &amp;ndash; very warm and friendly. When I met her at base camp, she immediately introduced herself in a very welcoming way, and when we took the van to set, she was like, &amp;lsquo;Have you met everyone?&amp;rsquo; She played a bit of a host, even though she had, of course, no obligation to do so. So when I brought up the musical, she didn&amp;rdquo;t even blink, she said, &amp;lsquo;Oh totally, and I have this great idea for it.&amp;rsquo; And she went on to describe how all the music and dancing could happen in one of the CSI character&amp;rdquo;s dreams. And then she said, &amp;lsquo;I&amp;rdquo;ve been pitching this, you gotta help me sell it to the producers.&amp;rsquo; So later, I walked up to one of the producers, mentioned my conversation with Jorja, and the musical CSI Las Vegas idea. He sorted grunted, nodded, and walked off. Hmmâ¦ guess that went over well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Examiner.com</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2012/examiner-com/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Oct 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2012/examiner-com/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;CSI,&amp;rdquo; which airs on CBS 2 in Queens, may be dealing with a possible act of terrorism in an upcoming episode. What happened? On Saturday,Â SpoilerTVÂ shared the following synopsis for episode 10, &amp;ldquo;Risky Business Class.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;When a small executive jet crash lands a mile off the Strip, the CSIs wonder if it was intended as an act of terror, and to solve the case, Sara teams up with a former colleague from San Francisco with whom she still has sparks.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Wild Flowers&amp;rdquo;Â did show Sara leaving Gil Grissom a voicemail, but it&amp;rsquo;s hard maintaining a long distance relationship, a fact she and D.B. discussed. Was that planting the seeds for some trouble in Sara and Gil&amp;rsquo;s relationship or at least the hint of trouble? Could this former colleague try to make a move since there&amp;rsquo;s still chemistry there and Sara has to point out that she still has Gil, even if they&amp;rsquo;re not living together at the moment?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Meanwhile, is this &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; case an act of terrorism or is it specific to who was on the jet? With it being an executive jet, we wouldn&amp;rsquo;t be surprised if it was the latterâand perhaps caused by someone who has a history with whoever was on board. Will the CSIs come across something that points in the direction of terrorism until perhaps the end of the episode? With even the possibility of this being an act of terror, they have to tread very carefully; if it was, there could be another attempted attack coming.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CSI Files (17 October 2012)</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2012/csi-files-04/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2012/csi-files-04/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;rdquo;&amp;lsquo;CSI Files:&amp;ldquo;&amp;rsquo; Sara [&amp;ldquo;&amp;lsquo;Jorja Fox&amp;rdquo;&amp;rsquo;] brings up her relationship with Grissom [&amp;ldquo;&amp;lsquo;William Petersen&amp;rdquo;&amp;rsquo;] this week. What&amp;rdquo;s the status with those two? Is he living in Vegas or is he still abroad?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;rdquo;&amp;lsquo;Pokaski:&amp;ldquo;&amp;rsquo; He&amp;rdquo;s still abroad. This year, without giving too much away, we&amp;rdquo;re going to start dealing with the fact that long-distance relationships are hard. I don&amp;rdquo;t know if you&amp;rdquo;ve ever been in a long-distance relationship, but my wife and I were apart for a while and there&amp;rdquo;s a lot of message leaving. So it starts with Sara leaving a message and kind of beginning in the sense that long-distance relationships have challenges.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;rdquo;&amp;lsquo;CSI Files:&amp;ldquo;&amp;rsquo; Since it&amp;rdquo;s hard to know what Billy&amp;rdquo;s involvement will be, is it easier having Grissom off and about than having the character in Vegas, or is it simply a story and creative decision?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;rdquo;&amp;lsquo;Pokaski:&amp;ldquo;&amp;rsquo; I can&amp;rdquo;t speak for everyone else, but I prefer having him abroad because it allows you to focus 100% on Sara and Jorja Fox who is another actress I&amp;rdquo;m just enamored with. It makes it easier to just look at her and not have to make up those weird stories like, &amp;lsquo;Oh you just missed him!&amp;rsquo; or &amp;lsquo;We had breakfast today.&amp;rsquo; It&amp;rdquo;s an easier thing for me to hang on to as a writer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ScreenPicks</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2012/screenpicks/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Oct 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2012/screenpicks/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Written in conjunction with PopCulturePassionistas.com.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jorja Fox, best know for her roles on &lt;em&gt;CSI: Crime Scene Investigation&lt;/em&gt; along with &lt;em&gt;The West Wing&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;ER&lt;/em&gt;, is also an avid environmentalist and conservationist. She is being honored this weekend with the Animal Champion Award for her work with Animal Defenders International. ADI has worked tirelessly to rescue and protect the abused and neglected animals across the globe.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The event this weekend, called the Lion Ark Night will focus on the rescue mission performed last year where ADI uncovered and put an end to cruelty to circus animals in Bolivia. They went undercover to rescue 29 lions and airlifted them from South America to Denver. *Price is Right *former host Bob Barker funded the entire thing and he, too, will be honored this weekend with ADI&amp;rdquo;s Lifetime Achievement Award. The entire rescue is being made into a documentary called &lt;em&gt;Lion Ark&lt;/em&gt; and clips will be shown at this weekend&amp;rdquo;s Hollywood Hills gala.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a recent exclusive interview, we spoke with Jorja about her work with ADI. We asked her about the event and she replied, &amp;lsquo;It&amp;rdquo;s going to be a heck of a partyâ¦ Bob Barker&amp;rdquo;s going to be there. You can&amp;rdquo;t beat that. I try never to miss a good party.&amp;rsquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jorja talked about working with Bob, &amp;lsquo;He&amp;rdquo;s a legend. He&amp;rdquo;s the nicest man. He&amp;rdquo;s funny. He&amp;rdquo;s got great style. Every time I see him I&amp;rdquo;m wondering what he&amp;rdquo;s going to be wearing. Maybe single handedly, more than anybody else that I know of, has been quietly contributing to causes that are very close to my heart and been contributing in extraordinary ways. Bob travels less than he used. He gets out in front of the public less than he used. And he&amp;rdquo;s been making up for that behind the scenes. He has given incredibly generous gifts to several organizations over the last couple of years that have really allowed the organizations to stay afloat.&amp;rsquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While she fully supports the award being bestowed on Barker this weekend, she is less than enthusiastic about her own honor. She stated, &amp;lsquo;It feels really undeserved. I feel I have a lot more to do, a lot more to accomplish.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But it seems to us that like Jorja has done plenty. She remarked, &amp;lsquo;Every time they call me, they call me for something extremely exciting.&amp;rsquo; Aside form her involvement in the Lion Ark project, she has produced a documentary called &lt;em&gt;How I Became an Elephant&lt;/em&gt;. It is the tale of a girl who travels to Thailand to rescue an elephant working in the entertainment industry. Jorja cautioned that this is not an isolated problem, but a global one. She pointed out that many animals in captivity are forced to live on concrete, which can kill them. She said countless elephants die in zoos due to of infection in their feet because they weren&amp;rdquo;t designed to stand on concrete. She noted, &amp;lsquo;That&amp;rdquo;s a crime. I think these animals deserve a lot better than that.&amp;rsquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jorja also went to Capital Hill with ADI last year to launch the &amp;lsquo;Traveling Exotic Animal Protection Act.&amp;rsquo; And she encourages all animal lovers to call or write their congressperson to support the bill which will protect animals in entertainment who travel and from state to state. She stated that they need a federal law to protect them because they fall through the cracks since each state&amp;rdquo;s laws vary.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She also emphasized the importance that the work of the ADI has not just for the animals but for humans as well. &amp;lsquo;We can&amp;rdquo;t exist without wildlife. We&amp;rdquo;re just completely kidding ourselves if we think we can go it alone without all these animals. And so looking after these animals is important to me for the sake of these animals but also for the sake of &amp;nbsp;people and the future of this planet. I don&amp;rdquo;t want to live on Mars.&amp;rsquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of her goals is to eradicate certain animal institutions. &amp;lsquo;If I had my way, circuses and zoos would be a thing of the past in the way that we know them now. I think there&amp;rdquo;s a place for those institutions in the future. But I don&amp;rdquo;t think they&amp;rdquo;d look anything like what they look like right now.&amp;rsquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So we asked what they would look like in her version of the future. And while she acknowledged some habitats that already look like her dream there are many more that don&amp;rdquo;t. &amp;lsquo;I&amp;rdquo;d like to see us moving under this umbrella term of &amp;ldquo;sanctuary,&amp;rdquo; so a tremendous amount of more space, no breeding programs. The public being able to see them would still happen but it would be more removed. People would be in a more respectful, quieter space.&amp;rsquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And to Jorja the perfect circus is one without animals like Cirque du Soleil. She stated, &amp;lsquo;We have so much to learn from these animals. We haven&amp;rdquo;t even begun to figure out what we can learn from them. But I know it&amp;rdquo;s not about watching an elephant put a basketball in a hoop. I think we can do better than that.&amp;rsquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tickets for Lion Ark Night 2012 on Saturday, October 13 are $150 and VIP tickets are $500 (which includes a VIP champagne reception). [&amp;hellip;] Jorja&amp;rdquo;s movie &lt;em&gt;How I Became an Elephant&lt;/em&gt; is being screened in the Los Angeles area this weekend. [&amp;hellip;] And if you&amp;rdquo;re in the New York area this fall, Jorja is producing a one woman show about Dusty Springfield. [&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CSI Files</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2012/csi-files-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Oct 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2012/csi-files-02/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Anyone who knows Jorja Fox&amp;nbsp;understands just how special of a woman she is. The Sara Sidle actress is not only amazingly humble, talented, and yes, beautiful, but she&amp;rdquo;s also incredibly&amp;nbsp;brilliant, kind, and well spoken, which makes anyone in her presence feel special. After playing this one character for over twelve seasons, she knows the ins and outs of her character to a T, and is always eager to add new layers and nuances to her performance. Fortunately, for fans, this season will be a year of personal development for many of the characters on &lt;em&gt;CSI&lt;/em&gt;, which will allow Fox to crank out some of those dramatic performances she&amp;rdquo;s known for. Which is the case tonight with the new episode &amp;lsquo;Code Blue Plate Special,&amp;rsquo; an installment that really hits close to home for Sara. Shane Saunders&amp;nbsp;caught up with the actress earlier this week to discuss character growth, upcoming episodes, and yes, the state of GSR. Spoilers after the jump.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CSI Files&lt;/strong&gt;: As I watched &amp;lsquo;Karma to Burn&amp;rsquo; I really thought back to the beginning of the series, and really up until a few seasons ago, how Sara was at times moody, insubordinate, and slightly immature, but now she&amp;rdquo;s this completely new woman who, to me, seems to have taken over, in a professional sense, the &amp;ldquo;Mother Hen&amp;rdquo; role from Catherine. There&amp;rdquo;s been this huge journey and evolution of the character, that, at least in my mind, seems to have taken this huge shift after she returned in Season Ten, announcing that she married Grissom. Would you say that&amp;rdquo;s one of the reasons as well?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt;: [Laughs.] &lt;em&gt;Oooooh&lt;/em&gt;. Marriage? Well, yeah, I think she&amp;rdquo;s aged, obviously, like everyone has and hopefully people get a little more mature as they age. I think that she needed to leave not just Vegas, but she had to leave that whole profession behind to just kind of really find her center and her balance. I think as a kid, having the experience she had with her mom and growing up in foster care, I think she had a drive that brought her to the field that she was in in kind of a blind, personal and passionate way. When she quit it and just left, started traveling around the world&amp;ndash;and eventually Grissom [&lt;strong&gt;William Petersen&lt;/strong&gt;] joined her&amp;ndash;I think she found the love for what she was doing from a whole different place. She buried some ghosts and buried some demons, and was able to come back at it. And, yes, absolutely I think being in a secure and loving relationship with Grissom&amp;ndash;I hope very much it&amp;rdquo;s helped her stability in that way. Although, I think, reading&amp;nbsp;in between&amp;nbsp;the lines, it&amp;rdquo;s really been awhile since we&amp;rdquo;ve seen Grissom so I&amp;rdquo;ve gotta imagine there&amp;rdquo;s got to be a little bit of tension there. But I wouldn&amp;rdquo;t know what it is yet because I&amp;rdquo;m not one of the writers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CSI Files&lt;/strong&gt;: I would imagine after playing this character for over a decade, portraying her in this new light gives you as an actress some fun things to do.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Fox&lt;/strong&gt;: Oh, yeah, and I think we&amp;rdquo;ve talked about this before, but to come into Season Thirteen&amp;ndash;really forget about of the same show, but of the same character&amp;ndash;is something I thought I&amp;rdquo;d never experience in my life. If someone had asked me about it when I was younger, I could never have even conceived playing a character that long; it probably would have scared me and might have been something I wouldn&amp;rdquo;t think would be fun. But I can&amp;rdquo;t believe after thirteen seasons, like, I&amp;rdquo;m not bored at all; I&amp;rdquo;m still like, &amp;ldquo;Wow, what&amp;rdquo;s going to happen this year? Who are the people that Sara&amp;rdquo;s going to meet this year?&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rdquo;s really exciting to have three new cast members kind of in one season. I could have thought that would be sort of disruptive and might shake the cast up in a way that&amp;ndash;because we&amp;rdquo;ve always been &lt;em&gt;so&lt;/em&gt; close and a really tight that cast that has always gotten along so well&amp;ndash;to sort of three wild cards in there you&amp;rdquo;d think, &amp;ldquo;Wowâ¦ this can&amp;rdquo;t go well. It&amp;rdquo;s just a question of how badly this is going to go.&amp;rdquo; And it&amp;rdquo;s been fantastic; I can&amp;rdquo;t even believe that we&amp;rdquo;ve been able to ride that wave and it&amp;rdquo;s just been so fun to have these people to work with, people that are amazingly cool and just incredibly kind and generous as actors and human beings. Of course I still miss &lt;strong&gt;Marg&lt;/strong&gt; [&lt;strong&gt;Helgenberger&lt;/strong&gt;, Catherine Willows], Billy and &lt;strong&gt;Gary&lt;/strong&gt; [&lt;strong&gt;Dourdan&lt;/strong&gt;, Warrick Brown] all the time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We just finished Episode Seven and we meet Warrick&amp;rdquo;s son, who we haven&amp;rdquo;t seen since the funeral [in &amp;ldquo;For Warrick&amp;rdquo;], and his ex-wife. It was a really difficult and devastating episode to shoot. I know I miss him and I really wish we would have never killed him off&amp;ndash;I feel like I really disagreed with The Powers That Be with that call. It was really hard to go back and shoot, but I really think it&amp;rdquo;s going to be a beautiful show.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CSI Files&lt;/strong&gt;: One of the big takeaways for me from last season was the dynamic of DB and Sara. Those two really hit it off, and I think they can relate in a way that, for example, they both have so much going on in their lives and have to work this grueling and taxing job, and put it all on the back-burner. And from what I read most fans feel that way, as well. What have you enjoyed most about working with &lt;strong&gt;Ted Danson&lt;/strong&gt;?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Fox&lt;/strong&gt;: He&amp;rdquo;s really amazing; I&amp;rdquo;m not sure he&amp;rdquo;s human. People know him for ten minutes, but he&amp;rdquo;s the kind of guy that can show up and create chemistry with someone. You could look into his eyes in a scene and feel like you&amp;rdquo;ve known each other ten years. Most people that work with him probably feel that way. [Laughs.] He has that amazing talent to make everyone feel special and on top of that he&amp;rdquo;s just an incredible leader. No matter how long a day yet, he&amp;rdquo;s still got his energy and his optimism. He&amp;rdquo;s incredibly funny and it&amp;rdquo;s really nice to stay around at work&amp;ndash;some of the days can be pretty gruesome and horrible&amp;ndash;and just kind of laugh. I&amp;rdquo;m glad they&amp;rdquo;ve been able to put a little bit of that into the show; I think the show will never be a comedy, but we&amp;rdquo;ve been able to do more funny stuff in this last season than probably in all the years of the show combined.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CSI Files&lt;/strong&gt;: From what I can gather, you&amp;rdquo;ll be doing a reduced number of episodes this season. Are we looking at doing more or less episodes than last season?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Fox&lt;/strong&gt;: That is not always totally in form; it doesn&amp;rdquo;t really take shape until we get through the season. I know that I&amp;rdquo;ll do a minimum of fifteen, so probably somewhere between fifteen and seventeen. We sort of take a couple months at a time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CSI Files&lt;/strong&gt;: You took a break seasons eight and nine. Is your plan as of now to see the show to the end?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Fox&lt;/strong&gt;: [Laughs.] I can&amp;rdquo;t answer that, Shane! Only because we always think, &amp;ldquo;&lt;em&gt;Aaah&lt;/em&gt;, it&amp;rdquo;s probably only one more season. Maybe two more seasons.&amp;rdquo; I sort of think we got to be coming close to the end, but who knows, right? Hopefully we can go another ten years. Yes, right now, theoretically, I think I&amp;rdquo;d like to see it to the end; that would be a really cool thing to accomplish. My goal as of now is to do twenty seasons in a row on primetime network television and this, for me, I&amp;rdquo;m starting season seventeen.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CSI Files&lt;/strong&gt;: Oh wow.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Fox&lt;/strong&gt;: Yeah. Some of those seasons I may have done only four or five shows, but I was in there; I snuck my face in there. [Laughs.]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CSI Files&lt;/strong&gt;: &amp;lsquo;Code Blue Plate Special,&amp;rsquo; is a rather significant installment for Sara. How personal of a case is this to her?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Fox&lt;/strong&gt;: Pretty personal. I think it&amp;rdquo;s going to be a really great episode; I haven&amp;rdquo;t seen it. [Laughs.] I totally expected it to be on last Wednesday&amp;ndash;I was like, &amp;lsquo;Where are all the shows?&amp;rsquo; I enjoyed watching the debates but didn&amp;rdquo;t realize how much they would preempt everything. Not only does Sara know the victim, but she believes she knows the suspect. It&amp;rdquo;s pretty personal, I think. It&amp;rdquo;s certainly something that Sara is incredibly passionate about. You&amp;rdquo;re going to see Sara get very angry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CSI Files&lt;/strong&gt;: We&amp;rdquo;ve seen her look into cases of those she&amp;rdquo;s known in the past; how emotionally invested is she in this case, as to say from &amp;lsquo;One Hit Wonder,&amp;rsquo; when her friend Melissa Winters goes from victim to suspect?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Fox&lt;/strong&gt;: [Laughs.] Oh, wow. That&amp;rdquo;sâ¦ thank you for mentioning that episode. [Laughs.] This is a person that Sara sees several times a week in her life. She knows the intricacies of this woman&amp;rdquo;s life and the suspect? She hates this guy. She hates him. He&amp;rdquo;s a really talented guy and he&amp;rdquo;s that guy I think where everyone wants to see him go down. I don&amp;rdquo;t know that Wednesday night&amp;rdquo;s episode is going to get 100% resolved.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CSI Files&lt;/strong&gt;: Episode Eight is in production right now. What else is going on for Sara in the first run of episodes?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Fox&lt;/strong&gt;: I have a really intense arc on Episode Seven which is the episode we bring Warrick&amp;rdquo;s son in. I think that episode, particularly for Nick [&lt;strong&gt;George Eads&lt;/strong&gt;] and Sara, is pretty devastating and heart-wrenching. Almost every character so far this season&amp;ndash;at least the six forensic investigators&amp;ndash;have had a chance to really delve very deeply into a case or situation. &lt;strong&gt;Eric&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;ldquo;s [&lt;strong&gt;Szmanda&lt;/strong&gt;, Greg Sanders] character has an episode that deals a lot with old Vegas and Vegas in the forties. &lt;strong&gt;Elisabeth Harnois&lt;/strong&gt; [Morgan Brody] has a case that deals with human trafficking that we really follow her for most of the episode. &lt;strong&gt;Elisabeth Shue&lt;/strong&gt; [Julie Finlay] in &amp;lsquo;CSI On Fire&amp;rsquo; is about to do that; that&amp;rdquo;s a cold case of hers that will also bring in her ex-husband. I think we&amp;rdquo;ve all been there supporting each other for a lot of these episodes, but there&amp;rdquo;s definitely one that is driving each episode. Russell&amp;rdquo;s son [&lt;strong&gt;Brandon W. Jones&lt;/strong&gt;] is accused of murder. There&amp;rdquo;s been a real theme of personal intimacy this season. I don&amp;rdquo;t know&amp;ndash;you tell me if you like them and if the fans like them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CSI Files&lt;/strong&gt;: Ted&amp;rdquo;s son on the show, Brandon, is a really good friend of mine and he was pretty excited about having a pretty big episode to work with.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Fox&lt;/strong&gt;: He was amazing; he did a great job. He&amp;rdquo;s been a great addition to the cast. Of course he&amp;rdquo;s not there every week, but he&amp;rdquo;s got such a great sense of energy and great spirit. It&amp;rdquo;s great to get to know him a little bit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CSI Files&lt;/strong&gt;: There&amp;rdquo;s always the rumor mill circulating at the beginning of a season when producers mention in interviews that they&amp;rdquo;d like to see Billy return, and that they enjoy the two of you having a creative input in the story-telling of GSR. Have you had any meetings thus far? I know Billy stepped away from &lt;em&gt;Hurt People&lt;/em&gt;, so is it looking more likely for him to make a cameo this year?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Fox&lt;/strong&gt;: I didn&amp;rdquo;t know he stepped away from &lt;em&gt;Hurt People&lt;/em&gt;. He did?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CSI Files&lt;/strong&gt;: About a month or so ago.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Fox&lt;/strong&gt;: I miss some of these important moments. Well, certainly if he steps away from &lt;strong&gt;Hurt People&lt;/strong&gt; then yes, I&amp;rdquo;d say there is a good chance than there might have been a month ago. I think a month or two ago it appeared like he might have been a bit too busy for us, so that&amp;rdquo;s exciting. I wish I had more to say about that, but it&amp;rdquo;s definitely promising now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CSI Files&lt;/strong&gt;: Over the summer you launched an official Facebook page, but haven&amp;rdquo;t really used it all too much so far. Are you sticking with Facebook for the most part, or are you thinking about attempting Twitter as well?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Fox&lt;/strong&gt;: Oh my gosh, well thank you for even seeing my Facebook. You see how neglected it is then you know that my obvious answer is I definitely can&amp;rdquo;t add another social media forum to my list. If I can&amp;rdquo;t even update&amp;ndash;I thought to myself, &amp;lsquo;All you have to do is post twice a week! It&amp;rdquo;s fun and creative and whatever it&amp;rdquo;s going to beâ¦&amp;rsquo; and weeks go by where I can&amp;rdquo;t even post anything. I&amp;rdquo;m an embarrassment to the online social media community, so yeah, no Twitter. [Laughs.] I still haven&amp;rdquo;t given up on Facebook. I apologize, and thank you for even caring.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CSI Files&lt;/strong&gt;: This weekend you&amp;rdquo;re receiving two awards: one from ADI and another for your film, &lt;em&gt;How I Became An Elephant&lt;/em&gt;. How does it feel to be recognized for your ongoing support of animal rights?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Fox&lt;/strong&gt;: It feels amazing, but I don&amp;rdquo;t really feel like I earned it yet. I don&amp;rdquo;t know that I&amp;rdquo;ve really put the time and the energy into getting awards of any kind, but obviously to be recognized is an amazing feeling. I&amp;rdquo;m going to have a very busy weekend and I&amp;rdquo;m really excited to celebrate those parts of my life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CSI Files&lt;/strong&gt;: One last question just for fun. Your schedule is incredibly busy, but what shows are you watching during your downtime?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Fox&lt;/strong&gt;: I love &lt;em&gt;Modern Family&lt;/em&gt;. I usually wait a couple weeks to watch them on my Tivo or try to watch a couple in a row. I&amp;rdquo;ve been watching &lt;em&gt;Homeland&lt;/em&gt;; I love &lt;em&gt;Homeland&lt;/em&gt;. [&lt;strong&gt;David&lt;/strong&gt;] &lt;strong&gt;Rambo&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;ldquo;s new show, &lt;em&gt;Revolution&lt;/em&gt;, I&amp;rdquo;m watching. I love some of the NatGeo sort of reality programming&amp;ndash;&lt;em&gt;Locked Up Abroad&lt;/em&gt;. And I&amp;rdquo;m excited about the premiere of &lt;em&gt;American Horror Story&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CSI Files</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2012/csi-files-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Sep 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2012/csi-files-10/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CSI Files:&lt;/strong&gt; It brought back memories from Season Four, when Sara started popping cough drops to mask her issues with alcohol and ultimately facing a DUI. If anyone is going to stop [Nick] from loosing focus, it&amp;rdquo;s her; and she did. Will they talk about this issue in subsequent episodes?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Barbour&lt;/strong&gt;: Yes. There was purpose to the fact that they&amp;rdquo;re in different places in their lives and yet it was very poignant for Sara and Nick to get into it. She does want to help him&amp;ndash;there&amp;rdquo;s the emotionalÂ push-backÂ of him quitting at the worst possible time; there&amp;rdquo;s never a good timeÂ *to*Â do these things, there&amp;rdquo;s always emotions so it&amp;rdquo;s messy. They can help each other, but like Nick said he&amp;rdquo;s not in a position to be lectured to, but that isn&amp;rdquo;t what she was trying to do. There was a little bit of miscommunication and they will try to help each other out. Sara has gained perspective so she understands where Nick is coming from and Nick is not at a point where he can easily hear that at this moment, at least in the premiere.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CSI Files&lt;/strong&gt;: Moving forward in the season, how will the dynamic of Nick, Sara and Greg Â shift? Is this a season of conflict for the three of them?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Barbour&lt;/strong&gt;: I think it&amp;rdquo;s probably more a season of maturity for Greg. An episode coming up will focus in on him and his further maturing at CSI and his personal life. I don&amp;rdquo;t think there&amp;rdquo;ll be conflict with them, but certainly things are changing in their lives. Things can never stay the same; you get comfortable with a certain situation, and you expect certain things and sometimes things change for good and sometimes they change for bad. I don&amp;rdquo;t know that they&amp;rdquo;re going to fight more, but certainly they are going to have to readjust their own expectations of what the job presents to them and how they can help each other.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>USA Today</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2012/usa-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Sep 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2012/usa-today/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;***CSI: Crime Scene Investigation&lt;br /&gt;
***CBS, Wednesdays, 10 ET/PT&lt;br /&gt;
Premiere: Sept. 26&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Where we left them:&lt;/strong&gt; Under attack from the former undersheriff of Las Vegas, the murderous Jeffrey McKeen (Conor O&amp;rsquo;Farrell) &amp;#8212; who runs an underworld empire of drugs and corrupt cops from his prison cell &amp;#8212; the CSI team was on the ropes, with Undersheriff Ecklie (Marc Vann) gunned down on the street, investigator Nick Stokes (George Eads) handing in his resignation in frustration, and supervisor D.B. Russell&amp;rsquo;s (Ted Danson) young granddaughter kidnapped.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Where they&amp;rsquo;re headed:&lt;/strong&gt; The Season 13(!) premiere picks up the moment the cliffhanger ended, with even more team members in danger &amp;#8212; including the newest, Julie Finlay (Elisabeth Shue), who takes off after the kidnapped Kaitlyn and shares a secret-filled past with Russell. The &amp;ldquo;&lt;em&gt;Cape-Fear&lt;/em&gt;-ish&amp;rdquo; storyline, says executive producer Don McGill, was designed to take the ever-serene D.B. and see &amp;ldquo;what would happen if we took that guy who seemed to have everything in control, his family and work, and really pushed him to the edge.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That push will carry through the season. &amp;ldquo;We show his worst fears, that his granddaughter is dead, and we see his demons and his darker side, his impulse to go an eye for an eye,&amp;rdquo; McGill says. &amp;ldquo;As we lean forward into the season, we&amp;rsquo;ll see that worst fear play out. Once something happens to a family &amp;#8212; even if the resolution seems neat and tidy &amp;#8212; the emotional fallout is anything but.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They&amp;rsquo;ll also explore the relationship between him and Shue&amp;rsquo;s Finn. &amp;ldquo;They have a long history,&amp;rdquo; albeit a mostly professional one, McGill says. While D.B. is committed to his family, &amp;ldquo;for Finley, who struggles to have relationships with men, Russell is kind of the perfect man &amp;#8212; but unattainable, which is part of the attraction.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Who&amp;rsquo;s new or returning:&lt;/strong&gt; McGill says they&amp;rsquo;ll focus on the core cast this season &amp;#8212; including, finally, answering the perplexing question: What&amp;rsquo;s up with Sara (Jorja Fox) and Grissom (the long-departed William Petersen)? He&amp;rsquo;s been in the jungle for years, but she&amp;rsquo;s still on the case &amp;#8212; are they even married anymore? &amp;ldquo;We&amp;rsquo;ll answer that, in a way that may surprise people.&amp;rdquo; McGill says. &amp;ldquo;We&amp;rsquo;ll deal with her dissatisfaction with the long-distance relationship, and may find a resolution as to where the marriage is headed.&amp;rdquo; The season also will explore the relationship of Ecklie to his estranged CSI daughter Morgan (Elisabeth Harnois) &amp;#8212; and his romance with Hodges&amp;rsquo; mom Olivia (guest Jaclyn Smith). &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&amp;#8212; Bruce Schwartz&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FormulaTV</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2012/formulatv/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Sep 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2012/formulatv/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Translated from Spanish.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;CSI: Las Vegas returns to Telecinco and does so with what is already its eleventh season.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Chain broadcast every Thursday from 22:00 two new episodes of the long-running fiction starring Marg Helgenberger, Laurence Fishburne, George Eads, Eric Szmanda and Robert David Hall, Jorja Fox. Recently, Jorja spoke about the premiere of new episodes and one of the major complaints: the lack of Gil Grissom. William Petersen will briefly return to the show via Skype and talk to his wife and mother.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;In the episode &amp;ldquo;The Two Mrs. Grissom&amp;rdquo; Sara Sidle uses sign language. Was it challenging for you?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At first, I panicked. I thought I would have to learn sign language for a scene and suddenly became half of the episode. The writers of &amp;#8216;CSI&amp;rsquo; give the best of themselves and go for broke.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Did you enjoy learning sign language?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was fun and ended up buying several videos of sign language. I have not yet had time to get to them, but I want to do in the offseason. It is a language that makes sense to me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How has having William Petersen back in the series?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was incredibly exciting and we did what we could to keep everything with the utmost secrecy. William decided he wanted to surprise the audience. If by chance you were watching the show, saw it, otherwise they would have to find him. It was an impossible task for us.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why did Sara Sidle and Gil Grissom used Skype to communicate?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There was an episode where Grissom Sara sent a video message by email, essentially to break with him from Shepard sea, off the coast of Galapagos Islands. We believed that this was the appropriate way Grissom and Sara had to report regularly. After that, he was in a jungle in Costa Rica, which is great.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Was it fun doing the episode &amp;ldquo;House of Hoarders&amp;rdquo;?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;George Eads had been talking about the idea of hoarders for two years, so it was very exciting to see the script when it came to light. The writers ran with it and became something bigger than George had imagined. I was very happy to oblige.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What effect did the episode &amp;ldquo;House of Hoarders&amp;rdquo; in the cast?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think George went home and ran saying it was a whole ciberacaparador. In my house, I&amp;rsquo;m very minimalist, but when I looked at my computer, my mails and texts that I save, I thought &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m hogging, only instead of at home on my computer&amp;rdquo;. If I could download everything I have on the computer, it may fill six houses.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why is the episode &amp;ldquo;Fracked&amp;rdquo; so important for everyone?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Humans are sharing increasingly smaller amounts of space and we have to invade areas who had been in the wild.&amp;rsquo;re being forced to pull resources from places that should have remained untouched forever. There is a long list of issues that are reaching critical mass. Hopefully everyone will enjoy it because I think all , almost anywhere, can take it to a personal level.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How has the character of Lady Heather developed in the eleventh season?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Her character has had the opportunity to be involved in many mysteries. offers a different side of herself in this episode that fans have not seen before and they will decide whether the new Lady Heather is authentic or not. has been very chameleon. has been able to do different things to different people.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Do you have a favorite episode of season 11?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of them is undoubtedly &amp;ldquo;House of Hoarders&amp;rdquo;. It was very deep, felt like I was going through a maze and suddenly I found myself in the middle and have to work to find the way back home. &amp;ldquo;The Two Mrs. Grissom&amp;rdquo; was great too, was something that normally is not usually done.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What you have told the followers of the series on the eleventh season?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Everything I&amp;rsquo;ve heard about Grissom&amp;rsquo;s return. It was incredible to see him again this season. The fans thanked him again and I hope this little glimpse have thought about how wonderful his life outside of Las Vegas.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Would you still like to play Sara Sidle?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I still have not spent a single minute playing Sara boring. Your life is fascinating and interesting. Changes and dangerous, but somehow always has a way out of the difficulties. If you keep calling me to play Sara, I will come.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>