<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>2014 on Fans of Le Fox Library</title>
    <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/tags/2014/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 2014 on Fans of Le Fox Library</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2014 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://jorjafox.net/library/tags/2014/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>RedCarpetReport TV</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2014/redcarpetreport-tv/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2014/redcarpetreport-tv/</guid>
      <description>Jorja Fox at the 30th Annual IDA Documentary Awards Gala #IDAawards
Quinn Marie: So what brings you out today? You are presenting, correct?
Jorja Fox: I am presenting best episodic series and best limited series, TV awards, which should be kind of fun.
QM: Very cool. And you recently narrated a documentary, correct?
JF: You know, I have actually. Thanks for knowing that! Actually a bit ago I narrated a documentary about Gidget.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ORIGIN Magazine</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2014/origin-magazine/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2014/origin-magazine/</guid>
      <description>Robert Piper: What inspires you?
Jorja Fox: Wow. I think I&amp;rsquo;m very easily inspired. People, wildlife, nature, music, art. I think that I&amp;rsquo;m lucky that I have this great sense of wonderment about life in general.
RP: How do you stay healthy?
JF: I like to think I&amp;rsquo;m healthy. I exercise a lot. I have this great dog, and I walk her about five days a week. I dance, I surf.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where Magazine</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2014/where-magazine/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2014/where-magazine/</guid>
      <description>&amp;rdquo;&amp;lsquo;Catch up with the CSI: Crime Scene Investigation star, find out her favorite places in Los Angeles and more.&amp;ldquo;&amp;rsquo;
Disclaimer: Jorja Fox&amp;rsquo;s is not a typical success story. The CSI: Crime Scene Investigation staple is in her 19th consecutive prime-time television season, a rarity in Hollywood. But acting almost wasn&amp;rsquo;t in the cards for Fox, who originally wanted to be a marine biologist or oceanographer. That passion led to her development of Seafox Productions, which has three wildlife documentaries under its belt.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Green with Tiffany</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2014/green-with-tiffany/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2014/green-with-tiffany/</guid>
      <description>Tiffany Paige: We&amp;rsquo;re here with actress Jorja Fox from CSI. What brings you here tonight?
Jorja Fox: I&amp;rsquo;m very excited about this event, it&amp;rsquo;s an event very close to my heart. I&amp;rsquo;m representing Artists &amp;amp; Athletes tonight. I&amp;rsquo;m on the advisory board and we&amp;rsquo;re a collective of artists and athletes that connect with Washington DC on issues that are close to everybody. Kind of create a dialogue between the different camps and bring us together to get things that we care about on the floor and up for conversation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zap2It </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2014/zap2it/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2014/zap2it/</guid>
      <description>It is hard to believe the &amp;ldquo; CSI: Crime Scene Investigation&amp;rdquo; writers specifically meant for an episode surrounding panic around an Ebola-like virus to land on the schedule exactly when Ebola panic has permeated the US consciousness at yet to be matched levels of cable news attention. Even so, with multiple references to Ebola in the first fifteen minutes alone, the comparisons are too timely and specific to be a complete coincidence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fashion and Style</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2014/fashion-and-style/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2014/fashion-and-style/</guid>
      <description>No one escapes alive.
At least, that&amp;rsquo;s what the promo for Sunday&amp;rsquo;s episode of &amp;ldquo;]CSI: Crime Scene Investigation&amp;rdquo;&amp;rsquo; would have us believe. In the preview for &amp;lsquo;Bad Blood&amp;rsquo;, Sara (&amp;ldquo;&amp;lsquo;Jorja Fox&amp;rdquo;&amp;rsquo;) and Greg (&amp;ldquo;&amp;lsquo;Eric Szmanda&amp;rdquo;&amp;rsquo;) aren&amp;rsquo;t looking so hot &amp;ndash; and it&amp;rsquo;s no wonder, as, while investigating a crime scene, they&amp;rsquo;re exposed to a deadly virus with a crushing fatality rate of 80%.
From the looks of it, the virus hits one of the pair harder than the other.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mashable</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2014/mashable/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2014/mashable/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
Luckily, there are brighter days ahead &amp;ndash; namely, two new love interests (one of whom may turn out to be a little suspicious) and an episode that takes a trio of CSI ladies to Las Vegas. &amp;ldquo;I want to do more girl-focused episodes,&amp;rdquo; Shue told Mashable. &amp;ldquo;I really want to work more with Jorja [Fox], and I think the girl power of CSI needs to be enhanced.&amp;rdquo;
[&amp;hellip;]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Guide Magazine</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2014/tv-guide-magazine/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2014/tv-guide-magazine/</guid>
      <description>RETURNS Sunday, Sept 28, 10/9c, CBS
Is the wrong man on death row thanks to D.B. Russell? Season 15 has the CSI night-shift chief, played by Ted Danson, dealing with a crisis of conscience, and a threat to his career, when Las Vegas is rattled by a series of murders strikingly similar to those committed by the Gig Harbor Killer &amp;#8212; aka Jared Briscoe (Mark-Paul Gossalaar) &amp;#8212; a sicko Russell put behind bars years ago.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Wire</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2014/the-wire-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2014/the-wire-2/</guid>
      <description>As of this month, *The West Wing *is 15 years old. We&amp;rsquo;ll pause as you absorb how long you&amp;rsquo;ve been without Jed Bartlet and his merry band in your life. Doesn&amp;rsquo;t it feel like just yesterday we all fell in love with Aaron Sorkin&amp;rsquo;s bastion of liberal idealism wrapped up in fast-paced dialogue usually said while walking?
[&amp;hellip;]
31. Gina Toscano
Played By: Jorja Fox
Number of episodes = 5</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Wire</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2014/the-wire-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2014/the-wire-1/</guid>
      <description>Twenty years ago this week, a little hospital show called &amp;ldquo;ER&amp;rdquo; debuted on NBC to much fanfare and managed to exceed the hype. For years, it was television&amp;rsquo;s #1 drama; it reinvented the television form, bringing a previously-unseen cinematic approach to shooting action in its Chicago hospital setting. And it had one of the deepest, craziest, most lovable ensembles in the history of television, both helped and eventually done in by its excessive longevity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CBS Watch! Magazine</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2014/cbs-watch/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2014/cbs-watch/</guid>
      <description>Jorja Fox of CSI: Crime Scene Investigation makes waves with her stylish selections
*Vacation Spot:
Hawaii.
*Workout:
Surfing.
*Designer:
Stella McCartney.
*Purse:
high*way NYC.
I love their nonleather stuff.
*Magazine:
Surfer magazine.
*Bling:
A gold and amethyst ring my mother designed.
*Activity:
All things romantic.
*Song:
&amp;ldquo;Freedom and Its Owner&amp;rdquo;
by Kings of Convenience.
*Book:
The Concious Cook
by chef Tal Ronnen.
*Movie:
Tootsie.
*Indulgence:
Wine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>News.com.au</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2014/news-com-au-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2014/news-com-au-1/</guid>
      <description>&amp;rdquo;&amp;lsquo;A DETECTIVE studies the body of George Tabin, a professional Elvis impersonator.&amp;ldquo;&amp;rsquo;
Poor Tabin, dead on a bus bench, has severe head wounds, but there&amp;rsquo;s no blood around to suggest he was murdered here.
Sara Sidle, played by Jorja Fox, stumbles upon a trail of blood drops, which lead her to where a blackbird &amp;ndash; a rook &amp;ndash; has been stabbed to death.
Soon enough, there&amp;rsquo;s a connection between the two deaths.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sweden with Love (May 6 2014)</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2014/sweden-with-love/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2014/sweden-with-love/</guid>
      <description>&amp;rdquo;&amp;lsquo;Actress Jorja Fox:&amp;ldquo;&amp;rsquo; &amp;ldquo;Since my early 20s, I&amp;rsquo;ve felt I had to wear heels when I get dressed up. You want to look great and you want to be like everyone else, you know? But now that I&amp;rsquo;m in my 40s, I&amp;rsquo;ve noticed I care a lot less what people think about me. And when you&amp;rsquo;re 5&amp;rsquo;9&amp;rdquo; and you wear heels, you&amp;rsquo;re towering over almost every woman in the room and half the men.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Viva Magazine</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2014/viva-magazine-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2014/viva-magazine-1/</guid>
      <description>FOR THE LAST 14 YEARS, WE&amp;rsquo;VE BEEN WATCHING JORJA FOX ON OUR TELEVISION SETS. HERE&amp;rsquo;S A LOOK AT HOW THE ACTOR SPENDS HER TIME OFF SCREEN, AND WHY SHE CONSIDERS HERSELF ONE LUCKY LADY.
Jorja Fox is really the antithesis of her television alter ego Sarah Sidle on the hit show CSI. Whereas Sidle is often sullen and dark, Fox is all smiles and has a bounce in her step that just makes you want to be around her.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Viva Magazine</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2014/viva-magazine-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2014/viva-magazine-2/</guid>
      <description>HOW DO YOU DEFINE BALANCED LIVING?
 JORJA FOX
VIVA COVER GIRL AND STAR OF CSI
Balance comes from the inside anbd I think it looks different for different people. What is balance for you and for me might be two different things. At the end of the day, if you are doing something you love, and if you can sleep at night, then that sets up a good equilibrium. An accomplishment and a restful night&amp;rsquo;s sleep help to keep me stable.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>News.com.au</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2014/news-com-au-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2014/news-com-au-2/</guid>
      <description>&amp;rdquo;&amp;lsquo;SHE plays forensic scientist Sara Sidle in one of most successful television dramas in history.&amp;ldquo;&amp;rsquo;
Yet actress Jorja Fox, who stars in CSI: Crime Scene Invesitgation, says how she first thought no-one would watch the show, which debuted in 2000.
&amp;ldquo;I have often thought of our show really as an action-adventure show &amp;ndash; you are going to be in for an amazing ride, an amazing hour of an exciting, dodgy, what&amp;rsquo;s-going-to-happen-next kind of ride.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Twitter Live Chat</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2014/twitter-live-chat/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Mar 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2014/twitter-live-chat/</guid>
      <description>Tweet
**&amp;#8212; Nikki @PenguinsFan87 **
Q: @JorjaFoxofficia How did you hear about CSI and how did u try auditioning for any of characters before you got Sara Sidle role? #CSI
&amp;#8212; LeFox @JorjaFoxofficia
A: .@PenguinsFan87 I had a birthday party at my house - someone at the party told me about it. Only auditioned for Sara. #CSI
&amp;#8212;-
Tweet
&amp;#8212; LeFox @JorjaFoxofficia
Everyone in here is telling me to be quiet so they can type.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Couriermail</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2014/couriermail/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2014/couriermail/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
&amp;rdquo;&amp;lsquo;How does it feel to be on a show that&amp;rsquo;s clocked up over 300 episodes?&amp;ldquo;&amp;rsquo;
It&amp;rsquo;s amazing and it hit me today because I saw Jorja (co-star Jorja Fox) in the trailer getting ready and for her, she has been here for (over) 300 episodes. So to see the impact on her made me realise how powerful it was. You know, I&amp;rsquo;ve only done 33 episodes, so I have such a great deal of respect for all the people that have made this show so amazing to make it last this long.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SharpHeels</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2014/sharpheels/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2014/sharpheels/</guid>
      <description>CSI&amp;rsquo;s Sara Sidle, aka Jorga Fox, is best known for her life-saving roles on-screen, but off screen, Fox is saving animals. With Seafox Productions, the long-time animal rights activist and burgeoning producer, Fox is quickly mixing her two passions with growing documentary portfolio. Her latest endeavor, Lion Ark, has been nominated for Outstanding International Motion Picture at this weekend&amp;rsquo;s 45th NAACP Image Awards.
Lion Ark tells the story of Animal Defenders International recent Bolivian campaign to ban traveling circuses throughout the country.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SuperPopACCESS</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2014/superpopaccess/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2014/superpopaccess/</guid>
      <description>INTERVIEW - Eric Szmanda, Jorja Fox on the best part about Grammy weekend at Universal Music Group 2014 Post Grammy Party at The Ace Hotel Theater on 2014-01-26 in Los Angeles, California.
[&amp;hellip;]
Interviewer: [&amp;hellip;] this weekend?
Eric Szmanda: Well this was both of our first times going to the ceremony and I think it was one of the best ones that I&amp;rsquo;ve seen in recent years. One of my favorite artists kind of swept the awards.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>News Articles ( 2014)</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2014/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2014/</guid>
      <description>  Date Source    February 21 SharpHeels   March 04 Couriermail   March 30 News.com.au   April 01 Viva Magazine   April 01 Viva Magazine   May 06 Sweden with Love (May 6 2014)   June 17 News.com.au   July 01 CBS Watch! Magazine   September 16 The Wire   September 22 TV Guide Magazine   September 22 The Wire   September 28 Mashable   October 12 Fashion and Style   October 13 Zap2It    November 01 Where Magazine   November 11 ORIGIN Magazine    </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>