<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>2006 on JFO Library</title>
    <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/tags/2006/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 2006 on JFO Library</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2006 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://jorjafox.net/library/tags/2006/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Defamer</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2006/defamer-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2006/defamer-2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dec. 14th.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; (Sara Sidle from CSI) at JCrew Fashion Square&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New York Magazine</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2006/new-york-magazine/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2006/new-york-magazine/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;rdquo;&amp;lsquo;9 Gil Grissom and Sara Sidle on &amp;#8216;CSI&amp;rsquo; &amp;ldquo;&amp;rsquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Last spring, in the last minute of the last episode of the season, Grissom (William Petersen) looked up from his bedtime reading at Sara (Jorja Fox) in the bathroom door, fresh from a shower. All this reticent fall, they haven&amp;rsquo;t touched and barely smiled, but their intimacy has a resounding vibe.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zap2it</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2006/zap2it/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2006/zap2it/</guid>
      <description>&lt;dl&gt;
&lt;dt&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/dt&gt;
&lt;dt&gt;:Raindrops on &amp;ldquo;Lost&amp;rdquo; and whiskers on kittens&lt;br /&gt;
:Television characters in whom I am smitten&lt;br /&gt;
:Brand new episodes tied up in string&lt;br /&gt;
:These are a few of my favorite things&lt;/dt&gt;
&lt;/dl&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When the TiVo breaks, when a plot development stings, when I&amp;rsquo;m feeling sad&lt;br /&gt;
I simply remember my favorite TV moments and then I don&amp;rsquo;t feeeeeeeeel so bad.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here are my 10 favorite TV moments of 2006.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1. Sara and Grissom are revealed to be in a relationship on &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; in &amp;ldquo;Way To Go&amp;rdquo; (May 18, 2006):&lt;/strong&gt; Why is this the best moment of 2006? For one thing it caused an absolute uproar among fans &amp;#8212; some of you loved it, some of you hated it &amp;#8212; but it definitely got you talking and wondering. Plus, I kind of love it when shows keep secrets from us. Heck, we still don&amp;rsquo;t know what&amp;rsquo;s going on between those two.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PR Newswire</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2006/pr-newswire/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2006/pr-newswire/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Top TV Moments of 2006 Survey Results&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;# Katie Couric&amp;rsquo;s last day on &amp;ldquo;Today&amp;rdquo;&lt;br /&gt;
# Mel Gibson&amp;rsquo;s interview with Diane Sawyer after his DWI arrest&lt;br /&gt;
# Oprah tells author James Frey he betrayed readers&lt;br /&gt;
# Sara and Grissom get together on &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>St. Paul Pioneer Press</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2006/st-paul-pioneer-press/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Nov 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2006/st-paul-pioneer-press/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Don&amp;rsquo;t worry, &amp;ldquo;CSI: Crime Scene Investigation&amp;rdquo; fans. CBS will not be changing the name of its hit drama to &amp;ldquo;When Sara Met Grissom.&amp;rdquo; But the network will continue to explore the love of these two forensic nerds.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jorja Fox, who plays Sara Sidle on the Top 10-rated series, says she&amp;rsquo;s excited about the possibilities. Fox says she&amp;rsquo;s excited that Sara and Gil are finally acting on the sexual tension in the series&amp;rsquo; seventh season.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The May-December romance (actor William Petersen is 53, so presumably his character is, too) also brings Fox a little job security. Two years ago, CBS fired and then rehired Fox after she initially refused to sign a return-to-work agreement.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here&amp;rsquo;s what the 38-year-old New York native had to say:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On Sara and Gil hooking up: &amp;ldquo;Sara was originally a love interest for the character of Gil Grissom. So being that it was on there (the original script), I was very intrigued and sort of thought it might happen. I think one of the coolest things about it, and the way that the story ended up being delivered at the end of season six, is to suddenly find these characters together, and we know how long it&amp;rsquo;s been going on. I think it&amp;rsquo;s brilliant.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rsquo;s&amp;rdquo; creative process: &amp;ldquo;You know, you just get this little description, and you take the journey. And the writers and producers are really kind. If there&amp;rsquo;s someplace we don&amp;rsquo;t really want to go or we really don&amp;rsquo;t feel safe, we can go to them, and generally they&amp;rsquo;ll change the course or direction for us.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CBS News</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2006/cbs-new-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2006/cbs-new-2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Hit Show&amp;rsquo;s Seventh Season Has Been An Eventful One&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The seventh season of &amp;ldquo;CSI: Crime Scene Investigation&amp;rdquo; has been a tumultuous one. So far, investigator Greg Sanders has been nearly beaten to death while Catherine Willows not only dealt with her daughter&amp;rsquo;s kidnapping but also with her father&amp;rsquo;s murder.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s not only a tough job emotionally, the logistics of shooting &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; can also take a toll. Recently, the crew filmed two episodes at the same time. Moreover, &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; has been in a back-and-forth ratings battle this year, pitted against the hospital drama &amp;ldquo;Grey&amp;rsquo;s Anatomy.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Certainly I think we&amp;rsquo;ve brought our competitive game,&amp;rdquo; said Jorja Fox, who plays Sara Sidle. &amp;ldquo;I think that we still definitely want to win, you know. I want to win. Who doesn&amp;rsquo;t want to win?&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Detroit News</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2006/detroit-news/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2006/detroit-news/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Don&amp;rsquo;t worry, &amp;ldquo;CSI: Crime Scene Investigation&amp;rdquo; fans. CBS will not be changing the name of its hit drama to &amp;ldquo;When Sara met Grissom.&amp;rdquo; But the network will continue to explore the love of these two forensic nerds if for no other reason than to compete with ABC&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Grey&amp;rsquo;s Anatomy,&amp;rdquo; which also airs at 9 p.m. Thursdays.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jorja Fox, who plays Sara Sidle on the Top 10-rated series, says she&amp;rsquo;s excited about the possibilities. Fox, who is best known for her roles on NBC&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;ER&amp;rdquo; and the sizzling indie flick &amp;ldquo;Memento,&amp;rdquo; says she&amp;rsquo;s excited that Sara and Gil are finally acting on the sexual tension in the series&amp;rsquo; seventh season.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The May-December romance (actor William Petersen is 53, so presumably his character is, too) also brings Fox a little job security. Two years ago, CBS fired and then rehired Fox after she initially refused to sign a return-to-work agreement.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here&amp;rsquo;s what the 38-year-old New York native had to say about &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; and other topics in Pasadena, Calif., this summer:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;On Sara and Gil hooking up:&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;ldquo;Sara was originally a love interest for the character of Gil Grissom. So being that it was on there (the original script), I was very intrigued and sort of thought it might happen. I think one of the coolest things about it and the way that the story ended up being delivered at the end of season six, is to suddenly find these characters together, and we know how long it&amp;rsquo;s been going on. I think it&amp;rsquo;s brilliant.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;On &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rsquo;s&amp;rdquo; creative process:&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;ldquo;You know, you just get this little description, and you take the journey. And the writers and producers are really kind. If there&amp;rsquo;s some place we don&amp;rsquo;t really want to go or we really don&amp;rsquo;t feel safe, we can go to them, and generally they&amp;rsquo;ll change the course or direction for us.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Global Surf News</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2006/global-surf-news/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2006/global-surf-news/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Oscar-winning actress Sally Field admits that Gidget was &amp;ldquo;my beginning and I loved her!&amp;rdquo; Former Motion Picture Academy President Frank Pierson calls Gidget as &amp;ldquo;a proto-feminist figure.&amp;rdquo; And says former U.S. Surf Champion Jericho Poppler Bartlow, &amp;ldquo;I remember thinking, `Gidget could do it.I know I can.&amp;lsquo;&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Accidental Icon: The Real Gidget Story,&amp;rdquo; a new one-hour documentary, will world premier on October 8, 2006, at the Malibu Celebration of Film festival.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Narrated by Jorja Fox (&amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo;) and produced by Brian L. Gillogly and Master Communication, the project explores the largely untold story of the real &amp;ldquo;Gidget,&amp;rdquo; Kathy Kohner Zuckerman, and how her account of surfing Malibu in the mid-50&amp;rsquo;s became the basis for a best-selling novel by her father Frederick Kohner.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A half century later, &amp;ldquo;Gidget&amp;rdquo; is celebrated as an enduring Hollywood movie/TV franchise and a slice of Americana, with considerable impact on popular culture and the sport of surfing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Surf legends and present-day &amp;ldquo;surfer girls&amp;rdquo; set the stage and take the Gidget story full circle. Prominent actors, writers and directors, many of whom brought Gidget to the big and small screen, provide an often enlightening behind-the-scenes perspective.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.MCOF.org&#34;&gt;http://www.MCOF.org&lt;/a&gt; www.MCOF.org]&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Buffalo News</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2006/buffalo-news/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2006/buffalo-news/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;7.&lt;/strong&gt; Yes, you might have seen Jorja Fox at a local restaurant. Fox, who plays Sara Sidle, Grissom&amp;rsquo;s (William Petersen) love interest on &amp;ldquo;CSI,&amp;rdquo; occasionally visits Western New York because she has relatives here.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Mirror</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2006/daily-mirror/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2006/daily-mirror/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;As forensic sleuth Sara Sidle on the hit series CSI: Crime Scene Investigation, Jorja Fox has had her share of murders to solve. But it doesn&amp;rsquo;t take a professional to figure out who the perpetrator is behind the deaths of the billions of animals killed for food every year &amp;#8212; namely, the meat industry. That&amp;rsquo;s why Jorja &amp;#8212; a longtime vegetarian &amp;#8212; jumped at the chance to shoot a provocative new pro-vegetarian ad for her friends at People for the Ethical Treatment of Animals (PETA) Asia-Pacific.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the ad, Jorja stands over a police chalk outline of a cow surrounded by crime-scene tape next to the tagline &amp;ldquo;Baka Kinain, Baka Kinatay. Kinain Mo Ba Ito? Investigate Vegetarianism.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While shooting the ad, Jorja took the time to explain that the more she learned about how animals are killed for food, the less she wanted to be a part of it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;I was having a meatball sub one day in Brooklyn [New York], and it just clicked,&amp;rdquo; says Jorja. &amp;ldquo;I was in the middle of that sandwich, and I put it down, and I never had meat again.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why do Jorja and PETA think that eating meat is a crime? On today&amp;rsquo;s animal factories, animals are crammed by the thousands into filthy windowless sheds, wire cages, gestation crates and other confinement systems. These animals will never raise their families, root in the soil, build nests or do anything that is natural to them. Cows, caives, pigs, chickens, turkeys, ducks, geese and other animals are kept in small cages, in jam-packed sheds or on filthy feedlots, often with so little space that they can&amp;rsquo;t even turn around or lie down comfortably. They are pumped full of antibiotics, hormones, and steroids in order to grow so fast that many become crippled under their own weight and die within inches of water and food.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;People who eat animals also suffer. Consumption of meat and other animal products has been conclusively linked with heart disease, diabetes and certain cancers &amp;#8212; all among leading killers in the Philippines &amp;#8212; as well as arthritis, osteoporosis, Alzheimer&amp;rsquo;s disease, asthma and impotence. Scientists have also found that vegetarians have stronger immune systems than meat-eaters and are less susceptible to everyday illnesses like the flu. Vegetarians and vegans live, on average, six to 10 years longer than meat-eaters.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For more information, visit PETA&amp;rsquo;s Web site GoVeg.com.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PETA Vegetarian Thanksgiving</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2006/peta-vegetarian-thanksgiving/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2006/peta-vegetarian-thanksgiving/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; One of the most amazing things about today, not only is the food gonna be way better than it ever is at my place &amp;ldquo;(laughs)&amp;rdquo;, and, and, and, far more beautifully prepared, uh, I don&amp;rsquo;t have to cook or do any dishes I don&amp;rsquo;t think - maybe I do, but nobody&amp;rsquo;s told me yet so that&amp;rsquo;d be really fun. &amp;ldquo;(laughs)&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; What a better way to spend this holiday that we really sorta celebrate peace and in a really peaceful way eating vegetarian.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;ldquo;(Jorja is holding a turkey in her lap)&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Off-camera voice&lt;/strong&gt; That&amp;rsquo;s nice.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; You wanna hold her?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Off-camera voice&lt;/strong&gt; I think that you&amp;rsquo;re it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; Okay. &amp;ldquo;(off-camera laughter)&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Off-camera voice&lt;/strong&gt; When you&amp;rsquo;re ready.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; Turkey holding duty. Okay. She&amp;rsquo;s pretty cool.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OK Weekly</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2006/ok-weekly/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2006/ok-weekly/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;My six-pack is not like most actresses&amp;rsquo; &amp;#8212; my six-pack is beer.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;From gritty crime scenes to sexy love scenes, JORJA FOX&amp;rsquo;s role on &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; has been through a lot of changes due to her new romance.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WITH HER TOMBOYISH&lt;/strong&gt; demeanor and love of rock music, surfing, beer and dogs, no one, least of all actress Jorja Fox, would have predicted that she&amp;rsquo;d be in one of the most talked-about love affairs on TV this season. But as one of the stars of &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo;, Jorja has given the CBS drama a hot new look, with her character, Sara Sidle, going from crime scenes to love scenes. Her surprising romance with fellow forensics investigator Gil Grissom (played by William Petersen) is keeping fans guessing at the snow near the top of the ratings in its Thursday-night battle against ABC&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Grey&amp;rsquo;s Anatomy&amp;rdquo;,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m really exited about the thing between Grissom and Sara,&amp;rdquo; Jorja told &amp;ldquo;OK!&amp;rdquo;. &amp;ldquo;What&amp;rsquo;s not sexy about William Petersen? Going into the seventh year of a show, to have something so big and so different to play after all this time is very unique and rare. We&amp;rsquo;re having a ball. I hope the fans love it.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A self-described hippie, Jorja often comes to work with her best friend, her dog Ali. &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m crazy for animals. I love them!&amp;rdquo; Jorja said when we caught up with her at the Oct. 5 opening of the North Central Animal Care Center, a remodeled Los Angeles city shelter for dogs, cats and rabbits. Jorja couldn&amp;rsquo;t be happier that the city has created a clean, safe facility where solar panels keep pets warm and a misting system keeps them cool until they can be adopted.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;ve been to the shelter a number of times,&amp;rdquo; she said. &amp;ldquo;I think it&amp;rsquo;s better than anybody could even imagine it. I would invite everybody who lives in Los Angeles to come down and check it out to see the future of L.A. and the commitment of Angelenos to caring for pets.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jorja&amp;rsquo;s four-legged pal, Ali, 10, is a shelter dog herself and is named for the famous boxer Muhammad Ali. &amp;ldquo;She&amp;rsquo;s Ali the boxer, because she&amp;rsquo;s so pretty,&amp;rdquo; Jorja smiled. &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;ve always had a dog in my life. I know this is a cliched thing to say, but she&amp;rsquo;s my best friend.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jorja&amp;rsquo;s love for animals affects her diet as well. &amp;ldquo;I am a 20-year vegetarian,&amp;rdquo; she said. &amp;ldquo;I eat a lot of grains and vegetables and fruit and soy products. I eat a little bit of dairy, especially if I can find it organic and made in local, humane and free-range conditions.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Still, she does admit to allowing herself &amp;ldquo;some&amp;rdquo; splurges. &amp;ldquo;Chocolate, coffee, pizza. And beer. I could show you my six-pack, which is not like most actresses&amp;rsquo; six-packs in this town!&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Calling herself a minimalist who doesn&amp;rsquo;t like to collect too many things, Jorja does make an exception for jeans. &amp;ldquo;I probably have 10 pairs of sneakers and nine pares of jeans. I like the old-school Levi&amp;rsquo;s and Wrangler&amp;rsquo;s that you might get an at army surplus store. I also wear a lot of Seven and True Religion.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jorja says in shape by running, hiking, camping and kayaking. She also finds herself surfing &amp;ldquo;just for the fun of it,&amp;rdquo; she said. &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m kind of goal oriented, and when I&amp;rsquo;m surfing, I have no goals at all. I just like to enjoy myself.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The 38-year-old star who once played rock music has put it on the back burner to focus on &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo;. &amp;ldquo;I get together with friends and play music from time to time, in the adult-alternative vein,&amp;rdquo; she said. &amp;ldquo;I don&amp;rsquo;t have the time to actually be in a band. Someday, when &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; is over and done, maybe I&amp;rsquo;ll start a new bad. Mostly I play guitar; most people don&amp;rsquo;t care for my singing. But I love to sing, so I do it a little bit,&amp;rdquo; she smiles.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jorja&amp;rsquo;s other favorite side project is producing plays. On her next hiatus, she hopes to help her friend, actress Kirsten Holly Smith, continue her one-woman show, &amp;ldquo;Blue-Eyed Soul: The Life and Times of Music Legend Dusty Springfield&amp;rdquo;, the story of the famed &amp;lsquo;60s soul singer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But her focus this fall is on her show, as &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; faces a ratings challenge from the sexy doctors of &amp;ldquo;Grey&amp;rsquo;s Anatomy&amp;rdquo;. &amp;ldquo;We&amp;rsquo;ve been number one for longer than I ever thought it would be possible to hold that title,&amp;rdquo; she said. &amp;ldquo;it&amp;rsquo;s been an amazing ride. I&amp;rsquo;d love to stay there. I think that we&amp;rsquo;ve all got our game faces on and we&amp;rsquo;re going into the season very humble and very hungry. It&amp;rsquo;s nice to have some competition. But I do hope we win!&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TFI</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2006/tfi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2006/tfi/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Translated from French&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The broadcasting of the sixth season has finished in France. What&amp;rsquo;s going to happen in season seven?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The producers keep it secret. It&amp;rsquo;s impossible to know where our characters will be in three months. I wonder if the writers haven&amp;rsquo;t though about killing Sara. She&amp;rsquo;s had almost everything else happen to her &amp;#8212; arrest, humiliation, bad dating &amp;hellip; She&amp;rsquo;s been the team&amp;rsquo;s scapegoat for a long time. Although, I can tell you that in season seven, [Gil] Grissom is going to make it up to her, which gives me a rest. At last, I can finally smile on screen!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;After seven years are you used to seeing corpses?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m stronger now, but I sometimes want to puke when I see all the special effects made by our special effects! Outdoing other TV shows has become a game for them. They never run out of ideas to show amazing deaths.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;All this [death] doesn&amp;rsquo;t seem to make for a cheerful atmosphere on the set!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not at all! We laugh and we play music. We made a band &amp;#8212; the actors and the technicians. Marg Helgenberger plays piano, Gary Dourdan plays bass and Robert David Hall plays guitar. I even want to film one of our impromptu gigs for our fans!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;When you meet fans, what do you talk about ?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All of them want to see Sara and Gil have a love story, which is going to happen in the new season. But &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; isn&amp;rsquo;t about the private lives of its heroes. Mysteries are at the heart of every episode.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Are you surprised by the infatuation of viewers about &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; ?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What really surprised me is the interest our fans have in crimes. Some of them tell me complex scenarios about the best way to kill someone. At first, I was terrified about it and I felt like I had serial killers in front of me! Now I&amp;rsquo;m more relaxed and I joke with them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We know very little about your private life. Why are you so secret ?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think it&amp;rsquo;s very important to keep the mystery secret. And also it&amp;rsquo;s good for the audience, so that people don&amp;rsquo;t confuse me with my character on &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You never act in movies during your summer holiday. Is it a personal choice ?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I work 14 hour days for nine and a half months and I don&amp;rsquo;t want to run everywhere during my holidays. Seven years ago, I created my own theater troupe. That&amp;rsquo;s how I relax.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Do you have a theater project going on?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m a producer of &amp;ldquo;Dear Bernard&amp;rdquo;, a musical comedy about an English girl who comes to Hollywood to be successful. I also suggested to the &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; producers that we write a musical episode for this season. Wouldn&amp;rsquo;t it be funny to see Grissom and his team singing during autopsies? We could even pretend it was all Sara&amp;rsquo;s dream!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Washington Times</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2006/washington-times/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2006/washington-times/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s as if those procedural dramas, after spending years putting female crime victims through the wringer (and inside locked cages and under floorboards) have run out of ideas and moved on to harassing female crime fighters instead.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yet it&amp;rsquo;s also the case that many shows &amp;#8212; facing softening ratings after many years on the air or tougher time-slot competition &amp;#8212; are attempting to inject more personal story lines into a genre that once regarded them like germs in the crime lab. That was before &amp;ldquo;Desperate Housewives,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;Grey&amp;rsquo;s Anatomy&amp;rdquo; and other shows that feature almost nothing but personal story lines (especially female-centric ones) came along to captivate audiences.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Still, it can be a dicey business rejiggering the formula at this late date.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;From the beginning of our fanship, there&amp;rsquo;s sort of been a split,&amp;rdquo; says &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; star Jorja Fox, whose show goes head-to-head with &amp;ldquo;Anatomy&amp;rdquo; on Thursdays at 9 p.m. and has lost the ratings race to the hospital drama three out of four weeks this season.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;There&amp;rsquo;s been about 50 percent of the audience who would like to know more about the characters and about 50 percent who would really rather stick to the stories.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Guide</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2006/tv-guide-13/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2006/tv-guide-13/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I beg forgiveness for all the mean things I&amp;rsquo;ve said recently about TV Guide, becuase I nearly died when I saw your Jorja Fox/William Petersen cover [&lt;sup&gt;9&lt;/sup&gt;&amp;frasl;&lt;sub&gt;25&lt;/sub&gt;]. He looks &amp;ldquo;soooooo&amp;rdquo; good. And Jorja&amp;rsquo;s a doll, too! &amp;#8212; &amp;ldquo;Lauren Kleinfeldt, Glendale, N.Y.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A million thanks for your gorgeous cover photo of Jorja Fox! I have followed &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; since Day 1, and I have watched Fox change form a pretty girl to a beautiful woman. Your cover is positive proof of that! &amp;#8212; &amp;ldquo;Maureen Holdridge, Plattsburgh, N.Y.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>