<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>2000 on Jorja Fox Library</title>
    <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/tags/2000/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 2000 on Jorja Fox Library</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2000 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://jorjafox.net/library/tags/2000/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>USA Today</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2000/usa-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2000/usa-today/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;12/21/00- Updated 07:16 PM ET&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;VALENCIA, Calif. &amp;#8212; Harsh sunlight burst through the ceiling of a burned-out house, turning the &lt;em&gt;CSI&lt;/em&gt; criminalists into shadows against the charred walls. Smoke particles hung in the air, but, three months after an arson, the crime scene appeared cold.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;There&amp;rsquo;s nothing left, Gris,&amp;rdquo; Warrick Brown (Gary Dourdan) said to his boss, Gil Grissom.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;More than you think,&amp;rdquo; the cerebral Grissom (William Petersen ) responded, already rooting out clues.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;More than you think&amp;rdquo; might as well be the slogan for CBS&amp;rsquo; &lt;em&gt;CSI: Crime Scene Investigation&lt;/em&gt;. It drew scant attention before its premiere but has emerged as TV&amp;rsquo;s top-rated new drama, getting about 15 million viewers per week, more than its heavily promoted lead-in, The Fugitive.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Friday sleeper has turned forensic science &amp;#8212; the evidence collection and examination that traditionally have served as background on police shows &amp;#8212; into prime time&amp;rsquo;s hot new occupation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If the subject matter is a little ghoulish, so be it, Zuiker and Mendelsohn say. They toned down the gore factor after test audiences blanched at all the blood and bugs &amp;hellip; but only a little. A mass murderer made bloody artwork of his victims in one episode, and well-fed maggots constitute a cast of thousands in tonight&amp;rsquo;s offering: &amp;ldquo;Sex, Lies and Larvae.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;My only fear about the job was whether I had the stomach for it,&amp;rdquo; jokes Jorja Fox, who plays Sara Sidle, an enthusiastic but inexperienced investigator.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Guide</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2000/tv-guide-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2000/tv-guide-2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Through its exploration of anal swabs and poisoned nipples, CSI: Crime Street Investigation - the CBS drama that has been described as Quincy meets Seven - has quickly become one of this season&amp;rsquo;s biggest hits. A large part of the show&amp;rsquo;s success can be chalked up to its stomach-churning shock value, an element that required its plucky cast - including actress Jorja Fox - to develop an extra layer of thick skin.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;I get nauseous just thinking about some of the things I&amp;rsquo;ve seen on the set,&amp;rdquo; Fox laughingly tells TV Guide Online. &amp;ldquo;We recently did an episode in the woods where we come across a murder victim covered with bugs - real ones. Generally, I&amp;rsquo;m not very squeamish, but there were thousands of them, including the ones you don&amp;rsquo;t normally see, like maggots. It was intense.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;To be honest,&amp;rdquo; she adds, &amp;ldquo;in the beginning, I had to ask myself if I could handle working on this show every day because the content is kinda heavy. It gives you a whole new respect for real-life crime lab experts.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Though CSI&amp;rsquo;s graphic tone can be a bit unsettling, it&amp;rsquo;s not nearly as dangerous as Fox&amp;rsquo;s last gig, which ultimately landed her in the hospital. As Gina Toscano, a Secret Service agent assigned to protect the President&amp;rsquo;s daughter on NBC&amp;rsquo;s The West Wing, Fox was run over by a limousine while shooting the season finale.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;We were filming the assassination attempt scene and everyone had to duck and run,&amp;rdquo; recalls Fox. &amp;ldquo;I was lying on the ground waiting for the director to yell cut, when I felt something heavy on my leg. I turned just as the wheel of the car was rolling over me.&amp;rdquo; As expected, panic ensued and Fox was rushed to the nearest emergency room, where she was immediately recognized for her former role as medical intern Maggie Doyle on ER. &amp;ldquo;Luckily, I wound up with just a few bruises,&amp;rdquo; she says, &amp;ldquo;but the whole thing was pretty hilarious.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In addition to starring on CSI, Fox can be seen in the upcoming indie film Momento, in which she appears opposite Carrie-Anne Moss and Guy Pearce. She&amp;rsquo;s also the co-founder of Honeypot Productions, an independent L.A. theater company. Right now, however, she&amp;rsquo;s focusing all her energy on playing CSI forensics expert Sara Sidle. Laughs Fox: &amp;ldquo;I barely passed 9th grade science, so now it&amp;rsquo;s like, &amp;#8216;Cool, look at me - I&amp;rsquo;m a hotshot scientist.&amp;lsquo;&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dallas Morning News</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2000/dallas-morning-news/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Nov 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2000/dallas-morning-news/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Question:&lt;/strong&gt; I&amp;rsquo;m interested in the actress Jorja Fox on the new show &amp;ldquo;CSI (Crime Scene Investigation).&amp;rdquo; Haven&amp;rsquo;t I seen her on &amp;ldquo;ER&amp;rdquo;? - C.C.L., Dallas&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Answer:&lt;/strong&gt; You have. She played Dr. Maggie Doyle on &amp;ldquo;ER.&amp;rdquo; After her exit in 1999 from &amp;ldquo;ER,&amp;rdquo; she joined The West Wing as secret service agent Gina Toscano. After appearing in &amp;ldquo;West Wing&amp;rsquo;s&amp;rdquo; second season premiere in October, she moved on again to the new CBS drama &amp;ldquo;CSI,&amp;rdquo; one of the highest rated new shows of the season. Fox is also co-founder of Honeypot Productions, an avant-garde theater company in Los Angeles.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Guide</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2000/tv-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2000/tv-guide/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;9-10PM, CBS&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;PREMIERES October 6&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;STARRING: Jorja Fox, Marg Helgenberger, William Petersen, George Eads, Gary Dourdan, Paul Guilfoyle&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;PREMISE: It&amp;rsquo;s the evidence, stupid. This slick crime drama focuses on &amp;ldquo;crime scene investigation,&amp;rdquo; the specialty of the forensic team in the Las Vegas police department&amp;rsquo;s Criminalistics Bureau. By relentlessly analyzing every detail at the scene of the crime, no matter how seemingly irrelevant or grotesque in nature, these sleuths have science and experience on their side to solve the case.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;THEY SAY: &amp;ldquo;It&amp;rsquo;s not so much who did it, but how was it done,&amp;rdquo; says series creator Anthony Zuiker, who describes C.S.I. as &amp;ldquo;Quincy on drugs.&amp;rdquo; As exec producer Carol Mendelsohn puts it, &amp;ldquo;They&amp;rsquo;re scientists with guns.&amp;rdquo; Jerry Bruckheimer, better known for action film spectaculars (Armageddon), says the show &amp;ldquo;takes you inside a world I&amp;rsquo;ve never seen before&amp;rdquo; &amp;#8212; literally inside, as when the camera zooms into a cadaver&amp;rsquo;s chest or intensely magnifies a hair fiber. Zuiker calls these shots &amp;ldquo;C.S.I. close-ups, something new and fresh.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;WE SAY: If only the characters were as animated as the evidence. The detective work is often gripping, but the detectives are mired in clich&amp;eacute;, including the always terrific Helgenberger (China Beach) as a conflicted single mom. Wasting actors like her and Petersen would be a crime. (Jorja Fox, last seen protecting the first daughter on The West Wing, joins C.S.I. in the second episode.)&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Las Vegas Review Journal</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2000/las-vegas-review-journal/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2000/las-vegas-review-journal/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s a Strip-to-strip week for &amp;ldquo;C.S.I.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The new prime-time crime drama about Las Vegas forensic investigators, which debuted last Friday on CBS, visits its small-screen hometown for three days starting Thursday.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And the whole &amp;ldquo;C.S.I&amp;rdquo; starring crew will be along for the ride &amp;#8212; one of them literally.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Series star William L. Petersen, who plays Criminalistics Bureau chief Gil Grissom, will brave the Manhattan Express roller coaster atop New York-New York for one scene. (If the grisly crime scenes he investigates don&amp;rsquo;t make him sick, he should be able to endure the coaster&amp;rsquo;s trademark heartline loop without losing his lunch.)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Joining Petersen on the road trip will be &amp;ldquo;C.S.I.&amp;rdquo; regulars Marg Helgenberger (who plays Catherine Willows), Gary Dourdan (Warrick Brown), George Eads (Nick Stokes), Jorja Fox (Sara Sidle) and Paul Guilfoyle (Capt. Jim Brass).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Other locations on the show&amp;rsquo;s Vegas schedule range from casino interiors to residential exteriors, along with stops at the Jockey Club parking lot and the Spearmint Rhino strip club.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And what would a made-in-Vegas TV show be without a chase along the Strip?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Most of the scenes will figure in the show&amp;rsquo;s sixth episode, &amp;ldquo;Who Are You,&amp;rdquo; which is keyed to the lyrics of the Who&amp;rsquo;s rock song of the same name.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Post-Gazette</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2000/post-gazette/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2000/post-gazette/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Who&amp;rsquo;s been shot?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s the question fans of NBC&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;The West Wing&amp;rdquo; have been asking all summer following the show&amp;rsquo;s season finale shooting attack on the president and his staff. Tonight viewers will get their answer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;NBC refused to send critics tapes of new episodes out of fear that some unthinking clod would lend the tape to his brother&amp;rsquo;s girlfriend&amp;rsquo;s cousin who might post revelations to a Web site, spoiling the surprise for everyone.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But here&amp;rsquo;s what I do know: NBC isn&amp;rsquo;t going to do a thing to mess with &amp;ldquo;The West Wing,&amp;rdquo; a medium-sized hit last season that&amp;rsquo;s poised to become a much bigger success this fall. Heck, I wouldn&amp;rsquo;t be surprised if &amp;ldquo;West Wing&amp;rdquo; takes the &amp;ldquo;ER&amp;rdquo; spot on Thursday night within a few years.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Don&amp;rsquo;t expect President Josiah Bartlet (Emmy nominee Martin Sheen) to die tonight, assuming he was even hit. But I wouldn&amp;rsquo;t get too attached to the female Secret Service agent played by Jorja Fox. She has lined up a series regular gig starting with the second episode of CBS&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;C.S.I.: Crime Scene Investigations.&amp;rdquo; Even if she survives the &amp;ldquo;West Wing&amp;rdquo; shooting, she&amp;rsquo;ll be an infrequent guest star, at best.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Moira Kelly, who played political operative Maddy Hampton, was not caught in the gunfire, but her character will disappear from the show.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Newsday</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2000/newsday/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2000/newsday/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;C.S.I.&lt;/strong&gt; (CBS, 9 p.m.): Weird, wild and witty. And in Vegas! You&amp;rsquo;d have to be strange to scrutinize crime there, so we have police crime scene investigators (as in the title) serving up chocolate-covered grasshoppers, synching &amp;ldquo;Dark Side of the Moon&amp;rdquo; to &amp;ldquo;The Wizard of Oz&amp;rdquo; and feeling &amp;ldquo;like King Kong on cocaine.&amp;rdquo; Their buzz comes from catching the baddies by &amp;ldquo;concentrating on what cannot lie: the evidence,&amp;rdquo; says sage boss William Petersen (&amp;ldquo;The Beast&amp;rdquo;), whose forensics team includes competitive hotshots Gary Dourdan and George Eads, single mom Marg Helgenberger and gung-ho newbie Jorja Fox. They get goofy over diminutive details such as toenail clippings and hair DNA, and downright delirious when they can use &amp;lsquo;em to nail the perps. You&amp;rsquo;d think it&amp;rsquo;d be dull, but characters don&amp;rsquo;t get much more vivid than these.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zetnet</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2000/zetnet/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2000/zetnet/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;After the promise of the no-budget London thriller *Following, *all eyes were on what Nolan would do with a little Hollywood cash. And he certainly hasn&amp;rsquo;t taken the easy road. **Memento **is told with an even more unconventional narrative that keeps your brain in high gear from the very first shot. And it&amp;rsquo;s absolutely brilliant-a terrific little thriller that takes the genre and turns it inside out.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Leonard (Pearce) has a memory disorder: Ever since his wife (Fox) was raped and murdered, he can&amp;rsquo;t create new memories, so he must use a series of Polaroids, notes and tattoos to remind himself where he is, who the people around him are and what he should be doing as he seeks revenge. &amp;ldquo;Remember Sammy Jankis&amp;rdquo; is his mantra, reminding him of a insurance investigation case from his &amp;ldquo;previous&amp;rdquo; life involving a man (Tobolowsky) who lost his memory and was cared for by his wife (Harris). But in the present there are lots of people scuttling around him, including a shifty fast-talker (Pantoliano), a victimised woman (Moss) and a vicious thug (Rennie). But who&amp;rsquo;s telling the truth &amp;hellip; and who&amp;rsquo;s using Leonard&amp;rsquo;s disorder to their advantage?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The film begins with a short backwards scene in which someone gets killed. Then the narrative splits off heading alternatively backwards and forwards in time until we get to the central, climactic scene in which all the loose threads are sorted out with a serious jolt. There are surprises at every turn, and it&amp;rsquo;s no mean feat to keep it all clear. But our attention is rewarded with a stunningly gripping story full of intelligence and wit. Nolan directs superbly, capturing tiny details with clever camera work and design that echo Hitchcock, among others. And as the story unfolds, builds and accelerates, there&amp;rsquo;s a real emotional punch to it all as well. The script is sharp, funny and very astute. And the performances are all first-rate. Pearce holds us right with him in each scene; and it&amp;rsquo;s great to see fine actors like Pantoliano &lt;em&gt;(The Matrix),&lt;/em&gt; Tobolowsky &lt;em&gt;(The Insider)&lt;/em&gt; and Harris *(Frasier) *shine in roles beyond what we&amp;rsquo;ve come to expect. Superb in every way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;*[15-themes, violence, strong language] 11.Sep.00&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;UK release 20.Oct.00*&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Student Advantage</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2000/student-advantage/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2000/student-advantage/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Scoop&lt;/strong&gt;: In Entertainment Weekly&amp;rsquo;s February cover story, director Aaron Sorkin discussed his plans for this year&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;The West Wing.&amp;rdquo; The most dramatic change is in the cast, since Moira Kelly is leaving.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Moira is a terrific actress,&amp;rdquo; Sorkin said. &amp;ldquo;But we just weren&amp;rsquo;t the right thing for her. She expressed that she felt the same way, and as a result, story lines haven&amp;rsquo;t been invested in that character, because we knew that at the end of the year, we&amp;rsquo;d be shaking hands and parting company.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sorkin also confirmed that Marlee Matlin&amp;rsquo;s character will take over much of Kelly&amp;rsquo;s character&amp;rsquo;s purpose and a younger female will be added to the team (Jorja Fox, formerly Dr. Maggie Doyle of &amp;ldquo;ER&amp;rdquo;). As for the season premiere, Sorkin didn&amp;rsquo;t say, but made a point to mention: &amp;ldquo;Last week I decided I want to [do] a two-part episode, which would be a flashback showing how everyone came to be part of the campaign. It&amp;rsquo;s a style of storytelling that really appeals to me. I think we&amp;rsquo;re gonna do that a lot next year  have [those] two parallel things going.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alliance-Atlantis</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2000/alliance-atlantis/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2000/alliance-atlantis/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Starring William Petersen (To Live and Die in L.A.) and Marg Helgenberger (China Beach)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Series Executive Produced by Action Feature Film Producer Jerry Bruckheimer (Pearl Harbour, Con Air)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;August 9, 2000 - Toronto&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;#8212; ALLIANCE ATLANTIS COMMUNICATIONS INC. announced today a co-production deal with CBS Productions and Jerry Bruckheimer Films Inc. to produce the one-hour crime drama &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;CSI: Crime Scene Investigation&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;. Twelve one-hour episodes began filming in Los Angeles on August 2, 2000, to premiere on the CBS Television Network this fall on Friday nights at 9 p.m. (ET/PT). The one-hour pilot was shot earlier this year.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;CSI&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;, a weekly one-hour series, chronicles the fast paced lives of a passionate team of investigators in Las Vegas who are trained to solve crimes the old fashioned way-by examining every bit of evidence. &lt;strong&gt;William Petersen&lt;/strong&gt; (&lt;em&gt;To Live and Die in L.A.&lt;/em&gt;) heads the team of forensic heroes as &amp;ldquo;Gil Grissom,&amp;rdquo; a senior forensics officer who, along with his team, works day and night solving crimes in ways that no other cops can. &lt;strong&gt;Petersen&lt;/strong&gt; also serves as a Producer for the series.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Other members of the investigative team include &amp;ldquo;Catherine Willows&amp;rdquo; (&lt;strong&gt;Marg Helgenberger&lt;/strong&gt; - &lt;em&gt;China Beach&lt;/em&gt;), a single parent juggling the job she loves and her family; &amp;ldquo;Warrick Brown&amp;rdquo; (&lt;strong&gt;Gary Dourdan&lt;/strong&gt; - &lt;em&gt;A Different World&lt;/em&gt;) and &amp;ldquo;Nick Stokes&amp;rdquo; (&lt;strong&gt;George Eads&lt;/strong&gt; - &lt;em&gt;E.R.&lt;/em&gt;), who are in head-to-head competition to solve their 100th crime; &amp;ldquo;Sara Sidle&amp;rdquo; (&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; - &lt;em&gt;The West Wing&lt;/em&gt;), the newest member of the team; and &amp;ldquo;Captain Jim Brass&amp;rdquo; (&lt;strong&gt;Paul Guilfoyle&lt;/strong&gt; - &lt;em&gt;L.A. Confidential&lt;/em&gt;), a no-nonsense kind of guy who is tough on everyone.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;CBS and Alliance Atlantis have built a great relationship over the years,&amp;rdquo; said Peter Sussman, President, ALLIANCE ATLANTIS ENTERTAINMENT. &amp;ldquo;It&amp;rsquo;s especially great to be expanding this relationship with a network series. &amp;ldquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Post-Gazette</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2000/post-gazette-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2000/post-gazette-2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jorja Fox, who played Maggie Doyle on &amp;ldquo;ER&amp;rdquo; and the Secret Service agent assigned to the president&amp;rsquo;s daughter on &amp;ldquo;West Wing,&amp;rdquo; said she has watched every episode of &amp;ldquo;Survivor.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;I really love Gervase and I love Richard,&amp;rdquo; she said at a CBS &amp;ldquo;Survivor&amp;rdquo;-themed party. Fox was there to promote her new CBS crime drama &amp;ldquo;C.S.I.&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;I was really hoping some of the cast would be here.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Post-Gazette</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2000/post-gazette-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2000/post-gazette-3/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Last season on &amp;ldquo;The West Wing,&amp;rdquo; actress Jorja Fox played a Secret Service agent willing to take a bullet for the president&amp;rsquo;s daughter. Turns out she suffered a different injury while filming the assassination attempt scene in the show&amp;rsquo;s season finale.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;We accidentally ran over her leg with a limousine &amp;#8212; and she was great about it,&amp;rdquo; said &amp;ldquo;West Wing&amp;rdquo; writer/creator Aaron Sorkin.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fox was filming on location in front of the Newseum in Arlington, Va. After the shooting, Fox fell to the asphalt alongside Dule Hill, who plays Charlie, the president&amp;rsquo;s aide.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;We were waiting for them to yell cut and all of a sudden I feel something heavy on my leg,&amp;rdquo; Fox said. &amp;ldquo;And there&amp;rsquo;s this limousine coming off my right leg. I was like, OK, it&amp;rsquo;s a new life experience. I&amp;rsquo;ve been run over by a presidential limousine, which is kind of hilarious.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fox jumped up immediately and she thought she was fine, but producers insisted she get checked out at a hospital, where all the nurses recognized her from her role on &amp;ldquo;ER.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;I felt like a walking miracle because I didn&amp;rsquo;t break anything,&amp;rdquo; Fox said. &amp;ldquo;It was kind of like a big bruise, a big contusion.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fox will return at least for the season premiere of &amp;ldquo;West Wing,&amp;rdquo; but she can&amp;rsquo;t reveal the fate of her character following the shooting. Whether or not she dies, she won&amp;rsquo;t be a &amp;ldquo;West Wing&amp;rdquo; regular. She&amp;rsquo;s starring in the new CBS drama &amp;ldquo;C.S.I.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Entertainment Weekly</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2000/entertainment-weekly/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Feb 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2000/entertainment-weekly/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another Sorkin mistake was casting Moira Kelly as a political consultant who began the series as Josh&amp;rsquo;s ex-girlfriend but whose scowly, abrasive role has evaporated into a series of background grimaces. &amp;ldquo;Moira is a terrific actress,&amp;rdquo; says Sorkin diplomatically. &amp;ldquo;[But] we just weren&amp;rsquo;t the right thing for her. She expressed that she felt the same way, and as a result, story lines haven&amp;rsquo;t been invested in that character, because we knew that at the end of the year, we&amp;rsquo;d be shaking hands and parting company.&amp;rdquo; Bye-bye, Moira, who did not respond to requests to comment on her departure.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In her place, Marlee Matlin has already filmed two episodes as a tough consultant who&amp;rsquo;ll tangle with Josh, and Sorkin confirms the rumor that next season, a few younger female characters will be added to the show-&amp;ldquo;because we work really hard and we deserve it,&amp;rdquo; he kids, before admitting it&amp;rsquo;s in response to a network desire to attract a younger demographic. &amp;ldquo;I will be introducing a cadre of specially trained 15-year-old senior counsels to the President,&amp;rdquo; jokes Sorkin. &amp;ldquo;It&amp;rsquo;s going to be like The Mod Squad.&amp;rdquo; But no kidding: New staffers will include Jorja Fox (formerly Dr. Maggie Doyle of ER) as a Secret Service agent assigned to protect the President&amp;rsquo;s daughter (played by Elizabeth Moss) as she attends college and fends off white-racist threats for dating Charlie-you know, the black tattooed love-god aide.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dish This</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2000/dish-this/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Feb 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2000/dish-this/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;President Bartlett heads out of Los Angeles for a big fundraiser this week on &amp;ldquo;The West Wing&amp;rdquo; (Wednesday, NBC, 9 p.m.). Look for Jorja Fox, who was so underused as Maggie Doyle on &amp;ldquo;ER,&amp;rdquo; to show up as the President&amp;rsquo;s daughter&amp;rsquo;s new Secret Service agent.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Georgia</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2000/georgia/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jan 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2000/georgia/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Pharr House Productions&amp;rsquo;&lt;/strong&gt; The Hungry Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s Club, a romantic comedy, opened at selected theaters nationwide on November 12. The feature film, which stars Atlanta&amp;rsquo;s Bill Nunn and Jorga Fox, was written by Georgia screenwriters Fred Dresch and Ron Ratliff, adapted frm a novel of the same name by Atlanta novelist Lynn Scott Myers, sister of Atlanta DP Ed Myers. Currently in development by Atlanta&amp;rsquo;s Pharr House Productions is the next novel written by Myers entitled Susceptible Terrain, another quirky romantic comedy. The film, to be adapted for the screen by the Dresch/Ratliff team and scheduled for a June 2000 production start, will star Bill Nunn and will be directed by Dresch.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>