<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>1999 on Fans of Le Fox Library</title>
    <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/tags/1999/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 1999 on Fans of Le Fox Library</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 Nov 1999 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://jorjafox.net/library/tags/1999/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Austin Chronicle Movies</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/1999/austin-chronicle-movies/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 1999 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/1999/austin-chronicle-movies/</guid>
      <description>Director: Gregory Ruzzin
Starring: Suzanne Mara, Bill Nunn, David Shackelford, Paul Provenza, Peter Murnik, Katherine Kendall, Jorja Fox
(PG-13, 93 min.)
Commercially speaking, this ingratiating low-budget romantic comedy seems bound for one of two starkly opposed fates: Death on arrival or modest word-of-mouth success among fans who root for the underdog in all areas of life. (These willful contrarians are easily identified by their tendency to drink Mr. Pibb, use Atari computers, and communicate by CB radio.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chicago Sun-Times</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/1999/chicago-sun-times/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 1999 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/1999/chicago-sun-times/</guid>
      <description>Mama&amp;rsquo;s Boys LLC presents a film directed by Gregory Ruzzin. Written by Fred Dresch and Ron Ratliff. Running time: 93 minutes. Rated PG-13 (for language). Opening today at Deerbrook, Lincoln Mall, Randhurst and Yorktown.
There are so many things wrong with &amp;ldquo;The Hungry Bachelors Club&amp;rdquo; that it&amp;rsquo;s easy to overlook some of the actors&amp;rsquo; fine work. It&amp;rsquo;s unfortunate that they&amp;rsquo;re stuck portraying one-dimensional characters who make the &amp;ldquo;Melrose Place&amp;rdquo; crew appear deep.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Entertainment Today</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/1999/entertainment-today-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 1999 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/1999/entertainment-today-2/</guid>
      <description>Offscreen bonds help the ensemble cast of The Hungry Bachelors Club bring a relaxed emotional honesty to their roles.
If you glimpsed the title The Hungry Bachelors Club on, say, a movie theater marquee, this romantic comedy might bring to mind a gaggle of frat boys chasing girls and chugging beer.
&amp;ldquo;I was afraid of that,&amp;rdquo; admitted director Gregory Ruzzin in an interview a week before his film&amp;rsquo;s opening.
But as Ruzzin and Club&amp;rsquo;s ensemble cast can tell you, once you get beneath the misleading title you&amp;rsquo;ll find a hometown story - about family, acceptance and new beginnings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Entertainment Today</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/1999/entertainment-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 1999 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/1999/entertainment-today/</guid>
      <description>Don&amp;rsquo;t let the slightly misogynistic title fool you. This food-themed film, focusing on thirtysomethings at the helm of change, can be compared to Soul Food and Eat Drink Man Woman with a dash of Like Water for Chocolate. Single mother Delmar Youngblood (Jorja Fox) dreams of opening a restaurant called The Hungry Bachelors Club, so named for the weekly bachelor-littered dinner parties she throws. Without enough money, however, Delmar agrees to &amp;ldquo;loan an egg and rent a womb&amp;rdquo; to a couple willing to pay $50,000.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Variety</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/1999/variety/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 1999 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/1999/variety/</guid>
      <description>A Mama&amp;rsquo;s Boys Prods. release of a Taggart Transcontinental and Managed Passion Films presentation of a Mama&amp;rsquo;s Boys production. Produced by Dan Gifford, Amy Sommer Gifford. Executive producer, Kimberly Becker. Co-producer, Robert Lynn New.
Directed by Gregory Ruzzin. Screenplay, Fred Dresch, Ron Ratliff, based on the novel by Lynn Scott Myers. Camera (FotoKem color), Robert Smith; supervising editors, Stephen Myers, Andrew Frank; music, Larry Brown; music supervisor, Spencer Proffer; production designer, Timothy Duffy; costumes, Katie Saunders; sound (Dolby), David Schaaf; supervising sound editor, Tim Kimmel; line producer, Jim Glander; assistant director, Jonathan Southard; casting, Peggy Larson.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Austin Chronicle Screens</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/1999/austin-chronicle-screens/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Oct 1999 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/1999/austin-chronicle-screens/</guid>
      <description>D: Werner Molinsky; with Jean Smart, Robert Wagner, Emily Procter, Justin William Root, Jorja Fox, Mink Stole.
Mix the tackiness of The Valley of the Dolls and the campiness of The Adventures of Priscilla: Queen of the Desert, and you get a sense of what Tiara Tango is all about. Jean Smart (Designing Women) stars as Lorelei, the former &amp;ldquo;Miss Texas Gal 1968,&amp;rdquo; who still manages beauty pageants and has now pinned her hopes on her beauty-contestant daughter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tuned In</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/1999/tuned-in/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jul 1999 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/1999/tuned-in/</guid>
      <description>PASADENA, CALIF. &amp;#8212; TV critics can be an unforgiving lot, but UPN&amp;rsquo;s fall schedule makes compassion tough to muster.
In an effort to draw more viewers &amp;#8212; particularly young, male viewers &amp;#8212; the struggling network has scheduled two hours of WWF wrestling Thursday night. Critics are bound to sneer, but it&amp;rsquo;s an easy move that&amp;rsquo;s likely to boost the network&amp;rsquo;s ratings.
[ &amp;hellip; ]
UPN entertainment president Tom Nunan said the Fontana/Levinson show, once titled &amp;ldquo;Flesh and Blood,&amp;rdquo; was filmed only as a presentation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MetroMix</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/1999/metromix/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 May 1999 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/1999/metromix/</guid>
      <description>Gregory Ruzzin&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;The Hungry Bachelors Club,&amp;rdquo; produced by the team that gave us the award-winning documentary &amp;ldquo;Waco: The Rules Of Engagement,&amp;rdquo; is in many ways a trifle, a low-key romantic comedy about a close-knit group of friendly oddballs who occasionally gather for discussion, companionship and home-cooked meals. Where it rises above the ordinary is in its attempt to address issues of personal consequence &amp;#8212; like infidelity, interracial romance and surrogate motherhood &amp;#8212; even as it maintains its tenuous comic roots.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bergen Records</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/1999/bergen-records/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Feb 1999 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/1999/bergen-records/</guid>
      <description>Special from The Philadelphia Inquirer
After hospitals (&amp;ldquo;St. Elsewhere&amp;rdquo;), cops (&amp;ldquo;Homicide&amp;rdquo;), and prison (&amp;ldquo;Oz&amp;rdquo;), what&amp;rsquo;s left for madly prolific producer Tom Fontana?
Why, all three, of course.
UPN&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;The True Story&amp;rdquo; (working title) stars Jorja Fox (intern Maggie Doyle on &amp;ldquo;ER&amp;rdquo;) as &amp;#8212; get this &amp;#8212; a medical intern whose father is in prison for killing her mother.
And, oh yes, intern Meghan has a brother who&amp;rsquo;s a cop.
&amp;ldquo;In one regard, this is a cavalcade of the work of Tom Fontana,&amp;rdquo; says the producer, who&amp;rsquo;s creating the new show with his longtime partner in crime, Barry Levinson.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Den</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/1999/the-den/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Feb 1999 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/1999/the-den/</guid>
      <description>Jorja who? No one really knows who the hell she is, but she&amp;rsquo;s pretty hot, she&amp;rsquo;s on ER, and that&amp;rsquo;s good enough for UPN.
Jorja Fox, who plays intern Maggie Doyle on ER, is apparently doing her best David Caruso impersonation by leaving a hit show to take the lead role on the new UPN sure-fire bomb The True Story.
The show, from the creators of Homicide, Tom Fontana and Barry Levinson, will be ready for UPN&amp;rsquo;s fall schedule provided the two&amp;rsquo;s escape from Betty Ford goes off without a hitch.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Gist</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/1999/the-gist/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Feb 1999 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/1999/the-gist/</guid>
      <description>Jorja Fox, who plays intern Maggie Doyle on ER, is going to keep her job even as she moves to a hospital on the UPN network. She will still be a medical intern on The True Story, a drama series being considered by UPN for its fall lineup. However, Fox will be the star instead of an ER bit player; her character&amp;rsquo;s father is in jail for killing her mother.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ultimate TV</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/1999/ultimate-tv/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Feb 1999 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/1999/ultimate-tv/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;ER&amp;rdquo; costar Jorja Fox has been cast as a lead on the new Tom Fontana/Barry Levinson series for UPN, according to Daily Variety. In &amp;ldquo;The True Story,&amp;rdquo; Fox is slated to play a medical intern &amp;#8212; basically the same role she currently has on TV&amp;rsquo;s hottest drama.
UPN is funding a pilot and six scripts of &amp;ldquo;True Story,&amp;rdquo; but will decide after the pilot is completed whether or not to commit to 13 episodes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apollo Guide</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/1999/apollo-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 1999 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/1999/apollo-guide/</guid>
      <description>You are two hours from collision with an asteroid, and pirates have disabled your spaceship, seeking the forty billion dollars in cash thatï¿½s stuffed in your hold. This is Velocity Trap. It&amp;rsquo;s pretty standard mid-range action science fiction fare that benefits a lot from recent improvements in special effects technology.
When watching this film, you must first ask yourself what are you looking for and how are you judging it? If your primary interest in watching films is great acting and a stellar plot, you really ought not to look here first.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Box Off</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/1999/box-off/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 1999 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/1999/box-off/</guid>
      <description>Starring Jorja Fox, Bill Nunn and Suzanne Mara. Directed by Gregory Ruzzin. Written by Fred Dresch and Ron Ratliff. Produced by Dan Gifford and Amy Sommer. A Mama&amp;rsquo;s Boys release. Romantic comedy. Rated PG-13 for some mature thematic elements. Running time: 91 min.
Intended as a succulent dish spiced with equal parts quirkiness and homeyness, &amp;ldquo;The Hungry Bachelors Club&amp;rdquo; starts out appetizing enough, but ends as a bland mishmash of conflicting ingredients.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Checkout</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/1999/checkout/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 1999 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/1999/checkout/</guid>
      <description>Gregory Ruzzin directs this romantic comedy about 30-somethings looking for love. Divorcee Delmar and her roommate Hortense prepare for one of their usual dinner parties for their sundry friends and associates. Hortense is anxiously waiting for her boyfriend Stanley (Paul Provenza) to propose, but instead he proposes an unusual request to Delmar: Would she being to bear a child for his boss and barren wife? Delmar agrees. Meanwhile, shy Moses (Bill Nunn) who lives in an old Cadillac, is being sought after by Delmar&amp;rsquo;s brother Jethro and his buddy Marlon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>News Articles (1999)</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/1999/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 1999 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/1999/</guid>
      <description>  Date Source    January 01 Apollo Guide   January 01 Box Off   January 01 Checkout   February 09 The Den   February 09 The Gist   February 09 Ultimate TV   February 24 Bergen Records   May 01 MetroMix   July 20 Tuned In   October 22 Austin Chronicle Screens   November 12 Austin Chronicle Movies   November 12 Chicago Sun-Times   November 12 Entertainment Today   November 12 Entertainment Today   November 12 Variety    </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>