<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Missing Persons on Jorja Fox Library</title>
    <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/tags/missing-persons/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Missing Persons on Jorja Fox Library</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 17 Feb 1994 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://jorjafox.net/library/tags/missing-persons/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>What Do You Want, a Signed Confession ... ?</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/mp/what-do-you-want-a-signed-confession/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 1994 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/mp/what-do-you-want-a-signed-confession/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;synopsis:00a550912602d65ff9d329142440dbf1&#34;&gt;Synopsis&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bobby is still under investigation for a suspected bribe and perverting the course of justice. Also a little girl, Molly Jewett, is snatched in a department store.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;connie-karadzic-review:00a550912602d65ff9d329142440dbf1&#34;&gt;Connie Karadzic Review&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Connie works with Carlos and Johnny to find the missing girl. Connie interviews the mother, keeping her company while Carlos and Johnny search the building. They find Molly&amp;rsquo;s jacket, and evidence she hasn&amp;rsquo;t been taken from the store.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;quotes:00a550912602d65ff9d329142440dbf1&#34;&gt;Quotes&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Connie:&lt;/strong&gt; Are you kidding me? I would be out there breaking her &amp;hellip; buns in order to clear Bobby!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tell Me You Didn&#39;t Do It ... I&#39;ll Go to the Wall for You</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/mp/tell-me-you-didnt-do-it-ill-go-to-the-wall-for-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 1994 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/mp/tell-me-you-didnt-do-it-ill-go-to-the-wall-for-you/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;synopsis:3224374f9a9b861c77ed649d3a64daed&#34;&gt;Synopsis&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ellen is making her mark on the department, buying doughnuts, making coffee, and being paired with Bobby on a seemingly straightforward parolee disappearance. Until Bobby is framed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;connie-karadzic-review:3224374f9a9b861c77ed649d3a64daed&#34;&gt;Connie Karadzic Review&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Connie looks into the case of David Roberts, 21-year old who is missing ten days from an upper Lakeview apartment. Mrs. Roberts explains that she and her son hadn&amp;rsquo;t talked in 3 years after his father threw him out for being gay. The mother finally got the courage to leave her husband and find David. The residents of David&amp;rsquo;s building are secretive and evasive, giving Connie few leads save his boss. While David has no phone, his boss has the number for a contact service. Connie gets in touch with David via the service and tells him she&amp;rsquo;s looking for him on behalf of his mother, and David hangs up on her. They&amp;rsquo;re able to trace his call to his apartment complex, where Connie tracks him down only to find he&amp;rsquo;s run off again. Since she can&amp;rsquo;t reunite mother and son, she instead gives his mother all the information she has.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;character-notes:3224374f9a9b861c77ed649d3a64daed&#34;&gt;Character Notes&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Connie likes a blueberry Bismark (jelly) donut.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Connie has a new boyfriend.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;quotes:3224374f9a9b861c77ed649d3a64daed&#34;&gt;Quotes&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Connie:&lt;/strong&gt; A few months ago I probably wouldn&amp;rsquo;t have even known who you were, but my new boyfriend takes me to all these art exhibits, and I&amp;rsquo;ve actually seen your work. It&amp;rsquo;s really interesting.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>All They Had to Do Was Ask...</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/mp/all-they-had-to-do-was-ask/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Feb 1994 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/mp/all-they-had-to-do-was-ask/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;synopsis:5e5c7074fadf6928245e13100703e679&#34;&gt;Synopsis&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ray is shocked when he is told his ex-partner is being transferred into his department. Problem is she is female and rumours were rife that they were having an affair. Meanwhile a boy goes missing from party of schoolchildren on a museum tour.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;connie-karadzic-review:5e5c7074fadf6928245e13100703e679&#34;&gt;Connie Karadzic Review&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Connie works the case of a disoriented woman brought in by a cabbie with no wallet, purse or ID, claiming her name is Minerva Fitzhugh. Minerva is aware that she&amp;rsquo;s lost and she can&amp;rsquo;t remember anything. She&amp;rsquo;s only one of a pair of little old ladies missing from a Gold Coast private residence. Apparently the girls were sisters and lived together, Minerva went off to look for her sister, Betty Carr. Due to a stroke, Minerva has trouble remembering what year it is, or even remembering who Connie or her doctor are. Betty has been caring for Minerva since the stroke.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While Connie&amp;rsquo;s at home, the morgue calls to tell her they found a woman matching Betty&amp;rsquo;s description, beaten to death. The housekeeper is able to ID the body as Betty, but the doctor doesn&amp;rsquo;t know how to handle Minerva. Suffering from both retrograde and anterograde amnesia, Minerva can&amp;rsquo;t remember anything after 1970, and can only hold onto new memories for a short while. Salvation is found when Joanne McDonald, the daughter of the oldest sister, arrives. Minerva mistakes Joanne for her sister, and Joanne offers to take Minerva home.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;character-notes:5e5c7074fadf6928245e13100703e679&#34;&gt;Character Notes&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Connie lives alone and sleeps in a twin bed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;quotes:5e5c7074fadf6928245e13100703e679&#34;&gt;Quotes&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bobby:&lt;/strong&gt; Who got the nothing on it?&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Connie:&lt;/strong&gt; Me!&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Bobby:&lt;/strong&gt; Oh, Connie, that&amp;rsquo;s what I love about you. Your spirit of adventure.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Beautiful Son is Okay</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/mp/my-beautiful-son-is-okay/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 1994 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/mp/my-beautiful-son-is-okay/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;synopsis:af88092756fa6c8ea048eddd3c3045e3&#34;&gt;Synopsis&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Johnny and Connie look for two little boys who went missing on their way home from school, while Bobby has the mysterious disappearance of a woman he met on a recent case on his hands. Carlos, Anita, Ray and Barbara spend the whole episode worrying about baby Carlito Ray who is sick.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;connie-karadzic-review:af88092756fa6c8ea048eddd3c3045e3&#34;&gt;Connie Karadzic Review&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Two boys, Joel and Ronnie, were playing along the railroad tracks, accidentally end up stuck in a grain car when the train pulls out of the depot. Both boys are huge basketball fans and were in a rush to get to school to meet the Chicago Bulls, who were coming for a special assembly after winning their third straight championship. Connie notices the train yard and suspects the boys cut through in their excitement. Upon searching the yard, they find the boys&amp;rsquo; bookbags.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After searching the cars, they find the basketball on top of one, and the boys under the grain in the car. They&amp;rsquo;re able to rescue the boys, both alive, if a bit worse for wear.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;character-notes:af88092756fa6c8ea048eddd3c3045e3&#34;&gt;Character Notes&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Connie went on a date to a Dadaist show in the art museum.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;quotes:af88092756fa6c8ea048eddd3c3045e3&#34;&gt;Quotes&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Connie&lt;/strong&gt;: Hobos!? You mean like those guy who sneak on trains like in old movies?&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I&#39;ve Got a Siren</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/mp/ive-got-a-siren/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 1994 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/mp/ive-got-a-siren/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;synopsis:f0fe67c338b3a2084d42dfe00f0e6b98&#34;&gt;Synopsis&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Connie helps a girl who is having a baby and is missing her boyfriend Jake, while Bobby meets an actress who models herself on Lauren Bacall and has driven her husband away with her constant role-playing games. Johnny is assigned desk duty after his father is investigated by internal affairs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;connie-karadzic-review:f0fe67c338b3a2084d42dfe00f0e6b98&#34;&gt;Connie Karadzic Review&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While interviewing Tamara Thorpe, the pregnant woman goes into labor and Connie rushes her to the hospital but it&amp;rsquo;s a false alarm. The neighbors explain that Jake, the boyfriend, has been missing for at least four months.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;character-notes:f0fe67c338b3a2084d42dfe00f0e6b98&#34;&gt;Character Notes&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Connie is awkward around babies.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>If You Could Pick Your Own Parents</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/mp/if-you-could-pick-your-own-parents/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 1994 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/mp/if-you-could-pick-your-own-parents/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;synopsis:72c9359eca76a31d332dbe5d90b6e294&#34;&gt;Synopsis&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Marsha and Phil Koppelman live upstairs from an older couple who don&amp;rsquo;t show up for a planned dinner. When Phil goes to check on them, he finds Bernice collapsed and Myron missing. Carlos goes looking for Myron, while Johnny looks for the full identity of a man named Dave, last seen leaping off a bridge. Connie has to sort through a high number of missing reports, most of them probably caused by a massive accident on the subway that has tied up trains for hours.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;connie-karadzic-review:72c9359eca76a31d332dbe5d90b6e294&#34;&gt;Connie Karadzic Review&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Connie is helping plan a surprise birthday party at Ray&amp;rsquo;s house with Ray&amp;rsquo;s wife, Barbara. She also mans the desks due to the high number of missing people following the subway accident. While many people are injured, a high number are also trapped underground and delayed. Connie gets the other detectives to help distract Ray while she goes to help Barbara with the party.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;character-notes:72c9359eca76a31d332dbe5d90b6e294&#34;&gt;Character Notes&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Connie is friendly with Ray&amp;rsquo;s wife, Barbara.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Hard Is It Just to Get Off at the Next Exit?</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/mp/how-hard-is-it-just-to-get-off-at-the-next-exit/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 1993 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/mp/how-hard-is-it-just-to-get-off-at-the-next-exit/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;synopsis:862140e8266c6b6ea86d3c0ae1cc82b3&#34;&gt;Synopsis&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A woman sees her missing son as she rides the bus, but by the time she gets off, he&amp;rsquo;s gone. Carlos goes to help the woman. Bobby looks for a missing express delivery man, while a councilman leans on Ray for a favor when his best-friend&amp;rsquo;s daughter goes missing right before her wedding. Johnny helps his family when his father, also a police officer, is shot.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;connie-karadzic-review:862140e8266c6b6ea86d3c0ae1cc82b3&#34;&gt;Connie Karadzic Review&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Connie helps Ray on his case, interviewing Cilla&amp;rsquo;s fiancee while Ray talks with the parents. While Sean can understand why she might leave her controlling family, he can&amp;rsquo;t fathom why she might leave him. After the bridesmaid leaves a message for Cilla, he calls someone and then vanishes too. Connie follows after the bridesmaid, certain that she arranged for Sean and Cilla to meet. Connie winds up attending the elopement of Sean and Cilla.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;character-notes:862140e8266c6b6ea86d3c0ae1cc82b3&#34;&gt;Character Notes##&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;quotes:862140e8266c6b6ea86d3c0ae1cc82b3&#34;&gt;Quotes##&lt;/h2&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Right Neighborhood ... Wrong Door</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/mp/right-neighborhood-wrong-door/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Dec 1993 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/mp/right-neighborhood-wrong-door/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;synopsis:315ab0c6d6e211fb241b50c15e351e4a&#34;&gt;Synopsis&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bobby helps his mother with a private matter when a member of her church goes missing. Connie looks into habitual runaway and train hopper, Joey Pender (age 8). Johnny looks into a missing rich Lake Shore Drive accountant.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;connie-karadzic-review:315ab0c6d6e211fb241b50c15e351e4a&#34;&gt;Connie Karadzic Review&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While Joey has hopped on busses and trains before, he always turns himself in at the Kedzie station. His father is a long-distance truck driver, and since his mother makes a big deal about when his father comes home, Joey decided the best way to get attention was to go away. This time he&amp;rsquo;s been out all night. Connie tracks Joey down to the A-train line and canvasses all the stations, as well as searching his house.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Joey&amp;rsquo;s favorite toy truck is missing from the house, but they find his favorite hat in lost-and-found. The CTA worker who found the hat explains Joey dropped it when he was woken up and ran off at the end of the train line: O&amp;rsquo;Hare. Connie works with the police at O&amp;rsquo;Hare and, since she knows what time the train arrived at O&amp;rsquo;Hare, they&amp;rsquo;re able to follow him on the surveillance tapes and find Joey snuck onto a plane to LA.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sometimes You Can&#39;t Help Getting Involved</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/mp/sometimes-you-cant-help-getting-involved/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Nov 1993 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/mp/sometimes-you-cant-help-getting-involved/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;synopsis:a88c79ce4644289b4fa88fca3edcd785&#34;&gt;Synopsis&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Connie and Carlos both have to find missing children. Connie&amp;rsquo;s case is a 4-year old who disappeared at nursery school, and Carlos&amp;rsquo;s is an 8-year old, who is later found badly beaten. When an ex-school friend of Ray&amp;rsquo;s, who had been injured in an accident many years ago resulting in him have the mental age of a 6-year old, is accused of the beating, Ray breaks his own number 1 rule and becomes personally involved trying to clear him.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;connie-karadzic-review:a88c79ce4644289b4fa88fca3edcd785&#34;&gt;Connie Karadzic Review&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Connie&amp;rsquo;s missing 4-year old, Jennifer, is suspected to have been abducted by her father, as the parents are divorced and Greg Demitrius has a restraining order. The mother, Sally, claims the parents are still in love, however, and Connie looks deeper into the mystery. Greg blames Sally&amp;rsquo;s mother, who bullies Sally, and insists he doesn&amp;rsquo;t have their daughter. The parents reconcile while Ray calls the FBI and Connie finds evidence that Jennifer is still hiding at the school, trapped behind a stuck door in the bell tower. Connie makes the news, for being a hero.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;character-notes:a88c79ce4644289b4fa88fca3edcd785&#34;&gt;Character Notes&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Connie still believes in love, and is happy when spouses are reunited.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I&#39;m Gonna Miss Him Too</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/mp/im-gonna-miss-him-too/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Nov 1993 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/mp/im-gonna-miss-him-too/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;synopsis:61bc50c56ee2d248bbcb75f9ee16a084&#34;&gt;Synopsis&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A young boy runs away from home, returning to take his little brother with him, after his potential stepfather steals from their home and blames it on him, and then threatens his life. Connie has to trace the family of an heroic John Doe who saved a little girl&amp;rsquo;s life, in order to find out what his medical problems are, and along the way feels some chemistry with the surgeon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;connie-karadzic-review:61bc50c56ee2d248bbcb75f9ee16a084&#34;&gt;Connie Karadzic Review&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dr. Eric Varga calls in a missing person in the case of a John Doe who had an allergic reaction in the middle of emergency surgery. They need to find who he is so they can find his medical records and save his life. His legs were run over by a car after he jumped in front of it to push a little girl aside. By tracking the bags pulled off of planes (due to unclaimed boarding passes), they find the John Doe is named Kevin Sullivan and is allergic to just about everything.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When Connie goes to follow up on Mr. Sullivan, Dr. Varga asks if her ring is decorative or functional, and is quite happy to learn it&amp;rsquo;s a fashion statement. Connie spends the night at the hospital to be sure everything turns out alright, and accepts a date with Dr. Varga.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;character-notes:61bc50c56ee2d248bbcb75f9ee16a084&#34;&gt;Character Notes&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Connie accepts a date with Dr. Varga.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;quotes:61bc50c56ee2d248bbcb75f9ee16a084&#34;&gt;Quotes&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dr. Varga:&lt;/strong&gt; You know, when I get up, I&amp;rsquo;m probably gonna be hungry. And I hate to eat alone.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Connie:&lt;/strong&gt; Okay, I&amp;rsquo;ll meet you. But you&amp;rsquo;re paying for dinner, I bought the coffee.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Some People&#39;s Priorities ...</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/mp/some-peoples-priorities/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Nov 1993 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/mp/some-peoples-priorities/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;synopsis:d544940ecd9df9aa7e8552ec7e026b81&#34;&gt;Synopsis&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bobby&amp;rsquo;s case of a missing dental student who apparently fell into voodoo returns when the parents decide they do want to find their wayward daughter, but she may be a victim of a serial killer. Connie looks into the case of a missing Indian woman who has been missing nine days. Johnny has a Tender Age case of an eleven year-old who went missing from a double-parked car in Lincoln Park.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;connie-karadzic-review:d544940ecd9df9aa7e8552ec7e026b81&#34;&gt;Connie Karadzic Review&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Connie&amp;rsquo;s case is of a missing Indian immigrant, Randa Punjabi. The husband, Mr. Najami, and children are concerned, but they claim there was no fight. He waited nine days because he didn&amp;rsquo;t want to alarm the children. The couple have different last names, and Connie finds no woman&amp;rsquo;s clothes in the closet. The husband explains that his wife was very progressive, and that it was her idea to learn jewelry making and move to the US. In the bathroom, Connie takes notes of the vast array of medicine and learns Mr. Najami is sick with leukemia, but refused to be hospitalized, telling the doctor that his wife was dead and he couldn&amp;rsquo;t leave his children alone.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When Mr. Najami refuses to let Connie talk to his children, or tell her the truth, she explains that she will have his sons taken away. He admits his name is Rajiv Bat, and his wife wanted custody in the divorce so he ran away with his boys. His wife filled a warrant for his arrest, so he changed his name. Once he learned he was dying, he decided to have Missing Persons find his wife so Randa could take the boys. Ray orders Connie to have the man arrested and the children sent to DCFS, but the man rabbits. The next day he starts to call Missing Persons every hour to see if they&amp;rsquo;ve found her, prompting Connie to man the phones and track Randa down to a restaurant in Chicago. Rajiv confesses to his children the truth, and returns his children to their mother.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Meanwhile, Connie&amp;rsquo;s had flower deliveries every day for three days. At first she claims they&amp;rsquo;re from her husband, who is apologizing for a fight. The second day, her coworkers speculate on if her husband or Connie is having an affair. Finally, on the third day, Connie tells Ray she&amp;rsquo;s divorced, after Ray&amp;rsquo;s wife called her, concerned.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;character-notes:d544940ecd9df9aa7e8552ec7e026b81&#34;&gt;Character Notes&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Connie&amp;rsquo;s parents are still pressuring her to remarry.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Connie initially claims the flowers are a make-up present from her husband.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Connie finally tells Ray she&amp;rsquo;s divorced.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ray&amp;rsquo;s wife is friendly with Connie.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;quotes:d544940ecd9df9aa7e8552ec7e026b81&#34;&gt;Quotes&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Connie:&lt;/strong&gt; I can find my own dates, Ma. &amp;hellip; Yeah, he was very nice, he just wasn&amp;rsquo;t my type. For starters, he flossed his teeth at the table. &amp;hellip; I&amp;rsquo;m not gonna end up some sort of &amp;lsquo;old maid&amp;rsquo; just because I&amp;rsquo;m divorced. &amp;hellip; You sound like dad.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Man&#39;s an Emotional Termite</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/mp/the-mans-an-emotional-termite/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 1993 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/mp/the-mans-an-emotional-termite/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;synopsis:1781ed09b60a552518903481bf327e66&#34;&gt;Synopsis&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A girl living with her grandmother in Cabrini Green and goes missing, while an older man loses his family following a vacation, and another young girl into voodoo goes missing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;connie-karadzic-review:1781ed09b60a552518903481bf327e66&#34;&gt;Connie Karadzic Review&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Connie works the case of a forgetful man who has lost his family following a month vacation. Victor Deely&amp;rsquo;s son Karl had gone to Florida but never returned. Victor presses Connie to learn about her personal life, and gets cagey when she says they&amp;rsquo;ll have to search his house. His house is all but empty, and while Victor is really friendly his explanations as to why the house is devoid of furniture and clothes are suspicious.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Victor comes to the unit with presents for everyone. Ray distracts him so Connie can go investigate his neighbors. The neighbors explain that Victor has been very needy and overly sweet to everyone since his wife died, and has been driving everyone crazy. As Connie&amp;rsquo;s there, the cops arrive to serve a warrant. Karl sold the house months ago, and the new owners want to evict Victor. After finding Karl, they learn that Karl had filed a missing persons on Victor three days ago.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They had put Victor in a nursing home due to his dementia, and Victor keeps running away to live with them again. He had forgotten that they&amp;rsquo;d moved. Everyone in the family loves him, but he drives everyone crazy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;character-notes:1781ed09b60a552518903481bf327e66&#34;&gt;Character Notes&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Connie is still pretending the man in the wedding photo on her desk is her husband, and not her brother Richard.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;quotes:1781ed09b60a552518903481bf327e66&#34;&gt;Quotes&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ray:&lt;/strong&gt; When your husband wants to take you out to dinner, where&amp;rsquo;s your favorite place to go?&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Connie:&lt;/strong&gt; A restaurant? Oh that&amp;rsquo;s easy. Schulers. They have the most fabulous cabbage soup there and this cookie for desert.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Ray:&lt;/strong&gt; No, no no no no. Romantic, it&amp;rsquo;s gotta be romantic.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Connie:&lt;/strong&gt; Well it is romantic! It&amp;rsquo;s dark and there are candles on the table and the waiters wear this sexy lederhosen. And the owner is a real hoot, he thinks he&amp;rsquo;s a &amp;#8211;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Ray:&lt;/strong&gt; Thanks. Go.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Connie:&lt;/strong&gt; You&amp;rsquo;re welcome.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>That&#39;s My Sister, Pal</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/mp/thats-my-sister-pal/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 1993 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/mp/thats-my-sister-pal/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;synopsis:508b64925287146d3246eae7380aaefd&#34;&gt;Synopsis&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While Connie and Carlos investigate the disappearance of a young Latino newly arrived from Mexico, Johnny has assigned himself an &amp;#8220;unofficial&amp;#8221; case. He thinks Connie&amp;rsquo;s husband is cheating on her and decides to find out for sure. Enlisting an unwilling Bobby, who is working a case involving the disappearance of a middle-aged widower, they find out more than they want to know. Ray, contacted by the wife of a missing old colleague of his, has to find the man. He does, also finding out more than he wants know.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;connie-karadzic-review:508b64925287146d3246eae7380aaefd&#34;&gt;Connie Karadzic Review&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Connie comes in with a bad mood, and when Bobby asks her where the days donuts are, Connie snarks that she shouldn&amp;rsquo;t have to get them every day. Johnny senses her bad mood, but Connie refuses to talk to him about it and asks for some time off because she might have cancer. Instead she works with Carlos on a case of a missing Latino immigrant, to keep her mind off things. While helping Carlos, a ground of gangbangers attempt to harass her, but she holds her own. When the missing boy&amp;rsquo;s sister is beaten by the gangbangers, Connie confesses that she too has been a victim and urges the girl to speak out against her attackers, which she does and has him arrested.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Johnny looks into her husband, Richard, who he saw kidding a woman in a bar. At the address of Karadzic Plumbing, Johnny sees Richard getting into a car with a woman he calls &amp;lsquo;honey&amp;rsquo; and Richard has a phone number at her apartment. Johnny finally confronts Richard, who explains Connie isn&amp;rsquo;t his wife, she&amp;rsquo;s his sister. Richard and Connie&amp;rsquo;s father explain to Johnny that Connie&amp;rsquo;s divorced, and her husband used to beat her. While Richard supports this, Connie&amp;rsquo;s father claims that she should have made it work, and this is the heart of a family dispute.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;character-notes:508b64925287146d3246eae7380aaefd&#34;&gt;Character Notes&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;No one at the office has ever met Connie&amp;rsquo;s husband.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Carlos asks about Connie&amp;rsquo;s claim to being a victim, but Connie says little more than it&amp;rsquo;s why she became a cop.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Connie has a cancer scare, made worse when the hospital looses her records, but in the end, she&amp;rsquo;s fine.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Connie tells Johnny that she appreciates his concern, and asks him to keep his mouth shut about what he learned.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;quotes:508b64925287146d3246eae7380aaefd&#34;&gt;Quotes&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bobby:&lt;/strong&gt; Yo, yo, Connie! What&amp;rsquo;s up? Where da donuts?&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Connie:&lt;/strong&gt; Why do I always have to get the donuts? Because I&amp;rsquo;m a woman?&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Can&#39;t Even Imagine</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/mp/i-cant-even-imagine/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 1993 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/mp/i-cant-even-imagine/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;synopsis:268bffc92caebb06c211147cf7307d0f&#34;&gt;Synopsis&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Connie works the case of Anne Conlin, whose parents find her apartment stripped clean, and Anne never got off the plane after a three month trip to Europe. Johnny works a case of kids who goe missing after a party on the South Side. Carlos hunts down Jerome Vincent, whose car is found abandoned in a parking lot with a suicide note, but no body. Meanwhile Bobby tries to find his mother the perfect birthday present.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;connie-karadzic-review:268bffc92caebb06c211147cf7307d0f&#34;&gt;Connie Karadzic Review&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Connie works on the Anne Conlin case, the oldest daughter whose boyfriend, Scott, died seven months before. The airline reports that Anne never caught the flight out to Europe, she never applied for a passport, and she paid her apartment for three months in advance, and cleaned out her bank account. Connie goes to talk to the feds, trying to find out if she&amp;rsquo;d been tossed in witness protection. Anne&amp;rsquo;s boyfriend&amp;rsquo;s parents claimed he died of cancer, but he had AIDS, and Anne was the only one who took care of him. Her best friend was afraid that Anne caught AIDS as well and died alone.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Scott&amp;rsquo;s parents know more about what happened to Anne, but refuse to talk about it. Connie determines Anne fell in with an underground AIDS ring, as no one really understood AIDS in 1993. Scott&amp;rsquo;s father relents, and leaves Connie a note saying which hospice Anne checked into, but the hospice refuses to share patient information. The doctor does pass on Connie&amp;rsquo;s information to Anne, in the hopes of encouraging reconciliation with Anne and her parents. Anne does contact Connie and agrees to see her and, eventually, to speak to her parents.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;character-notes:268bffc92caebb06c211147cf7307d0f&#34;&gt;Character Notes&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Connie adopts a Columbo schtick when interrogating families, pretending to be simple minded in order to draw out information.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;quotes:268bffc92caebb06c211147cf7307d0f&#34;&gt;Quotes##&lt;/h2&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>People Don&#39;t Talk to Cops, People Lie to Cops</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/mp/people-dont-talk-to-cops-people-lie-to-cops/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 1993 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/mp/people-dont-talk-to-cops-people-lie-to-cops/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;synopsis:d784d589dcf57a85e7530409bc1d46bd&#34;&gt;Synopsis&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A young boy goes missing from his backyard, which Bobby works on. Johnny looks into a husband gone missing, and Connie works on a wife who vanished after shopping. In all three cases, the families declare that there&amp;rsquo;s nothing unsavory about their missing loved ones or themselves.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;connie-karadzic-review:d784d589dcf57a85e7530409bc1d46bd&#34;&gt;Connie Karadzic Review&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Connie brings in bagels instead of donuts, causing complaints from some of the other cops who aren&amp;rsquo;t as pleased about the health kick.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For the second episode in a row, Connie gets her own case, this time of a wife who never came home after going out for groceries, shortly after having a fight with her husband. Ray tells her to mark it up as voluntary, mere moments after chiding Johnny for making gross assumptions about &lt;em&gt;his&lt;/em&gt; case, a point that Connie brings up. In gushing over the contents of the wife&amp;rsquo;s closet, Connie determines she took neither her wallet nor keys, so she grills the husband about the fight. Asking the friends, Connie finds out that Charlene was supposed to contact her best friend in the morning, after being loaned $100, but she never did. Also, Charlene had cheated on her ex, and her husband John was always worried and jealous about that fact.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ray is still dismissive of Connie needing to do any work on the case, but she follows up and finds the car was used in the robbery of a convenience store the night before. The car has blood in it and has clearly been shot. The cops at the robbery thing Charlene was shot by the robber and carjacked. Since Connie has details about the woman, she fires up a search order in the area. They find Charlene, after Connie bullies the search patrol into keeping trying, and she&amp;rsquo;s alive, but badly injured.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;quotes:d784d589dcf57a85e7530409bc1d46bd&#34;&gt;Quotes&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Connie:&lt;/strong&gt; I can see her lying to her friends, but why would she lie to me?&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Ray:&lt;/strong&gt; You&amp;rsquo;re a cop, Connie. People don&amp;rsquo;t talk to cops, people lie to cops.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>