<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Transcript on Jorja Fox Library</title>
    <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/tags/transcript/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Transcript on Jorja Fox Library</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2013 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://jorjafox.net/library/tags/transcript/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>CableTV.com</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2013/cabletv-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2013/cabletv-1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Monica Gleberman&lt;/strong&gt; .. and just ask you, how did you get involved in acting to begin with?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; Oh my goodness. I wanted to act since I was probably four or five years old. I think that the television that sat in the living room of my house was one of the bigger influences in my life. It was definitely a babysitter for me. You know, I grew up in a small town, so there weren&amp;rsquo;t many acting programs. And it was high school before I was able to be in a drama class. I think there were two things that happened. First of all I love it so much, and then second of all, people were really supportive of me, and doing acting. I think I had a lot of support doing it, and so there was no doubt in my mind. I went to New York and got lucky. I got in [something] very quickly because I ignored all these signs that said &amp;ldquo;Do Not Enter.&amp;rdquo; [laughter] I didn&amp;rsquo;t have an agency, you know &amp;#8216;Don&amp;rsquo;t go beyond this point.&amp;rsquo; And I sort of ignored all of those signs that told me not to go further and landed up in an agency, and I was able to have a conversation with my agency and I had an audition, and they started sending me out. It was so processed. But definitely I started my career in New York and was there for probably seven years before ending up in Los Angeles.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Monica&lt;/strong&gt; I have followed your career, and of course I did research before this. You have had some major television show lucky jobs. Some of the biggest shows known to man. So I want to ask you, of course you were on ER, you were on The West Wing. What was it like- I know when you&amp;rsquo;re on it, you might not think &amp;#8216;This is huge&amp;rsquo; and might not realize how big it is. But looking back, reflecting back on your appearances, what does that feel like? To look back and note that you were on these two shows that are probably going down in history as some of the best television?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja&lt;/strong&gt; Oh wow. Thank you. I think it was huge at the time for me. &lt;em&gt;ER&lt;/em&gt; in particular because I started on &lt;em&gt;ER&lt;/em&gt; in season three and they were the number one show in the country and those numbers were bigger then what you see now because there was less television to choose from. And less appointment television. I don&amp;rsquo;t know if you remember, but people had to actually turn on the TV at the right time. VCR&amp;rsquo;s existed but even then, people wanted to a lot of the bigger shows live so they could talk about them the next day. So I was terrified. Even though I hadn’t watched ER, it was my mom’s favorite show and a lot of my friends favorite shows and I was absolutely terrified when I got the job because I felt like in a week or two&amp;rsquo;s time, everyone in America was going to know I was an impostor. That I was just claiming to be an actor and I was terrible. So I came really close to just driving to Mexico the week before I started and forgetting the whole thing. But I&amp;rsquo;m glad I didn&amp;rsquo;t. I always felt it was a pretty incredible learning experience, to get to spend time with that caliber of people every day, writers and actors and BPs(?) and directors.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And absolutely the same goes for &lt;em&gt;West Wing&lt;/em&gt;. I think &lt;em&gt;West Wing&lt;/em&gt;&amp;hellip; I was a huge fan then, of Sorkin, and &lt;em&gt;ER&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;West Wing&lt;/em&gt; had a number of the same producers. I think the thing that surprised me the most for myself was I could get to be a part of telling a wonderful story like that. It was something that I hadn&amp;rsquo;t even dreamed of. I just felt like it was such an honor to get to try and tell that story. I really like looked after Martin Sheen&amp;rsquo;s daughter. I couldn&amp;rsquo;t believe it! I got to do something like that! I think that Sorkin, he said at the time on &lt;em&gt;West Wing&lt;/em&gt;, he&amp;rsquo;s alone, and there had been very few women Secret Service Agents at that time, that had actually been on screen. Even getting to be that, getting to be this female Secret Service Agent was kind of a lot of fun that people hadn&amp;rsquo;t gotten to do.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Monica&lt;/strong&gt; And I know, obviously, you&amp;rsquo;ve done a ton of movies and other TV shows, and then you land &lt;em&gt;CSI&lt;/em&gt;. Which, again, another- it&amp;rsquo;s like crazy, your career, because it&amp;rsquo;s another huge show! So I want to go back to Season one, and what that was like, finding out you&amp;rsquo;re going to be playing Sara, and where your mind was when you got that call.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja&lt;/strong&gt; Um. That was also a big surprise. I really didn’t think that &lt;em&gt;CSI&lt;/em&gt; was going to be successful. I fell in love with the story and the idea of it. Again, at the time it was something that was pretty different and something that I hadn’t really read about often. You know, &lt;em&gt;Quincy&lt;/em&gt; was sort of the thing that I could think of that sort of reminded me a little of &lt;em&gt;CSI&lt;/em&gt;. And I thought nobody was really going to watch a show about death on a Friday night, that is just kind of not a really American culture thing to do. I was so wrong about that. I really thought I would do &lt;em&gt;CSI&lt;/em&gt;, have some fun and be back on &lt;em&gt;The West Wing&lt;/em&gt; by Christmas. You know, that&amp;rsquo;s what I thought was going to happen! I thought the show was going to get canceled and here I am thirteen years later. And it was just this monster. Not &amp;#8212; I guess monster&amp;rsquo;s kind of &amp;#8212; this behemoth that none of us expected. I think that nobody could have imagined how big the ride was going to get.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And thank you for saying that! I&amp;rsquo;m actually starting my eighteenth consecutive season in a row on Prime Time television. It&amp;rsquo;s big for me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Monica&lt;/strong&gt; I know! It&amp;rsquo;s crazy!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja&lt;/strong&gt; So thanks for talking about that stuff.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Monica&lt;/strong&gt; I want to ask- so were you surprised &amp;#8212; before we get into Sara and where she&amp;rsquo;s gone over the course of- and now we&amp;rsquo;re in- there&amp;rsquo;s gonna be a fourteenth season. I want to ask you, I know that in 2007 you had announced that you were leaving the show. Were you surprised at how many fans freaked out and started sending in gifts and money and started a campaign to try to keep you on &lt;em&gt;CSI&lt;/em&gt;? Was that shocking to you at how many people cared about this character?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja&lt;/strong&gt; Absolutely. Yes. Absolutely. It was one of the most magnificent experiences. I had no idea there would be that kind of a response. Truthfully, that was my season twelve in a row, and I was tired. I was just thinking &amp;#8216;Oh my god, I just need to lie down for a minute.&amp;rsquo; I just needed to kind of sit down and reground. So I wanted to get off-screen before it started to show on screen, or before my coworkers started to notice. It was an amazing show of support, and I wished I could have changed my mind to show the fans the amount of gratitude I had for them suggesting that I stay. Honestly, if I wasn&amp;rsquo;t so exhausted, I absolutely would have. So yeah, it was an amazing feeling of surprise.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Monica&lt;/strong&gt; So now that you&amp;rsquo;re back, and you&amp;rsquo;ve been back for a while, everyone&amp;rsquo;s been super excited. I want to know from you how has Sara changed from season one, I know she&amp;rsquo;s had a lot of life changes with the proposal and getting married, but how has she changed from season one to season thirteen?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja&lt;/strong&gt; It&amp;rsquo;s funny. I think in some ways she really hasn’t changed that much [laughs]. There&amp;rsquo;s been some &lt;em&gt;seemingly&lt;/em&gt; big changes. When we met Sara in 2000, if anything I think she was very much a product of her past and of her history and the things she experienced as a young kid. You know, her mother killed her father and she was in foster care for a period of time. I think that she had this drive to be a CSI that definitely stems from her experiences as a kid. I think when she left in season 7, and was gone most of season 8, she had a chance to really wrestle those demons and maybe not feel like she is controlled by her past anymore. She kind of cleared all of the ghosts out for herself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And yet, here we are in season thirteen and I feel like we have a very mature character, who is just as passionate about the cases and just as invested, but is somehow free of her history and that is kind of the way I&amp;rsquo;ve been playing the character for the last couple of season. And yet at the same time, now we are in season fourteen, I do feel that Sara- there is this compulsive drive, something very deep rooted. She can&amp;rsquo;t stop being a CSI, it&amp;rsquo;s what fuels her, maybe the duration of her life, she&amp;rsquo;s going to be there in the trenches, on the street, in the muck, in the darkness, trying to get justice for people. I&amp;rsquo;m looking at it again, myself, and like &amp;ldquo;huh!&amp;rdquo; I thought the compulsive side of her was finished, and now maybe it&amp;rsquo;s not, not at all. Maybe she&amp;rsquo;s just the same.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Monica&lt;/strong&gt; What can fans look forward to this season? What kind of cases? What are you guys going to get involved with, cause there&amp;rsquo;s always a craziness happening every episode. So what can fans expect this season for the upcoming episodes?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja&lt;/strong&gt; I think so far &amp;#8212; we are in the middle of episode 7 and I&amp;rsquo;ve seen the script for eight, and I think we have an amazing season opening up. Really exciting. We have some incredible guest stars including somebody like… oh you know what I don’t know if I could say cause I don&amp;rsquo;t know if I&amp;rsquo;m a spoiler alert. [laughs] We have some really interesting guest stars and a cooking show in episode four that is kind of based on these food contests on the food networks. There is funny stuff, there is haunting stuff — I think the writers this year again, they suggested to me, they like to pick a theme every season, and this one is definitely going to be about darkness and going darker and going deeper.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s going to be a darker season of &lt;em&gt;CSI&lt;/em&gt;, but within that also there&amp;rsquo;s going to be as much character stuff as there was last year. I think they&amp;rsquo;re continuing to write a lot of character stuff, which is great. Certainly we start the season with Morgan in jeopardy, the stakes are really high. We also start the season with a funeral and it’s not really until we get to the end of the show that you, the audience, will come to find out why we&amp;rsquo;re at the funeral and who has passed. It’s a very compelling kind of suspenseful episode.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You know, yeah it gets crazier every year. I don&amp;rsquo;t know how the writers come up with stuff in season fourteen. The unfortunate thing is there&amp;rsquo;s no shortage of crazy crime in America to draw from. But the stakes continue to get higher, and I hope the fans will continue to enjoy that. I always am partial to the action/adventure show. And so in those episodes where we get a little kooky, hopefully the fans will still be able to roll with us.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Monica&lt;/strong&gt; I wanted to ask you, was it nice that all current cast members continued on for season fourteen?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja&lt;/strong&gt; Absolutely! Because we have had so many changes. You know, part of me, you were speaking about &lt;em&gt;ER&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;ER&lt;/em&gt; began to lose their core cast members in season three. So the fact that our show made it to season seven with the core cast intact, I think is a testament to the show and a compliment to how much we actually did get along and liked working together and did like the work itself. I think very few shows have gone seven seasons retaining their full original cast.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But yes, it&amp;rsquo;s been really nice to have a cast that&amp;rsquo;s been able to stay together for a couple of seasons. You can&amp;rsquo;t fake chemistry. You&amp;rsquo;ve sort of got to build it organically. The more you know each other, the more you work together, the deeper you can go. It&amp;rsquo;s given a chance for that. I think it&amp;rsquo;s been kind of a really great thing for the writers, because there were a lot of seasons where it was really hard for them to start breaking stories over the summer, because they weren&amp;rsquo;t completely sure who their cast was going to be. Knowing early enough that they were going to have everyone has allowed them to spread their wings more than they could for a bunch of season.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This team, this troupe of actors, you never think that &amp;#8216;Wow, three new actors in practically one season. This is definitely- this can&amp;rsquo;t go well. This is going to be difficult.&amp;rsquo; And to love these three actors as much as I do, as much as we all do, we&amp;rsquo;re having so much fun every day. I hope it shows on screen. As usual, I&amp;rsquo;m just grateful I get to come here and hang out, because it&amp;rsquo;s a really fun place to be.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Monica&lt;/strong&gt; Of course I have to ask too, season fourteen, will mark the 300th episode, which is like, nuts. So what is that? What have you guys, I think it&amp;rsquo;s like mid-season, right? The 300th?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja&lt;/strong&gt; The 300th? Episode five. We&amp;rsquo;re pretty soon, like pretty pretty soon. We&amp;rsquo;re going to do ten new shows in a row. I don&amp;rsquo;t think we&amp;rsquo;ve done that before. And so, yeah, I think five weeks after the premiere tomorrow, you&amp;rsquo;ll be able to see the 300th episode.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Monica&lt;/strong&gt; So what is that like? Being a part of &amp;hellip; I feel like a lot of this interview is about you being a part of these crazy, amazing, genius shows. And not only do you have this awesome career, but you&amp;rsquo;re a part of another benchmark, which is the 300th episode. So what is that like, being a part of?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja&lt;/strong&gt; It was such an honor for me. You know, it is a milestone. I didn&amp;rsquo;t think much about it going in, but then we all showed up for work the first day, and a couple people gave speeches, and I started to feel the gravity of it all. I think it&amp;rsquo;s been a great second chance for me. I missed the 200th episode, I wasn&amp;rsquo;t here. I was here for the 100th episode. And to get to be a part of the 300th episode meant a lot to me. More than I even imagined it would. I haven&amp;rsquo;t done 300 episodes yet, I&amp;rsquo;m behind several members of the cast because I did take that season off, and I don&amp;rsquo;t appear in every episode every year. I think with my combined with my &lt;em&gt;ER&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;West Wing&lt;/em&gt; I might be on episode 296 or something. I can share that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s funny, because &lt;em&gt;ER&lt;/em&gt; went 300 episodes, and Marg Helgenberger, George Eads and myself had all had parts on &lt;em&gt;ER&lt;/em&gt;, so with another show that the three of us can be happy for and be a part of this tiny piece of &lt;em&gt;ER&lt;/em&gt; history. Of course, the history that we have on &lt;em&gt;CSI&lt;/em&gt; is a lot deeper and bigger. It&amp;rsquo;s really cool. I don&amp;rsquo;t think it&amp;rsquo;s ever going to happen to me again, to be a part of something like this. I don&amp;rsquo;t know if it&amp;rsquo;s going to be possible for a lot of shows to get to do this. Most shows are doing 13 episodes a year instead of 24, which is what we started out with. It takes a long time doing 13 episodes a season to get to 300 episodes. I think this is kind of a marker we may not see that much of in the future. It meant a lot and I&amp;rsquo;m really proud of- for everyone. I&amp;rsquo;m really proud of everyone and just very excited to get to be a part of it. It&amp;rsquo;s cool.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Monica&lt;/strong&gt; I want to ask, and I know it could be a little spoiler, but in the 300th episode, I&amp;rsquo;ve heard rumors there might be some flash backs? Is that&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja&lt;/strong&gt; Ah yes. Flashbacks slash faux-backs. [laughs] That&amp;rsquo;s what we&amp;rsquo;re calling them. We did out best. It has been thirteen years. [laughs] Thirteen meaningful years. But it was truly fun and embarrassing and silly to try and do it- I hope we pulled it off. I hope the fans enjoy it. There&amp;rsquo;s- You know it&amp;rsquo;s not a huge chunk of the show, but three flashbacks. Four I think! We go back to 2000. There&amp;rsquo;s some funny clothes, and funny hairstyles. I threw in a wig. And it&amp;rsquo;s great. We do, we&amp;rsquo;re- the episode is really about a cold case from 2000, that has certainly haunted Sara for the last thirteen years. And I think it, within the show, Sara feels a certain exuberance at having a second chance at a case she thought had really slipped through her fingers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So not only did I get a second chance to be a part of something so exciting, but she&amp;rsquo;s getting a second chance to really try and find justice for somebody who&amp;rsquo;s living a nightmare several times.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Monica&lt;/strong&gt; Is there anything else you want to tell to the fans who are super excited &amp;#8212; they&amp;rsquo;re counting down the hours to the premiere. Is there anything you want to say to them? Anything about the season or just in general that you want them to know?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja&lt;/strong&gt; I think yes. I wanna say to all the fans of CSI, thank you so much! Thank you thank you thank you thank you for your support all these years. We are continually surprised and completely elated that we get ratings every years, that we continue to get to be on this show and do these things, that&amp;rsquo;s all because of you. Thank you for your loyalty and your willingness to go on some really crazy rides with us. I hope this year we don&amp;rsquo;t disappoint you and we&amp;rsquo;re really excited to show you what we have coming up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Monica&lt;/strong&gt; Okay! Great! Those were all my questions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja&lt;/strong&gt; Thank you so much, Monica, it was great speaking with you.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ADI Jorja Fox Addresses Congress</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2011/adi-addresses-congress/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2011/adi-addresses-congress/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I do think that a question that some of you may be asking right now is &amp;ldquo;Well what about my kids? Can&amp;rsquo;t my kids have the same chance I did to go to these traveling circuses?&amp;rdquo; Or maybe these circuses your parents went to. And I thought about this at length, and I think the truth is that our kids look to us for what is right, and our kids look to us for what is fun.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And I think we can do more for our kids if we do the compassionate thing, the respectful thing. These animals do deserve our kindness, and they do deserve our respect. And I think that often our kids understand that better than us most of the time/&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If our kids knew how cruel and violent these events were, I think they&amp;rsquo;d be very disappointed in us, for bringing us to these places.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This bill is the right thing to do, and I urge you to let your congresspeople know that you support it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank you very much.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KPIX - Rescued Lions from Bolivia Arrive at SFO (27 May 2010)</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2010/kpix-rescued-lions-from-bolivia-arrive-at-sfo/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 May 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2010/kpix-rescued-lions-from-bolivia-arrive-at-sfo/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Don Knapp&lt;/strong&gt; And along for the trip tonight was Jorja Fox, of &lt;em&gt;CSI&lt;/em&gt;, she&amp;rsquo;s lending her celebrity and her back.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; I know I am, I&amp;rsquo;m sure all of us are very concerned about everything that&amp;rsquo;s going on in the gulf. The news is so bad, so devastating, and this is just a very small moment where we can look at ourselves as people and say, &amp;ldquo;You know, we&amp;rsquo;re doing something good.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CSI season 7 DVD extras</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2007/csi-season-7-dvd-extras/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jul 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2007/csi-season-7-dvd-extras/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;ldquo;(on Billy Petersen leaving the show for four weeks in November of 2006)&amp;rdquo; I wasn&amp;rsquo;t disappointed at all, I think, you know, obviously as I met Billy he had come almost directly out of this excitement of theater he was doing in Chicago and he&amp;rsquo;s very famous for that theater that he&amp;rsquo;s done. I think that it&amp;rsquo;s been the heart of his work over the time of his career, he&amp;rsquo;s done some films that are ground-breaking and memorable and everybody, those, that&amp;rsquo;s probably the way that the most people know Billy Petersen, but I think that people who know Billy Petersen &amp;ldquo;know&amp;rdquo; that his heart and his soul has always been in the theater, so, and it&amp;rsquo;s almost as if in a sense odd that it took him six years to find his way into one, you know, and I think that it&amp;rsquo;s a testament to the show, how much &amp;ldquo;CSI:&amp;rdquo; has all this passion that he hasn&amp;rsquo;t felt like he could go do a play at the same time. Cause he&amp;rsquo;s also fairly multi-faceted, much more so than I am and I think some of us are on the show.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; From the very beginning of the inception of my character coming on to the pro- the show of &amp;ldquo;CSI:&amp;rdquo; and them deciding to add this character, there&amp;rsquo;s this little piece of paper that you get when you go to audition for these roles, and, and , I think the first sentence said &amp;#8216;love interest for Grissom&amp;rsquo;. So from like day one of me kind of going for the audition this was a story that hung there in the ethers and then, you know, as we started to go into season 1 and season 2 and started to realize that we were going to have a season 3 I think there was interest on everybody&amp;rsquo;s part not to, so to speak, &amp;#8216;blow our wad&amp;rsquo; too soon, you know &amp;ldquo;(laughs)&amp;rdquo;. You tell this story then where do you go from there and it could be, you know, if we were lucky enough which it &amp;ldquo;seemed&amp;rdquo; might be happening, there&amp;rsquo;d be years of awkwardness after the break-up or stuff that you know &amp;ldquo;(laughs)&amp;rdquo; we didn&amp;rsquo;t want to play for three seasons. So I think that it, it was kind of wise to hold back on it and, and then we got to a point where we thought that maybe the fans were not interested in it any more.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;ldquo;(voiceover)&amp;rdquo; We&amp;rsquo;d already begun shooting the last episode of season 6, the script had been out, there was an ending set, and I got a call from Carol Mendelsohn suggesting &amp;lsquo;hey, what do you think about this and would you want to do this&amp;rsquo; and is this interesting to you. Which is also something that&amp;rsquo;s great about this show and I think very unique is I don&amp;rsquo;t know how often actors get those calls. I was shocked, very surprised, and, and, and very very intrigued. I thought it could make season 7 extremely interesting for my character and certainly a storyline that I had always been gearing up to play and wanted to play, and I&amp;rsquo;ve always loved the dynamic between Grissom and Sara, I love that it&amp;rsquo;s a &amp;ldquo;little&amp;rdquo; bit sort of scandalous, it&amp;rsquo;s untraditional in, in a couple of respects, and I love those kinds of love stories. So&amp;hellip; I was thrilled.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; It&amp;rsquo;s a complete and utter shock and surprise. First of all I can&amp;rsquo;t believe it&amp;rsquo;s been seven years. One of the reasons I &amp;ldquo;hate&amp;rdquo; doing interviews like this is &amp;lsquo;cause I&amp;rsquo;m reminded that it&amp;rsquo;s been seven years, &amp;ldquo;(laughs)&amp;rdquo; because it doesn&amp;rsquo;t feel like seven years. It&amp;rsquo;s like &amp;#8216;yeah, a couple of years&amp;rsquo;, you know, it&amp;rsquo;s the coolest thing ever, I never could have even wished for this, to be a part of a show this long and never would have expected that it would ever happen and I can&amp;rsquo;t believe that it has, in many respects, we still have a gazillion cool stories left to tell. So&amp;hellip; yeah, it&amp;rsquo;s pretty weird.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PETA Vegetarian Thanksgiving</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2006/peta-vegetarian-thanksgiving/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2006/peta-vegetarian-thanksgiving/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; One of the most amazing things about today, not only is the food gonna be way better than it ever is at my place &amp;ldquo;(laughs)&amp;rdquo;, and, and, and, far more beautifully prepared, uh, I don&amp;rsquo;t have to cook or do any dishes I don&amp;rsquo;t think - maybe I do, but nobody&amp;rsquo;s told me yet so that&amp;rsquo;d be really fun. &amp;ldquo;(laughs)&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; What a better way to spend this holiday that we really sorta celebrate peace and in a really peaceful way eating vegetarian.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;ldquo;(Jorja is holding a turkey in her lap)&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Off-camera voice&lt;/strong&gt; That&amp;rsquo;s nice.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; You wanna hold her?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Off-camera voice&lt;/strong&gt; I think that you&amp;rsquo;re it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; Okay. &amp;ldquo;(off-camera laughter)&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Off-camera voice&lt;/strong&gt; When you&amp;rsquo;re ready.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; Turkey holding duty. Okay. She&amp;rsquo;s pretty cool.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PETA Gala and Humanitarian Awards</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2005/peta-gala-and-humanitarian-awards/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Sep 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2005/peta-gala-and-humanitarian-awards/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; I&amp;rsquo;ve been a vegetarian since I was nineteen. I come from like a French-Canadian family who ate meat and potatoes every day, three times a day for my entire youth, and I used to tease the heck out of my friends that were vegetarians, and I had a lot of &amp;lsquo;em, and then when I became a vegetarian I just decided that I was going to try and learn as much I could so that when people teased me, maybe I&amp;rsquo;d have a couple of things to say. So PETA very quickly in New York City was an organization that I&amp;rsquo;d heard about, and I read about, and I started going to rallies, and demonstrations, and protests. Um, and I&amp;rsquo;ve been a huge supporter and fan of ever since, y&amp;rsquo;know, you guys rock and I think, you know, you, you do it in such a sort of an alternatively exciting, and fresh, and, um, confrontational way, and that&amp;rsquo;s awesome.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; Hi, I&amp;rsquo;m Jorja Fox, I&amp;rsquo;m an actor, I&amp;rsquo;m a guitar player, I&amp;rsquo;m a surfer, uh, I&amp;rsquo;m a sister and a daughter, and I am a vegetarian.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;VegTV&lt;/strong&gt; How long have you been involved with PETA?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; Well I&amp;rsquo;ve been a fan and supporter and rally-er from many many years, since I&amp;rsquo;ve been a vegetarian, so that&amp;rsquo;s like forty years ago, you know, fifty.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;VegTV&lt;/strong&gt; You haven&amp;rsquo;t been a vegetarian for forty years, you haven&amp;rsquo;t been on this planet for forty years. &amp;ldquo;(Jorja laughs)&amp;rdquo; How long have you been a vegetarian?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; Uh, you&amp;rsquo;re gonna laugh, um, I&amp;rsquo;d say six- eighteen years, yeah.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;VegTV&lt;/strong&gt; Most of your life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; Yeah, yeah, since I was a teenager or so, there you go.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;VegTV&lt;/strong&gt; What was the epiphany, what, what was it made you become vegetarian?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; Y&amp;rsquo;know, it was a meatball sandwich in Brooklyn one afternoon and I don&amp;rsquo;t know what it was about it, but y&amp;rsquo;know I, those little moments, I had friends, and people I&amp;rsquo;d gone out with who were vegetarians and bands that I liked that were vegetarian, Morrisey&amp;rsquo;s here tonight, I&amp;rsquo;m very excited to see them, and uh, and it just kinda all came together over a meatball hero in Brooklyn one day and that was that. And then I was really that person who would tease those people quite a bit, you know, the type of person that&amp;rsquo;d be &amp;#8216;oh, y&amp;rsquo;know, well vegetables are alive too and you&amp;rsquo;re killing vegetables if you eat them&amp;rsquo;, and so I decided to get as educated as I could, cause I, I, you know, didn&amp;rsquo;t want to get the same teasing back at me after I was a vegetarian, so I found PETA very quickly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;VegTV&lt;/strong&gt; Would you do one of those ads for PETA, would you take off your clothes?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; Go naked? Maybe. I might, yeah. I haven&amp;rsquo;t been naked yet actually, so I might. I wouldn&amp;rsquo;t look good enough, but I&amp;rsquo;ll do it, yeah. &amp;ldquo;(laughs)&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;VegTV&lt;/strong&gt; Anything new, anything upcoming for you?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; Um, we got a bunch of CSI coming out, and it&amp;rsquo;s all very horrible, and there&amp;rsquo;s lots of dead people, and we&amp;rsquo;re excited. I have a little play I&amp;rsquo;m producing that&amp;rsquo;s going to London in March 2006.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;VegTV&lt;/strong&gt; What&amp;rsquo;s the play about?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; Uh, it&amp;rsquo;s the story, it&amp;rsquo;s actually based on a true story of a young woman from a small town in England that comes to America in the late sixties to follow her dreams, so it&amp;rsquo;s very, yeah, takes advantage of New York City in the early seventies; it&amp;rsquo;s a good story, lotta heart.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;VegTV&lt;/strong&gt; Anywhere we can follow that? Is it on the Internet?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; Uh, yeah, &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.dearbernard.com/&#34;&gt;dearbernard.com&lt;/a&gt;, it&amp;rsquo;s on the Internet, it&amp;rsquo;s a full length original musical, so we&amp;rsquo;ll see. We put it up in L.A. last year, and we&amp;rsquo;re taking, slowly getting to London in March.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CSI Season 5 DVD extras</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2005/csi-season-5-dvd-extras/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2005/csi-season-5-dvd-extras/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; All bets are off, and on at the same time. Anything can happen to anybody, there&amp;rsquo;s lines that have been drawn, and uh, it does make it really fascinating.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; It, we&amp;rsquo;re split almost down the middle, 50 percent of the people who watch &amp;ldquo;CSI:&amp;rdquo; want more character stuff, and 50 percent of the people who watch the show don&amp;rsquo;t want that much of it, they really like the stories and the science. So the writers are sort of always letting down somebody, and I think that they&amp;rsquo;ve done a really good job of, of just deciding to follow their hearts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; I knew probably by season 3 that the writers thought there might be something personal in Sara&amp;rsquo;s past that, uh, really prompted her to go into this line of work, but, uh, had no idea what that might be.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; I was hoping, &amp;#8216;wow, I was hoping we can pull this off in a way that it&amp;rsquo;s good&amp;rsquo; and it&amp;rsquo;s dark and it&amp;rsquo;s funny but you also don&amp;rsquo;t end up making somebody, you know, sort of seem like the exhibit at the zoo or something like that, and I think Richard Lewis {director} pulled that off brilliantly.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Ellen Degeneres Show</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2004/the-ellen-degeneres-show/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 May 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2004/the-ellen-degeneres-show/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ellen DeGeneres&lt;/strong&gt; Our next guest is a star of the popular forensic drama, CSI. Watch her at work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ellen&lt;/strong&gt; Please welcome, Jorja Fox!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ellen&lt;/strong&gt; Hi!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; Hi! I brought you something.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ellen&lt;/strong&gt; Merci.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja&lt;/strong&gt; Oh, great.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ellen&lt;/strong&gt; Merci beaucoup.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja&lt;/strong&gt; That&amp;rsquo;s all I know.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ellen&lt;/strong&gt; What does that mean, what is this?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja&lt;/strong&gt; Well I know you&amp;rsquo;ve been studying a little French on the show, and so I thought these might help; they&amp;rsquo;re French art deco cosmetic labels. You just put &amp;lsquo;em on all the products in your bathroom, &amp;ndash;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ellen&lt;/strong&gt; Really?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;ndash; and they&amp;rsquo;re French then.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ellen&lt;/strong&gt; Lotion vegetale.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja&lt;/strong&gt; Yeah. And it&amp;rsquo;ll help, you know, with the French thing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ellen&lt;/strong&gt; What is &amp;#8216;vegetale&amp;rsquo;?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja&lt;/strong&gt; Umm&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ellen&lt;/strong&gt; You don&amp;rsquo;t know.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja&lt;/strong&gt; I don&amp;rsquo;t really speak French, no, but I, uh&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ellen&lt;/strong&gt; That&amp;rsquo;s a clever thing, to put stickers on things so you know what it is. I don&amp;rsquo;t, it&amp;rsquo;s not, the problem is the accent really. It&amp;rsquo;s, it&amp;rsquo;s I &amp;ndash;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja&lt;/strong&gt; Ah.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ellen&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;ndash; That&amp;rsquo;s my problem.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja&lt;/strong&gt; Right.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ellen&lt;/strong&gt; It&amp;rsquo;s not so much that I can&amp;rsquo;t read &amp;ndash;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja&lt;/strong&gt; Oh, the &amp;#8216;rrrrrrrrrr.&amp;rsquo; Can you do that?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ellen&lt;/strong&gt; Yeah.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;#8216;Rrrrrrr.&amp;rsquo; You know the French thing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ellen&lt;/strong&gt; If I wanted to I could, yeah.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;ndash; where you roll the &amp;#8216;r&amp;rsquo; thing, ya.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ellen&lt;/strong&gt; Yeah. I don&amp;rsquo;t, I don&amp;rsquo;t think they do that. That, you&amp;rsquo;re thinking of Charo, I think.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja&lt;/strong&gt; Is that another language? Alright!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ellen&lt;/strong&gt; No one does &amp;#8216;rrrrrrrr&amp;rsquo;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja&lt;/strong&gt; I&amp;rsquo;m terrible at languages.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ellen&lt;/strong&gt; No, they do a &amp;#8216;gaaaak&amp;rsquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja&lt;/strong&gt; I think it&amp;rsquo;s a &amp;#8216;rrrrrrrrr&amp;rsquo;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ellen&lt;/strong&gt; A &amp;#8216;rrrrrr&amp;rsquo;?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;#8216;Rrrrrrrrr&amp;rsquo;. Yeah, like &amp;ndash;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ellen&lt;/strong&gt; Like what word has &amp;#8216;rrrrrrrr&amp;rsquo; in it?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja&lt;/strong&gt; Farah. Faragh?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ellen&lt;/strong&gt; Grrrrraaa&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja&lt;/strong&gt; Yeah. Something like that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ellen&lt;/strong&gt; All right. No that&amp;rsquo;s not why, that&amp;rsquo;s probably why I don&amp;rsquo;t speak it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja&lt;/strong&gt; I speak English okay.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ellen&lt;/strong&gt; Yeah, I, um &amp;ndash;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja&lt;/strong&gt; That&amp;rsquo;s about it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ellen&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;ndash; I&amp;rsquo;m barely mastering that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;ldquo;(laughing)&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ellen&lt;/strong&gt; But, but good to see you and I haven&amp;rsquo;t seen you in a long time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja&lt;/strong&gt; A long time. Y&amp;rsquo;know I&amp;rsquo;ve been wanting to tell you, and I, and I, we&amp;rsquo;ve crossed paths several times &amp;ndash;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ellen&lt;/strong&gt; Mmm-hmm.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;ndash; not for a while, and when I first moved to Los Angeles like 8 or 9 years ago - well maybe we won&amp;rsquo;t get into that exactly how long ago - but one of the first things that I ever did, and I know that you won&amp;rsquo;t remember this, was I was invited to Ellen DeGeneres&amp;rsquo; birthday party. And of course we didn&amp;rsquo;t know each other and you &amp;ndash;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ellen&lt;/strong&gt; No. How were you invited?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja&lt;/strong&gt; Y&amp;rsquo;know, I knew the uh, y&amp;rsquo;know, the coat check guy &amp;ndash;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ellen&lt;/strong&gt; Oh.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;ndash; really well &amp;ndash;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ellen&lt;/strong&gt; Ah.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;ndash; yeah, at the Chateau Marmonde, from New York.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ellen&lt;/strong&gt; Slip him a twenty?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja&lt;/strong&gt; Yeah, yeah, y&amp;rsquo;know because I bartended there and &amp;ndash;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ellen&lt;/strong&gt; Uh-huh.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;ndash; Yeah. No, mutual friends invited and it was like, it was so huge and I was like fresh from New York City, very excited, here I was in Hollywood, and the first place that I, that I was invited to go to was your party and you were actually very nice to me, I mean until that thing happened in the parking lot&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ellen&lt;/strong&gt; Uh-huh.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja&lt;/strong&gt; And uh, and uh, I haven&amp;rsquo;t been to any of your birthday parties since, but &amp;ndash;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ellen&lt;/strong&gt; Uh-huh.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;ndash; but it was great, and I remember it, y&amp;rsquo;know I cherish that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ellen&lt;/strong&gt; Yeah, I uh, that was a great party wasn&amp;rsquo;t it?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja&lt;/strong&gt; Yeah, Chateau Marmonde, do you, yeah&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ellen&lt;/strong&gt; Yes, oh I remember that party.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja&lt;/strong&gt; Like swanky soiree.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ellen&lt;/strong&gt; Yeah. You have one of these parties that you try to top every year and you just know, it was one of those magical nights that it was so, so cool and people showed up that, I had no idea who a lot of the people were.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja&lt;/strong&gt; Yeah, yeah.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ellen&lt;/strong&gt; People like you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja&lt;/strong&gt; Yeah.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ellen&lt;/strong&gt; But it was fun.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja&lt;/strong&gt; Right.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ellen&lt;/strong&gt; And what did you bring me? What kind of gift?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja&lt;/strong&gt; A gift? Um, y&amp;rsquo;know I um, I do not &amp;ndash;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ellen&lt;/strong&gt; Perhaps that&amp;rsquo;s why you &amp;ndash;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;ndash; it really wasn&amp;rsquo;t that kind of party I don&amp;rsquo;t think.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ellen&lt;/strong&gt; No, well they say it&amp;rsquo;s not kind but you still bring a gift.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja&lt;/strong&gt; I remember, I distinctly remember, yeah, &amp;#8216;no gifts&amp;rsquo;, no gifts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ellen&lt;/strong&gt; Well I &amp;ndash;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja&lt;/strong&gt; In capital letters but I&amp;rsquo;m making up for it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ellen&lt;/strong&gt; Well when people say that you still have to bring a gift. That&amp;rsquo;s, that&amp;rsquo;s why you&amp;rsquo;ve not been invited back.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja&lt;/strong&gt; I, I don&amp;rsquo;t think you&amp;rsquo;re uh&amp;hellip; Right. You didn&amp;rsquo;t get as much for those as, as you did for the watch, but maybe, y&amp;rsquo;know &amp;ndash;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ellen&lt;/strong&gt; And I appreciate this.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;ndash; something will come of that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ellen&lt;/strong&gt; And I&amp;rsquo;ll look through &amp;lsquo;em and maybe say some things later. Um, all right, so uh, so now you&amp;rsquo;ve been here for how long? Nine years?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja&lt;/strong&gt; Yeah, I think almost nine years.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ellen&lt;/strong&gt; And, and where are you living, what area?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja&lt;/strong&gt; Ah, y&amp;rsquo;know I&amp;rsquo;m living in Hollywood, I just got a new place &amp;ndash;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ellen&lt;/strong&gt; Mmm-hmm.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;ndash; new house, I&amp;rsquo;m sleeping on the kitchen, on an air mattress with my dog, and uh &amp;ndash;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ellen&lt;/strong&gt; That&amp;rsquo;s not a good house.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja&lt;/strong&gt; Well, it&amp;rsquo;s, it&amp;rsquo;s a big empty house. Y&amp;rsquo;know it&amp;rsquo;s funny, I got my dog, I went out &amp;ndash;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ellen&lt;/strong&gt; But why, why are you in the kitchen though?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja&lt;/strong&gt; They&amp;rsquo;ve been doing some work in the other, in the rest of the house, in the bedrooms and stuff.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ellen&lt;/strong&gt; On all the rest of the house? The only thing you&amp;rsquo;re not doing work on is the kitchen?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja&lt;/strong&gt; Yeah, yeah kind of, yeah. Yeah, and I was on friend&amp;rsquo;s couches for a couple of weeks, and that was really fun, and everybody was really gracious, and &amp;ndash;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ellen&lt;/strong&gt; Uh-huh.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;ndash; then I kinda ran out of places to stay so &amp;ndash;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ellen&lt;/strong&gt; Right.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;ndash; now I&amp;rsquo;m in the kitchen.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ellen&lt;/strong&gt; Okay, so and, and when is the work going to be done?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja&lt;/strong&gt; I think, y&amp;rsquo;know they keep saying y&amp;rsquo;know, &amp;#8216;any day&amp;rsquo; &amp;ndash;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ellen&lt;/strong&gt; Oh.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;ndash; y&amp;rsquo;know, &amp;lsquo;tomorrow, tomorrow&amp;rsquo;&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ellen&lt;/strong&gt; Oh&amp;hellip; whatever they say, don&amp;rsquo;t believe &amp;lsquo;em.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja&lt;/strong&gt; Yeah.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ellen&lt;/strong&gt; That&amp;rsquo;s uh, that&amp;rsquo;s, that&amp;rsquo;s, oh, work is&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja&lt;/strong&gt; You know of any good hotels, actually? In the L.A. area?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ellen&lt;/strong&gt; Sure - Chateau Marmonde.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;ldquo;(laughs)&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ellen&lt;/strong&gt; That&amp;rsquo;s a good hotel. All right, so the season finale of &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; is uh, on Thursday at nine o&amp;rsquo;clock on CBS, and everybody in the audience is getting, uh, a copy of the third season on DVD. That&amp;rsquo;s right. Oh, they&amp;rsquo;re happy. The big finish is next, don&amp;rsquo;t go away.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CSI Season 3 DVD extras</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2003/CSI_Season_3_Dvd_Extras_%282003%29/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2003/CSI_Season_3_Dvd_Extras_%282003%29/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;crash-and-burn:bc34ae24366084c3a1c1117294a3d832&#34;&gt;Crash and Burn&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; You know, Sara Sidle had a very dark year in season 3; she had a tough one, she really had a tough one. It really started, uh, I would say, in January, about midway through the season. Ah, the first thing that happens is, is, a very good friend of hers betrays her very personally. And the next time we see Sara, her boyfriend, it turns out, has a girlfriend and he also betrays her.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; And I think for her, you know, the type of person that she is and what she does for a living, she&amp;rsquo;s so sure that she knows the truth about everyone, and to find out that two people she was very very close to were, were lying to her all along is a pretty hard thing for her to digest. You know, just above and beyond the fact that these relationships both go sour but then &amp;#8216;wow, that somebody, she was fooled, she was tricked&amp;rsquo; by people she was close to. Then, ah, we see her again in another episode and the lab blows up and she, she walks away from the explosion, her and Greg Sanders get blown up together, and that was a very hard thing, I think for her, you know, personally, and, and the episode ends with-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;play-with-fire:bc34ae24366084c3a1c1117294a3d832&#34;&gt;Play With Fire&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;ndash; a pretty certain refusal from Grissom that anything will ever happen between the two of them, so, that was, that season 3 for Sara was &amp;ldquo;hard&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; [Director] Danny [Cannon] is fast, he&amp;rsquo;s like the lightning bolt director, and everybody loves, you know, just starting out with him they know that they&amp;rsquo;re gonna get, they&amp;rsquo;re gonna have a shorter day with him and that things are going to move very quickly and people really like that, you know, it&amp;rsquo;s, it&amp;rsquo;s, when you&amp;rsquo;re on show 12 and you&amp;rsquo;ve been working for five months the idea of having a short day is really good.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Guide Channel Insider</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2008/TV_Guide_Channel_Insider_%282003%29/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2008/TV_Guide_Channel_Insider_%282003%29/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; Wow, um. Thank you. I&amp;rsquo;m hearing that, people have been saying that. And that&amp;rsquo;s amazing, I think- You know, the other reason that I thought the show was going to flop was because it was about science. And I thought that was going to be a very hard thing to make to look fascinating and interesting and exciting to people. I thought it was very fascinating, like reading the script I had a tremendous amount of faith in the show and I just had no idea how we would pull it off. So if people responded in that kind of way where they actually maybe kind of might be more interested in science than they were, that&amp;rsquo;s a pretty cool thing. And science is great because it&amp;rsquo;s evolving every day, as well as technology and a lot of the computer stuff- A lot of the stuff we get to do on the show is groundbreaking technology and it&amp;rsquo;s going to continue to do that over the next maybe five to ten years, so it&amp;rsquo;s a great time to be telling these stories. There&amp;rsquo;s never an ending amount of new ideas and it&amp;rsquo;s probably a really good time for people to get into the field. It&amp;rsquo;s going to be interesting to see how many people will stick around, cause, you know, there&amp;rsquo;s certain things on TV that we can&amp;rsquo;t really share with the audience. Like the smell! &amp;ldquo;(laugh)&amp;rdquo; Some of the more horrible aspects of doing the job. So I&amp;rsquo;m interested to see what happens.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CSI season 2 DVD extras</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2002/csi-season-2-dvd-extras/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2002/csi-season-2-dvd-extras/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;ldquo;(shot of the characters viewing a &amp;lsquo;corpse&amp;rsquo;; Jorja walks away holding her stomach)&amp;rdquo; Uh. It&amp;rsquo;s too early. &amp;ldquo;(to &amp;lsquo;corpse&amp;rsquo;)&amp;rdquo; I mean, I&amp;rsquo;m sure you&amp;rsquo;re a really nice guy&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Early Show</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2002/the-early-show/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2002/the-early-show/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bryant Gumbel&lt;/strong&gt;: Although it now may seem hard to believe, it was just two years ago the hit drama &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; barely made it on to the primetime schedule. The show has since become a hit with an unusual look at forensic investigators who solve crimes with science.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bryant Gumbel&lt;/strong&gt; The stars of &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; are William Petersen, Marg Helgenberger, Gary Dourdan, Jorja Fox and Paul Guilfoyle. Good morning, everybody.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(EVERYONE): Good morning, Bryant.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bryant Gumbel&lt;/strong&gt; Show of hands. Who thought this show was gonna be a hit? &amp;ldquo;(Everyone but Jorja raises their hands.)&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bryant Gumbel&lt;/strong&gt; Oh, come on!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Gary Dourdan&lt;/strong&gt; It was the script. See, it was the material&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Marg Helgenberger&lt;/strong&gt; Absolutely. No doubt in my mind.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bryant Gumbel&lt;/strong&gt; Really?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Gary Dourdan&lt;/strong&gt; A hit. We knew it was gonna be good, but I think that no one expected it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;William Petersen&lt;/strong&gt; We didn&amp;rsquo;t know it was gonna be, you know, 25, 28 million people watching.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Marg Helgenberger&lt;/strong&gt; We didn&amp;rsquo;t think&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Paul Guilfoyle&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;ldquo;(jokingly)&amp;rdquo; And I think everything I do is gonna be a hit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bryant Gumbel&lt;/strong&gt; Well, it&amp;rsquo;s the one next to you &amp;ldquo;(pointing to Jorja)&amp;rdquo; that seems to be the good luck charm. I mean, regular on &amp;ldquo;[[ER]],&amp;rdquo; regular on &amp;ldquo;[[The West Wing|West Wing]],&amp;rdquo; regular on &amp;ldquo;CSI.&amp;rdquo; Sign you up in the making!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; Thank you. I didn&amp;rsquo;t think the show was gonna be a hit. I think I was the only one that didn&amp;rsquo;t. I had so much hope and faith and so much belief in &amp;ldquo;CSI,&amp;rdquo; but I really wasn&amp;rsquo;t quite sure we were gonna stay on the air, but I was really happy&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bryant Gumbel&lt;/strong&gt; Why not?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; Well, I think it was a hard pitch at first for a lot of people. We were last to go at everything. Last to get picked up, like you said. And talking about death and science.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;William Petersen&lt;/strong&gt; Hair fibers are a major element of the thing, and fingerprints. It was a question of how well we were gonna be able to translate that to the screen.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bryant Gumbel&lt;/strong&gt; Well, usually audiences are turned off by things that are about death, that are bloody, that are macabre. What are they responding to in this case?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Paul Guilfoyle&lt;/strong&gt; Well, I think that the professionalism of the people. I think all drama is about people and interaction and I think they&amp;rsquo;re really responding to all of us as a group. However we all cemented together is, I think, what people are responding to.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;William Petersen&lt;/strong&gt; We&amp;rsquo;re all just working people, I mean, on the show and we operate in our jobs the way people go to work and operate in their jobs. We&amp;rsquo;re very technical, very proficient, and I think it&amp;rsquo;s interesting to watch the process. I think people enjoy watching the process of us put the science to the crime and solve the puzzle.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bryant Gumbel&lt;/strong&gt; But most of the time, people view people who are engaged with science as nerds. How are nerds turned into heroes?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; We&amp;rsquo;re nerds.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;William Petersen&lt;/strong&gt; We&amp;rsquo;re nerds. We just have better clothes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Paul Guilfoyle&lt;/strong&gt; I think also that the plot, that crime is the antagonist of our show. So, you watch this group of dedicated professionals try to come up against or conflict with the crime itself. So I think that&amp;rsquo;s what takes it away from the nerd thing is because of what we&amp;rsquo;re dealing with.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bryant Gumbel&lt;/strong&gt; How much do you really know, any of you, about forensics?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Marg Helgenberger&lt;/strong&gt; We&amp;rsquo;re getting to know more and more everyday. I mean, I knew very little when we began.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Paul Guilfoyle&lt;/strong&gt; And I don&amp;rsquo;t leave my fingerprints on anything.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Marg Helgenberger&lt;/strong&gt; No, I do. I think about that all the time, whether or not I need to put on a pair of gloves or not.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bryant Gumbel&lt;/strong&gt; Come on!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Marg Helgenberger&lt;/strong&gt; I do!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;William Petersen&lt;/strong&gt; Every couple of months, we get better and better, at least, at being able to use the tools and being able to know what the tools are used for. I&amp;rsquo;m certain now if we came across a crime scene, we would at least know how to secure it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Marg Helgenberger&lt;/strong&gt; Well, for instance, sometimes they&amp;rsquo;ll do shots that don&amp;rsquo;t include us, like tape-lifting prints from something and it would have been an added shot. And I saw this on an episode recently and my character was supposed to be doing it and I actually did it on the master. And then I saw the close-up and it was not my print. And it was so sloppy. And I felt like I wanna be doing my own inserts now because it was done&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bryant Gumbel&lt;/strong&gt; I&amp;rsquo;m gonna ask you, look, the show is fiction, but is the science [exact]? I mean, is that the one thing you never tamper with?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;William Petersen&lt;/strong&gt; The science is all real. The stuff we use is real, and the way we use it is all real.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Paul Guilfoyle&lt;/strong&gt; And I think some of the crimes are all real. They&amp;rsquo;re based on real crimes. There&amp;rsquo;s a lot of crime out there, unfortunately.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Marg Helgenberger&lt;/strong&gt; The process is sped up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bryant Gumbel&lt;/strong&gt; You&amp;rsquo;re never hurting for story lines.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Paul Guilfoyle&lt;/strong&gt; No.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; Unfortunately.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bryant Gumbel&lt;/strong&gt; Yeah, it is unfortunate. Talk to me about the collaborative effort of this. I mean, as I look at all of you, you&amp;rsquo;ve all had individual achievements and have been primary players in something else. Is it something where you have to check your ego at the door of a show like this?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;William Petersen&lt;/strong&gt; I think that&amp;rsquo;s the wise thing to do with all work. Otherwise, it&amp;rsquo;s a long day. It&amp;rsquo;s a long day if you don&amp;rsquo;t. And the great thing about this show, and I think in this case we&amp;rsquo;re different than a lot of &amp;ldquo;hit&amp;rdquo; television shows in that our writers, our producers, our actors, our crew, even all the way to the network, we are very collaborative. It&amp;rsquo;s not just one person&amp;rsquo;s decision, as many hit television shows are. They come from one voice. We have a whole lot of people that work very hard all day long with each other to try and make this stuff work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bryant Gumbel&lt;/strong&gt; Do you get involved in the plot lines, the story lines? You&amp;rsquo;re making a face there, Jorja. Yeah?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; Yeah. We do.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Gary Dourdan&lt;/strong&gt; Somewhat, yeah.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;#8216;Cause we&amp;rsquo;re dedicated. So, I don&amp;rsquo;t know. Sometimes even for better for worse, I don&amp;rsquo;t know if everybody always wants to hear from us, but they always act like they do. And they let us talk and they listen to us a lot, which is very kind of them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Paul Guilfoyle&lt;/strong&gt; And acting is kind of the detailed work, almost like the way forensics is and in the course of the process of creating a television show, the acting is kind of the final touchstone of reality, and so I think that&amp;rsquo;s where we all have our own unique experiences.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bryant Gumbel&lt;/strong&gt; In the final moments we&amp;rsquo;ve got left the show is now going to have a spin-off. How uncomfortable are all of you with that?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;William Petersen&lt;/strong&gt; As actors, I think anytime something else comes along to try and compare to your stuff, you get a little queasy about it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bryant Gumbel&lt;/strong&gt; But you have the same people and they now have their attention split.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;William Petersen&lt;/strong&gt; Here&amp;rsquo;s the deal. It&amp;rsquo;s a very successful show and the network is &amp;hellip; and what &amp;ldquo;Law and Order&amp;rdquo; has done to television is a remarkable thing and I think that CBS is interested in some of that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Paul Guilfoyle&lt;/strong&gt; That&amp;rsquo;s a very provocative question, by the way, Bryant.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bryant Gumbel&lt;/strong&gt; We&amp;rsquo;ll have to pursue it during the commercial. Guys, thanks very much and congratulations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;William Petersen&lt;/strong&gt; Congratulations to you. Great job all these years.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bryant Gumbel&lt;/strong&gt; Thanks, Bill. The season finale of &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; airs tomorrow night at 9, of course, here on CBS. We&amp;rsquo;re back in a moment, right after this.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CSI Season 1 DVD extras</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2001/csi-dvd-extras/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jul 2001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2001/csi-dvd-extras/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; Ah, my character&amp;rsquo;s name is Sara Sidle, and she&amp;rsquo;s come in from San Francisco, ah, the character of Grissom has called her up and said there&amp;rsquo;s, you know, there&amp;rsquo;s a major problem happening down in Vegas, would you come down and help out for a while. So that&amp;rsquo;s what I&amp;rsquo;ve done, I&amp;rsquo;ve sort of just come off an airplane and like everybody else I haven&amp;rsquo;t slept in like two days, came right in. So that idea is that, ah, I&amp;rsquo;ll just sort of see if I can help out getting to the bottom of this disaster and then go on home to San Francisco.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; I&amp;rsquo;m a CSI 2 and I&amp;rsquo;m a forensic scientist who also does some investigative work. So I think that science is my specialty, but I&amp;rsquo;ll be doing a lot of investigating.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; A lot of people attracted to the show will be puzzle solvers and will be very interested in getting to the, the truth of the matter and getting to the depth of the matter, so&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; I can only say that my biggest concern about being so excited to do the show was the day to day of being in the gore and how I deal with that, you know, like &amp;#8216;would that be fun&amp;rsquo; or would that be like I wasn&amp;rsquo;t quite sure and&amp;hellip; I think it&amp;rsquo;s going to be&amp;hellip; okay, you know, I still know like if there&amp;rsquo;s something particularly disturbing I probably will skip lunch until we shoot it, finish it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; I have so much respect and admiration, actually, for the folks who do this, you know, who can, who can show up every day and kind of try and figure out what has happened.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; Sara Sidle is not squeamish. I think she&amp;rsquo;s, you know, she&amp;rsquo;s very cerebral, and she really, she lives for what she does, and I think, uh, she, she can become emotionally affected by what she&amp;rsquo;s experiencing, but it doesn&amp;rsquo;t get in the way of her ability to, to be there and be present in it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; The intent is not to be gratuitous, you know, but at the same time, ah, because the show is so visual, and, and we can go places with that. There&amp;rsquo;s moments like, you know, we can show this pulsing heart, we have the technology, you know, so you want to have that opportunity if you can.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>