<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>2003 on Fans of Le Fox Library</title>
    <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/tags/2003/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 2003 on Fans of Le Fox Library</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2003 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://jorjafox.net/library/tags/2003/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Los Angeles Magazine</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2003/los-angeles-magazine/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2003/los-angeles-magazine/</guid>
      <description>The fight against cancer is a team effort. Nowhere is that more evident than at the annual Komen Las Angeles County Race for the Cure, at the Pasadena Rose Bowl on November 2. Jorja Fox of CBS&amp;rsquo; CSI: Crime Scene Investigation, who is serving as spokesperson for the cause [&amp;hellip;] felt passionate about joining the fight after losing both her mother and a friend to cancer. &amp;ldquo;One of the keys to having a great life is to get involved in things that you care about.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>National Examiner</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2003/national-examiner/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2003/national-examiner/</guid>
      <description>There&amp;rsquo;s a battle royal going on behind the scenes at CSI: Crime Scene Investigation &amp;#8212; should Gil Grissom leap into the sack with Sara Sidle?
Fans of TV&amp;rsquo;s top-rated show, now in its fourth season, think it&amp;rsquo;s a pretty hot drama. But backstage fights over what should happen between the characters played by William Petersen and Jorja Fox make the on-screen happenings seem like winter in Antarctica, say insiders.
&amp;ldquo;The production team has been torn apart,&amp;rdquo; a source says.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>93.7 The Buzz</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2003/93.7-the-buzz/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2003/93.7-the-buzz/</guid>
      <description>93.7 BZZ is a top-40 station with all of today&amp;rsquo;s new music.
Bubba: Has it hit you yet that you&amp;rsquo;re on, like, the number one television show in the world?
Jorja Fox: No, absolutely not. I don&amp;rsquo;t know if it&amp;rsquo;ll ever really hit me. I don&amp;rsquo;t really know, I mean it&amp;rsquo;s kind of like fantastically overwhelming to think of.
Bubba: And it&amp;rsquo;s not like you&amp;rsquo;re a bit player in the show, that you like are taking credit for the whole show, you&amp;rsquo;re actually are the show.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E Online</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2003/e-online/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2003/e-online/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
From copssister: Any scoop on CSI?
The scuttlebutt going around is that producers are planning for Grissom and Sara to hookity-hook it, but that stars William Petersen and Jorja Fox have conflicting opinions on whether they want to. She does; he doesn&amp;rsquo;t.
[&amp;hellip;]
From copssister: Have you been able to scrape up info on Without a Trace. It&amp;rsquo;s so good, it made me tape ER and watch it!
I hear there are office romances on Without a Trace, CSI and CSI: Miami this year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Living TV</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2003/living-tv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2003/living-tv/</guid>
      <description>Living TV is &amp;ldquo;Women orientated entertainment&amp;rdquo; and is available on Sky, Telewest and NTL.
Marc: Looking quite glamorous is Jorja from CSI.
Jorja: Thank you very much.
Marc: Chewing gum on the red carpet.
Jorja: Well it&amp;rsquo;s better than a cigar right?
Marc: Ok, you heard it here first, this is a fashion statement, gum chewing, as they say. No let&amp;rsquo;s face it. CSI, the runaway hit, everyone&amp;rsquo;s talking about it, you guys have gotta be feeling pretty good about yourselves.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Guide</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2003/tv-guide-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2003/tv-guide-5/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
Question:
I enjoy your column, but I had to throw my two cents in on the
CSI romance issue. I think you were hasty in saying that a pairing
would be disastrous. The show already deals with a tremendous amount of
non-case driven material &amp;mdash; just look at how Catherine Willows is
portrayed: single mother (as is mentioned almost every episode), former
stripper, has a murdered, violent ex-husband, her possible father may be a</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Guide</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2003/tv-guide-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2003/tv-guide-4/</guid>
      <description>Question: Okay, what is up with CSI? In the beginning it was no romance,
strictly science. Well now, all the hype is that Gil and Sara are going to
fall in love, or whatever they&amp;rsquo;re saying. I mean, what about the finale?
Why didn&amp;rsquo;t they have Gil tell Sara about his surgery, if the master plan is
to have them together? Why would he tell Catherine if really he wants to be</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New York Post</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2003/new-york-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2003/new-york-post/</guid>
      <description>ONE question romantically inclined TV audiences never tire of asking is &amp;ldquo;Will they or won&amp;rsquo;t they?&amp;rdquo;
These days, the most unlikely TV couple who&amp;rsquo;s keeping them guessing is &amp;ldquo; CSI: Crime Scene Investigation &amp;ldquo; &amp;rsquo;s Sara Sidle and her boss, Gil Grissom, played by Jorja Fox and William Petersen.
If you&amp;rsquo;ve been focusing on the series&amp;rsquo; parade of autopsies rather than its more subtle relationship dynamics, you missed one of last season&amp;rsquo;s most heartbreaking below-the-radar attempts at pairing off.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Herald Sun TV Guide</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2003/herald-sun-tv-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2003/herald-sun-tv-guide/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
&amp;ldquo;They have an expression that&amp;rsquo;s so popular among the producers, writers and cast of CSI that they made it the title of a two part episode that will open the show&amp;rsquo;s next season = &amp;ldquo;Assume nothing.
Mainly it concerns the scientific unravelling of the most minute clues left in the wake of murders, when the CSI team moves in with its hi-tech equipment. But if you want to know about something that appears to be far more simple, say a personal relationship between the CSI team&amp;rsquo;s aloof boss, Gil Grissom and TV&amp;rsquo;s sexiest scientist Sara Sidle you can apply the same rule.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Love the &#39;70s</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2003/i-love-the-70s/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2003/i-love-the-70s/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;I Love the 70s&amp;rdquo; is a television mini-series shown on VH1, and was created after the success of &amp;ldquo;I Love the &amp;lsquo;80s&amp;rdquo;.
##Appearances##
Jorja appeared in 5 episodes of the miniseries:
 1970 - Original Airdate 08.18.2003
 1973 - Original Airdate 08.19.2003
 1974 - Original Airdate 08.20.2003
 1976 - Original Airdate 08.21.2003
 1977 - Original Airdate 08.21.2003  ##See Also##
VH1 - I Love the &amp;lsquo;70s</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Sierra Club</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2003/the-sierra-club/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2003/the-sierra-club/</guid>
      <description>The scene: the Utah desert, 35 miles from Salt Lake City. Tons of nuclear waste could soon be rumbling toward the Skull Valley Indian Reservation, whose band of Goshutes is already beset by nearby nerve-gas storage and hazardous-waste incinerators. Enter James Cromwell, who played the U.S. president in the nuclear-weapons thriller The Sum of All Fears. In 2002, the actor addressed senators in Utah and traveled to Washington, D.C., to fight a proposed storage facility for 44,000 tons of high-level nuclear waste on Goshute land.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>USA Today Weekend</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2003/usa-today-weekend-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2003/usa-today-weekend-2/</guid>
      <description>With all the comic book-inspired movies out lately, we asked super celebrities which hero they&amp;rsquo;d most like to play.
It&amp;rsquo;s a lineup that would leave even Doctor Doom shaking in his steel booties. Spurred by the success three years ago of &amp;ldquo;X-Men&amp;rdquo; and last year&amp;rsquo;s smash hit &amp;ldquo;Spider-Man&amp;rdquo;, which spun its way to being one of the highest-grossing movies of all time, comic-book films are enjoying a golden age. &amp;ldquo;Daredevil&amp;rdquo; premiered in February with a $42.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WTEV CBS Flordia</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2003/wtev-cbs-flordia/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2003/wtev-cbs-flordia/</guid>
      <description>The producers of hit TV drama CSI: Crime Scene Investigation are stepping up security on the show&amp;rsquo;s California set after cast members received a barrage of death threat mail and calls.
Sickos claiming to be fans have been getting too close to stars like Marg Helgenberger and Jorja Fox - uncovering personal phone numbers and addresses, and demanding to meet them.
A set insider says, &amp;ldquo;Producers didn&amp;rsquo;t take the threats lightly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CSI Season 3 DVD extras</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2003/csi_season_3_dvd_extras_2003/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2003/csi_season_3_dvd_extras_2003/</guid>
      <description>Crash and Burn Jorja Fox You know, Sara Sidle had a very dark year in season 3; she had a tough one, she really had a tough one. It really started, uh, I would say, in January, about midway through the season. Ah, the first thing that happens is, is, a very good friend of hers betrays her very personally. And the next time we see Sara, her boyfriend, it turns out, has a girlfriend and he also betrays her.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Star Magazine</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2003/star-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2003/star-1/</guid>
      <description>CSI star Jorja Fox is tired of looking like a dowdy stiff. She thinks her lab-tech character Sara should be able to show as much skin as the cadavers in the Las Vegas morgue. What prompted this sudden change? The single star was horrified when she began getting calls from pals asking if she was pregnant - because she looks so heavy on TV in lab coats and baggy shirts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Florida Today</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2003/florida-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2003/florida-today/</guid>
      <description>When teenager Jorjan Fox left Melbourne Beach for good, midway through her senior year in December 1985, she had no idea where she was going. Well, to New York City, for sure, but beyond that, it was a shot in the dark.
The resume was modest. She had taken modeling classes as a kid, done a little drama work in high school, and she&amp;rsquo;d had a couple of brief glimpses of gore as an emergency-room volunteer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>People Magazine</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2003/people-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 May 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2003/people-2/</guid>
      <description>CSI&amp;rsquo;s Jorja Fox has a simple plan: Don&amp;rsquo;t worry, be hippie.
Out of the darkness of the CSI morgue, actress Jorja Fox lightens up as a guitar-toting, happy-go-lucky hippie.
*Between the loss of her mother and CSI&amp;rsquo;s grim plots, &amp;ldquo;I realize that the veil between life and death is thinner than I thought,&amp;rdquo; says Fox &amp;hellip;*
Ask Jorja Fox about the small gap between her front teeth, and she presses her lips together in mock sensitivity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Gal</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2003/tv-gal-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2003/tv-gal-2/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
We haven&amp;rsquo;t really had a good Grissom and Sara moment since that day at the ice-skating rink when he told her started caring about beauty since he met her. We&amp;rsquo;re promised another key scene in their relationship on &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; (Thursday, CBS, 9 p.m.) when an explosion hits too close to home.
[&amp;hellip;]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Guide</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2003/tv-guide-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2003/tv-guide-3/</guid>
      <description>TV&amp;rsquo;s No. 1 show finally investigates the team&amp;rsquo;s private lives.
CSI: Crime Scene Investigation has always been stingy with details about the private lives of its workaholic characters, and they, in turn, don&amp;rsquo;t know much about one another. But this &amp;ldquo;don&amp;rsquo;t ask, don&amp;rsquo;t tell&amp;rdquo; policy is about to backfire on forensics chief Gil Grissom (played by William Petersen). His crime lab will blow up in the May 8 episode, triggering revalations &amp;ldquo;that are bigger than the explosion itself,&amp;rdquo; says Carol Mendelsohn, executive producer of the CBS hit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Playboy</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2003/playboy/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2003/playboy/</guid>
      <description>The star of TV&amp;rsquo;s top show, CSI, on marriage allergies, getting frisked and bad smells in the lab.
1
PLAYBOY : When confronted with something gruesome, who is more likely to get queasy, you or your co-star Marg Helgenberger?
FOX : Me, for sure. Marg is one of the strongest and toughest women I&amp;rsquo;ve ever met. Recently, while filming scenes for CSI, she has been in a meat market working with carcasses, walked through garbage at a disgusting landfill in Santa Clarita, California and worked in the pouring rain for days.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Guide Channel Insider</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2008/tv_guide_channel_insider_2003/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2008/tv_guide_channel_insider_2003/</guid>
      <description>Jorja Fox Wow, um. Thank you. I&amp;rsquo;m hearing that, people have been saying that. And that&amp;rsquo;s amazing, I think- You know, the other reason that I thought the show was going to flop was because it was about science. And I thought that was going to be a very hard thing to make to look fascinating and interesting and exciting to people. I thought it was very fascinating, like reading the script I had a tremendous amount of faith in the show and I just had no idea how we would pull it off.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Guide</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2003/tv-guide-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2003/tv-guide-2/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
Question: Is CSI ever going to get involved with the characters&amp;rsquo; personal lives? I love the show (no show can compare, in my opinion), but many people, including myself, are dying for some romance. Are they holding out on us, or are Catherine and Grissom just never going to open their eyes and see that they want one another? &amp;#8212; Janine
Matt: I think the show is wise to make this sort of thing subtext, not put on the front burner.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>People Magazine</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2003/people-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2003/people-1/</guid>
      <description>She plays a steel-nerved forensics investigator on CSI, but Jorja Fox still gets squeamish recalling her anatomy class at Melbourne (Fla.) High School. &amp;ldquo;It required dissecting. When the cats arrived, I asked for a pregnant one,&amp;rdquo; says Fox, 34. &amp;ldquo;I thought I was really rugged, but by week&amp;rsquo;s end, I could barely stay in class.&amp;rdquo; Fortunately for Fox, the atmosphere on the CSI set isn&amp;rsquo;t particularly grim. &amp;ldquo;We shot a scene with an actress who was strapped on a gurney and couldn&amp;rsquo;t move,&amp;rdquo; says Fox.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Star Online</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2003/the-star-online/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2003/the-star-online/</guid>
      <description>Variety puts a call through to California and speaks to Jorja Fox about what&amp;rsquo;s fast becoming everyone&amp;rsquo;s favourite crime series on television, C.S.I.: Crime Scene Investigation. MUMTAJ BEGUM dusts for prints and gets the inside story.
NO one was more surprised than Jorja (pronounced Georgia, like the US state) Fox when the television series C.S.I.: Crime Scene Investigation took off the way it did. Embraced by both critics and viewers, it was the highest-rated new drama in 2000-2001 in the United States.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>INQ7</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2003/inq7/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2003/inq7/</guid>
      <description>TELEVISION actress Jorja Fox is no stranger to violence: She plays
criminal scene investigator Sara Sidle in the top-rating &amp;ldquo;CSI: Crime
Scene Investigation,&amp;rdquo; aired on cable TV over the AXN channel.
But Fox, who has been exposed to numerous cases of death and
suffering in the action-adventure series is against the ongoing US-led
attack on Iraq.
&amp;ldquo;I send all my prayers to the people of Iraq, especially to the
women and children,&amp;rdquo; she told a group of Southeast Asian writers in a</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Week</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2003/tv-week/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Mar 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2003/tv-week/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
Would you enjoy a real-life career in criminology?
I have no desire to do this job! I have a tremendous amount of respect and regard for the people that do. I feel lucky to have gotten to know a couple of people who are criminalists, and have the best idea that I can of what they do. It is very brave and very dark and very intense and very driven.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>After Ellen</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2003/after-ellen/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2003/after-ellen/</guid>
      <description>**1996 saw an &amp;ldquo;explosion&amp;rdquo; of lesbians on TV compared to previous years: we were introduced to **lesbian twenty-something Rhonda Roth on the new (and short-lived) series [http://www.afterellen.com/TV/relativity.html Relativity], Paul&amp;rsquo;s sister came out on Mad About You, Roseanne&amp;rsquo;s mom came out on Roseanne, lesbian Officer Abby Sullivan joined NYPD Blue-and Dr. Maggie Doyle became the first lesbian to join the staff of the hit NBC series [http://www.afterellen.com/TV/er.html ER], then in its third season.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Gal</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2003/tv-gal-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2003/tv-gal-1/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
Sarah continues to have a personal life on &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; (Thursday, CBS, 9 p.m.). This week her boyfriend Hank is injured. Let&amp;rsquo;s just see how Grissom feels about that.
[&amp;hellip;]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>In Style</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2003/in-style/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2003/in-style/</guid>
      <description>A future Academy Award winner, perhaps. Today&amp;rsquo;s stars recall how time spent waiting for their big break often meant waiting on customers.
[&amp;hellip;]
Jorja Fox
&amp;ldquo;I waitressed for one night. I spilled food on people three times and I was never allowed back in the restaurant again. I was horrible. I just couldn&amp;rsquo;t do the whole balancing thing.&amp;rdquo;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Guide</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2003/tv-guide-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2003/tv-guide-1/</guid>
      <description>Pizza to die for
Jorja Fox sees dead people - but that&amp;rsquo;s her job. As forensic crime scene investigator Sara Sidle on CSI, she determines the cause of death by examining evidence with high-tech toys. Forensic science allows the dead to communicate with the living and producer Jerry Bruckheimer has made it chic to be a science geek.
What viewer see each week, such as the path of a bullet travelling through a human body could put anyone off eating meat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The View</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2003/the-view/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2003/the-view/</guid>
      <description>The New York Times had run a story saying that Jorja would be appearing on the show &amp;ldquo;The Bachelorette&amp;rdquo; - she joked about in on &amp;ldquo;The View&amp;rdquo;.
Meredith: Welcome to &amp;ldquo;The View&amp;rdquo;, live from L.A. &amp;ldquo;CSI:&amp;rdquo; star Jorja Fox is our celebrity co-host today. Welcome to you, you look great.
Jorja Fox: Thank you so much. I feel like I&amp;rsquo;m in New York City right now, being with you guys, which is so nice for me, cause I&amp;rsquo;m from there-</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Better Nutrition</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2003/better-nutrition/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2003/better-nutrition/</guid>
      <description>vegetarian girl next door catapults to stardom
As a star on the top-rated CBS police drama CSI: Crime Scene Investigation, Jorja (pronounced Georgia) Fox as to watch what she eats. Not or health reasons- although nutrition certainly is important to the devoted vegetarian- but becuase of the show&amp;rsquo;s sometimes gory realism. &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;ve learned not to eat before certain scenes,&amp;rdquo; she says.
That&amp;rsquo;s hardly surprising give the fact that Fox&amp;rsquo;s character, Sara Sidle- a name that, she says, &amp;ldquo;sounds a little too much like &amp;lsquo;suicidal&amp;rdquo;]- works as a member of the CSI autopsy team.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teen Television</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2003/teen-television/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2003/teen-television/</guid>
      <description>CSI: Crime Scene Investigation stars Jorja Fox and Gary Dourdan have become best friends after the actor delayed a promotional trip to Europe to wait for his sick pal. Fox claims the cast of the hit show have been close from the beginning, but when Dourdan gave up his dream trip to Europe to help nurse the actress back to full health when she caught the flu, she knew that he was extra special.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Times</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2003/tv-times/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2003/tv-times/</guid>
      <description>Gruesome but gripping &amp;#8212; that&amp;rsquo;s CSI, the US crime series that&amp;rsquo;s gained quiet a reputation
If you were asked to name the most successful American TV show, you&amp;rsquo;d probably think of Friends, ER, The Sopranos, or Sex and the City. In fact, it&amp;rsquo;s none of those &amp;#8212; it&amp;rsquo;s actually CSI: Crime Scene Investigation, which has taken America by storm and is winning plenty of fans here too.
Returning for a third season this week, it&amp;rsquo;s a crime drama with a difference &amp;#8212; with forensic science being the star of the show, rather than the actors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Look</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2003/the-look/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2003/the-look/</guid>
      <description>Lead roles in ER and CSI have made Jorja Fox one of the most envied actresses in Hollywood.
There are three reasons why Jorja Fox particularly enjoys her job &amp;#8212; and they all involve staring opposite Hollywood hunks. First there was George Clooney, then Rob Lowe and now there&amp;rsquo;s Gary Dourdan. &amp;ldquo;Believe me, there&amp;rsquo;s no such thing as a bad day when you&amp;rsquo;re going to work with those guys,&amp;rdquo; she laughs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>USA Today Weekend</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2003/usa-today-weekend-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jan 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2003/usa-today-weekend-1/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
**Two &amp;ldquo;West Wing&amp;rdquo; women &amp;#8212; Jorja Fox, who played a Secret Service agent for the president&amp;rsquo;s daughter, and Emily Procter, who played conservative White House counselor Ainsley Hayes &amp;#8212; have landed in great new jobs on &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;CSI: Miami&amp;rdquo;, respectively. Does that mean we won&amp;rsquo;t see them again on &amp;ldquo;The West Wing&amp;rdquo;?
Michael Mendez, El Paso**
It&amp;rsquo;s not impossible, but it&amp;rsquo;s improbable. NBC&amp;rsquo;s loss is CBS&amp;rsquo; gain and a huge boost to the women&amp;rsquo;s careers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CBS News</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2003/cbs-news/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2003/cbs-news/</guid>
      <description>(CBS) Every week, the cast and crew of &amp;ldquo;C.S.I.&amp;rdquo; find themselves immersed in
bone-chilling tales, made even more haunting by the music that accompanies
each scene, reports The Early Show co-anchor Julie Chen.
While &amp;ldquo;C.S.I.&amp;rdquo; is famous for its high-tech gadgets, the music on the show
is also cutting edge.
&amp;ldquo;We try to choose the edgiest, coolest, hippest music,&amp;rdquo; says the show&amp;rsquo;s
executive producer, Anthony Zucker. &amp;ldquo;As we watch these shows in the editing</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Early Show</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2003/the-early-show/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2003/the-early-show/</guid>
      <description>This particular article was about the music of &amp;ldquo;CSI:&amp;ldquo;; in the beginning was an interview with series creator Anthony Zuiker, discussing how music is chosen for various segments.
(brief clip of Jorja and Gary Dourdan jamming on the set with the crew, something they do on a regular basis. Jorja plays guitar while Gary plays bass)
 Julie Chen: But the music isn&amp;rsquo;t just fun, it&amp;rsquo;s theraputic, an escape from the disturbing drama.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>News Articles (2003)</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2003/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2003/</guid>
      <description>  Date Source    January 09 CBS News   January 12 USA Today Weekend   January 25 TV Times   January 25 The Look   January 26 Teen Television   February 01 Better Nutrition   February 22 TV Guide   March 01 In Style   March 07 TV Gal   March 15 After Ellen   March 29 TV Week   April 03 INQ7   April 06 The Star Online   April 07 People Magazine   April 14 TV Guide   May 01 Playboy   May 03 TV Guide   May 08 TV Gal   May 26 People Magazine   June 11 Florida Today   June 17 Star Magazine   July 03 WTEV CBS Flordia   July 04 USA Today Weekend   July 08 The Sierra Club   August 24 Herald Sun TV Guide   September 03 New York Post   September 08 TV Guide   September 15 TV Guide   September 25 E Online   September 30 National Examiner   October 01 Los Angeles Magazine    </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>