<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Acting on JFO Library</title>
    <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/tags/acting/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Acting on JFO Library</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="http://jorjafox.net/library/tags/acting/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Acting</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/actor/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/actor/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Screen Actors Guild</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/sag/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/sag/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;The Screen Actors Guild (aka SAG) is an American labor union representing over 120,000 film and television principal performers and background performers worldwide. According to SAG&amp;rsquo;s Mission Statement, the Guild seeks to: negotiate and enforce collective bargaining agreements that establish equitable levels of compensation, benefits, and working conditions for its performers; collect compensation for exploitation of recorded performances by its members, and provide protection against unauthorized use of those performances; and preserve and expand work opportunities for its members.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;predicted-2008-strike:6ef3ad411af21fcfc5e715a6708f35b3&#34;&gt;Predicted 2008 Strike&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The film industry is anticipating a strike by SAG, in addition to the recently resolved writers strike against the Alliance of Motion Picture and Television Producers (AMPTP). The strike, which could occur after the expiration of SAG&amp;rsquo;s major contracts in June 2008, would stem from the current handling of royalties from the sale of films distributed through new media methods. This includes royalties earned from Internet distribution services such as iTunes, as well as DVD sales, neither of which are currently written into actors&amp;rsquo;, writers&amp;rsquo;, and directors&amp;rsquo; contracts. The strike date of June 2008 was chosen due to its coinciding with the expiration of several contracts between SAG and AMPTP.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jorja Fox supported the strike and filmed a promo for the SAG, showing her support. She was also a SAG negotiator for the strike.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hi there, I&amp;rsquo;m Jorja Fox. I&amp;rsquo;m a proud card carrying SAG member and AFRA member. I would like to ask you to support your SAG negotiating team. They are working diligently, around the clock, for months now, to ensure that all of us have work for 10 and 20 and 30 years into the future. Respect them, support them, they do a great thing for all of us.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;see-also:6ef3ad411af21fcfc5e715a6708f35b3&#34;&gt;See Also&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.sag.org/files/documents/Solidarity_Statement_Ad.pdf&#34;&gt;SAG Solidarity&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>