<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Transcript on Jorja Fox Library</title>
    <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Transcript on Jorja Fox Library</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 24 Oct 2015 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Extra at the EMA Awards Green Carpet</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2015/ema-awards/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Oct 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2015/ema-awards/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Renee Bargh:&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;hellip; Ah but first up we&amp;rsquo;ve got Jorja Fox from &lt;em&gt;CSI&lt;/em&gt;. Hi, how are you?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; You look amazing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Renee:&lt;/strong&gt; You love wonderful.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; Thank you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Renee:&lt;/strong&gt; You look great. So tell me, why is it so important to be at this event?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; I think it&amp;rsquo;s one of the most important events that you could attend in Los Angeles. Bringing attention to environmental awareness, which is at such a critical, frightening stage right now. I&amp;rsquo;m super excited to celebrate &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://jorjafox.net/library/library/advocacy/racing-extinction/&#34;&gt;Racing Extinction&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt; tonight, I&amp;rsquo;ve had the pleasure of seeing it already. It&amp;rsquo;s one of the greatest films I&amp;rsquo;ve ever seen.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Renee:&lt;/strong&gt; Really?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; Yeah.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Renee:&lt;/strong&gt; Why so?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; There&amp;rsquo;s a context that the filmmakers are able to sort of just put everything in perspective, and share it in such a way that you feel it cerebrally. You feel it in your heart, you feel it through your body. You just want to get up and do something. It&amp;rsquo;s also a hopeful film, believe it or not. You don&amp;rsquo;t leave the theater going &amp;lsquo;Oh well. Everything&amp;rsquo;s lost.&amp;rsquo; Which is great.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Renee:&lt;/strong&gt; That&amp;rsquo;s amazing. That you so much for being here. We&amp;rsquo;re gonna let you get down the carpet, &amp;lsquo;cause everyone wants to talk to you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; Thank you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Renee:&lt;/strong&gt; But we&amp;rsquo;ll see you inside. Thank you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; Thank you.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lylapalooza</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2015/lylapalooza/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2015/lylapalooza/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;CSI star Jorja Fox takes time out to chat with Lyla about dogs, insects, and ice cream. Special guest appearance by Belle the puppy.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lyla:&lt;/strong&gt; This is Lylapalooza and we have Jorja Fox on our show today. Hello, Jorja, how are you today?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; I am very good, Lyla, how are you doing?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lyla:&lt;/strong&gt; Good. This is my shnuffler. Shnuffle. Do you have anything to say?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Belle the Puppy:** *silence*&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lyla:&lt;/strong&gt; Okay! So.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; Profound.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lyla:&lt;/strong&gt; Yes. For our first question. Jorja, what would your favorite color be?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; I think my favorite color, and it changes a lot but right now it&amp;rsquo;s blue. Cuz it reminds me of the ocean and sky and the nighttime.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lyla:&lt;/strong&gt; Yes. The same with me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; Oh really? Profound.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lyla:&lt;/strong&gt; I also really like orange right now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; Me too! Cuz it&amp;rsquo;s like the sun.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lyla:&lt;/strong&gt; Mmm hmm! And the sand.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; Yes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lyla:&lt;/strong&gt; For our second question today, with Jorja Fox. Jorja &amp;hellip; Hmm. What&amp;rsquo;s your favorite insect?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; My favorite insect is dragonflies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lyla:&lt;/strong&gt; I personally like bumblebees.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; Bumblebees are amazing. And you know what else? Maybe fireflies too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lyla:&lt;/strong&gt; Oh yes! And ladybugs!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; Ladybugs, of course! It&amp;rsquo;s hard to- you can&amp;rsquo;t maybe pick one favorite.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lyla:&lt;/strong&gt; This is hard! What is your favorite animal?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; My favorite animal has to be my dog, Bexar. She&amp;rsquo;s like a poodle mix. But her full name is Bexar County Rodeo Princess. She&amp;rsquo;s from Texas.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lyla:&lt;/strong&gt; That makes a lot of sense.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; Thank you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lyla:&lt;/strong&gt; Okay. What is your favorite article of clothing?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; My favorite article of clothing is sunglasses.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lyla:&lt;/strong&gt; I like sweatshirts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; Sweatshirts are good.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lyla:&lt;/strong&gt; What is your favorite &amp;hellip; hmm &amp;hellip; way to help animals?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; My favorite way to help animals is to &amp;hellip; not eat them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lyla:&lt;/strong&gt; My favorite way to help animals is &amp;hellip; I don&amp;rsquo;t like to litter. I never litter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; You don&amp;rsquo;t do it?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lyla:&lt;/strong&gt; I don&amp;rsquo;t litter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; Me either. No, that&amp;rsquo;s terrible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lyla:&lt;/strong&gt; So bad for the earth.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; Bad for the seals and the sea turtles and the dolphins.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lyla:&lt;/strong&gt; And everything that can eat stuff off the ground.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; Yes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lyla:&lt;/strong&gt; And the sea.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; Like Belle!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lyla:&lt;/strong&gt; Like Belle! Like baby. Okay. For our sixth question, what&amp;rsquo;s your favorite type of music?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; I love all music. Like every kind, it&amp;rsquo;s my favorite thing in the whole world. But if I had to pick a favorite style it would probably be &amp;hellip; like &amp;hellip; Jazz. Maybe?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lyla:&lt;/strong&gt; Jorja! What&amp;rsquo;s your favorite type of ice cream?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; Well, Lyla. I think my favorite kind of ice cream is called Kind Cream. And it&amp;rsquo;s the cookies&amp;rsquo;n&amp;rsquo;cream flavor. Classic cookies&amp;rsquo;n&amp;rsquo;cream. And they used the cookies they get them from Baby Cakes Bakery in New York City. What about you?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lyla:&lt;/strong&gt; I like &amp;hellip; Hmmm &amp;hellip; So my three favorites would probably be- I just have three favorites because I can&amp;rsquo;t choose.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; You can&amp;rsquo;t choose!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lyla:&lt;/strong&gt; So I have cotton candy, chocolate, aaaaand &amp;hellip; So there&amp;rsquo;s an ice cream store on Fire Island, it&amp;rsquo;s called Unfriendly&amp;rsquo;s Ice Cream, and one of their flavors is called Play-doh. It&amp;rsquo;s vanilla ice cream dyed yellow, with little bits of cookie chunks in it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; Wow!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lyla:&lt;/strong&gt; And they&amp;rsquo;re dyed blue and orange and red to look like play-doh. This is Lylapalooza signing out! Good bye! Goodbye!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; Bye!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shark Allies</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2015/shark-allies/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2015/shark-allies/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Jorja Fox talks about her personal connection to the ocean and her perception of trophy hunting and the misrepresentation of sharks in the media.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Our Connection to the Ocean&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I spend as much time on the water as I can. I&amp;rsquo;ve been bodyboarding since I was about six and surfing for about the last fifteen years. So I&amp;rsquo;m there, you know, several times a week if I can be.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A long time ago, when you think of how mankind kind of evolved on earth, it was this battle&lt;br /&gt;
between man and nature. Man needed to dominate nature in order to survive. And we won that battle a long time ago. Now, you know, our job and and our kids&amp;rsquo; job is to figure out the balance on the planet. I guess at the end of the day, it&amp;rsquo;s really important to know that that without the ocean, human survival will end. We need fish for our own survival and we need water and oxygen for out own survival. The ocean makes the bulk of the world&amp;rsquo;s oxygen. If the oceans are sick, then the balance of the entire planet will fall apart.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We cannot survive without a healthy ocean.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sharks and the Media&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The shark programing, I think it&amp;rsquo;s been very, very unfortunate you know in the last twenty or thirty years. On one hand, we know more about sharks than we ever did, and we&amp;rsquo;ve been exposed to sharks more than we could have ever imagined. But so much of that information has been negative information or kind of information that&amp;rsquo;s more for to instill fear in people or to instill cheap kinda thrills, action packed thrills.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The media, whether it&amp;rsquo;s been intentional or not, often focuses on stories that are gonna have a shock value for people, that are going to get people&amp;rsquo;s attention. So, often, that&amp;rsquo;s what sharks have have done inadvertently to people, or how people have been harmed by sharks. But I think what would be really important piece of this puzzle is if the media could start focusing on on how we are affecting short survival.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Trophy Hunting&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sport fishing, in my opinion, and hunting for sport is kind of something that should go the way the history books. Something that people did. We don&amp;rsquo;t do that anymore. Now we&amp;rsquo;re actually trying to create sustainable habitat for wildlife and for sea life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There was a time where lead paint was a great idea and where asbestos was a great idea. And both of them are sort of human ingenuity and we kind of&lt;br /&gt;
realized &amp;ldquo;Okay, well that was then and let&amp;rsquo;s build things differently now and and and do things differently now because that&amp;rsquo;s not sustainable for us anymore.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well me, personally, I&amp;rsquo;m not a fan of any kind of hunting and that would include commercial and sport fishing. It&amp;rsquo;s just not something that I really understand and &amp;hellip; I think I would invite anybody who does enjoy that activity to take a few moments and ask themselves what about killing is so satisfying for them. I&amp;rsquo;m not really sure where the the sport or the fun is in that and I would encourage people just ask that question to themselves.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ExtraTV</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2015/extra-tv/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2015/extra-tv/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;on-the-set-of-csi-all-the-scoop-on-the-series-finale:7c9f9b2aab93a103cf2adb3a780260c5&#34;&gt;On the Set of &amp;lsquo;CSI&amp;rsquo;! All the Scoop on the Series Finale&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;*&amp;lsquo;Crime Watch Daily&amp;rsquo; host Matt Doran was the perfect &amp;lsquo;Extra&amp;rsquo; special correspondent to stop by the &amp;lsquo;CSI&amp;rsquo; set to get the scoop on the series finale. Watch!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Catch the final episode Sept. 27 at 9 PM on CBS.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Matt Doran:&lt;/strong&gt; (voice over) Jorja Fox, ready to put her work boots on one last time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Matt Doran:&lt;/strong&gt; What can you tell us about what we can expect from the finale?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; My character, not unlike her, is pretty angry for most of the finale (laughter). Been a series of extreme bombings in the city, and she&amp;rsquo;s running the case.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Matt Doran:&lt;/strong&gt; It&amp;rsquo;s a hard thing to imagine, life after CSI.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; Mmhmm. And I&amp;rsquo;m a little longer in the tooth (laughter) than I was when I started.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Matt Doran:&lt;/strong&gt; I refuse to believe that. Annually you get voted among the world&amp;rsquo;s sexiest vegetarians.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; Oh, come on!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Matt Doran:&lt;/strong&gt; Oh yeah!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; Thank you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interviews (2015)</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2015/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;table class=&#34;jfoinfobox&#34;&gt;

	&lt;thead&gt;&lt;tr&gt;
		&lt;th&gt;Date&lt;/th&gt;
		&lt;th&gt;Source&lt;/th&gt;
	&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/thead&gt;

	&lt;tbody&gt;
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		

			&lt;tr&gt;
				&lt;td&gt;August 18&lt;/td&gt;
				&lt;td&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2015/extra-tv/&#34;&gt;ExtraTV&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
			&lt;/tr&gt;

		
	
		

		

			&lt;tr&gt;
				&lt;td&gt;September 29&lt;/td&gt;
				&lt;td&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2015/lylapalooza/&#34;&gt;Lylapalooza&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
			&lt;/tr&gt;

		
	
		

		

			&lt;tr&gt;
				&lt;td&gt;September 29&lt;/td&gt;
				&lt;td&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2015/shark-allies/&#34;&gt;Shark Allies&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
			&lt;/tr&gt;

		
	
		

		

			&lt;tr&gt;
				&lt;td&gt;October 24&lt;/td&gt;
				&lt;td&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2015/ema-awards/&#34;&gt;Extra at the EMA Awards Green Carpet&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
			&lt;/tr&gt;

		
	
	&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RedCarpetReport TV</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2014/redcarpetreport-tv/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2014/redcarpetreport-tv/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Jorja Fox at the 30th Annual IDA Documentary Awards Gala #IDAawards&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Quinn Marie:&lt;/strong&gt; So what brings you out today? You are presenting, correct?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; I am presenting best episodic series and best limited series, TV awards, which should be kind of fun.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;QM:&lt;/strong&gt; Very cool. And you recently narrated a documentary, correct?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;JF:&lt;/strong&gt; You know, I have actually. Thanks for knowing that! Actually a bit ago I narrated a documentary about Gidget. One of the first female surfers in California. I produced a couple of documentaries and most of those are wildlife based. Lion Ark, Extinction Soup, and How I Became an Elephant.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;QM:&lt;/strong&gt; Awesome. Working in television and documentaries, what is the different process that you go through initially?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;JF:&lt;/strong&gt; Entirely different process. Obviously usually with television you&amp;rsquo;re dealing with a script- at least in my world! I&amp;rsquo;m not part of reality television or news television. And so you&amp;rsquo;ll develop a script for a really long time and then hopefully somebody will be interested in it. And I think with documentaries, at least for me so far, someone has just had an idea and a camera and decided that they had a story that they needed to tell, and almost started the process of telling it without even knowing where it was going to end up, or what the results were going to be. Those are the projects that I&amp;rsquo;ve been a part of so far. I think there can be pre-production in documentaries. People sit down and they kind of scope it out. But so far ours have just sort of been like run and wing it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;QM:&lt;/strong&gt; Very cool. Do you plan on doing more in the future?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;JF:&lt;/strong&gt; I hope so, yeah. I&amp;rsquo;ve been really enjoying it. It&amp;rsquo;s a fun thing to do.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;QM:&lt;/strong&gt; And then &amp;hellip; Robert Redford is being honored tonight. He&amp;rsquo;s kind of been the founder of Sundance-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;JF:&lt;/strong&gt; Do you see my boots shaking?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;QM:&lt;/strong&gt; Are you a- Obviously you a fan, yes?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;JF:&lt;/strong&gt; Yes. You know, I think everybody has a couple heroes in their lives. For many, many people, Robert Redford is one of those people. He&amp;rsquo;s absolutely one of mine from the time that I can remember. I am a huge, huge &amp;#8212; not only fan of his but he&amp;rsquo;s been a personal hero for me. So yeah, it&amp;rsquo;s going to be incredibly exciting to see him. An honor he clearly deserves, and I&amp;rsquo;m sure it&amp;rsquo;s going to be fun to see.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;QM:&lt;/strong&gt; That&amp;rsquo;s so cool. Thank you so much, have fun tonight!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;JF:&lt;/strong&gt; Alright, thank you.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Green with Tiffany</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2014/green-with-tiffany/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2014/green-with-tiffany/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tiffany Paige:&lt;/strong&gt; We&amp;rsquo;re here with actress Jorja Fox from CSI. What brings you here tonight?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; I&amp;rsquo;m very excited about this event, it&amp;rsquo;s an event very close to my heart. I&amp;rsquo;m representing Artists &amp;amp; Athletes tonight. I&amp;rsquo;m on the advisory board and we&amp;rsquo;re a collective of artists and athletes that connect with Washington DC on issues that are close to everybody. Kind of create a dialogue between the different camps and bring us together to get things that we care about on the floor and up for conversation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;TP:&lt;/strong&gt; That&amp;rsquo;s so important. Are you an athlete yourself?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;JF:&lt;/strong&gt; I&amp;rsquo;m a surfer. I don&amp;rsquo;t know if that really counts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;TP:&lt;/strong&gt; Of course that counts. [&amp;hellip;] Do you have a green tip? Is there something that you could tell our viewers?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;JF:&lt;/strong&gt; Okay, well I&amp;rsquo;m going out on the edge here, but I&amp;rsquo;d like to take &amp;ldquo;Meatless Mondays&amp;rdquo; into three more days a week. Probably the single-handed biggest thing that any individual can do to really help the environment is to eat vegetarian. And maybe not all the time, but even just more would make a huge difference.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;TP:&lt;/strong&gt; That is a good one. So are you a vegetarian?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;JF:&lt;/strong&gt; I am, yes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;TP:&lt;/strong&gt; How long have you been a vegetarian?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;JF:&lt;/strong&gt; Like &amp;hellip; twenty-two years?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;TP:&lt;/strong&gt; Wow!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;JF:&lt;/strong&gt; Yeah like that. You know, for me it&amp;rsquo;s something I don&amp;rsquo;t even think about anymore. It&amp;rsquo;s just&amp;hellip; it&amp;rsquo;s not complicated, it&amp;rsquo;s not hard. [&amp;hellip;] In terms of raising cattle and raising food, the water that gets used and the land that gets sort of clear-cut to make that happen&amp;hellip; you don&amp;rsquo;t think about that when- I mean, why would we?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;TP:&lt;/strong&gt; I don&amp;rsquo;t think people put faces to their food. How that works, where their food comes from. That is a great one, thank you for that tip.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;JF:&lt;/strong&gt; Thanks Tiffany.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;TP:&lt;/strong&gt; Have a great night.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;JF:&lt;/strong&gt; Alright, you too.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Twitter Live Chat</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2014/twitter-live-chat/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Mar 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2014/twitter-live-chat/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/jorjafoxofficia/status/441408995996078081&#34;&gt;Tweet&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;**&amp;#8212; Nikki @PenguinsFan87 **&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Q:&lt;/em&gt; @JorjaFoxofficia How did you hear about CSI and how did u try auditioning for any of characters before you got Sara Sidle role? #CSI&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;#8212; LeFox @JorjaFoxofficia&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;A:&lt;/em&gt; .@PenguinsFan87 I had a birthday party at my house - someone at the party told me about it. Only auditioned for Sara. #CSI&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#8212;-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/jorjafoxofficia/status/441409403053289472&#34;&gt;Tweet&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;#8212; LeFox @JorjaFoxofficia&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Everyone in here is telling me to be quiet so they can type. #CSI&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#8212;-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/jorjafoxofficia/status/441409730754277376&#34;&gt;Tweet&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;#8212; Joyce @ohmycsi&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Q:&lt;/em&gt; @JorjaFoxofficia Do you think that Sara, Nick and Greg are like siblings ? #CSI&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;#8212; LeFox @JorjaFoxofficia&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;A:&lt;/em&gt; .@ohmycsi we&amp;rsquo;re just three lost souls swimming in a fish bowl. #CSI&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#8212;-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/JorjaFoxofficia/status/441410037961879553&#34;&gt;Tweet&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;#8212; WiilDion @wil_dion&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Q:&lt;/em&gt; @JorjaFoxofficia What is your favorite scene with George Eads? #CSI&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;#8212; LeFox @JorjaFoxofficia&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;A:&lt;/em&gt; .@wil_dion End of Gum Drops, and last year when he was in the drunk tank. #CSI&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#8212;-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/JorjaFoxofficia/status/441410420650176512&#34;&gt;Tweet&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;#8212; Lauren, a blackbird @luckylauren81&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Q:&lt;/em&gt; @JorjaFoxofficia I know #Blackbird is a favorite song of yours, it&amp;rsquo;s one of mine too! Why do you love it? For me it&amp;rsquo;s hopeful.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;#8212; LeFox @JorjaFoxofficia&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;A:&lt;/em&gt; .@luckylauren81 and haunting. it&amp;rsquo;s so hard to be both. #CSI&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#8212;-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/JorjaFoxofficia/status/441410528104050688&#34;&gt;Tweet&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;-Steph @GladCaskettCame&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Q:&lt;/em&gt; @JorjaFoxofficia Jorja what is your favorite #CSI episode so far?&lt;br /&gt;
I LOVE U! &amp;lt;3 &lt;strong&gt;&amp;#8212; LeFox @JorjaFoxofficia&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;A:&lt;/em&gt; .@GladCaskettCame I hope we haven&amp;rsquo;t shot it yet! #CSI&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#8212;-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/JorjaFoxofficia/status/441410977871835136&#34;&gt;Tweet&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;-Kimmy @missbkimmer&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Q:&lt;/em&gt; @ericszmanda @kingoftrace @AlimiBallard @CSICast @JorjaFoxofficia do you have a favorite guest actor that you worked with?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;#8212; LeFox @JorjaFoxofficia&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;A:&lt;/em&gt; .@missbkimmer @ericszmanda @kingoftrace @AlimiBallard @CSICast @juliettegoglia . I hope we go head to head again someday. #CSI&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#8212;-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/JorjaFoxofficia/status/441411235330805761&#34;&gt;Tweet&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;#8212; Aeris @AerisGaladriel&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Q:&lt;/em&gt; @JorjaFoxofficia what was your very first role? #CSI&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;#8212; LeFox @JorjaFoxofficia&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;A:&lt;/em&gt; .@AerisGaladriel I played a heroin addict in a movie called The Kill Off #CSI&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#8212;-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/JorjaFoxofficia/status/441411364184018945&#34;&gt;Tweet&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;#8212; LeFox @JorjaFoxofficia&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
I love him (Ron Glass) so much. #CSI&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#8212;-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/JorjaFoxofficia/status/441411623878553600&#34;&gt;Tweet&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;-Taryn minahan @taryn_minahan&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Q:&lt;/em&gt; @CSI_CBS @JorjaFoxofficia if you could be any other character who would it be? #CSI&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;#8212; LeFox @JorjaFoxofficia&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;A:&lt;/em&gt; .@taryn_minahan @CSI_CBS I&amp;rsquo;d love to be Doc Robbins! #CSI&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#8212;-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/JorjaFoxofficia/status/441411767411830784&#34;&gt;Tweet&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;#8212; Kelly @kellyobrien8255&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Q:&lt;/em&gt; @JorjaFoxofficia are you a fan of chess? #csi&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;#8212; LeFox @JorjaFoxofficia&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;A:&lt;/em&gt; @kellyobrien8255 I&amp;rsquo;m better at Jenga! #CSI&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#8212;-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/JorjaFoxofficia/status/441411965924032512&#34;&gt;Tweet&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;#8212; VitÃ³ria @Vitoria_SQ&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Q:&lt;/em&gt; @JorjaFoxofficia What is your favorite band at the moment? #CSI&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;#8212; LeFox @JorjaFoxofficia&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;A:&lt;/em&gt; @Vitoria_SQ Jack Johnson! @jackjohnson #CSI&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#8212;-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/JorjaFoxofficia/status/441412109092409344&#34;&gt;Tweet&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;#8212; LeFox @JorjaFoxofficia&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Favorite shot in the show coming up right now. #CSI&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#8212;-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/JorjaFoxofficia/status/441412372251430912&#34;&gt;Tweet&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;-Clara @TX_Clarebear&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Q:&lt;/em&gt; @ElisabethHarnoi @JorjaFoxofficia @ericszmanda @Alecdow @kingoftrace How do u guys like working with Ted Danson? I think he&amp;rsquo;s a great actor&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;#8212; LeFox @JorjaFoxofficia&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;A:&lt;/em&gt; @TX_Clarebear @ElisabethHarnoi @ericszmanda @Alecdow @kingoftrace Yes. Ted&amp;rsquo;s a supernova. #CSI&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#8212;-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/JorjaFoxofficia/status/441412675705122816&#34;&gt;Tweet&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;#8212; Nancy Provenzano @NancyProvenzan1&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Q:&lt;/em&gt; @JorjaFoxofficia Do you think they will give you a love interest? love watching you &amp;amp; csi. . #csi&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;#8212; LeFox @JorjaFoxofficia&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;A:&lt;/em&gt; @NancyProvenzan1 a girl can dream. thank you. #CSI&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#8212;-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/JorjaFoxofficia/status/441412843481489410&#34;&gt;Tweet&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;#8212; gabriella @oidelvato&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Q:&lt;/em&gt; @JorjaFoxofficia what is your favorite sport? #CSISLive&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;#8212; LeFox @JorjaFoxofficia&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;A:&lt;/em&gt; @oidelvato surfing. #CSI&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#8212;-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/JorjaFoxofficia/status/441412906907729921&#34;&gt;Tweet&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;#8212; Im A Fox¤ @CSINYFanDk&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Q:&lt;/em&gt; @JorjaFoxofficia do you miss working with Marg? Shes also a perfect actror! Right?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;#8212; LeFox @JorjaFoxofficia&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;A:&lt;/em&gt; @CSINYFanDk Yes! She&amp;rsquo;s amazing. #CSI&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#8212;-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/JorjaFoxofficia/status/441413398748622850&#34;&gt;Tweet&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;#8212; Aeris @AerisGaladriel&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Q:&lt;/em&gt; @JorjaFoxofficia @AlimiBallard @ericszmanda @ElisabethHarnoi @kingoftrace do you guys play tricks on each other on set? #CSI&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;#8212; LeFox @JorjaFoxofficia&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;A:&lt;/em&gt; @AerisGaladriel @ElisabethHarnoi does. #CSI&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#8212;-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/JorjaFoxofficia/status/441413602453360640&#34;&gt;Tweet&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;#8212; gabriella @oidelvato&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Q:&lt;/em&gt; @JorjaFoxofficia you have a favorite movie? if yes, how?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;#8212; LeFox @JorjaFoxofficia&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;A:&lt;/em&gt; @oidelvato Tootsie and Forrest Gump. #CSI&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#8212;-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/JorjaFoxofficia/status/441413846662524928&#34;&gt;Tweet&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;#8212; Atthebeachpeach @Atthebeachpeach&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Q:&lt;/em&gt; @JorjaFoxofficia ever eaten fried olives? #CSI&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;#8212; LeFox @JorjaFoxofficia&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;A:&lt;/em&gt; @Atthebeachpeach yes! #CSI&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#8212;-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/JorjaFoxofficia/status/441414210228977665&#34;&gt;Tweet&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;#8212; David B @DMan016&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Q:&lt;/em&gt; @JorjaFoxofficia @ElisabethHarnoi @ericszmanda what do u guys do when not working? #CSI&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;#8212; LeFox @JorjaFoxofficia&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;A:&lt;/em&gt; @DMan016 @ElisabethHarnoi @ericszmanda we have twitter parties!!! #CSI&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#8212;-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/JorjaFoxofficia/status/441414274322165762&#34;&gt;Tweet&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;#8212; LeFox @JorjaFoxofficia&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Dance break. @kingoftrace &amp;#8216;s montage. #CSI&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#8212;-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/JorjaFoxofficia/status/441414443298091008&#34;&gt;Tweet&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;-Brittany Marie @Brittany21693V&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Q:&lt;/em&gt; Nothing to do with #CSI but @JorjaFoxofficia I just wanted to thank you, you inspired me to become a vegetarian. @peta&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;#8212; LeFox @JorjaFoxofficia&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;A:&lt;/em&gt; @Brittany21693V @peta Thank you! #CSI&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#8212;-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/JorjaFoxofficia/status/441414617634308096&#34;&gt;Tweet&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;#8212; Joyce @ohmycsi&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Q:&lt;/em&gt; @JorjaFoxofficia What is your favorite animal ? #CSI&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;#8212; LeFox @JorjaFoxofficia&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;A:&lt;/em&gt; @ohmycsi Humans. #CSI&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#8212;-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/JorjaFoxofficia/status/441414720986165248&#34;&gt;Tweet&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;#8212; Katarina @boomboxandsocks&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Q:&lt;/em&gt; @JorjaFoxofficia did you have to watch a real autopsy when you first started the show #csi&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;#8212; LeFox @JorjaFoxofficia&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;A:&lt;/em&gt; @boomboxandsocks It wasn&amp;rsquo;t mandatory, but yes I did. #CSI&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#8212;-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/JorjaFoxofficia/status/441414811465695233&#34;&gt;Tweet&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;#8212; Anne aka Sweet Lady @GetMe2TheGeek&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Q:&lt;/em&gt; @JorjaFoxofficia @ElisabethHarnoi @ericszmanda @kingoftrace What&amp;rsquo;s the best thing about of being in CSI?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;#8212; LeFox @JorjaFoxofficia&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;A:&lt;/em&gt; @GetMe2TheGeek @ElisabethHarnoi @ericszmanda @kingoftrace The people that I get to work with. #CSI&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#8212;-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/JorjaFoxofficia/status/441415016713953280&#34;&gt;Tweet&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;#8212; Georghia Allons-y @NahmenJaydenFBI&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Q:&lt;/em&gt; @JorjaFoxofficia how is the learning to play drums going? 😛 #csi&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;#8212; LeFox @JorjaFoxofficia&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;A:&lt;/em&gt; @NahmenJaydenFBI terrible. I have no talent. #CSI&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#8212;-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/jorjafoxofficia/status/441415370994221056&#34;&gt;Tweet&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;-Karen Gibbons @KarGibbons&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Q:&lt;/em&gt; @ElisabethHarnoi would you like to do another girls weekend away ep with @JorjaFoxofficia and #lisashue #CSI&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;#8212; LeFox @JorjaFoxofficia&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;A:&lt;/em&gt; @KarGibbons @ElisabethHarnoi yes, @Alecdow @ElisabethHarnoi and Lisa Shue are simply amazing to work with and super fun. #CSI&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#8212;-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/jorjafoxofficia/status/441415569539989504&#34;&gt;Tweet&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;#8212; Natalie C. @NatC101712&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Q:&lt;/em&gt; @JorjaFoxofficia have you ever gone blond? Or thought about it? Or any other color for your hair? #csi thank you!!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;#8212; LeFox @JorjaFoxofficia&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;A:&lt;/em&gt; @NatC101712 yes, blonde, purple, black, fire engine red&amp;hellip;. #CSI&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#8212;-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/jorjafoxofficia/status/441415880157560832&#34;&gt;Tweet&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;-Morganders! (Grody) @CSIMorganders&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Q:&lt;/em&gt; @JorjaFoxofficia @ElisabethHarnoi If you were to kill someone, what weapon would you use? #CSI&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;#8212; LeFox @JorjaFoxofficia&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;A:&lt;/em&gt; @CSIMorganders @ElisabethHarnoi a shard of ice! #CSI&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#8212;-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/jorjafoxofficia/status/441416318164545537&#34;&gt;Tweet&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;-Janet Westhead @csivegasrocks&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Q:&lt;/em&gt; #CSI @JorjaFoxofficia oh no! Please tell me thats not the same garage where Sara was kidnapped!?!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;#8212; LeFox @JorjaFoxofficia&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;A:&lt;/em&gt; @csivegasrocks No. I was tasered on the backlot of Universal. This garage was off the lot. #CSI&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#8212;-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/jorjafoxofficia/status/441416412637044736&#34;&gt;Tweet&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;#8212; Erin @harnoisfan&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Q:&lt;/em&gt; @JorjaFoxofficia what&amp;rsquo;s the biggest difference between you and Sara? #csi&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;#8212; LeFox @JorjaFoxofficia&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;A:&lt;/em&gt; @harnoisfan Sara has more ghosts than I do. #CSI&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#8212;-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/jorjafoxofficia/status/441416510607609856&#34;&gt;Tweet&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;-Katarina @boomboxandsocks&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Q:&lt;/em&gt; @ericszmanda @JorjaFoxofficia @ElisabethHarnoi did you film at all in Las Vegas in this episode #csi&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;#8212; LeFox @JorjaFoxofficia&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;A:&lt;/em&gt; @boomboxandsocks @ericszmanda @ElisabethHarnoi No. #CSI&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#8212;-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/jorjafoxofficia/status/441416944588029952&#34;&gt;Tweet&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;-Danielle¡CSI¡RipCory @1RASCALFLATTfan&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Q:&lt;/em&gt; Will there be a SEASON 15 I hope. What do you think #csi. @ericszmanda @JorjaFoxofficia @ElisabethHarnoi @kingoftrace @AlimiBallard .&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;#8212; LeFox @JorjaFoxofficia&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;A:&lt;/em&gt; @1RASCALFLATTfan @ericszmanda @ElisabethHarnoi @kingoftrace @AlimiBallard I hope so! #CSI&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#8212;-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/jorjafoxofficia/status/441417220095090688&#34;&gt;Tweet&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;#8212; LeFox @JorjaFoxofficia&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
This song is All Good People by Yes. It&amp;rsquo;s about chess. Amazing classic and a great remix. #CSI&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#8212;-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/jorjafoxofficia/status/441417590506680320&#34;&gt;Tweet&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;#8212; LucÃ­a Friely @LuciaFriely&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Q:&lt;/em&gt; @JorjaFoxofficia What do you like most about acting? #CSI&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;#8212; LeFox @JorjaFoxofficia&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;A:&lt;/em&gt; @LuciaFriely I get to do things and experience things that I&amp;rsquo;d never get to do in my own life. #CSI&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#8212;-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/jorjafoxofficia/status/441417726607638528&#34;&gt;Tweet&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;-Natalia Ruiz @Nat_Ruiz&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
@ericszmanda @ElisabethHarnoi @kingoftrace @JorjaFoxofficia Do you watch Intelligence? #CSI&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;#8212; LeFox @JorjaFoxofficia&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;A:&lt;/em&gt; @Nat_Ruiz @ericszmanda @ElisabethHarnoi @kingoftrace Yes, I&amp;rsquo;ve seen it. It&amp;rsquo;s wonderful. #CSI&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#8212;-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/jorjafoxofficia/status/441418115906166784&#34;&gt;Tweet&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;#8212; EFFIE @trueswiftiets&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Q:&lt;/em&gt; @JorjaFoxofficia smartest person on set? #CSI&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;#8212; LeFox @JorjaFoxofficia&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;A:&lt;/em&gt; @trueswiftiets Larry Mitchell, our on set tech-adviser. #CSI&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#8212;-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/jorjafoxofficia/status/441418422975356928&#34;&gt;Tweet&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;#8212; Ana @AnaLuisa_Guedes&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Q:&lt;/em&gt; @JorjaFoxofficia Do you have a favorite episode from this 14 years? #CSI&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;#8212; LeFox @JorjaFoxofficia&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;A:&lt;/em&gt; @AnaLuisa_Guedes I still love Blood Drops from season 1. #CSI&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#8212;-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/jorjafoxofficia/status/441418583176777729&#34;&gt;Tweet&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;#8212; Kate @keskt42&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Q:&lt;/em&gt; @JorjaFoxofficia Is Sara over Grissom?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;#8212; LeFox @JorjaFoxofficia&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;A:&lt;/em&gt; @keskt42 It ain&amp;rsquo;t over &amp;lsquo;til it&amp;rsquo;s over. #CSI&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#8212;-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/jorjafoxofficia/status/441418870151061504&#34;&gt;Tweet&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;#8212; LeFox @JorjaFoxofficia&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Get &amp;lsquo;em Ali! @AlimiBallard #CSI&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#8212;-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/jorjafoxofficia/status/441419382611120129&#34;&gt;Tweet&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;#8212; Fernando&amp;hellip; @In_MyRemains&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Q:&lt;/em&gt; @JorjaFoxofficia How was your first time being part of the show? #csi&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;#8212; LeFox @JorjaFoxofficia&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;A:&lt;/em&gt; @In_MyRemains We worked 19 hours a day in extreme heat. I didn&amp;rsquo;t think I was gonna make it. #CSI&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#8212;-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/jorjafoxofficia/status/441419875777384449&#34;&gt;Tweet&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;#8212; Shiela Urbano @Shiela_Urbano&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Q:&lt;/em&gt; @JorjaFoxofficia what is the saddest #CSI seaaon/episode for you?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;#8212; LeFox @JorjaFoxofficia&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;A:&lt;/em&gt; @Shiela_Urbano Forget Me Not from season 13. I cried every night when I went home. #CSI&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#8212;-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/jorjafoxofficia/status/441419655513505792&#34;&gt;Tweet&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;-Sandy @SandNole&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Q:&lt;/em&gt; Would Greg ever have a chance with Sara if there was no Grissom? #CSI @JorjaFoxofficia @ericszmanda&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;-Eric Szmanda @ericszmanda&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;A:&lt;/em&gt; Greg tried years ago, but Sara turned him down #CSI @SandNole @JorjaFoxofficia&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;#8212; LeFox @JorjaFoxofficia&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;A:&lt;/em&gt; @ericszmanda @SandNole He was too young! But he&amp;rsquo;s not anymore&amp;hellip;. #CSI&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#8212;-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/jorjafoxofficia/status/441420506235809793&#34;&gt;Tweet&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;#8212; LeFox @JorjaFoxofficia&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Look! @ElisabethHarnoi is on fire! #CSI&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#8212;-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/jorjafoxofficia/status/441420817704816640&#34;&gt;Tweet&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;#8212; Georghia Allons-y @NahmenJaydenFBI&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Q:&lt;/em&gt; @JorjaFoxofficia what will be your next philanthropical project? #csi&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;#8212; LeFox @JorjaFoxofficia&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;A:&lt;/em&gt; @NahmenJaydenFBI I&amp;rsquo;m one of the producers on a doc called Extinction Soup. #CSI&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#8212;-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/jorjafoxofficia/status/441420967848329216&#34;&gt;Tweet&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;-David B @DMan016&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Q:&lt;/em&gt; @CSI_CBS @JorjaFoxofficia @ericszmanda I still love the Doll House Killer. One of the best stories on #CSI&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;#8212; LeFox @JorjaFoxofficia&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;A:&lt;/em&gt; @DMan016 @CSI_CBS @ericszmanda my nemesis! #CSI&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#8212;-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/jorjafoxofficia/status/441421153228169216&#34;&gt;Tweet&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;#8212; Ashley @ashleynoelle87&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Q:&lt;/em&gt; @JorjaFoxofficia @ericszmanda @ElisabethHarnoi @kingoftrace Is George&amp;rsquo;s sexy accent distracting when you have to remember your lines?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;#8212; LeFox @JorjaFoxofficia&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;A:&lt;/em&gt; @ashleynoelle87 @ericszmanda @ElisabethHarnoi @kingoftrace Yes! #CSI&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#8212;-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/jorjafoxofficia/status/441421361685094400&#34;&gt;Tweet&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;-Marianne. @mymurdergene&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
@JorjaFoxofficia I quote &amp;ldquo;Do you thing there&amp;rsquo;s a murder gene?&amp;rdquo;, so do you think Sara has it? #csi&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;#8212; LeFox @JorjaFoxofficia&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;A:&lt;/em&gt; @mymurdergene Sara is a pacifist, through and through. #CSI&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#8212;-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/jorjafoxofficia/status/441421616304496641&#34;&gt;Tweet&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;#8212; Fernando&amp;hellip; @In_MyRemains&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Q:&lt;/em&gt; @JorjaFoxofficia Do you like Beyonce&amp;rsquo;s songs? #csi&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;#8212; LeFox @JorjaFoxofficia&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;A:&lt;/em&gt; @In_MyRemains Yes! #CSI&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#8212;-&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/jorjafoxofficia/status/441421777583882240&#34;&gt;Tweet&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;-Lauren&amp;hellip; @LAUR3N_&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Q:&lt;/em&gt; @jorjafoxofficia Do you still like the Kings of Convenience? :) #CSI&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;#8212; LeFox @JorjaFoxofficia&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;A:&lt;/em&gt; .@LAUR3N_ yes, love them! #CSI&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#8212;-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/jorjafoxofficia/status/441421974116392961&#34;&gt;Tweet&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;#8212; Chayenne Valentini @Chayeenne&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Q:&lt;/em&gt; @JorjaFoxofficia how about a &amp;ldquo;HELLO&amp;rdquo; for your brazilian fans ? #CSI&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;#8212; LeFox @JorjaFoxofficia&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;A:&lt;/em&gt; @Chayeenne obrigado! #CSI&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#8212;-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/jorjafoxofficia/status/441422382201176064&#34;&gt;Tweet&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;#8212; ¡ Courtney ¡ @CourtneyLinn18&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Q:&lt;/em&gt; @JorjaFoxofficia What is your favorite Beyoncé song? #CSI&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;#8212; LeFox @JorjaFoxofficia&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;A:&lt;/em&gt; @CourtneyLinn18 Why Don&amp;rsquo;t You Love Me #CSI&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#8212;-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/JorjaFoxofficia/status/441422382201176064&#34;&gt;Tweet&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;#8212; I ¥gsr @ysksm1&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Q:&lt;/em&gt; @NatC101712 @JorjaFoxofficia @ericszmanda @SandNole And he isn&amp;rsquo;t Grissom #csi&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;#8212; Morganders Hope @morganders4&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Q:&lt;/em&gt; @ysksm1 @NatC101712 @JorjaFoxofficia @ericszmanda @SandNole #Morgandersonly #AntiSandles #sorrynotsorry #CSI&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;#8212; LeFox @JorjaFoxofficia&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;A:&lt;/em&gt; .@morganders4 @ysksm1 @NatC101712 @ericszmanda @SandNole fair enough. #CSI&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#8212;-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/JorjaFoxofficia/status/441422489114005504&#34;&gt;Tweet&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;#8212; Miranda Bristow Wgnr @mirandawagner2&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Q:&lt;/em&gt; @JorjaFoxofficia you don&amp;rsquo;t age do you? Look the same from season one FYI #CSI&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;#8212; LeFox @JorjaFoxofficia&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;A:&lt;/em&gt; .@mirandawagner2 not true, but thank you very much! #CSI&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#8212;-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/jorjafoxofficia/status/441422570508673024&#34;&gt;Tweet&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;#8212; LeFox @JorjaFoxofficia&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Thank you so much. You guys are the best fans in the galaxy! #CSI&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#8212;-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/JorjaFoxofficia/status/441423071061106688&#34;&gt;Tweet&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;#8212; LeFox @JorjaFoxofficia&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
CSI co-workers, wonderful work tonight! #CSI&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SuperPopACCESS</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2014/superpopaccess/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2014/superpopaccess/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;INTERVIEW - Eric Szmanda, Jorja Fox on the best part about Grammy weekend at Universal Music Group 2014 Post Grammy Party at The Ace Hotel Theater on 2014-01-26 in Los Angeles, California.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Interviewer&lt;/strong&gt;: [&amp;hellip;] this weekend?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Eric Szmanda&lt;/strong&gt;: Well this was both of our first times going to the ceremony and I think it was one of the best ones that I&amp;rsquo;ve seen in recent years. One of my favorite artists kind of swept the awards. Daft Punk won album of the year &amp;#8212;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt;: Again and again!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Eric&lt;/strong&gt;: &amp;#8212; Song of the year &amp;#8212;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jorja: Again and again! It was very exciting.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Eric&lt;/strong&gt;: It was very cool to see to see them up there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Interviewer&lt;/strong&gt;: And then who have you guys actually had a chance to meet that was insane for you?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja&lt;/strong&gt;: Eric Szmanda. I mean, my life changed forever when I met this man. You mean tonight?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Interviewer&lt;/strong&gt;: That was very sweet!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja&lt;/strong&gt;: Well, it&amp;rsquo;s true! It is true. I think I&amp;rsquo;m hoping to meet someone, still, tonight.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Eric:&lt;/strong&gt; We met a lot of nice people that work with CBS.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Interviewer:&lt;/strong&gt; Well go enjoy yourselves, guys. Thank you.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interviews (2014)</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2014/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2014/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;table class=&#34;jfoinfobox&#34;&gt;

	&lt;thead&gt;&lt;tr&gt;
		&lt;th&gt;Date&lt;/th&gt;
		&lt;th&gt;Source&lt;/th&gt;
	&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/thead&gt;

	&lt;tbody&gt;
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		

			&lt;tr&gt;
				&lt;td&gt;January 26&lt;/td&gt;
				&lt;td&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2014/superpopaccess/&#34;&gt;SuperPopACCESS&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
			&lt;/tr&gt;

		
	
		

		

			&lt;tr&gt;
				&lt;td&gt;March 05&lt;/td&gt;
				&lt;td&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2014/twitter-live-chat/&#34;&gt;Twitter Live Chat&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
			&lt;/tr&gt;

		
	
		

		

			&lt;tr&gt;
				&lt;td&gt;October 18&lt;/td&gt;
				&lt;td&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2014/green-with-tiffany/&#34;&gt;Green with Tiffany&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
			&lt;/tr&gt;

		
	
		

		

			&lt;tr&gt;
				&lt;td&gt;December 05&lt;/td&gt;
				&lt;td&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2014/redcarpetreport-tv/&#34;&gt;RedCarpetReport TV&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
			&lt;/tr&gt;

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
		

		
	
	&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ISSUES with Jane Velez-Mitchell</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2013/issues-with-jane-velez-mitchell/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2013/issues-with-jane-velez-mitchell/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jane Velez-Mitchell: CSI star Jorja Fox plays a determined crime scene investigator, who won&amp;rsquo;t let anything stand in her pursuit of the truth. When she&amp;rsquo;s off the set, she&amp;rsquo;s just as determined to free animals from captivity. I talked to Jorja about why she thinks Blackfish is a giant step for all animals in captivity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[Clip of CSI]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jane Velez-Mitchell: Jorja Fox, you play Sara Sidle on CSI and you do such a great job of investigating. In this movie, Blackfish, the director describes it as an investigation into what lies below the surface. Do you relate to that?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jorja Fox: Absolutely, and I&amp;rsquo;m so very thrilled that this documentary is out there and it&amp;rsquo;s going to be televised. I think that this is an issue that people are really going to respond to in a powerful, powerful way. And it&amp;rsquo;s a story whose time has come.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jane Velez-Mitchell: So when Sea World says &amp;ldquo;Hey, we&amp;rsquo;re the leaders in animal husbandry, we&amp;rsquo;re breeding these orcas in captivity.&amp;rdquo; is that a good thing or a bad thing in your opinion?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jorja Fox: It&amp;rsquo;s a bad thing, in my opinion. And it&amp;rsquo;s a pointless thing, in my opinion. It&amp;rsquo;s absolutely pointless. These animals live really long lives, sometimes, if they&amp;rsquo;re lucky, they live shorter lives. A life in captivity, for a wild marine mammal, is a life of suffering and misery and loneliness. It goes against every innate desire that they have.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[Clip of the movie]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jorja Fox: A good number of these captive orcas and killer whales were rounded up in a certain time in history. We have watched these pods in the wild for many years. We know where most of these orcas and killer whales, we know where their families are, we know where their pods are &amp;#8212;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jane Velez-Mitchell: So you endorse what Russell Simmons suggested? Change it radically, eliminate the performance of the orcas or shut down?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jorja Fox: I think the future that we&amp;rsquo;re looking at, if these animals can&amp;rsquo;t be released into the wild, then we can do much better by them. I&amp;rsquo;m talking about sanctuaries, I&amp;rsquo;m talking about ecological preserves, marine preserves, where these animals can live out their lives in somewhat more of a normal way. My first and foremost idea would be lets release as many of these animals as we can into the wild, and lets take the risk and see what happens.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(COMMERCIAL BREAK)&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Talk (23 October 2013)</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2013/the-talk-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2013/the-talk-2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sara Gilbert:&lt;/strong&gt; I have to congratulate you guys on 300 episodes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[audience cheers]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; [pointing at Eric] He&amp;rsquo;s the only man in the pilot. Right here. All 300.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sara Gilbert:&lt;/strong&gt; You&amp;rsquo;ve been there since the first season, but I heard, Jorja, that you didn&amp;rsquo;t think the show was gonna take off.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; No, and I can say that we&amp;rsquo;re [Jorja and Eric] getting old. [laughter] I can&amp;rsquo;t speak for you guys [Elisabeth and Ted] at all. When I see a grey hair on his [Eric&amp;rsquo;s] head, I&amp;rsquo;m done. I&amp;rsquo;m out. That&amp;rsquo;s when it&amp;rsquo;s over. [group laughter] I though, &amp;ldquo;Okay it&amp;rsquo;s this show about death. It&amp;rsquo;s gonna be on a Friday night. Death in the Western Hemisphere culture, not so much.&amp;rdquo; I thought we were doomed. I thought we were gonna do six shows and we were canceled. I knew &lt;em&gt;I&lt;/em&gt; loved it! And I still love it. It&amp;rsquo;s weird&amp;hellip; we&amp;rsquo;re still here.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Aisha Tyler:&lt;/strong&gt; That&amp;rsquo;s awesome.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[audience applause]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[interview with Eric, Elisabeth, and Ted]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Julie Chen:&lt;/strong&gt; Now Jorja. The show is so serious, and you guys have such a great sense of humor, but it must get dark on the set at times because of the content. What do you do between takes to lighten the mood?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; Well, as a matter of fact, we have one of the great funny men of all time on the show now: Mr. Ted Danson. [audience laughter and cheers] And he &amp;#8212; he does some dancing. He was a competitive dancer, yeah, and many times, when it gets a little intense, you dance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ted Danson:&lt;/strong&gt; You know what it is? My hips are going. I fall. [audience laughter] I sway and fall and it looks like a dance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Julie Chen:&lt;/strong&gt; Are you gonna bust a move?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Aisha Tyler:&lt;/strong&gt; Yeah! We were hoping that &amp;#8212;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Julie Chen:&lt;/strong&gt; Come on, you&amp;rsquo;ve got to. One or two steps.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[audience cheers this idea on]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ted Danson:&lt;/strong&gt; I&amp;rsquo;ll dance, if Jorja &amp;#8212; cause she does these funny things where she takes her clothes off-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[The Talk ladies break into hysterics, Jorja laughs]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Julie Chen:&lt;/strong&gt; Fair is fair!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; Not in these heels, they&amp;rsquo;re not right for a dance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ted Danson:&lt;/strong&gt; No no! I will, but you&amp;rsquo;ve got to [laughter]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Julie Chen:&lt;/strong&gt; We want to keep it PG here! Maybe later Ted will bust a move. [&amp;hellip;]eros as an actor, and from the first day that we worked together, you kind of looked him in the eye and there was- as if we&amp;rsquo;d know each other ten years. He&amp;rsquo;s a master at intimacy. It&amp;rsquo;s not forced, it&amp;rsquo;s authentic, and it comes from, you know, like &amp;#8216;actor to actor.&amp;rsquo; I&amp;rsquo;ve said this before, but I swear he&amp;rsquo;s got wings on. Like under his jacket, there&amp;rsquo;s wings. He is an amazing guy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[group &amp;#8216;awwww&amp;rsquo; and applause]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Chen:&lt;/strong&gt; Now, in addition to your work on CSI, you work on other projects including &amp;#8212; there&amp;rsquo;s one that&amp;rsquo;s coming out later this year, and you&amp;rsquo;re really proud of it. It&amp;rsquo;s called &amp;ldquo;How I Became An Elephant.&amp;rdquo; Tell us about that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; Thank you for asking about that. It&amp;rsquo;s a documentary, feature documentary, that I produced a couple years ago. It&amp;rsquo;s really the story of a young girl, from southern California, who travels to Thailand to rescue an elephant. The heart of the story is that no matter how old you are or where you&amp;rsquo;re from or where your circumstances are, if you have a passion about something, you can make a difference. One person &lt;em&gt;can&lt;/em&gt; make a difference. The larger picture, of course, the umbrella is it&amp;rsquo;s a movie about wildlife habitats and environmentalism and preserving these wild places so that these creatures can continue to have a place to live.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[applause]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; Thank you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Chen:&lt;/strong&gt; Jorja Fox everyone, Jorja Fox. CSI: Crime Scene Investigation airs Wednesday at ten, right here on CBS. We&amp;rsquo;ll be back.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CBS CSI300 EPK</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2013/cbs-csi300-epk/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2013/cbs-csi300-epk/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jorja Fox: I was blown away by it, it was so different and I hadn&amp;rsquo;t seen anything ever like it. A show about death, on a Friday night? This is going to be canceled in six weeks, no one&amp;rsquo;s going to watch this! America&amp;rsquo;s not gonna watch this show! And boy was I &amp;hellip; that was extremely wrong about that! [breaks up laughing]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jorja Fox: It&amp;rsquo;s a great place to go back to. And also, under the umbrella of justice and truth and really trying to get to the heart of a very sad story is really awesomely compelling, I think, for us to get to tell.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jorja Fox: Being on a successful show is the cooling thing that could ever happen to a person. I wouldn&amp;rsquo;t trade it for anything. But I think &amp;hellip; I show up because I love being with the people that I get to work with every day.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mill Valley Film Festival Screening (05 October 2013)</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2013/mill-valley-film-festival-screening/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Oct 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2013/mill-valley-film-festival-screening/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;introduction:d8a5738ef7f3b53ed23480f0c7f01a6f&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Announcer:&lt;/strong&gt; Please, before we start anything, give a big hand to Pacific Sun, who is responsible for letting &lt;em&gt;Lion Ark&lt;/em&gt; be here today.  The film is co-presented by Animal Defenders International, which had, obviously you&amp;rsquo;ll see, an integral part in the creation of &lt;em&gt;Lion Ark&lt;/em&gt;. We&amp;rsquo;re very happy to have this film, it&amp;rsquo;s a powerful film, it&amp;rsquo;s an exciting film. It&amp;rsquo;s going to subvert a lot of your expectations about both seeing a documentary and about some of the assumptions we had growing up or seeing in our culture. I think it&amp;rsquo;s going to be a really successful event today. Please give a warm welcome to an ambassador for Animal Defenders International, and also the associate producer, Jorja Fox.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; Thank you. Thank you very much. Good afternoon everyone, &lt;em&gt;[Light laughter]&lt;/em&gt; and welcome to the North American premiere of &lt;em&gt;Lion Ark&lt;/em&gt;.  Very exciting day for us. On behalf of the filmmakers, Tim Phillips and Jan Creamer, we want to humbly thank the Mill Valley Film Festival for having us at this incredible event. And we also want to thank you very much for coming out to see the movie.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Being a part of &lt;em&gt;Lion Ark&lt;/em&gt; has been an epic adventure for me, and today is no exception. I&amp;rsquo;m thrilled to get to watch all of you watch the movie. It&amp;rsquo;s very fitting for &lt;em&gt;Lion Ark&lt;/em&gt; that we&amp;rsquo;re premiering here, as it&amp;rsquo;s the first place the first group of lions landed from Bolivia, back in the spring of 2010. Those four lions are living in the PAWS Sanctuary, near [Gulf(?)], California. Moving lions on airplanes is kind of a strange and rare thing. And the city of San Francisco, San Francisco International Airport and the surrounding areas were so very kind to us and welcomed us with a very serene calm and gracious resolve. We&amp;rsquo;re very grateful for that.  &lt;em&gt;Lion Ark&lt;/em&gt;&amp;#8216;s biggest stars, the main stars of the movie, lions, of course couldn&amp;rsquo;t be here today. They&amp;rsquo;re tired from their life in show business. But many of the key human players are here. They&amp;rsquo;ve traveled far and wide, from the United Kingdom to South America.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are having a Q&amp;amp;A immediately after the film, and I very much hope you&amp;rsquo;ll stick around for questions and comments, and to hear from this amazing and diverse group of people who are all experts in their fields. We&amp;rsquo;re also having a party tonight, a bit of a fundraiser for the next chapter of &lt;em&gt;Lion Ark&lt;/em&gt;. We cordially invite all of you to come. It&amp;rsquo;s going to be at Bungalow 44 at six o&amp;rsquo;clock. You can see anyone in the black &lt;em&gt;Lion Ark&lt;/em&gt; t-shirts with clipboards for tickets, and tickets will also be available at the door if we don&amp;rsquo;t sell out. Tickets are $70. As I mentioned, it&amp;rsquo;s a fundraiser. You&amp;rsquo;ll get drinks and appetizers, and a chance to mingle with the filmmakers and the rescue team. We hope to see all of you there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lastly, and I&amp;rsquo;ll be brief, I just want to talk about the film makers. Jane Creamer and Tim Phillips for a minute. Jan and Tim have been working absolutely tirelessly for over thirty years for the betterment of wild and domesticated animals alike, across the globe. They run an organization called Animal Defenders International. This wonderful film that you&amp;rsquo;re about to see highlights just one of their campaigns. Needless to say, they lead very exciting lives. From bustling cities to the most barren and remote landscapes, Jan and Tim have a knack for making friends and allies wherever they go. They&amp;rsquo;re bridge builders, of a sort. Metaphoric bridge building is a very rare skill, a very special skill. I think it&amp;rsquo;s a skill that&amp;rsquo;s sorely lacking in most fields in the landscape today. And I think that it is the Golden Key to finding solutions for our planets&amp;rsquo; issues.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Animal Defenders International works from private support. They depend on private support for the work that they do. If you feel inspired by this film, and I think you will, please offer up your own support, be it a donation, spreading the world, or volunteering, or all of the above. It&amp;rsquo;s ADI&amp;rsquo;s greatest hope &amp;#8212; sorry, forgot to change my page &lt;em&gt;[Jorja laughs at herself]&lt;/em&gt; &amp;#8212; It&amp;rsquo;s ADI&amp;rsquo;s greatest hope to give as many animals as possible, out in the world, a happy ending.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ladies and gentlemen, &lt;em&gt;Lion Ark&lt;/em&gt;. Thank you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#8212;-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;q-a:d8a5738ef7f3b53ed23480f0c7f01a6f&#34;&gt;Q&amp;amp;A&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[Asked how they got involved]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; I think I was lucky I grew up in a very small town in Florida. My grandmother was very influential in my life. She was a rabid environmentalist, and kind of a modern thinker on a lot of levels, and I took after her quite a bit. I think I also &amp;#8212; it was also the &amp;lsquo;80s, and it was music videos and it was new media and there were a couple kids in my school, eccentric kids in my school, who were vegetarians and would talk about that stuff. It kind of opened a door for me to learn as much as I could. I had a lot to do with books at that time too. I think it&amp;rsquo;s amazing, in the few short years since the &amp;lsquo;80s, how far some of these ideas have come. I really do think we&amp;rsquo;re reaching a tipping point with animals and entertainment and circuses and zoos. There&amp;rsquo;s better options. There&amp;rsquo;s PAWS and the Wild Animal Sanctuary and I think we&amp;rsquo;re starting to get those ideas, and I think we&amp;rsquo;re going to see some really positive changes over the next ten, fifteen, years. Maybe we&amp;rsquo;ll be thinking that&amp;rsquo;s really a thing of the past, it&amp;rsquo;s really not that cool to see an animal in a cage do a trick, like roll a ball or whatever. There&amp;rsquo;s far cool things they can do.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[How do they get all these animals in circuses?]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; You (Jan Creamer) kind of just said what I was going to say. Most of it, especially in the United States, all comes from breeding programs. The animals are here. It&amp;rsquo;s actually very difficult now to get them across International borders. People do it, sometimes for the right reasons, and sometimes not. I think there&amp;rsquo;s a whole bunch of animals up at PAWS that started out in somebody&amp;rsquo;s basement. They bought it on a black market, it was a pet for a time, and then it got too big, too strong, and they had to figure out what to do with it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#8212;-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Post Screening&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; You know, I love the film so much. And I&amp;rsquo;ve really only seen it finished twice, so today was my second time. I was moved a little more than I wanted to be, &amp;lsquo;cause I was in this public theater with a lot of people. I wanted to be so very cool and calm and collected. It was a thrill and a half. It was amazing. We&amp;rsquo;re so happy to be here at the Mill Valley Festival. We want to thank everybody or having us.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Interviewer:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;[unintelligible question]&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; Yeah, I think so. Not too many people left early, so that&amp;rsquo;s always a really good sign. I do, I kind of see the film as an action/adventure piece. It is a documentary, and it&amp;rsquo;s real events, but to me there&amp;rsquo;s a lot of hair-raising, edge-of-your-seats moments, and yes, I think the audience very much stayed with us for the film.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Interviewer:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;[unintelligible question]&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; Why did I have to make it? I think I was lucky to get to be a part of the film. The events, moving the lions from Bolivia to the United States a couple years ago, I got to be a part of that move, and at the time I remember somebody saying &amp;ldquo;Oh yeah, we&amp;rsquo;re documenting this.&amp;rdquo; and we all had mics on. I was just really thrilled to get to be a part of it. It was, I think, an epic accomplishment to move 28 lions 48,000 miles to a sanctuary. I really wasn&amp;rsquo;t sure that it could be done, that it could be pulled off. Certainly there would be some hitch somewhere along the way. You know, it&amp;rsquo;s funny. For a movie that&amp;rsquo;s so exciting, so much of the work that went into the actual move was so slow, and meticulous and methodical, including securing these laws on traveling circuses throughout the world. It&amp;rsquo;s very tedious work. It was a miracle that it all came together.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Interviewer:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;[unintelligible question]&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; It&amp;rsquo;s Northern California, I love this part of the country, I come here often. I think that Mill Valley is a very peaceful place, it&amp;rsquo;s a place that&amp;rsquo;s very connected with the nature surrounding it. There&amp;rsquo;s water everywhere, it&amp;rsquo;s in the foothills and the redwoods. There&amp;rsquo;s amazing surfing and sailing. So particularly, not only for this film, &lt;em&gt;Lion Ark&lt;/em&gt;, I think it&amp;rsquo;s a perfect match in terms of content in a place, but also for me as a person who&amp;rsquo;s a surfer and an outdoor person, it&amp;rsquo;s always good to be up here. I love the food here. I love the wine, I love the coffee. It&amp;rsquo;s a really great place to visit, and I&amp;rsquo;m sure a great place to live.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CableTV.com</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2013/cabletv-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2013/cabletv-1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Monica Gleberman&lt;/strong&gt; .. and just ask you, how did you get involved in acting to begin with?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; Oh my goodness. I wanted to act since I was probably four or five years old. I think that the television that sat in the living room of my house was one of the bigger influences in my life. It was definitely a babysitter for me. You know, I grew up in a small town, so there weren&amp;rsquo;t many acting programs. And it was high school before I was able to be in a drama class. I think there were two things that happened. First of all I love it so much, and then second of all, people were really supportive of me, and doing acting. I think I had a lot of support doing it, and so there was no doubt in my mind. I went to New York and got lucky. I got in [something] very quickly because I ignored all these signs that said &amp;ldquo;Do Not Enter.&amp;rdquo; [laughter] I didn&amp;rsquo;t have an agency, you know &amp;#8216;Don&amp;rsquo;t go beyond this point.&amp;rsquo; And I sort of ignored all of those signs that told me not to go further and landed up in an agency, and I was able to have a conversation with my agency and I had an audition, and they started sending me out. It was so processed. But definitely I started my career in New York and was there for probably seven years before ending up in Los Angeles.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Monica&lt;/strong&gt; I have followed your career, and of course I did research before this. You have had some major television show lucky jobs. Some of the biggest shows known to man. So I want to ask you, of course you were on ER, you were on The West Wing. What was it like- I know when you&amp;rsquo;re on it, you might not think &amp;#8216;This is huge&amp;rsquo; and might not realize how big it is. But looking back, reflecting back on your appearances, what does that feel like? To look back and note that you were on these two shows that are probably going down in history as some of the best television?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja&lt;/strong&gt; Oh wow. Thank you. I think it was huge at the time for me. &lt;em&gt;ER&lt;/em&gt; in particular because I started on &lt;em&gt;ER&lt;/em&gt; in season three and they were the number one show in the country and those numbers were bigger then what you see now because there was less television to choose from. And less appointment television. I don&amp;rsquo;t know if you remember, but people had to actually turn on the TV at the right time. VCR&amp;rsquo;s existed but even then, people wanted to a lot of the bigger shows live so they could talk about them the next day. So I was terrified. Even though I hadnât watched ER, it was my momâs favorite show and a lot of my friends favorite shows and I was absolutely terrified when I got the job because I felt like in a week or two&amp;rsquo;s time, everyone in America was going to know I was an impostor. That I was just claiming to be an actor and I was terrible. So I came really close to just driving to Mexico the week before I started and forgetting the whole thing. But I&amp;rsquo;m glad I didn&amp;rsquo;t. I always felt it was a pretty incredible learning experience, to get to spend time with that caliber of people every day, writers and actors and BPs(?) and directors.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And absolutely the same goes for &lt;em&gt;West Wing&lt;/em&gt;. I think &lt;em&gt;West Wing&lt;/em&gt;&amp;hellip; I was a huge fan then, of Sorkin, and &lt;em&gt;ER&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;West Wing&lt;/em&gt; had a number of the same producers. I think the thing that surprised me the most for myself was I could get to be a part of telling a wonderful story like that. It was something that I hadn&amp;rsquo;t even dreamed of. I just felt like it was such an honor to get to try and tell that story. I really like looked after Martin Sheen&amp;rsquo;s daughter. I couldn&amp;rsquo;t believe it! I got to do something like that! I think that Sorkin, he said at the time on &lt;em&gt;West Wing&lt;/em&gt;, he&amp;rsquo;s alone, and there had been very few women Secret Service Agents at that time, that had actually been on screen. Even getting to be that, getting to be this female Secret Service Agent was kind of a lot of fun that people hadn&amp;rsquo;t gotten to do.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Monica&lt;/strong&gt; And I know, obviously, you&amp;rsquo;ve done a ton of movies and other TV shows, and then you land &lt;em&gt;CSI&lt;/em&gt;. Which, again, another- it&amp;rsquo;s like crazy, your career, because it&amp;rsquo;s another huge show! So I want to go back to Season one, and what that was like, finding out you&amp;rsquo;re going to be playing Sara, and where your mind was when you got that call.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja&lt;/strong&gt; Um. That was also a big surprise. I really didnât think that &lt;em&gt;CSI&lt;/em&gt; was going to be successful. I fell in love with the story and the idea of it. Again, at the time it was something that was pretty different and something that I hadnât really read about often. You know, &lt;em&gt;Quincy&lt;/em&gt; was sort of the thing that I could think of that sort of reminded me a little of &lt;em&gt;CSI&lt;/em&gt;. And I thought nobody was really going to watch a show about death on a Friday night, that is just kind of not a really American culture thing to do. I was so wrong about that. I really thought I would do &lt;em&gt;CSI&lt;/em&gt;, have some fun and be back on &lt;em&gt;The West Wing&lt;/em&gt; by Christmas. You know, that&amp;rsquo;s what I thought was going to happen! I thought the show was going to get canceled and here I am thirteen years later. And it was just this monster. Not &amp;#8212; I guess monster&amp;rsquo;s kind of &amp;#8212; this behemoth that none of us expected. I think that nobody could have imagined how big the ride was going to get.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And thank you for saying that! I&amp;rsquo;m actually starting my eighteenth consecutive season in a row on Prime Time television. It&amp;rsquo;s big for me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Monica&lt;/strong&gt; I know! It&amp;rsquo;s crazy!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja&lt;/strong&gt; So thanks for talking about that stuff.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Monica&lt;/strong&gt; I want to ask- so were you surprised &amp;#8212; before we get into Sara and where she&amp;rsquo;s gone over the course of- and now we&amp;rsquo;re in- there&amp;rsquo;s gonna be a fourteenth season. I want to ask you, I know that in 2007 you had announced that you were leaving the show. Were you surprised at how many fans freaked out and started sending in gifts and money and started a campaign to try to keep you on &lt;em&gt;CSI&lt;/em&gt;? Was that shocking to you at how many people cared about this character?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja&lt;/strong&gt; Absolutely. Yes. Absolutely. It was one of the most magnificent experiences. I had no idea there would be that kind of a response. Truthfully, that was my season twelve in a row, and I was tired. I was just thinking &amp;#8216;Oh my god, I just need to lie down for a minute.&amp;rsquo; I just needed to kind of sit down and reground. So I wanted to get off-screen before it started to show on screen, or before my coworkers started to notice. It was an amazing show of support, and I wished I could have changed my mind to show the fans the amount of gratitude I had for them suggesting that I stay. Honestly, if I wasn&amp;rsquo;t so exhausted, I absolutely would have. So yeah, it was an amazing feeling of surprise.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Monica&lt;/strong&gt; So now that you&amp;rsquo;re back, and you&amp;rsquo;ve been back for a while, everyone&amp;rsquo;s been super excited. I want to know from you how has Sara changed from season one, I know she&amp;rsquo;s had a lot of life changes with the proposal and getting married, but how has she changed from season one to season thirteen?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja&lt;/strong&gt; It&amp;rsquo;s funny. I think in some ways she really hasnât changed that much [laughs]. There&amp;rsquo;s been some &lt;em&gt;seemingly&lt;/em&gt; big changes. When we met Sara in 2000, if anything I think she was very much a product of her past and of her history and the things she experienced as a young kid. You know, her mother killed her father and she was in foster care for a period of time. I think that she had this drive to be a CSI that definitely stems from her experiences as a kid. I think when she left in season 7, and was gone most of season 8, she had a chance to really wrestle those demons and maybe not feel like she is controlled by her past anymore. She kind of cleared all of the ghosts out for herself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And yet, here we are in season thirteen and I feel like we have a very mature character, who is just as passionate about the cases and just as invested, but is somehow free of her history and that is kind of the way I&amp;rsquo;ve been playing the character for the last couple of season. And yet at the same time, now we are in season fourteen, I do feel that Sara- there is this compulsive drive, something very deep rooted. She can&amp;rsquo;t stop being a CSI, it&amp;rsquo;s what fuels her, maybe the duration of her life, she&amp;rsquo;s going to be there in the trenches, on the street, in the muck, in the darkness, trying to get justice for people. I&amp;rsquo;m looking at it again, myself, and like &amp;ldquo;huh!&amp;rdquo; I thought the compulsive side of her was finished, and now maybe it&amp;rsquo;s not, not at all. Maybe she&amp;rsquo;s just the same.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Monica&lt;/strong&gt; What can fans look forward to this season? What kind of cases? What are you guys going to get involved with, cause there&amp;rsquo;s always a craziness happening every episode. So what can fans expect this season for the upcoming episodes?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja&lt;/strong&gt; I think so far &amp;#8212; we are in the middle of episode 7 and I&amp;rsquo;ve seen the script for eight, and I think we have an amazing season opening up. Really exciting. We have some incredible guest stars including somebody likeâ¦ oh you know what I donât know if I could say cause I don&amp;rsquo;t know if I&amp;rsquo;m a spoiler alert. [laughs] We have some really interesting guest stars and a cooking show in episode four that is kind of based on these food contests on the food networks. There is funny stuff, there is haunting stuff â I think the writers this year again, they suggested to me, they like to pick a theme every season, and this one is definitely going to be about darkness and going darker and going deeper.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s going to be a darker season of &lt;em&gt;CSI&lt;/em&gt;, but within that also there&amp;rsquo;s going to be as much character stuff as there was last year. I think they&amp;rsquo;re continuing to write a lot of character stuff, which is great. Certainly we start the season with Morgan in jeopardy, the stakes are really high. We also start the season with a funeral and itâs not really until we get to the end of the show that you, the audience, will come to find out why we&amp;rsquo;re at the funeral and who has passed. Itâs a very compelling kind of suspenseful episode.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You know, yeah it gets crazier every year. I don&amp;rsquo;t know how the writers come up with stuff in season fourteen. The unfortunate thing is there&amp;rsquo;s no shortage of crazy crime in America to draw from. But the stakes continue to get higher, and I hope the fans will continue to enjoy that. I always am partial to the action/adventure show. And so in those episodes where we get a little kooky, hopefully the fans will still be able to roll with us.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Monica&lt;/strong&gt; I wanted to ask you, was it nice that all current cast members continued on for season fourteen?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja&lt;/strong&gt; Absolutely! Because we have had so many changes. You know, part of me, you were speaking about &lt;em&gt;ER&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;ER&lt;/em&gt; began to lose their core cast members in season three. So the fact that our show made it to season seven with the core cast intact, I think is a testament to the show and a compliment to how much we actually did get along and liked working together and did like the work itself. I think very few shows have gone seven seasons retaining their full original cast.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But yes, it&amp;rsquo;s been really nice to have a cast that&amp;rsquo;s been able to stay together for a couple of seasons. You can&amp;rsquo;t fake chemistry. You&amp;rsquo;ve sort of got to build it organically. The more you know each other, the more you work together, the deeper you can go. It&amp;rsquo;s given a chance for that. I think it&amp;rsquo;s been kind of a really great thing for the writers, because there were a lot of seasons where it was really hard for them to start breaking stories over the summer, because they weren&amp;rsquo;t completely sure who their cast was going to be. Knowing early enough that they were going to have everyone has allowed them to spread their wings more than they could for a bunch of season.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This team, this troupe of actors, you never think that &amp;#8216;Wow, three new actors in practically one season. This is definitely- this can&amp;rsquo;t go well. This is going to be difficult.&amp;rsquo; And to love these three actors as much as I do, as much as we all do, we&amp;rsquo;re having so much fun every day. I hope it shows on screen. As usual, I&amp;rsquo;m just grateful I get to come here and hang out, because it&amp;rsquo;s a really fun place to be.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Monica&lt;/strong&gt; Of course I have to ask too, season fourteen, will mark the 300th episode, which is like, nuts. So what is that? What have you guys, I think it&amp;rsquo;s like mid-season, right? The 300th?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja&lt;/strong&gt; The 300th? Episode five. We&amp;rsquo;re pretty soon, like pretty pretty soon. We&amp;rsquo;re going to do ten new shows in a row. I don&amp;rsquo;t think we&amp;rsquo;ve done that before. And so, yeah, I think five weeks after the premiere tomorrow, you&amp;rsquo;ll be able to see the 300th episode.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Monica&lt;/strong&gt; So what is that like? Being a part of &amp;hellip; I feel like a lot of this interview is about you being a part of these crazy, amazing, genius shows. And not only do you have this awesome career, but you&amp;rsquo;re a part of another benchmark, which is the 300th episode. So what is that like, being a part of?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja&lt;/strong&gt; It was such an honor for me. You know, it is a milestone. I didn&amp;rsquo;t think much about it going in, but then we all showed up for work the first day, and a couple people gave speeches, and I started to feel the gravity of it all. I think it&amp;rsquo;s been a great second chance for me. I missed the 200th episode, I wasn&amp;rsquo;t here. I was here for the 100th episode. And to get to be a part of the 300th episode meant a lot to me. More than I even imagined it would. I haven&amp;rsquo;t done 300 episodes yet, I&amp;rsquo;m behind several members of the cast because I did take that season off, and I don&amp;rsquo;t appear in every episode every year. I think with my combined with my &lt;em&gt;ER&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;West Wing&lt;/em&gt; I might be on episode 296 or something. I can share that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s funny, because &lt;em&gt;ER&lt;/em&gt; went 300 episodes, and Marg Helgenberger, George Eads and myself had all had parts on &lt;em&gt;ER&lt;/em&gt;, so with another show that the three of us can be happy for and be a part of this tiny piece of &lt;em&gt;ER&lt;/em&gt; history. Of course, the history that we have on &lt;em&gt;CSI&lt;/em&gt; is a lot deeper and bigger. It&amp;rsquo;s really cool. I don&amp;rsquo;t think it&amp;rsquo;s ever going to happen to me again, to be a part of something like this. I don&amp;rsquo;t know if it&amp;rsquo;s going to be possible for a lot of shows to get to do this. Most shows are doing 13 episodes a year instead of 24, which is what we started out with. It takes a long time doing 13 episodes a season to get to 300 episodes. I think this is kind of a marker we may not see that much of in the future. It meant a lot and I&amp;rsquo;m really proud of- for everyone. I&amp;rsquo;m really proud of everyone and just very excited to get to be a part of it. It&amp;rsquo;s cool.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Monica&lt;/strong&gt; I want to ask, and I know it could be a little spoiler, but in the 300th episode, I&amp;rsquo;ve heard rumors there might be some flash backs? Is that&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja&lt;/strong&gt; Ah yes. Flashbacks slash faux-backs. [laughs] That&amp;rsquo;s what we&amp;rsquo;re calling them. We did out best. It has been thirteen years. [laughs] Thirteen meaningful years. But it was truly fun and embarrassing and silly to try and do it- I hope we pulled it off. I hope the fans enjoy it. There&amp;rsquo;s- You know it&amp;rsquo;s not a huge chunk of the show, but three flashbacks. Four I think! We go back to 2000. There&amp;rsquo;s some funny clothes, and funny hairstyles. I threw in a wig. And it&amp;rsquo;s great. We do, we&amp;rsquo;re- the episode is really about a cold case from 2000, that has certainly haunted Sara for the last thirteen years. And I think it, within the show, Sara feels a certain exuberance at having a second chance at a case she thought had really slipped through her fingers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So not only did I get a second chance to be a part of something so exciting, but she&amp;rsquo;s getting a second chance to really try and find justice for somebody who&amp;rsquo;s living a nightmare several times.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Monica&lt;/strong&gt; Is there anything else you want to tell to the fans who are super excited &amp;#8212; they&amp;rsquo;re counting down the hours to the premiere. Is there anything you want to say to them? Anything about the season or just in general that you want them to know?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja&lt;/strong&gt; I think yes. I wanna say to all the fans of CSI, thank you so much! Thank you thank you thank you thank you for your support all these years. We are continually surprised and completely elated that we get ratings every years, that we continue to get to be on this show and do these things, that&amp;rsquo;s all because of you. Thank you for your loyalty and your willingness to go on some really crazy rides with us. I hope this year we don&amp;rsquo;t disappoint you and we&amp;rsquo;re really excited to show you what we have coming up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Monica&lt;/strong&gt; Okay! Great! Those were all my questions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja&lt;/strong&gt; Thank you so much, Monica, it was great speaking with you.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>