<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>2007 on Fans of Le Fox Library</title>
    <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/tags/2007/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 2007 on Fans of Le Fox Library</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2007 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://jorjafox.net/library/tags/2007/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Chicago Sun-Times </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/chicago-sun-times-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/chicago-sun-times-2/</guid>
      <description>REVIEW | Dazzling visuals set pace for TV procedurals, making departure of Fox or anyone else secondary
Jorja Fox fans surely will be bummed when &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; returns with a new episode tonight. Fox left the show a few weeks ago, and she took away her character, Sara Sidle. But don&amp;rsquo;t expect &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; to suffer much because, duh, the true star of America&amp;rsquo;s No. 1 drama is its sci-fi special effects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Buddy TV </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/buddy-tv-12/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/buddy-tv-12/</guid>
      <description>Though Sara Sidle has already left &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo;, fans of the forensic drama are still determined to convey their support to her portrayer, Jorja Fox.
Previously, fans combined their efforts to come up with a &amp;ldquo;Jorja Fox Appreciation Campaign&amp;rdquo; to prevent the 39-year-old actress from leaving the show. When Fox officially exited the CBS series, the excess money raised by the crusade was donated to charity. And now that the campaign is over, a new drive is being created that aims to thank the former &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; actress.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Guide </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/tv-guide-27/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/tv-guide-27/</guid>
      <description>Question: Just wanted to thank you for your recent comments about &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; and Jorja Fox. Your response to Sandra S.&amp;rsquo; question about whether Grissom and Sara&amp;rsquo;s relationship hurt &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; was the most accurate evaluation of their romance and the last couple of seasons of the show that I&amp;rsquo;ve read. It was nice to see someone in the media not jumping on the &amp;ldquo;they turned the show into a soap opera!&amp;rdquo; bandwagon, which so many fans inexplicably have joined.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Guide</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/tv-guide-21/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/tv-guide-21/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
Question: There has been speculation that in last week&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo;, the letter Sara left for Grissom wasn&amp;rsquo;t a breakup letter but a suicide note. Do you know anything about this? &amp;ndash; Ginny
Ausiello: I know that&amp;rsquo;s a pretty silly theory, considering what Carol Mendelsohn told me last month.
[&amp;hellip;]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The View</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2007/the-view/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Nov 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2007/the-view/</guid>
      <description>Jorja Fox: Thank you, so honored to be here with all of you. &amp;ldquo;(to Whoopi)&amp;rdquo; And happy birthday to you, a day late.
Joy: You&amp;rsquo;ve been here a few times&amp;hellip;
Jorja Fox: This is my fourth round. Second time in the hot seat &amp;ldquo;(pats the table)&amp;rdquo;, and I&amp;rsquo;m just very excited. And awake.
Whoopi: Yeah. Well awake isn&amp;rsquo;t always important. Me, halfway. But let me ask you - you, you&amp;rsquo;re about to make a big change in your life, are you not?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BuddyTV </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/buddy-tv-11/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/buddy-tv-11/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ll preface this by admitting that I was not a big Sara fan. I think I turned against Jorja Fox after the first contract dispute. To me, &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; is more of an ensemble show, so even though I have my favorites, *cough* Warrick *cough*, I resented the impression I got that she thought she was more important than any of the others. Besides that, I kinda wanted Lady Heather to loosen Grissom up a bit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CTV </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/ctv-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/ctv-2/</guid>
      <description>Last Thursday marked the departure of Sara Sidle (Jorja Fox) from the long-running hit drama &amp;ldquo;CSI.&amp;rdquo;
Appearing as a guest co-host on &amp;ldquo;The View&amp;rdquo; this week, Fox says she&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;fortunate&amp;rdquo; to have been a part of the series. She went on to say that the decision to leave was &amp;ldquo;the hardest decision I ever made.&amp;rdquo;
The actress is an original cast member from debut season in 2000, as a quasi love interest for lead investigator Gil Grissom.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chinaview.cn </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/chinaview-cn/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/chinaview-cn/</guid>
      <description>After eight seasons on one of TV&amp;rsquo;s highest-rated shows, Jorja Fox left the CBS drama &amp;ldquo;CSI: Crime Scene Investigation&amp;rdquo; Thursday night.
Fox, who played Sara Sidle in the hot TV series, has told several publications that she decided not to renew her contract so she could pursue other interests.
&amp;ldquo;It&amp;rsquo;s one of the hardest decisions I&amp;rsquo;ve made in my life,&amp;rdquo; Fox told Entertainment Weekly. &amp;ldquo;It has nothing to do with my contract, nothing to do with money.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EFlux Media </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/eflux-media/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/eflux-media/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Goodbye and Good Luck&amp;rdquo; was Jorja Fox&amp;rsquo;s last appearance on the popular CBS series &amp;ldquo;CSI,&amp;rdquo; after a seven-year tenure on the show.
Forensic scientist Sara Sidle, the character Fox had portrayed since 2000, was very popular with fans â so much so that, when the actress was fired in 2004. It was a temporary dismissal, as the public reacted strongly, demanding that she return.
Thursday night&amp;rsquo;s episode was the last Fox filmed as Sara Sidle and a worthy farewell for a notable character.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Film.com </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/film-com/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/film-com/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
&amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; is probably a strong enough concept to survive cast changes, witness the success of the two spinoffs. But until now, its producers and CBS have never had to wonder. The original cast from the pilot episode-Petersen, Helgenberger, George Eads, Gary Dourdan, and Paul Guilfoyle-is still intact. Jorja Fox joined the cast for the second episode, and her Sara Sidle character becomes the first major departure from the show tonight.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Guide</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/tv-guide-14/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/tv-guide-14/</guid>
      <description>Question: Jorja Fox&amp;rsquo;s last &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; episode just aired, and that got me to thinking about all the brouhaha back when the relationship between Grissom and Sara was revealed in the Season 6 finale. At the time, there were dire predictions that this was the end of the rope for the series. It had become a soap, turned a corner, jumped the shark, etc. Looking back at it now, do you think that the romance &amp;ndash; its reveal, and the way it was woven into Seasons 7 and 8 &amp;ndash; was a detriment to the show?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Brandeis Hoot </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/the-brandeis-hoot/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/the-brandeis-hoot/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Wouldn&amp;rsquo;t you if you were married to Mrs. Roper?&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;I don&amp;rsquo;t even have to turn around. Sara Sidle.&amp;rdquo;
With this brief interchange, crime scene investigator Sara Sidle made her first appearance on the CBS hit show, CSI: Crime Scene Investigation. Yesterday, she made her final appearance. After a tumultuous seven years on the show, actress Jorja Fox finally packed up her fingerprint kit.
Fox enjoyed a long run of success with the show as a materials and element analysis specialist who was originally brought in during the first season by Gil Grissom (actor William Petersen) to do an internal affairs investigation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zap2It.com </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/zap2it-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/zap2it-2/</guid>
      <description>Which is the better way to go out, with a bang or a whimper? Unlike its Miami-based counterpart, &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; has never been about the bang. The flagship show&amp;rsquo;s characters are more cerebral, its sets dressed in somber blues. It may have made for better storytelling to have Sara Sidle die at the hands of the Miniature Killer, but her actual departure fit better with the show&amp;rsquo;s sensibilities.
[Sara didn&amp;rsquo;t have the sawdust to handle spoilers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Albuquerque Tribune </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/albuquerque-tribune/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/albuquerque-tribune/</guid>
      <description>For months, we&amp;rsquo;ve all known it was coming - the departure of a beloved &amp;ldquo;CSI: Crime Scene Investigation&amp;rdquo; (8 p.m., KRQE News 13) character.
Sara Sidle (Jorja Fox) makes her last appearance in tonight&amp;rsquo;s episode, and mostly this makes me sad.
She&amp;rsquo;s an interesting and complex character who truly bonds with people. I like her eccentricities, and while her hair will never be as cute as Catherine&amp;rsquo;s (Marg Helgenberger), she still manages to look good while knee deep in gross stuff.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Boston Herald </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/boston-herald-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/boston-herald-2/</guid>
      <description>Fans put through ringer on Jorja Fox&amp;rsquo;s farewell episode
Do the creators of &amp;ldquo;CSI: Crime Scene Investigation&amp;rdquo; enjoy torturing their fans?
Jorja Fox&amp;rsquo;s last appearance as a regular (Wednesday night at 9 on WBZ, Ch. 4) was bound to be difficult. &amp;ldquo;Goodbye &amp;amp; Good Luck&amp;rdquo; is excruciating. Given the final moments, the title seems cruelly ironic.
CBS has asked that I refrain from any potential spoilers. If the network were serious, it would have gagged both Fox and the &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; producers weeks ago.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Buddy TV </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/buddy-tv-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/buddy-tv-10/</guid>
      <description>The time has finally come for fans to bid farewell to one of the key players of &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo;. After seven years of playing Sara Sidle, Jorja Fox is ready to exit the forensic drama and move on. But before she leaves, the 39-year-old actress will be portraying her character one last time, giving closure to the &amp;ldquo;Grissom Sara Romance&amp;rdquo; many fans have learned to adore, in tonight&amp;rsquo;s episode entitled &amp;ldquo;Goodbye and Good Luck.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NY Daily News </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/ny-daily-news-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/ny-daily-news-4/</guid>
      <description>Original &amp;ldquo;CSI: Crime Scene Investigation&amp;rdquo; cast member Jorja Fox leaves the hit CBS drama Thursday night, but expect the series to be just fine without her.
&amp;ldquo;CSI,&amp;rdquo; which debuted in 2000, has been the most-watched scripted show on TV for the past five years, and its audience isn&amp;rsquo;t going anywhere.
&amp;ldquo;&amp;#8216;CSI&amp;rsquo; has built its success over the years by being more story-driven than star-driven,&amp;rdquo; Vincent Fitzgerald, who heads the communications department at the College of Mount Saint Vincent in Riverdale, told the Daily News.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New York Post </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/new-york-post-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/new-york-post-3/</guid>
      <description>AS if &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; wasn&amp;rsquo;t de pressing enough, to night&amp;rsquo;s episode is devoted entirely to the disillusionment of Sara Sidle.
It&amp;rsquo;s the long-awaited episode in which sourpuss Sara (Jorja Fox) makes her exit from the show - finally.
Fox had been rumored to be on the way out last season when it seemed as if her character would not survive being pinned under a car in the cliff- hanging final episode following an &amp;ldquo;accident&amp;rdquo; engineered by the serial murderer known as &amp;ldquo;the miniature killer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Newsday.com</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/newsday.com-the-tv-zone/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/newsday.com-the-tv-zone/</guid>
      <description>Watch tonight&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; and you too will understand why Jorja Fox - Sara Sidle - quit.
Murders, suicide, a drag and dump (whatever that is), woman with knife in back, pre-pubescent homicidal insanity&amp;hellip;all within 44 minutes. You&amp;rsquo;d quit too. One wonders what kind of toll this takes on an intelligent sensitive actress like Fox - year after year of it. She told &amp;ldquo;EW&amp;rdquo; that she wanted to start a family, but starting families requires a certain frame of mind, and &amp;ldquo;optimism&amp;rdquo; has to be a basic minimum requirement â optimism about life, your life, and the life of your unborn children.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Orlando Sentinel </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/orlando-sentinel-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/orlando-sentinel-3/</guid>
      <description>Beloved characters deserve fitting farewells, and Sara Sidle (Jorja Fox) receives one tonight from CSI.
The episode, titled &amp;ldquo;Goodbye &amp;amp; Good Luck,&amp;rdquo; vividly makes you feel Sara&amp;rsquo;s disillusionment with her work. In witnessing an eerie case of domestic abuse, she remains oddly remote.
The real crisis for Sara, however, comes from familiar sources. Returning in creepy style are Marlon West (Douglas Smith) and his genius little sister, Hannah (Juliette Goglia).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ottawa Citizen </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/ottawa-citizen/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/ottawa-citizen/</guid>
      <description>CSI is a curiosity. Long before the popular procedural drama became TV&amp;rsquo;s most-watched crime show, it bucked TV convention. CSI debuted on the same night and the same network as a slick, glossy remake of The Fugitive, one of TV&amp;rsquo;s most respected and fondly remembered classics. The conventional wisdom was that The Fugitive remake, starring a dashing Tim Daly, would be a hit, and CSI would be lucky if it played out the string for a season or two.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pittsburgh Post-Gazette </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/pittsburgh-post-gazette-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/pittsburgh-post-gazette-2/</guid>
      <description>Maybe I&amp;rsquo;m too well-adjusted to relate (and that would be a first), but Sara Sidle (Jorja Fox) departs CBS&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;CSI: Crime Scene Investigation&amp;rdquo; (9 tonight) in the most unrealistic, only-on-TV way possible.
To really get into a critique of her departure would entail giving away things that CBS has asked critics not to reveal, but from my perspective, it&amp;rsquo;s not how real people say goodbye to those they love.
The episode finds Sara confronting a case from her past when a crime in the present sends a coed plunging out a dorm room window.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>St. Petersburg Times</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/st-petersburg-times-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/st-petersburg-times-2/</guid>
      <description>When I finally sat down to watch an advance copy of tonight&amp;rsquo;s CSI showing the exit of fan protest magnet Jorja Fox, I couldn&amp;rsquo;t help thinking of Devon Pierce.
If you&amp;rsquo;re a regular blog reader, you know I wrote about Pierce weeks ago, outlining her efforts from a room in her father&amp;rsquo;s Dunedin hearing aid clinic to run a massive fan effort aimed at convincing CSI producers to keep Fox&amp;rsquo;s Sara Sidle character on the show.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>St. Petersburg Times </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/st-petersburg-times/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/st-petersburg-times/</guid>
      <description>Jorja Fox&amp;rsquo;s character is written out of CSI in a way that writes her off.
[&amp;hellip;]
As somebody who has never really understood the popularity of CBS&amp;rsquo;s three blockbuster CSI series, watching each episode is like getting random pokes from a tiny acupuncture needle every time something outlandish happens.
So watching an advance copy of tonight&amp;rsquo;s installment from the mothership CSI, the last episode featuring fan protest magnet Jorja Fox, felt a little like this:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Guide</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/tv-guide-13/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/tv-guide-13/</guid>
      <description>On last week&amp;rsquo;s episode of &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo;, in the crossover stunt featuring &amp;ldquo;Without a Trace**s Jack Malone, Sara Sidle was shown as visibly shaken at an especially unsettling crime scene, walking away as if she&amp;rsquo;d had enough. Her psychological unease and emotional exhaustion had been well established even before last season&amp;rsquo;s cliff-hanger that left her trapped under a car in the desert, as fans wondered all summer if TV&amp;rsquo;s top procedural was going to kill off one of its own.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Fayetteville Observer </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/the-fayetteville-observer/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/the-fayetteville-observer/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
&amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo;
Jorja Fox is one gutsy gal. After eight seasons on one of TV&amp;rsquo;s highest-rated shows, Fox, who plays Sara Sidle, is leaving. She wasn&amp;rsquo;t fired. She decided not to renew her contract so she could pursue other interests. At least that&amp;rsquo;s what she has told several publications. Will she be back? That&amp;rsquo;s what fans of the Sara-Grissom relationship want to know. After all, they are engaged. A season-finale surprise appearance might be the way to go, if you ask me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Mercury News </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/the-mercury-news/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/the-mercury-news/</guid>
      <description>newstitle = &amp;ldquo;Sara leaves &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; and other notes on tonight&amp;rsquo;s TV&amp;rdquo; newsauthor = &amp;ldquo;Charlie McCollum&amp;rdquo; newssource = &amp;ldquo;The Mercury News&amp;rdquo; newsurl = &amp;ldquo;http://blogs.mercurynews.com/aei/2007/11/sara_leaves_csi_and_other_notes_on_tonights_tv.html &amp;ldquo; +++ There are a couple of notable departures on television tonight, csistarting Jorja Fox&amp;rsquo;s last regular appearance as Sara Sidle on &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; (9 p.m., CBS).
As you may already know, Fox &amp;ndash; who has had a sometimes contentious relationship with the folks who produce the series &amp;ndash; decided to bow out of the &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; world earlier this year, giving the writers a chance to prepare a proper farewell to an important character.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Half-Life Source </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/half-life-source/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/half-life-source/</guid>
      <description>The TV hit series CSI will lose Jorja Fox as one of their starring actors.
Jorja Fox, who plays Sara Sidle on &amp;ldquo;CSI,&amp;rdquo; is leaving the show to pursue other opportunities. Fox has been on the show since it premiered in 2000.
Fox first broke the news in October that she would be leaving the hit crime drama to explore other opportunities before she gets too old.
It&amp;rsquo;s not unusual for actors to leave a successful show after a long run to pursue other opportunities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MSNBC </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/msnbc-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/msnbc-2/</guid>
      <description>Jorja Fox&amp;rsquo;s character valuable to show, and she&amp;rsquo;s a role model, readers say
It&amp;rsquo;s not unusual for actors to leave a successful show after a long run to pursue other opportunities. George Clooney did so successfully. But whether or not Jorja Fox can pull off the same feat when she leaves âCSI&amp;rsquo;s&amp;rsquo; Sara Sidle behind is of little worry for fans of the hit crime drama &amp;ndash; they&amp;rsquo;re more concerned that the show will suffer without her.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MSNBC (2) </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/msnbc-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/msnbc-3/</guid>
      <description>Readers dish on why Jorja Fox&amp;rsquo;s departure from &amp;lsquo;CSI&amp;rsquo; should be celebrated
In October, Jorja Fox, who has played Sara Sidle on &amp;lsquo;CSI&amp;rsquo; since the show premiered in 2000, told EW.com she would be leaving the hit crime drama to explore other opportunities &amp;ldquo;before (she) gets too old.&amp;rdquo; We asked readers to weigh in on her departure, and while some fans were upset over the seemingly definite demise of GSR, others were practically jubilant.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>USA Today </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/usa-today-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/usa-today-2/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
&amp;bull;If you&amp;rsquo;re a fan of &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; (CBS, 9 ET/PT), you&amp;rsquo;ve probably heard this was coming. Even if you haven&amp;rsquo;t, you&amp;rsquo;ve probably picked up on the signs the past few weeks, as Jorja Fox&amp;rsquo;s Sara Sidle has given way to horror and despair.
Tonight, Fox says goodbye to Sara and &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo;, exiting in a terrific episode that uses an old case (a child who tricked her back in 2006) to make her confront her current problems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Buddy TV </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/buddy-tv-9/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/buddy-tv-9/</guid>
      <description>In just a few days, viewers will have to say farewell to &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo;&amp;rsquo;s Sara Sidle. After seven years of portraying the Las Vegas forensic scientist and one of the core players of the show, Jorja Fox has ultimately decided to move on and have a break from the commitment of a weekly television series. But before she leaves, she&amp;rsquo;ll be playing Sara one last time in the episode fittingly called &amp;ldquo;Goodbye and Good Luck,&amp;rdquo; which airs on Thursday, November 15.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Official CSI Magazine </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/the-official-csi-magazine/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/the-official-csi-magazine/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;After eight years playing Sara Sidle, Jorja Fox is bitting farewell to&amp;rdquo; CSI: Crime Scene Investigation. &amp;ldquo;In an exclusive interview with&amp;rdquo; The Official CSI Magazine, &amp;ldquo;the actress chats about her final episodes&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo;
November 8, 2007 proved a sad day for &amp;ldquo;CSI: Crime Scene Investigation&amp;rdquo; fans when Sara Sidle left the Las Vegas Crime Lab for the last time. After escaping death at the nads of minature kill Natalie Kimble in the season eight opener &amp;ldquo;Dead Doll,&amp;rdquo; the gutsy CSI had struggled to settle back into her job, with even a marriage proposal from Grissom doing little to raise her spirits.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Orlando Sentinel </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/orlando-sentinel-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/orlando-sentinel-2/</guid>
      <description>Jorja Fox&amp;rsquo;s Sara Sidle leaves &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; Thursday night. No matter how you feel about that development, the episode is tremendous. All actors who depart long-running series should receive such heartfelt, memorable sendoffs.
The episode, titled &amp;ldquo;Goodbye &amp;amp; Good Luck,&amp;rdquo; skillfully makes you feel Sara&amp;rsquo;s disillusionment. She witnesses an eerie case of domestic abuse and remains strangely remote.
But the real crisis for Sara arrives with the return of Marlon West (Douglas Smith) and his genius little sister, Hannah (Juliette Goglia).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Guide Magazine </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/tv-guide-08/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Nov 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/tv-guide-08/</guid>
      <description>Three separate articles/mentions can be found in this issue.
DRAMA CSI: Crime Scene Investigation
CBS, 9/8c Good-bye Sara Sidle! It won&amp;rsquo;t be the same without workaholic Sara, but after tonight&amp;rsquo;s episode the criminologist who ranks No. 1 in the hearts of many viewers &amp;ndash; not to mention Gil Grissom &amp;ndash; parts ways with the crime lab when a case comes back to haunt her.
[&amp;hellip;]
##BYE-BYE, JORJA!
CSI: Crime Scene Investigation (CBS, 9/8c) TV loses its Fox-iest lady tonight as Sara hangs up her goggles and heads out of Grissom&amp;rsquo;s life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PrideSource </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/pridesource/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Nov 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/pridesource/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
Speaking of television returns, Jorja Fox may not be completely gone from &amp;ldquo;CSI.&amp;rdquo; Carol Mendelsohn, head honcho at &amp;ldquo;CSI,&amp;rdquo; has stated that it is a priority for her to woo the lady-loving thespian back to the hit show. When asked directly if Jorja will be back, Mendelsohn said, &amp;ldquo;Yes. You can count on it.&amp;rdquo;
What will Jorja do on her time off? Among other things, she&amp;rsquo;s producing a one-woman show about Dusty Springfield which will star her friend Kirsten Holly Smith.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Defamer (6 November 2007)</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/defamer-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Nov 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/defamer-4/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
Nov 4, Silverlake. Whilst enjoying a nice brunch at my fave place (that i will not name), spotted soon to be former CSI Jorja Fox brunching with some friends. Taller than you&amp;rsquo;d expect and dressed quite frumpily. [&amp;hellip;]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>&#39;RTL.de - Germany</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2007/rtl-de-germany/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2007/rtl-de-germany/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Why Sara decided to leave&amp;rdquo; Jorja Fox: &amp;hellip;you know, a series of events between the whole miniature killer thing and some other events, she&amp;rsquo;d had so many recent close calls. Um, the job was just too much for her to, it was too much with her, and I think she knew that if she asked Grissom to go with her, even if he said yes, that would be the end of him, you know &amp;ldquo;(very emotional)&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MSN.com </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/msn-com/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/msn-com/</guid>
      <description>** Our editor&amp;rsquo;s picks for the best and worst dressed celebs last week.**
[&amp;hellip;]
Jorja Fox
This CSI is in desperate need of the style police. Hopefully she puts more of an effort into her post-CSI job hunt than she does into her wardrobe because this ensemble is seriously lacking in interest. The top is unflattering, the skirt is shapeless and the shoes look more orthopaedic than red carpet ready.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Telestar (November 2007)</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/telestar/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/telestar/</guid>
      <description>Sara Sidle is leaving the TF1 hit series
JORJA FOX
&amp;ldquo;On the 15th of October last year, Jorja Fox shot her last episode of &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo;. It then is an exit for Sara Sidle! For the moment at least.&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;It could be the biggest mistake of my life. Only time will tell.&amp;rdquo; It is with these words that Jorja Fox commented on her last appearance in the show &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; that millions of Americans will watch this coming November.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Guide Online </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/tv-guide-34/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/tv-guide-34/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
Question: Anything on CSI? &amp;ndash; Joel
Ausiello: CBS has finally confirmed Jorja Fox&amp;rsquo;s final air&amp;rdquo; date = Nov. 15.
[&amp;hellip;]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Star Phoenix </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/the-star-phoenix/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/the-star-phoenix/</guid>
      <description>Some shows can&amp;rsquo;t survive characters finally getting together
[&amp;hellip;]
Resolving the sexual tension between the two leads is usually the quickest way to kill the chemistry.
[&amp;hellip;]
3) CSI Las Vegas: Sara Sidle and Gil Grissom
After months of speculation, fans of CSI: Las Vegas were recently informed of the long-time secret affair between Gil Grissom (William Petersen) and Sara Sidle (Jorja Fox). Unfortunately, in the wake of Grissom&amp;rsquo;s recent proposal to Sara (she said yes!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ET</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2007/et/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Oct 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2007/et/</guid>
      <description>Announcer: And sad news for &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; fans as a star says goodbye.
Jorja Fox: That&amp;rsquo;s the end of me for a while
Announcer: At the Frederick&amp;rsquo;s of Hollywood Fashion show last night Jorja Fox told &amp;ldquo;ET&amp;rdquo; the real reason she&amp;rsquo;s leaving CBS&amp;rsquo;s crime solving show
Jorja Fox: I just need to take a little break, and do some evaluating. Hopefully I will return.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>USA Today </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/usa-today-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Oct 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/usa-today-1/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
Jorja Fox, soon to be off CBS&amp;rsquo; &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo;, hoped the evening&amp;rsquo;s sexy lingerie offerings would inspire Hollywood&amp;rsquo;s young to cover up during the coming cooler months: &amp;ldquo;Lingerie is warm enough for everyone to be wearing it,&amp;rdquo; said Fox, who will segue from &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; to producing a one-woman play about bisexual rock star Dusty Springfield, making its debut in January at L.A.&amp;rsquo;s Lily Tomlin Theatre.
[&amp;hellip;]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact Music </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/contact-music/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Oct 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/contact-music/</guid>
      <description>Fans of TV drama CSI: CRIME SCENE INVESTIGATION have started a grassroots online campaign to persuade departing castmember JORJA FOX to stay. Fox announced she was leaving the show in an interview with TV Guide magazine last month (Sep07), sending shockwaves through the programme&amp;rsquo;s avid global fanbase. Her character, Sara Sidle, is a fan favourite and website DollarsForSense.com has been asking fans to send in letters voicing disapproval over Fox&amp;rsquo;s departure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Defamer </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/defamer-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/defamer-3/</guid>
      <description>In this post-Jericho era, any network executive or TV producer who&amp;rsquo;s just signed off on a potentially unpopular change now expects to spend their next day at the office buried underneath an avalanche of foodstuffs delivered by protesting viewers who now believe that even the most stubborn of minds can be changed with a metric ton of peanuts. Discussing the announcement of Jorja Fox&amp;rsquo;s (officially voluntary) departure from CSI with TVGuide.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EW.com </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/ew-7/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/ew-7/</guid>
      <description>The actress&amp;rsquo; decision to leave TV&amp;rsquo;s No. 1 show has &amp;ldquo;nothing to do with money,&amp;rdquo; she tells EW in an exclusive sit-down
In the Sept. 27 premiere of CSI, the show&amp;rsquo;s 25.2 million fans were relieved to learn that not only had Jorja Fox&amp;rsquo;s alter ego, Sara Sidle, survived a brutal abduction by the infamous Miniature Killer, but Internet rumors of her departure from the seven-year-old drama were greatly exaggerated. Or so they thought.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Guide</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/tv-guide-17/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/tv-guide-17/</guid>
      <description>Now that Jorja Fox has officially confirmed the/ worst kept secret in the TV biz &amp;ndash; she&amp;rsquo;s ditching CSI next month after seven years in the forensics lab &amp;ndash; we can start to focus on more important things in life. Like, you know, her return to the show! In her only interview, CSI&amp;#8216;s top gun, Carol Mendelsohn, weighs in on the circumstances surrounding Fox&amp;rsquo;s exit, responds to published reports that she considered killing her off, previews tonight&amp;rsquo;s big marriage proposal, and utters the words grieving fans have been dying to hear: Sara Sidle will be back.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AOL Money and Finance </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/aol-money-and-finance/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/aol-money-and-finance/</guid>
      <description>NEW YORK (AP) - Jorja Fox is waving goodbye to &amp;ldquo;CSI: Crime Scene Investigation.&amp;rdquo;
Fox, 39, tells EW.com she has quit the Las Vegas-based forensics drama, saying she wants to explore other opportunities.
&amp;ldquo;There are all these things I want to do,&amp;rdquo; she said in a story posted Monday on the Web site. &amp;ldquo;Some are personal. Some are professional. And I really need to do some of them before I get too old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CBC </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/cbc/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/cbc/</guid>
      <description>Confirming rumours that have been circulating since last season&amp;rsquo;s cliffhanger finale, original cast member Jorja Fox has announced she is leaving TV&amp;rsquo;s No. 1 show, &amp;ldquo;CSI: Crime Scene Investigation.&amp;rdquo;
The 39-year-old actress cited her desire for a break from the commitments of filming a weekly television series for her departure from the hit forensics drama.
&amp;ldquo;There are all these things I want to do. Some are personal. Some are professional. And I really need to do some of them before I get too old,&amp;rdquo; Fox told Entertainment Weekly magazine, in a short piece posted to its website</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cinema Blend </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/cinema-blend/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/cinema-blend/</guid>
      <description>Well &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; fans, it looks like its official. Despite the online campaigns and petitions set up by fans to keep her around, Jorja Fox is leaving &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo;. TV Guide&amp;rsquo;s Ausiello interviewed Fox last month and at that time, she refused to respond to the rumors about her departure from the series. Today, Entertainment Weekly has reported that the rumors are true.
Fox reportedly told &amp;ldquo;EW&amp;rdquo; that her decision to leave the show wasn&amp;rsquo;t money related.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Florida Today </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/florida-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/florida-today/</guid>
      <description>Jorja Fox, who plays Sara Sidle on CSI, has decided to leave the CBS crime show, USA Today reported today.
&amp;ldquo;There are all theses things I want to do. Some are personal and some are professional and I really need to do some of them before I get too old,&amp;rdquo; Fox told EW.com.
Fox, 39, will appear in five more episodes before heading off on her own.
Fox left Melbourne Beach midway through her senior year in December 1985.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NY Daily News </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/ny-daily-news-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/ny-daily-news-3/</guid>
      <description>Jorja Fox has confirmed the talk: She has quit &amp;ldquo;CSI: Crime Scene Investigation.&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;There are all these things I want to do,&amp;rdquo; the 39-year-old actress told EW.com yesterday. &amp;ldquo;Some are personal. Some are professional. And I really need to do some of them before I get too old. If I thought the show were on its last legs, I would&amp;rsquo;ve tried harder to stay the course. But I feel like it&amp;rsquo;s going to be around for a while; if I don&amp;rsquo;t want some of those dreams to pass me by, have to get off the ride for a while.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>St. Petersburg Times </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/st-petersburg-times-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/st-petersburg-times-3/</guid>
      <description>A Dunedin woman is rallying the troops online to keep Jorja Fox on &amp;ldquo;CSI: Crime Scene Investigation.&amp;rdquo;
DUNEDIN - Swathed in yellow crime scene tape, a large pegboard features the fruits of Devon Pierce&amp;rsquo;s work. One flier pleads &amp;ldquo;Don&amp;rsquo;t burst our bubble. Keep Jorja Fox on &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo;.&amp;rdquo; Another promises it is &amp;ldquo;saving Sara one dollar at a time.&amp;rdquo; A note of thanks from Fox - a 39-year-old ex-Floridian who has played forensic investigator Sara Sidle since the hit crime drama &amp;ldquo;CSI: Crime Scene Investigation&amp;rdquo; debuted in fall 2000 - compliments Pierce and her friends for their devotion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Guide </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/tv-guide-15/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/tv-guide-15/</guid>
      <description>Explaining that there are many things, both personal and professional, that she wants to do &amp;ndash; &amp;ldquo;and I really need to do some of them before I get too old&amp;rdquo; &amp;ndash; Jorja Fox confirms the biz&amp;rsquo;s worst-kept secret, that her days as a &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; are ending, partly because the hit procedural &amp;ldquo;isn&amp;rsquo;t&amp;rdquo;. &amp;ldquo;If I thought the show were on its last legs, I would&amp;rsquo;ve tried harder to stay the course,&amp;rdquo; she tells &amp;ldquo;Entertainment Weekly&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Day </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/the-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/the-day/</guid>
      <description>It became official on Monday, when Jorja Fox, who plays the recovering alcoholic Sara Sidle on the still-enormously popular CBS crime show, CSI, confirmed to ew.com that she is leaving the show this fall.
There had been much speculation in the TV press that Fox was quitting in this, the show&amp;rsquo;s eighth season. Last season&amp;rsquo;s glimpses of Sara&amp;rsquo;s and Grissom&amp;rsquo;s personal lives (they are a couple) led close followers to believe that Sara was doomed as a character, as no love goes unpunished on this show.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Buddy TV </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/buddy-tv-8/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Oct 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/buddy-tv-8/</guid>
      <description>The noise surrounding Jorja Fox&amp;rsquo;s reported departure on &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; has fueled fans to exert great efforts to keep her character, Sara Sidle, on the CBS show. Although the 39-year-old actress has neither confirmed nor denied the controversy, supporters have quickly found ways to demonstrate their support by putting up websites such as The Jorja Fox Appreciation Campaign and Dollars for Sense.
So far, fans&amp;rsquo; efforts include sending letters and flyers to the CBS studios and signing online petitions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Defamer </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/defamer-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Oct 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/defamer-2/</guid>
      <description>CSIs Jorja Fox has announced that she&amp;rsquo;s leaving the show, hoping to pursue roles that involve dramatic challenges more demanding than holding a blacklight over a semen-splattered corpse week after week . Thankfully, her departure from the series seems more amicable than that of recent &amp;ldquo;Prison Break&amp;rdquo; escapee Sarah Wayne Callies, so maybe she&amp;rsquo;ll be able to avoid having her severed head wind up in a box on her farewell episode</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E! Online </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/e-online-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Oct 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/e-online-4/</guid>
      <description>Well, I suppose this puts the nail in the coffin. Sorry, Sara Sidle fans.
Despite the promo taunting you all with a Gil-Sara marriage proposal, Jorja Fox has confirmed to Entertainment Weekly that she&amp;rsquo;s leaving &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo;, saying she will appear in only five episodes this season.
&amp;ldquo;There are all these things I want to do. Some are personal. Some are professional. And I really need to do some of them before I get too old,&amp;rdquo; explains Fox.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EW.com </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/ew-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Oct 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/ew-6/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo;&amp;rsquo;s Jorja Fox &amp;ndash; the 39-year-old actress whose tenure on TV&amp;rsquo;s No. 1 drama almost ended in 2004 when she was temporarily fired during tense contract negotiations &amp;ndash; has quit the show. She wrapped production on the drama last week. Fox told EW.com exclusively that her decision to give up the role of Sara Sidle had nothing to do with money and everything to with wanting a break from the commitment of a weekly television series.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Entertainment Tonight </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/entertainment-tonight/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Oct 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/entertainment-tonight/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The actress will hang up her badge in November.&amp;rdquo;
ET confirms that JORJA FOX will be leaving &amp;ldquo;CSI: Crime Scene Investigation.&amp;rdquo; She will exit the long-running drama sometime in November.
In last season&amp;rsquo;s cliffhanger, it was unclear whether Fox&amp;rsquo;s character, investigator Sara Sidle, would be returning to the show, as her life hung in the balance after she was attacked by the &amp;ldquo;Miniature Killer.&amp;rdquo;
Fox, who has also starred on &amp;ldquo;The West Wing&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;ER,&amp;rdquo; has been on &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; since its beginning in 2000.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MeeVee </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/meevee/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Oct 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/meevee/</guid>
      <description>TV executives all over Hollywood must just want to beat Nina Tassler like a gong. The CBS Entertainment chief brought back &amp;ldquo;Jericho&amp;rdquo; for a deserved midseason run and admitted that the &amp;ldquo;Nuts to CBS&amp;rdquo; campaign by fans was a factor in the show&amp;rsquo;s survival. Now every Comic Book Guy and No. #1 Fan out there is managing a campaign to save their favorite canceled show or fired actor. Aside from &amp;ldquo;Jericho&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Cagney and Lacey&amp;rdquo; back in the &amp;lsquo;80s, there&amp;rsquo;s seldom any sign that these campaigns are effective.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Philadelphia Inquirer </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/philadelphia-inquirer-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Oct 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/philadelphia-inquirer-2/</guid>
      <description>You may have read that Gary Sinise got a healthy salary bump this week. He&amp;rsquo;ll now be pulling down $5 million a year for scowling on CSI: NY. No mention of any increase for his costar, Melina Kanakaredes.
If this television season has taught us anything, it&amp;rsquo;s that women in prime time shouldn&amp;rsquo;t ask for raises - unless they are prepared to see their characters tortured or killed.
Take Jorja Fox, who has a history of playing contract hardball with the CSI mothership.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Roanoke Times </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/the-roanoke-times/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Oct 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/the-roanoke-times/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
Q: I heard that Jorja Fox is leaving &amp;ldquo;CSI.&amp;rdquo; I know she had contract disputes a few years back, but I thought that had been sorted out.
&amp;#8212; A Reader
A: Jorja&amp;rsquo;s contract expired last season, and it apparently has not been renewed. Back in 2004, she and co-star George Eads infamously held out for more money and were unceremoniously fired from the top-rated crime drama. Shortly thereafter they were rehired &amp;#8212; at the same rate they had been paid previously.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EW.com </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/ew-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/ew-5/</guid>
      <description>As fans continue to fret about whether Jorja Fox will walk away from her six-figure gig on &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo;, an insider tells EW.com that the Oct. 18 episode will feature a very unorthodox marriage proposal by Gil to Fox&amp;rsquo;s character, Sara. So far, very little has been revealed about the duo&amp;rsquo;s clandestine relationship, though fans first got an idea that something was up in the season finale two years ago, and over last season, when Sara was seen sitting up in bed with Gil (William Peterson) in one episode.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Sundial </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/daily-sundial/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Oct 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/daily-sundial/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
Scenes filmed on campus involved series regular Jorja Fox, who plays Crime Scene Investigator Sara Sidle, and guest star Juliette Goglia, who&amp;rsquo;ll be reprising her role as Hannah West, a 12-year-old genius introduced in the sixth season episode, &amp;ldquo;The Unusual Suspect.&amp;rdquo;
Filmed on the quad outside of Eucalyptus Hall, the crime scene features Sidle speaking with West and showing her photograph. Sidle&amp;rsquo;s words and the photograph provoke West, who becomes upset and starts crying and shouting at her.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dose.CA </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/dose-ca/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Oct 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/dose-ca/</guid>
      <description>A ratings juggernaut like &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; hardly needs the help of a rabid fan campaign. But after news that &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; star Jorja Fox would be quitting the show, Internet crazies started rallying together to keep her fighting TV crime.
So far, online group Dollarforsense.com has deluged CBS&amp;rsquo;s offices with whack-job gifts in the hopes of keeping Fox&amp;rsquo;s character, Sara Sidle, on the show. So far, their stunts have stopped just short of being mistaken as the calling cards of one of &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo;&amp;rsquo;s rotating cast of psycho killers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E Online </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/e-online-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Oct 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/e-online-3/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
Suzie from somewhere in the U.K.: Watch the skies over the Universal buildings in Los Angeles on Tuesday, Oct. 10 at 10 a.m. This will be the third flyover in a campaign to get &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; to re-sign Jorja Fox! &amp;ldquo;Jericho&amp;rdquo; is peanuts compared to this!
Will do, and best of luck.
[&amp;hellip;]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EW.com </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/ew-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Oct 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/ew-4/</guid>
      <description>In reaction to published reports that&amp;rdquo; CSI&amp;rsquo;s&amp;rdquo; Jorja Fox is expected to leave the popular CBS drama by year&amp;rsquo;s end, fans are stealing a page from the &amp;ldquo;Jericho&amp;rdquo; chronicles by launching an Internet campaign to save their favorite character, Sara Sidle. So far, they&amp;rsquo;ve orchestrated three airplane flyovers in the airspace above the Universal lot in Los Angeles (with &amp;ldquo;Save Jorja&amp;rdquo; banners) and sent $3,500 in cash to the &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; production offices (to help offset Fox&amp;rsquo;s six-figure salary).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The TV Addict </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/the-tv-addict/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Oct 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/the-tv-addict/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
Best of the Week #2: CSI: CRIME SCENE INVESTIGATION
It has to be acknowledged that for the first time, fans are finally given a glimpse into the Grissom/Sara backstory. The interaction between the two this week was an example of âhow it&amp;rsquo;s done&amp;rsquo;, acting-wise. As a friend of mine pointed out, it was like watching fan fiction come to life. And with Jorja Fox&amp;rsquo;s impending departure, that symbolic last scene was just heartbreaking for a die hard GSR shipper like myself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Guide Online </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/tv-guide-04/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Oct 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/tv-guide-04/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
Question: Got any tidbits about Jorja Fox&amp;rsquo;s final &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; episode on Nov. 15? &amp;ndash; Tami
Ausiello: I actually just screened the episode, but CBS personally pleaded with me via a standard form letter to refrain from revealing the &amp;ldquo;how&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;why&amp;rdquo; of Sara&amp;rsquo;s departure. All that leaves me to scoop is the &amp;ldquo;where&amp;rdquo; (it&amp;rsquo;s a vehicle of some sort), the &amp;ldquo;when&amp;rdquo; (it&amp;rsquo;s at night) and the &amp;ldquo;who&amp;rdquo; (the episode&amp;rsquo;s final frame is a close-up of someone other than Sara).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chicago Sun-Times </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/chicago-sun-times-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/chicago-sun-times-1/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Scene&amp;rsquo; and unseen**
Jorja Fox will leave the long-running hit &amp;ldquo;CSI: Crime Scene Investigation&amp;rdquo; next month, TV Guide reports. She&amp;rsquo;s been there seven years, although she and co-star George Eads were temporarily fired after a salary dispute in &amp;lsquo;04.
This is, I think, not a bluff. She&amp;rsquo;s been bitter since that previous contract trouble, and turned down a modest raise then because it entailed a one-year extension.
She told the mag she regrets not working any longer with co-star William Petersen: &amp;ldquo;He&amp;rsquo;s the most incredible scene partner I&amp;rsquo;ve ever had and he&amp;rsquo;s a great friend.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ET Online</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2007/et-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Oct 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2007/et-2/</guid>
      <description>Jorja Fox: How fun is this, right? And what a tease for me!
Jann Carl: I know!
Fox: Such a tease! They tell &amp;ndash; I&amp;rsquo;m under the understanding that when I&amp;rsquo;m done today, they&amp;rsquo;re gonna let me take a little spin around the track.
[&amp;hellip;]
Carl: You&amp;rsquo;re back?
Fox: I made it! I made it. I survived. I know.
Carl: And you don&amp;rsquo;t look any worse off for it.
Fox: Well thank you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ET Online </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/et-online-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Oct 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/et-online-2/</guid>
      <description>The CSI team investigates the suspicious death of a go-cart racer who took his hobby to the highway, when a severed head rolls through tonight&amp;rsquo;s episode of &amp;ldquo;CSI: Crime Scene Investigation,&amp;rdquo; airing at 9 p.m. on CBS.
Then the murder rate doubles when the team gets a second case &amp;#8212; the murder of a HUGH HEFNER-like publisher at a hip new restaurant where customers dine in the dark.
[&amp;hellip;]
The best part of the episode for many fans may be the return of Sara Sidle (JORJA FOX) to action, following her near-death experience in last week&amp;rsquo;s season premiere.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zap2It </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/zap2it-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Oct 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/zap2it-1/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
Jorja Fox leaving CSI
I with you guys. I&amp;rsquo;m upset that Jorja Fox is leaving CSI. In fact, I&amp;rsquo;m not happy at all. So as promised, here&amp;rsquo;s the link of a campaign fans have started to keep her on the show.
http://www.dollarforsense.com/index.html
[&amp;hellip;]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Washington Times </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/the-washington-times/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Oct 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/the-washington-times/</guid>
      <description>Sara sidles out
Sara Sidle, the lab technician character on &amp;ldquo;CSI: Crime Scene Investigation,&amp;rdquo; may have survived the first episode of the show&amp;rsquo;s new season. But she won&amp;rsquo;t make it to the last installment.
Jorja Fox, who has played the role on the hit CBS series since it began in 2000, will not complete the current season and will leave after the seventh episode in November, E! Online reports.
Her departure comes after rocky contract negotiations offscreen and an onscreen story line that has been foreshadowing for months a less than happy ending for her character.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Fodder </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/tv-fodder/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Oct 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/tv-fodder/</guid>
      <description>When &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; ended last season, the fate of lab tech Sara Sidle was up in the air, both on and off the screen. Viewers were left wondering whether the character would survive, especially since the actress that plays her, Jorja Fox, had not yet renewed her contract. According to Entertainment Weekly, Fox finally made up her mind and will leave the hit show by the end of the year.
Fox will continue to star as her character until the end of 2007, after which she will exit the show.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yahoo News </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/yahoo-news/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Oct 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/yahoo-news/</guid>
      <description>Want to walk for a good cause but find yourself strapped for time or physically incapable? Welcome to the &amp;ldquo;virtual walk&amp;rdquo; where you can raise money for charity without ever stepping out the front door.
Some 1,500 women began a 31-city virtual walk across the United States on Monday to benefit breast cancer courtesy of a computer, an avatar and a $3 donation.
Participants included home design guru Martha Stewart, British actress Lynn Redgrave, actress Mena Suvari and Jorja Fox of the &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; television show in what organizers said was the world&amp;rsquo;s first interactive virtual walk.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Detroit Free Press </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/detroit-free-press/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Sep 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/detroit-free-press/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
Jorja Fox to sidle off
TVGuide.com&amp;rsquo;s Michael Ausiello reports that even though the &amp;ldquo;CSI: Crime Scene Investigation&amp;rdquo; character Sara Sidle survived her run-in with the Miniature Killer in Thursday night&amp;rsquo;s gripping season premiere, her time on the show has nonetheless come to an end.
Multiple sources confirm that Jorja Fox &amp;#8212; whose contract expired at the end of last season &amp;#8212; will depart the hit procedural in November, after failing to come to terms on a new long-term deal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NY Daily News </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/ny-daily-news-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Sep 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/ny-daily-news-2/</guid>
      <description>Jorja Fox&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; character, Sara Sidle, survived a harrowing run-in with a killer in Thursday&amp;rsquo;s season premiere, but now it seems Fox is a goner.
Reports at TVGuide.com and EOnline.com yesterday have Fox leaving the crime series in November. Her contract expired in May, and there&amp;rsquo;s been speculation for months that she would exit the show.
Fox was nearly fired in 2004 over a contract dispute.
Word of her departure came just as CBS was celebrating big numbers for Thursday&amp;rsquo;s telecast, which averaged 25.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Buddy TV </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/buddy-tv-7/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/buddy-tv-7/</guid>
      <description>There was much speculation about whether or not Sara Sidle would make it out alive from her encounter with &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo;&amp;rsquo;s Miniature Killer. While the season premiere answered that question, the resolution was overshadowed by word that despite surviving, Sara is still not long for the CSI world &amp;hellip; because Jorja Fox, the actress who plays her, will be leaving &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo;.
Although it hasn&amp;rsquo;t been definitively confirmed, multiple sources have said that she will be leaving the show this November, after failing to arrive at a resolution for a new contract.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E Online</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/e-online-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/e-online-1/</guid>
      <description>Sara Sidle is a survivor. The actor that plays her, not so much.
Jorja Fox, who has starred on &amp;ldquo;CSI: Crime Scene Investigation&amp;rdquo; since its inception in 2000, will not complete the series&amp;rsquo; current season, bowing out after the seventh episode in November, E! Online TV columnist Kristin Dos Santos reports.
The news will no doubt be a blow to fans of the actress, albeit not a surprising one.
Her departure comes after rocky contract negotiations offscreen and an onscreen story line that has been foreshadowing for months a less than happy ending for her character.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E Online</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/e-online-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/e-online-2/</guid>
      <description>She&amp;rsquo;s outta there.
That&amp;rsquo;s what I can tell you about Jorja Fox&amp;rsquo;s status on &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo;, the hit series that bested &amp;ldquo;Grey**s in the ratings last night.
As I mentioned on &amp;ldquo;E! News&amp;rdquo; on Wednesday [&amp;hellip;], reliable sources close to the show tell me Jorja will not be a part of &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; as of the seventh episode of the current season.
So, do not let the fact that Sara Sidle survived last night&amp;rsquo;s premiere fool you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EW </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/ew-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/ew-3/</guid>
      <description>**Jorja Fox Leaving &amp;#8216;CSI&amp;rdquo;
The actress will appear in six or seven episodes this year before leaving the top-rated show that made her a household name
&amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo;&amp;rsquo;s Jorja Fox &amp;ndash; who was briefly fired from the show in 2004 during an ugly contract dispute with CBS &amp;ndash; is expected to leave the top-rated drama before year&amp;rsquo;s end. A source close to the show confirms that Fox, whose contract expired last season, has agreed to appear in six or seven episodes this year before leaving the show that made her a household name and turned her into an unwilling poster child for greedy TV actors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Earth Times </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/earth-times/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/earth-times/</guid>
      <description>Hollywood actress Jorja Fox is reportedly planning to leave the popular police procedural, &amp;ldquo;CSI: Crime Scene Investigation.&amp;rdquo;
E! News has reported that Fox&amp;rsquo;s character, Sara Sidle, will not be on the show after this season&amp;rsquo;s seventh episode.
TV Guide has also said Fox will be leaving the long-running series in November.
The actress has reportedly been having more trouble negotiating her contract with CBS.
She was fired and rehired after a high-profile contract dispute in 2004.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New York Post </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/new-york-post-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/new-york-post-2/</guid>
      <description>SARA lives.
Lab tech Sara Sidle sur vived last season&amp;rsquo;s cliffhanger ending of &amp;ldquo;CSI: Crime Scene Investigation,&amp;rdquo; fans of the show learned last night in the premiere episode of the series&amp;rsquo; eighth season.
The survival of Sara, who was left to die in the Las Vegas desert by the serial murderer known as &amp;ldquo;the miniature killer&amp;rdquo; - for the miniature models of crime scenes she would build and leave for CSI investigators - means cast member Jorja Fox will be sticking around for a while on the top-rated CBS drama.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Squad </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/tv-squad-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/tv-squad-2/</guid>
      <description>The day finally arrived: &amp;ldquo;CSI: Crime Scene Investigation&amp;rdquo; fans finally know if Sara Sidle, played by Jorja Fox, survived or not. Last year&amp;rsquo;s finale had the CSI team not only continue their search for the &amp;ldquo;Miniature Killer&amp;rdquo; but also for Sara, who became the killer&amp;rsquo;s last victim. There was a lot of speculation over the summer surrounding Sara&amp;rsquo;s fate especially since the show was doing its best to keep it a secret (fans were told they would at least see Sara under the car in the premiere but didn&amp;rsquo;t say more).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NY Daily News </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/ny-daily-news-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/ny-daily-news-1/</guid>
      <description>The eighth season of &amp;ldquo;CSI: Crime Scene Investigation&amp;rdquo; traverses a tense path that long-time fans of the show will find familiar: a race-against-time CSI team effort to find one of their own, left to die in the desert by a vengeful killer.
Last time this happened, the intended victim was Nick (George Eads), buried alive - but eventually rescued - in an episode directed by Quentin Tarantino. This time, Nick is one of the team members using all his skills and instincts to help his colleague, Sara (Jorja Fox), escape a similar fate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Guide </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/tv-guide-31/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/tv-guide-31/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; Fans: What Are You Doing After the Premiere!?
You&amp;rsquo;re coming straight here, &amp;ldquo;that&amp;rsquo;s&amp;rdquo; what you are doing!
As I&amp;rsquo;ve been telling you for weeks, I&amp;rsquo;ll be posting an exclusive story immediately followingCSIs eighth season premiere tonight and, trust me, it&amp;rsquo;s a must-read for followers of the show and, more importantly, Jorja Fox/Sara Sidle. I don&amp;rsquo;t think I&amp;rsquo;m being overly-dramatic when I say it&amp;rsquo;s a matter of life and death.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Guide Online </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/tv-guide-30/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/tv-guide-30/</guid>
      <description>Warning: If You Haven&amp;rsquo;t Watched Tonight&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo;, Stop Reading!
How&amp;rsquo;s this for a twisty turnabout: Even though Sara Sidle survived her run-in with CSI&amp;rsquo;s Miniature Killer in tonight&amp;rsquo;s gripping season premiere, her time on the show has nonetheless come to an end. Multiple sources confirm that Jorja Fox &amp;ndash; whose contract expired at the end of last season &amp;ndash; will depart the hit procedural this November after failing to come to terms on a new long-term deal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MSNBC </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/msnbc-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Sep 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/msnbc-1/</guid>
      <description>The pros and cons on how last season&amp;rsquo;s cliffhanger might end
The seventh season of &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; ended earlier this year with crime scene investigator Sara Sidle trapped under an overturned vintage muscle car, her hand twitching with faint signs of life. Back at the Las Vegas lab, Sara&amp;rsquo;s boss and secret lover, Gil Grissom, finished his interrogation of a psychotic young cleaning woman who turned out to be the lab&amp;rsquo;s season-long nemesis, the Miniature Killer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Guide </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/tv-guide-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/tv-guide-20/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
Question: Please tell me you&amp;rsquo;ve heard something about Sara Sidle&amp;rsquo;s fate on &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo;. Did Jorja Fox renew her contract? Or are you not at liberty to say? &amp;#8212; Rachel
Ausiello: The only thing I&amp;rsquo;m at liberty to say is make sure you check my Ausiello Report blog immediately following the CSI season premiere next Thursday.
[&amp;hellip;]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Guide </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/tv-guide-18/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Sep 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/tv-guide-18/</guid>
      <description>Sara Sidle is carrying a heavy weight on her shoulders these days.
When the eighth season of &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; opens, Jorja Fox&amp;rsquo;s character will still be where she was at the end of May&amp;rsquo;s finale: stuck under a car in the Nevada desert, courtesy of a psycho killer &amp;#8212; and Fox&amp;rsquo;s contract negotiations with CBS.
But while producers promise to resolve this cliff-hanger one way or another (though they&amp;rsquo;re staying silent about Fox&amp;rsquo;s fate &amp;#8212; hmmm, she&amp;rsquo;s not in the network&amp;rsquo;s cast shot, left), they do say her costars will be carrying their share of dramatic weight this season.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Us Weekly </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/us-weekly/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Sep 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/us-weekly/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
Where we left off: The miniature killer left Sara (Jorja Fox) for dead under a car. The reult: Grissom (William Petersen) came clean about the pair&amp;rsquo;s romance.
Exit Wounds: Despite talk of Fox&amp;rsquo;s departure, &amp;ldquo;Sara does interact with the killer in the premiere,&amp;rdquo; coexec producer Carol Mendelsohn tells Us -but later adds, &amp;ldquo;You&amp;rsquo;ll need a Kleenex for that episode. Another hint? A smart, lively new investigator (Jessica Lucas) steps in for a four-show run October 11.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chicago Tribune </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/chicago-tribune-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Sep 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/chicago-tribune-2/</guid>
      <description>So what is happening with Sara Sidle on &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo;?
The character appeared to have been crushed under a car as the Season 7 finale ended, and all summer blogs have buzzed with speculation about actress Jorja Fox&amp;rsquo;s contract negotiations with CBS. Does it mean anything that Fox wasn&amp;rsquo;t in a recent &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; cast photo in TV Guide?
Sidle, as fans know, was in a relationship with Gil Grissom (William Petersen), and the entire &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; team found out about the romance in the season finale.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Philadelphia Inquirer </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/philadelphia-inquirer-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Sep 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/philadelphia-inquirer-1/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
CSI: Crime Scene Investigation CBS. Thursdays, 9 p.m. Humor and personality distinguish America&amp;rsquo;s favorite scripted series from so many other &amp;ldquo;procedurals,&amp;rdquo; and last season was perhaps its best. When it ended, Grissom&amp;rsquo;s secret girlfriend, Sara, was lying pinned under a car, and rumors abound that Jorja Fox, who plays her, is leaving the show. Sexy Jessica Lucas (&amp;ldquo;Life as We Know It&amp;rdquo;) has been signed as a hotshot new CSI.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BuddyTV </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/buddy-tv-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Sep 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/buddy-tv-6/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
&amp;ldquo;VickiM&amp;rdquo; said: Anything new regarding CSI?
CSI: *extra juicy* Okay, someone sent me some script pages for upcoming episodes and Sarah is never mentioned. So either she will indeed die, or her character will be written off, or her character is still on the show but not in those episodes.
[&amp;hellip;]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>&#39;RTL.de - Germany</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2007/rtl-de-germany-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Sep 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2007/rtl-de-germany-2/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Jorja Fox &amp;ldquo;Sara Sidle&amp;rdquo; - Why Season 7 is so great&amp;rdquo; Jorja Fox: What separates season 7 from all the other seasons in &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; is for a very long time, we&amp;rsquo;re very content that our stories sort of had a beginning, a middle and an end within themselves, so if you watch a show from season 3 or season 1 or season 5 you kinda could watch them and they didn&amp;rsquo;t have to be in a particular order, you know.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>After Ellen </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/after-ellen/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Aug 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/after-ellen/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
If you watch &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; at all, then you are likely aware of Jorja Fox&amp;rsquo;s reported contract difficulties. At the end of this past season, viewers were left with an image of her character, Sara Sidle, trapped under a wrecked sports car in the middle of nowhere. Signs of life were, shall we say, limited. For &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; fans, the debate has been raging since before the finale ever aired about whether or not Sara would survive the crash.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Buddy TV </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/buddy-tv-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Aug 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/buddy-tv-5/</guid>
      <description>Like other actors on the &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; franchise, William Petersen (Gil Grissom) and Jorja Fox (Sara Sidle) feel fortunate to portray their respective characters and to be part of such an award-winning series.
Petersen, 54, reveals that science was something he was never really good at. But since landing the role of the forensic entomologist, he has developed a keen interest in the field and has seen some surprising changes in his personality.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Guide </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/tv-guide-29/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Aug 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/tv-guide-29/</guid>
      <description>Question: This question has been eating away at me for months and I&amp;rsquo;m hoping you can help me out. I&amp;rsquo;ve always enjoyed spoilers. I&amp;rsquo;m the impatient type, and summer is usually the worst stretch of time for me. TVGuide.com is obviously known for giving out little tidbits here and there about certain shows, but why aren&amp;rsquo;t we &amp;ldquo;allowed&amp;rdquo; to know specific details? I&amp;rsquo;ll use &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; as an example, or more to the point, Jorja Fox.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Guide Magazine</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/tv-guide-28/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Aug 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/tv-guide-28/</guid>
      <description>Sneak Peek CSI
Instead of using &amp;ldquo;Who Are You?&amp;rdquo; as it&amp;rsquo;s theme song this year, &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; producers might want to consider the Clash&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Should I Stay or Should I Go.&amp;rdquo;
In last spring&amp;rsquo;s season finale, Sara Sidle (Jorja Fox) was left trapped under a car in the Nevada desert by a serial killer &amp;#8212; with pouring rain threatening to drown her &amp;#8212; while Gil Grissom (William Petersen), her boyfriend and boss, and the rest of the CSIs frantically tried to find her.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VegTV (25 August 2007)</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2007/vegtv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Aug 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2007/vegtv/</guid>
      <description>Announcer: VegTV on the road with Marie Oser.
Marie Oser: I&amp;rsquo;m here with Jorja Fox from &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo;, a long time vegetarian, vegan. I asked you once what was your epiphany; it was a meatball sub in Brooklyn. And that was great!
Jorja Fox: &amp;ldquo;*laughing*&amp;rdquo; I told that story a couple of days ago to a friend! &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; &amp;rsquo;s out here in force tonight, there&amp;rsquo;s actually a little posse of us. There&amp;rsquo;s a couple vegetarians that I work with and a couple of vegans.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Guide </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/tv-guide-23/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Aug 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/tv-guide-23/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
Don&amp;rsquo;t play coy, TV gossip god! What&amp;rsquo;s the word on Jorja Fox staying/going on &amp;ldquo;CSI?&amp;rdquo; &amp;#8212; Cicero
Ausiello: Sorry, but I&amp;rsquo;ve been sworn to secrecy. What I &amp;ldquo;can&amp;rdquo; say is that the answer is complicated.
[&amp;hellip;]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Hollywood Reporter </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/the-hollywood-reporter/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Aug 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/the-hollywood-reporter/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; adds new cast member
Jessica Lucas is joining the cast of CBS&amp;rsquo; &amp;ldquo;CSI: Crime Scene Investigation&amp;rdquo; as a recurring.
She will play Veronica Lake, aka Ronnie, a young, vivacious, smart, sought-after newbie CSI in training who gets multiple job offers but chooses to go to Las Vegas because of the increase in crime rates there.
Ever since the role cropped up on breakdowns around town, it prompted speculation that the character might be groomed as a replacement for Sara Sidle (Jorja Fox), who was left crushed under a car with her hand barely moving in the Season 7 finale.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Guide CA </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/tv-guide-ca/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Aug 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/tv-guide-ca/</guid>
      <description>** Executive producer confirms that Sara Sidle is&amp;hellip;**
[Spoiler Alert!]
&amp;hellip; in the September season premiere.
&amp;ldquo;I hate spoilers,&amp;rdquo; sighs Naren Shankar, co-executive producer and co-showrunner for CSI. He&amp;rsquo;s speaking to me over the phone from Los Angeles, where he and the rest of the CSI writing staff are breaking the story for the CSI/Without a Trace crossover episode.
&amp;ldquo;It&amp;rsquo;s a great way to flex some writing muscles,&amp;rdquo; Shakar says of the May sweeps storyline while munching on his lunch.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Guide </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/tv-guide-12/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Aug 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/tv-guide-12/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
Have you found out anything definitive about Jorja Fox staying or going on &amp;ldquo;CSI?&amp;rdquo; &amp;#8212; Betsy
Ausiello: Yes, I have.
[&amp;hellip;]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DIVA (August 2007)</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/diva/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Aug 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/diva/</guid>
      <description>Jorja Fox
She&amp;rsquo;s played a lesbian intern and a forensic investigator. But in her spare time, Jorja Fox is a bit of a surfer-babe.
We were strolling along the sandy shores of Venice Beach, LA, in search of hot surfer chicks when we bumped into rather famous actress and lesbian icon Jorja Fox, fresh from a wave-riding session.
You may know her as the firm but fair Sara Sidle from the popular TV crime series &amp;ldquo;CSI: Crime Scene Investigation&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BuddyTV </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/buddy-tv-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jul 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/buddy-tv-4/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
MsMzz said: Any news on CSI and the Jorja Fox situation?
CSI: The decision has not been officially announced yet. The only word I got about it was the rumor saying that she would be back for 1 episode and that&amp;rsquo;s it. POLL TIME!
[&amp;hellip;]
Let&amp;rsquo;s check our POLL!
CSI: 75% of voters want Jorja Fox to remain on the show&amp;hellip; we should soon learn if your wish will be granted.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Squad </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/tv-squad-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jul 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/tv-squad-1/</guid>
      <description>On the heels of news that Rory Cochrane is returning to one of the other CSI shows, CSI: Miami, comes this news: Jorja Fox is probably on her way out.
CSI Producer Carol Mendolsohn tells TV Guide&amp;rsquo;s Michael Ausiello that they have just cast a new female lab technician that will be introduced in the third episode, and there are hints that she&amp;rsquo;s not just a new cast member but a new cast member that will take over for Jorja Fox, whose Sara character might die in that car crash.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Toronto Star </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/toronto-star-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jul 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/toronto-star-2/</guid>
      <description>Who are you? Looks like &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; producers are making way for a replacement for Jorja Fox&amp;rsquo;s Sara Sidle. A new female character, a CSI or lab tech in her 20s, will turn up in the season&amp;rsquo;s third episode. Sara was last spotted in a car wreck, meaning she probably won&amp;rsquo;t survive. What is known is that Fox will appear in the Sept. 27 season premiere â but under the car.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Guide</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/tv-guide-25/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jul 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/tv-guide-25/</guid>
      <description>Although &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; hasn&amp;rsquo;t even pronounced Sara dead yet, it sounds suspiciously like the powers-that-be are already planning to breathe new life into the show by introducing a replacement for Jorja Fox&amp;rsquo;s hot cop.
Executive producer Carol Mendolsohn has told me exclusively that a new female character will turn up in this season&amp;rsquo;s third episode. &amp;ldquo;[She] may be a CSI or lab tech,&amp;rdquo; the boss said. And, according to my casting spies, the junior detective will be in her mid-twenties, fresh out of college and lacking the capacity for self-censorship.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pittsburgh Post-Gazette </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/pittsburgh-post-gazette-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jul 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/pittsburgh-post-gazette-1/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
&amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; creator Anthony Zuiker: He wouldn&amp;rsquo;t say anything about the fate of Sara Sidle (Jorja Fox), except that it will &amp;ldquo;evolve quickly in the first episode.&amp;rdquo;
[&amp;hellip;]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Orlando Sentinel </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/orlando-sentinel-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jul 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/orlando-sentinel-1/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
&amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo;: &amp;ldquo;The Sara-Grissom storyline is going to conclude,&amp;rdquo; Littman says. &amp;ldquo;Don&amp;rsquo;t take it in that definitive term. It&amp;rsquo;s very smartly done.&amp;rdquo;
Tell me more.
&amp;ldquo;We have a big storyline finish at the start of the season,&amp;rdquo; he says. &amp;ldquo;It will play out for a few episodes. &amp;hellip; The ambition of their [the writers&amp;rsquo;] stories is once again extremely high and extremely quirky. That arc worked so well with Grissom and Sara, that we are going to let these characters breathe this year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seat42f</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/seat42f-too-much-tv/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jul 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/seat42f-too-much-tv/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
It&amp;rsquo;s all very reminiscent of Jorja Fox&amp;rsquo;s holdouts with &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo;and twice now she has played chicken with CBS and won. While Jorja is on the hit series &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; she is nowhere near as important to the shows success as Mandy is to the ratings monster &amp;ldquo;Criminal Minds&amp;rdquo;. [&amp;hellip;]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Guide </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/tv-guide-07/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jul 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/tv-guide-07/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
Question: I heard that Jorja Fox only signed for the first five episodes of &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo;. Is this true?&amp;ndash; Alice
Ausiello: That&amp;rsquo;s a new one. Hopefully, I&amp;rsquo;ll get to the bottom of JF&amp;rsquo;s contract sitch at press tour next week.
[&amp;hellip;]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Animal Acres (08-14 July 2007)</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/animal-acres/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jul 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/animal-acres/</guid>
      <description>A Benefit to Build L.A.&amp;rsquo;s Farmed Animal Sanctuary
Gala Chairperson Jorja Fox and many other special friends of farmed animals* invite you to the Animal Acres Gala on Saturday, August 25, for a truly memorable evening of dining and dancing under the stars in the beautiful sanctuary rose garden.
[&amp;hellip;]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CSI season 7 DVD extras</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2007/csi-season-7-dvd-extras/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jul 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2007/csi-season-7-dvd-extras/</guid>
      <description>Jorja Fox &amp;ldquo;(on Billy Petersen leaving the show for four weeks in November of 2006)&amp;rdquo; I wasn&amp;rsquo;t disappointed at all, I think, you know, obviously as I met Billy he had come almost directly out of this excitement of theater he was doing in Chicago and he&amp;rsquo;s very famous for that theater that he&amp;rsquo;s done. I think that it&amp;rsquo;s been the heart of his work over the time of his career, he&amp;rsquo;s done some films that are ground-breaking and memorable and everybody, those, that&amp;rsquo;s probably the way that the most people know Billy Petersen, but I think that people who know Billy Petersen &amp;ldquo;know&amp;rdquo; that his heart and his soul has always been in the theater, so, and it&amp;rsquo;s almost as if in a sense odd that it took him six years to find his way into one, you know, and I think that it&amp;rsquo;s a testament to the show, how much &amp;ldquo;CSI:&amp;rdquo; has all this passion that he hasn&amp;rsquo;t felt like he could go do a play at the same time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV and Satellite Week</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/tv-and-satellite-week-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jun 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/tv-and-satellite-week-2/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
While cast and crew remain tight-lipped on the details, we can reveal that the violent outcome has a major bearing on another of the show&amp;rsquo;s most intriguing storylines &amp;#8212; the clandestine relationship between Grissom and his fiesty colleague Sara Sidle (Jorja Fox).
As the CSI team tries to track down the killer, Sara goes missing and her secret relationship with Grissom is forced into the open.
Whether Sara becomes another victim of the mini-replica killer remains to be seen, especially in the light of speculation over Jorja Fox&amp;rsquo;s future on the show.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>&#39;Wowow TV - Japan</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2007/wowow-tv-japan/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jun 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2007/wowow-tv-japan/</guid>
      <description>Question - about Sara Sidle(?) Jorja Fox: Uh, yes, well I think that Marg and I feel very very lucky to play the women we get to play on TV, you know. The character I get to play is &amp;ldquo;so&amp;rdquo; much smarter than I am, number one, &amp;ldquo;(laughs)&amp;rdquo; which is really fun, you never get tired of doing that, and they&amp;rsquo;re just, you know they&amp;rsquo;re strong women, and they&amp;rsquo;re professional, they&amp;rsquo;re completely intellectual and at the same time they feel very real, they feel like real people to me, they don&amp;rsquo;t feel, feels like a person that somebody could actually be.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Entertainment Weekly </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/ew-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/ew-2/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
On CBS&amp;rsquo; CSI, a series that&amp;rsquo;s not too concerned with personal lives, Jorja Fox has made her Sara a tough, world-weary pro who&amp;rsquo;s also a vulnerable woman hopelessly involved with her enigmatic equal, Gil Grissom. Hopefully, her previous shunning by the academy is a crime that Emmy voters will take time to investigate - and solve.
[&amp;hellip;]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Planet Jackson Hole </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/planet-jackson-hole-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jun 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/planet-jackson-hole-2/</guid>
      <description>News about Thora Birch and Jorja Fox at last weekend&amp;rsquo;s Jackson Hole Film Festival popped up on the Internet almost immediately. Even while the festival was still in progress, we caught photos of television star Jorja Fox (&amp;ldquo;ER,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo;) on one of her major fansites, JorjaAllAround.com. In the photos, Fox was inexplicably dressed in khaki pants worn UNDERNEATH a pretty sundress, posing with Thora Birch, who looked like she had no idea how to stand in front of the &amp;ldquo;red carpet&amp;rdquo; camera.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Guide </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/tv-guide-09/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jun 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/tv-guide-09/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
Question: What&amp;rsquo;s the latest on Jorja Fox&amp;rsquo;s contract situation? &amp;#8212; Spiffym212
Ausiello: Nothing&amp;rsquo;s official, but I hear she&amp;rsquo;s close to re-signing.
[&amp;hellip;]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Planet Jackson Hole </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/planet-jackson-hole-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/planet-jackson-hole-1/</guid>
      <description>Jackson Hole Film Festival - The Jackson Hole Film Festival party at Q Roadhouse Saturday night marked the last big hurrah of the soirees organized around the festival. Just before hundreds of revelers arrived to imbibe in food and drink and watch Sierra Leone&amp;rsquo;s Refugee All Stars, Planet Jackson Hole had a chance to walk across Q&amp;rsquo;s grassy lawn and sit down with noted television actress Jorja Fox.
Fox got her break on the hit NBC show &amp;ldquo;ER&amp;rdquo; playing Dr.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Curve Magazine (June 2007)</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/curve-magazine/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jun 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/curve-magazine/</guid>
      <description>Every lesbian&amp;rsquo;s favourite &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; star, Jorja Fox, isn&amp;rsquo;t your average sexpot. The attractive but geeky tomboy hasn&amp;rsquo;t graced the pages of Vogue, she doesn&amp;rsquo;t spend each episode in impossibly high heels, and you&amp;rsquo;re more likely to find her at a PETA rally protesting animal cruelty than pitching Revlon products to you from a talk show on the Oxygen Network. That&amp;rsquo;s why we love her and her strong, sexy brand of androgyny and even her slightly intoxicating don&amp;rsquo;t-care-to-talk-about-my-personal-life attitude.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Guide</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/tv-guide-32/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 May 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/tv-guide-32/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
We Know Jorja Fox&amp;rsquo;s conract is under negotiation, but is her character, Sara, going to survive being abducted by the &amp;ldquo;miniature killer&amp;rdquo; in CSIs season finale?
Executive Producer Naren Shankar says: I&amp;rsquo;m going to be asked that all summer! My response: Tune in to the season opener. We know where we&amp;rsquo;re going with it. It&amp;rsquo;s where we&amp;rsquo;ve talked about going from the beginning of this season. We&amp;rsquo;d ended last year with the reveal of Sara and Grissom&amp;rsquo;s relationship and had been doing that dance of who in the lab is going to know.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Guide </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/tv-guide-26/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 May 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/tv-guide-26/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
While the cast gushed about the exhibit, they remained tight-lipped about the fate of Sara (Jorja Fox), whose life hung in the balance at the end of the May 17 season finale. &amp;ldquo;We ended this season with Sara under a car and that&amp;rsquo;s how we&amp;rsquo;ll start Season 8,&amp;rdquo; says executive producer Carol Mendelsohn. One promising sign: Fox, who&amp;rsquo;s been in contract negotiations with the show, was in attendance last night.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CBS 2 Chicago Evening News (23 May 2007)</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2007/cbs-2-chicago-evening-news/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 May 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2007/cbs-2-chicago-evening-news/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
I know more about maggots that I really ever thought I would ever know. And I love them now! You know, the first four seasons it was a little creepy and they kind of scared me. And now I just enjoy their company when they&amp;rsquo;re on set.
[&amp;hellip;]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Guide </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/tv-guide-24/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 May 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/tv-guide-24/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
Question: Do you have a concrete answer on whether or not Jorja Fox will be back on &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; next season?&amp;ndash; Marly
Ausiello: Still up in the air, and my &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; mole says it could go either way.
[&amp;hellip;]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Show News </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/tv-show-news/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 May 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/tv-show-news/</guid>
      <description>Be there as the cast and executive producers of &amp;ldquo;CSI: Crime Scene Investigation &amp;ldquo;walk the “green carpet” at the &amp;ldquo;CSI: The Experience &amp;ldquo;exhibit preview party&amp;rdquo;-&amp;ldquo;May 23&amp;rdquo; at &amp;ldquo;Chicago’s Museum of Science and Industry. Cast attendees will include:
William Peterson, Marg Helgenberger, George Eads, Gary Dourdan, Jorja Fox, and more.
In &amp;ldquo;CSI: The Experience,&amp;rdquo; an immersive interactive forensic science exhibit based on the hit CBS show,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;guests will learn scientific principles and real investigative techniques as they try to solve one of three crime scene mysteries using DNA and fingerprint analysis, forensic anthropology and more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Movie City News </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/movie-city-news/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 May 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/movie-city-news/</guid>
      <description>THE 2007 JACKSON HOLE FILM FESTIVAL
GEARS UP FOR A WEEK OF SCREENINGS,
PANEL DISCUSSIONS, SPECIAL PROGRAMS AND EVENTS
AS THEY CELEBRATE THE BEST OF INDEPENDENT FILM
[&amp;hellip;]
The 2007 Jackson Hole Film Festival is also pleased to welcome to Jackson Hole a prestigious list of judges including Golden Globe and Emmy Award nominated actress **Thora Birch, **acclaimed actress and Screen Actors Guild Award winner **Jorja Fox, **renowned USA Today film critic **Claudia Puig, **director and Jackson Hole Film Festival Rosemount Diamond Award Winner Robert Collector, critically acclaimed director and Jackson Hole Film Festival Audience Choice Award Winner James Burke, producer **Cevin Cathell, **director and cinematographer Brian Liu, award winning producer, writer and director **Joe Fab, **writer, producer and director **Ryan Engle **and President of Sidney Kimmel Entertainment Mark Lindsay.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Early Show</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2007/the-early-show-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 May 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2007/the-early-show-2/</guid>
      <description>Jorja Fox: I&amp;rsquo;m not a big fan of Sara being in, in peril. I think that when you play a character as long as I have, what, it&amp;rsquo;s going on 36 years? No, 7 years, you become very, very, very, very, very close to that character in ways that, uh, are difficult to describe. So intrinsically as an artist, y&amp;rsquo;know, my desire is to protect that character and keep that character safe.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Star </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/star/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 May 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/star/</guid>
      <description>Frustrated by their star&amp;rsquo;s continuing complaints, sources say, &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; decides to get rid of Jorja Fox once and for all &amp;#8212; but the actress finds a way to foil their plans (for now!)
Head honchos at CBS&amp;rsquo;s top-rated crime drama &amp;ldquo;CSI: Crime Scene Investigation&amp;rdquo;, sick of actress **Jorja Fox&amp;rdquo;s unending salary demands, decided to kill off her popular character &amp;#8212; Sara Sidle &amp;#8212; once and for all, a source tells &amp;ldquo;Star&amp;rdquo;!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Guide </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/tv-guide-11/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 May 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/tv-guide-11/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
Way back then, viewers were just coming to terms with his secret relationship with Sara Sidle (Jorja Fox). And in the finale, according to Shankar, &amp;ldquo;this is the episode where Grissom goes public about the relationship&amp;rdquo; after Sara suddenly disappears. Fox&amp;rsquo;s contract with the show is up at the end of this season, and the network has no comment on wether she&amp;rsquo;ll be returning next season. Shankar will only admit that the situation Sara finds herself in &amp;ldquo;will have some significant ramifications for her relationship with Grissom.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bay Windows </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/bay-windows/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 May 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/bay-windows/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
I&amp;rsquo;ve never watched any of those &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; shows &amp;ndash; except for the Faye Dunaway episode! But, I&amp;rsquo;m always looking out for Jorja Fox, since we&amp;rsquo;re both alums of the American Academy of Dramatic Arts in NYC. Alas, the actress&amp;rsquo; future with CSI is in jeopardy. There&amp;rsquo;s the well-documented salary dispute she and co-star George Eads had (they walked out, CBS said fine, they came back without a raise). Now we hear that when the show wanted to film Foxy&amp;rsquo;s death scene, she refused to show up on the set &amp;ndash; smart girl!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Early Show</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2007/the-early-show/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 May 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2007/the-early-show/</guid>
      <description>Chen&amp;rsquo;s &amp;lsquo;CSI&amp;rsquo; Investigation
Julie Chen gets an exclusive behind-the-scenes look at the hit crime drama &amp;ldquo;CSI.&amp;rdquo; She speaks with actors Marg Helgenberger, William Petersen, Paul Guilfoyle and Jorja Fox.
Julie Chen: This season, CSI has given us everything from Grissom and Sara big romance to the so-called &amp;lsquo;Miniature killer&amp;rsquo; who left scale model miniature of crime scenes. Cast members told me those models were as fascinating for them as they were for viewers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>STLtoday </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/stltoday/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 May 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/stltoday/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
Characters MIA in season finales will include Dr. Luka Kovac (Goran Visnjic) of &amp;ldquo;ER&amp;rdquo; and investigator Sara Sidle (Jorja Fox) of &amp;ldquo;CSI.&amp;rdquo; Visnjic&amp;rsquo;s contract was up when Luka flew off to Croatia, probably never to return. Fox, also at a contract impasse, was scheduled to be killed off &amp;ndash; until, gossip has it, she refused to show up to film her death scene. Finding out Sara&amp;rsquo;s fate may mean staying tuned until fall.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Herald </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/the-herald/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 May 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/the-herald/</guid>
      <description>On the election, the online petition site ePetitions has a call for an international commission to investigate Scotland&amp;rsquo;s voting chaos as its top petition yesterday. To show the seriousness of the situation, a petition demanding that the writers of hit TV series CSI do not kill off Las Vegas investigator Sara Sidle, played by Jorja Fox, was beaten into third place.
[&amp;hellip;]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Buddy TV </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/buddy-tv-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 May 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/buddy-tv-3/</guid>
      <description>As we told you last week, speculation is running rampant about whether Jorja Fox, who plays Sara Sidle, will be leaving CSI. Now more possible details have emerged â but are they true? You be the judge.
Beware of possible spoilers for the upcoming season finale, set to air May 17.
Previously it was reported that her character was set to go missing, but this week the New York Post reported that her character was slated to die in a car accident because of Jorja Fox&amp;rsquo;s ongoing contract dispute with the show.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KansasCity.com </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/kansascity-com/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 May 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/kansascity-com/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
Not going easily&amp;hellip;
[&amp;hellip;]
And &amp;hellip; SPOILER ALERT &amp;hellip; Jorja Fox&amp;rsquo;s character on &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; is apparently a goner due to a salary dispute, but she apparently got some revenge by refusing to show up to shoot the death scene.
Her spokesperson says she did eventually show up, but The &amp;ldquo;New York Post&amp;rdquo; says the show had already done an alternate ending.
[&amp;hellip;]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Philadelphia Daily News </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/philadelphia-daily-news-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 May 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/philadelphia-daily-news-2/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
Correction: In [[Philadelphia Daily News (03 May 2007)|yesterday&amp;rsquo;s]] item on Jorja Fox and &amp;ldquo;CSI,&amp;rdquo; we quoted a CBS spokesperson. The quotes actually came from Jorja&amp;rsquo;s spokesperson. Our bad.
[&amp;hellip;]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E Canada Now </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/e-canada-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 May 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/e-canada-now/</guid>
      <description>Jorja Fox was supposed to die at the end of &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; this year - but she has refused to show up for work on the set to film her &amp;ldquo;death scene.&amp;rdquo;
According to reports, the show&amp;rsquo;s execs have been unhappy with the star&amp;rsquo;s salary demands, and decided to kill off her CSI character, Sara Sidle, who&amp;rsquo;s in a secret romance with boss Gil Grissom (William Petersen).
Fox was scheduled to film Sara&amp;rsquo;s death scene late last month, when her character was supposed to be crushed by a car for the May 17 season finale.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ETonline </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/et-online-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 May 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/et-online-1/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
Another ongoing storyline this season has been the secret romance between Grissom and Sara Sidle (JORJA FOX). Because of that, Thea, who watched as Billy Petersen interrupted her interview with Marg to plant a big kiss on his co-star&amp;rsquo;s mouth, had to ask where he sees his on-screen romance going.
&amp;ldquo;Grissom and Sara have had a relationship for a while,&amp;rdquo; he points out. &amp;ldquo;We don&amp;rsquo;t know for how long and in what way, but they have, obviously, had a relationship for a long time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Philadelphia Daily News </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/philadelphia-daily-news-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 May 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/philadelphia-daily-news-1/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
Jorja on our minds
That Jorja Fox is one feisty &amp;ldquo;CSI.&amp;rdquo; No wonder Grissom loves her.
According to the &amp;ldquo;Star&amp;rdquo; and the &amp;ldquo;New York Post&amp;rdquo;, Fox, who plays Sara Sidle on the hit CBS show, was supposed to bite the Las Vegas desert dust in this season&amp;rsquo;s sweeps finale, but she&amp;rsquo;s refused to show up for work to shoot her death scene.
&amp;ldquo;Her contract is up and they are in conversations,&amp;rdquo; said a CBS spokeswoman.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Guide </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/tv-guide-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 May 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/tv-guide-01/</guid>
      <description>Jorja has a raise on her mind. The star of &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; staged a one-day walkout from the set during the shoot of the CBS show&amp;rsquo;s season finale, which airs May 17. The actress is in talks with producers about a new contract to keep her on the show, sources familiar with the discussions tell TV Guide. How those talks go may decide the result of the cliff-hanging finale in which Fox&amp;rsquo;s character, Sara Sidle, is struck by an automobile.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Toronto Star </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/toronto-star-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 May 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/toronto-star-1/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
Dead Beat: Jorja Fox refuses to play dead. Her character, Sarah Sidle, was supposed to die at the end of this season&amp;rsquo;s CSI. CBS sources say the network decided to kill her off after failing to come to a salary agreement for next season. Only Fox refused to show up on set, meaning expensive reshoots with Marg Helgenberger.
[&amp;hellip;]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MSN </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/msn/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 May 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/msn/</guid>
      <description>**Another contract dispute with CBS may mean Sara Sidle is toast **
Here we go again.
In a repeat performance of 2004, Jorja Fox refused to show up on the set of CSI because of a salary dispute with CBS.
The New York Post is reporting that Fox&amp;rsquo;s character, Sara Sidle, was being written off the forensics drama because show execs weren&amp;rsquo;t happy with her contract demands, one of which was a &amp;ldquo;major raise&amp;rdquo; from her $100,000 US per episode.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New York Post </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/new-york-post-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 May 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/new-york-post-1/</guid>
      <description>** &amp;#8216;CSI&amp;rsquo; STAR REFUSES TO DIE**
JORJA Fox was supposed to die at the end of &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; this year - but she has refused to show up on the set to film her &amp;ldquo;death scene,&amp;rdquo; according to a published report.
A salary dispute with CBS was at the bottom of the unusual stand-off.
Unhappy with Fox&amp;rsquo;s demands, execs decided to kill off her &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; character, Sara Sidle, who&amp;rsquo;s romantically involved with boss Gil Grissom (William Petersen).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Celebrity Dog Watcher </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/celebrity-dog-watcher/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 May 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/celebrity-dog-watcher/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Los Angeles Confidential&amp;rdquo; magazine featured &amp;ldquo;CSI: Crime Scene Investigation**s Jorja Fox in the May issue, âGimmie Shelter&amp;rsquo; column.
Jorja talked about her ten-and-a-half-year-old Boxer Ali (yes, as in Muhammad Ali), a rescue dog from New York.
The article revealed Fox&amp;rsquo;s soft spot for animals, her childhood dream to have a show on &amp;ldquo;Animal Planet&amp;rdquo; that hasn&amp;rsquo;t gone away and her assistance with the &amp;ldquo;North Central Animal Shelter&amp;rdquo; last year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Journal of The American Academy of Dramatic Arts </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/journal-of-the-american-academy-of-dramatic-arts/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 May 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/journal-of-the-american-academy-of-dramatic-arts/</guid>
      <description>We recently invited Jorja Fox and Eric Szmanda of the hit television series *CSI: Crime Scene Investigation *to share their professional and Academy experiences with us.
In what ways do you value the training you received at AADA?
AADA really taught me to be in the moment. To be as present as I can. I use that training all the time every day. The teachers had high expectations of us, but were very kind and supportive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Los Angeles Confidential</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/los-angeles-confidential/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 May 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/los-angeles-confidential/</guid>
      <description>Jorja Fox may have new mysteries to solve every week on CSI, but she has a kindhearted philosophy about animals all figured out.
LOS ANGELES CONFIDENTIAL: You&amp;rsquo;re currently starring on CSI: Crime Scene Investigation, one of the hottest shows on TV, yet it&amp;rsquo;s rumored your dream job would be to have a show on Animal Planet. Is that true?
JORJA FOX: It was one of those childhood dreams that never completely went away.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Buddy TV </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/buddy-tv-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Apr 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/buddy-tv-2/</guid>
      <description>Although many deem the Grissom-Sara love affair to be a significant contributing factor for the intriguing yet forced plot of the show, the couple&amp;rsquo;s fans might need to say goodbye to their on screen romance. Although it hasn&amp;rsquo;t been confirmed or denied by CBS, many speculate that Jorja Fox, actress who plays Sara Sidle on Crime Scene Investigation, will be leaving the Emmy Award-winning CBS television series. According to TV Guide, Fox&amp;rsquo;s contract is up to next month and that she may not renew for the next season.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Associated Content </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/associated-content/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/associated-content/</guid>
      <description>Rumors are swirling that CSI is set to kill off Sara Sidle. &amp;ldquo;TV Guide&amp;rdquo; is reporting that the Jorja Fox&amp;rsquo;s contract is up next month and that she may not renew.
&amp;ldquo;TV Guide&amp;rdquo; quotes a source close to the show, &amp;ldquo;Her leaving makes perfect sense. She&amp;rsquo;s been there for seven years, she&amp;rsquo;s made a ton of money, and it allows the show to resolve the Sara-Grissom thing.&amp;rdquo;
On the other hand Fox seems perfectly content and hasn&amp;rsquo;t made any public rumblings about leaving.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Guide </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/tv-guide-22/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Apr 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/tv-guide-22/</guid>
      <description>A &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; Contract Drama
I hate to be the bearer of bad news, but next time &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rsquo;s&amp;rdquo; Jorja Fox goes in for a costume fitting, she might find a body bag hanging in her closet. Although a rep for the actress declined to comment, a source close to the show confirms that her contract expires next month and she&amp;rsquo;s itching to pursue greener (and less grisly) pastures. &amp;ldquo;Her leaving makes perfect sense,&amp;rdquo; says my spy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CTV </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/ctv-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Apr 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/ctv-1/</guid>
      <description>Underneath the crime scenes and forensic labs on &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; lays one of the show&amp;rsquo;s most compelling mysteries: the relationship between Gil Grissom, head of the crime lab, and investigator Sara Sidle.
Their relationship, which has been suggested went back years before the series began at a seminar in San Francisco, has evolved from season to season.
And as the seventh season of the show comes to a close, the situation could turn sour for the crime-scene couple.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Guide </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/tv-guide-19/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Apr 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/tv-guide-19/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
Question: Do you have any news on Jorja Fox&amp;rsquo;s contract negotiations with &amp;ldquo;CSI?&amp;rdquo; - Stephanie
Ausiello: I do, but I&amp;rsquo;m going to have to refer you to my Ausiello Report vodcast for the latest. (The vodcast can be viewed on the video player in the upper right-hand corner at Ausiello Central.)
[&amp;hellip;]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Guide </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/tv-guide-16/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Apr 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/tv-guide-16/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
CSI may be headed toward another contract showdown with its star, Jorja Fox. According to sources, the actress&amp;rsquo;s commitment with the show ends next month and she has yet to sign a new deal, and she may not.
Sources say Fox is itching for those elusive greener pastures and after seven years on the show and millions of dollars in the bank, it might be time for a change. A spokesperson from the show had no comment, but a close look at the show reveals that producers may already be laying the groundwork for her character&amp;rsquo;s exit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Capilano College Film Centre </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/capilano-college-film-centre/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Apr 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/capilano-college-film-centre/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
After David [Berman], we spoke with Jorja Fox who plays Sara Sidle. Jorja was absolutely hilarious and incredibly down-to-earth. She kept making faces at David during our interview with him and making him laugh.
[&amp;hellip;]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Popgurls.com </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/popgurls-com/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Apr 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/popgurls-com/</guid>
      <description>The first thing that I notice about Jorja Fox is how quick she is to laugh. It&amp;rsquo;s a little disarming, considering her character on CSI: Crime Scene Investigation, Sara Sidle, is not known for her jovial sense of humor. Disarming, yet infectious and even over the phone, its feels less like an interview and more like we&amp;rsquo;re kicking back a few beers in a local pub and sharing stories.
She talks to PopGurls about the community on CSI, the Grissom/Sara relationship, Eric Szmanda&amp;rsquo;s influence and being homeless in Europe at 17.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chicago Tribune </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/chicago-tribune-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Apr 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/chicago-tribune-1/</guid>
      <description>Because I like stirring up &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; fans, I thought I&amp;rsquo;d post this summary of what&amp;rsquo;s going to happen on the May 17 season finale of the CBS show. Standard spoiler alert: Avert your eyes if you don&amp;rsquo;t want to know.
You&amp;rsquo;ll recall that a year ago, fans of the show were either really happy or really angry that a romantic relationship between Grissom (William L. Petersen) and Sara (Jorja Fox) was revealed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ecorazzi </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/ecorazzi/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/ecorazzi/</guid>
      <description>Actress Jorja Fox is a committed environmentalist and animal rights activist. As I&amp;rsquo;ve just seen in an amusing video, she&amp;rsquo;s also really into biking. The clip shows Jorja and SpinDaily host, Katherine, Orange20 Bikes in LA and checking out all the new models &amp;ndash; from hybrid to fixed gear. It&amp;rsquo;s a pretty candid take on their time there with Jorja and Katherine performing &amp;ldquo;ride-bys&amp;rdquo; while singing songs. As Cyclelicious points out, there are also some great quotes:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cyclelicious </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/cyclelicious/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Mar 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/cyclelicious/</guid>
      <description>Jorja Fox plays the brainy brunette on CSI. She demonstrates her smarts by confessing, &amp;ldquo;The only crime here is that we don&amp;rsquo;t have bicycles.&amp;rdquo; Jorja and Katherine of SpinDaily visit Orange 20 Bikes in Los Angeles, trying out a hybrid, a nice Breezer Bike, and even a fixed gear bicycle. Jorja needs a bike that can carry a surf board on the bike.
Some select quotes:
 &amp;ldquo;If I had a bike, I wouldn&amp;rsquo;t have to worry about two hour parking or parking meters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Los Angeles Times </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/los-angeles-times/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Mar 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/los-angeles-times/</guid>
      <description>This &amp;#8216;CSI&amp;rsquo; snoop knows how to locate L.A.&amp;rsquo;s vegetarian options YOU know the face. Jorja Fox has had major roles in three of TV&amp;rsquo;s biggest hits &amp;ndash; &amp;ldquo;ER&amp;rdquo; (as Dr. Maggie Doyle), &amp;ldquo;The West Wing&amp;rdquo; (as Agent Gina Toscano) and for the last seven seasons as Investigator Sara Sidle on CBS&amp;rsquo; &amp;ldquo;CSI.&amp;rdquo; Keep your eye out tonight for this single-but-involved, very vegetarian L.A. resident. She&amp;rsquo;s featured in a &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; episode called &amp;ldquo;Empty Eyes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Entertainment Weekly </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/ew-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Mar 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/ew-1/</guid>
      <description>Last year, &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo;&amp;rsquo;s Jorja Fox and Eric Szmanda (above) were teammates on an Adult Kickball League team called the Royal Blue Balls. How did the actors fare on the court? So-so: The Balls were eliminated from competition in the semifinals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Buddy TV </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/buddy-tv-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Mar 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/buddy-tv-1/</guid>
      <description>On CBS&amp;rsquo;s hit CSI flagship show, the romantic relationship between CSIs Sara Sidle and her boss Gil Grissom has been a matter of much controversy with fans weighing in on both sides.
For years fans have speculated on the nature of their relationship, as the characters were introduced as having a mysterious past history that hinted at more than just a mentor and student bond. While both at times were shown in fleeting relationships with other people, it turns out now that they&amp;rsquo;ve been together for a while.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SpinDaily</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2007/spindaily/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2007/spindaily/</guid>
      <description>Katherine: Hi, I&amp;rsquo;m Katherine from SpinDaily.
Jorja Fox: Hi, I&amp;rsquo;m Jorja Fox from &amp;ldquo;CSI:&amp;ldquo;, and the only crime here is that we don&amp;rsquo;t have bicycles.
[&amp;hellip;]
Jorja Fox: I am looking for a recreational, kind of weekend bike. I surf, I would love to get a bicycle that I could put a rack on the side, and I could take my bike to the beach.
Katherine: Wait, can you put a surfboard, carry a surfboard on a bike?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Malay Mail </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/the-malay-mail/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Mar 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/the-malay-mail/</guid>
      <description>GET ready for more intriguing crimebusting as our hardworking Las Vegas Crime Scene Investigators return on AXN in a brand new season that is &amp;ldquo;built to kill&amp;rdquo;.
[&amp;hellip;]
And finally, fans of gossip and rumours get something hot this season &amp;#8212; a passionate secret affair! Just as the crimes become more intense, the sexual and emotional attraction between team leader Gil Grissom and the freckled Sara Sidle brews under the covers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>San Francisco Bay Area Independent Media Center </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/san-francisco-bay-area-independent-media-center/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/san-francisco-bay-area-independent-media-center/</guid>
      <description>San Francisco Indie Fest Closes with controversial film &amp;ldquo;Your Mommy Kills Animals&amp;rdquo;.
[&amp;hellip;]
&amp;ldquo;Your Mommy Kills Animals&amp;rdquo; is an in-depth look at the controversial animal rights movement and the FBI&amp;rsquo;s recent declaration calling them the number one domestic terrorist threat to the United States. While showing both the good and the problems in the movement, doc covers the landmark case against Stop Huntingdon Animal Cruelty (SHAC) and the resulting conviction which literally has changed the course of activism in this country .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Boston Herald </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/boston-herald-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/boston-herald-1/</guid>
      <description>Love makes the TV story line go round.
Without it, the pretty interns would be stuck just treating patients on &amp;ldquo;Grey&amp;rsquo;s Anatomy.&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;The Office&amp;rdquo; would be a savage satire without any heart.
In honor of Valentine&amp;rsquo;s Day, consider a few top TV couples:
[&amp;hellip;]
[*]Sara and Grissom on CBS&amp;rsquo; &amp;ldquo;CSI: Crime Scene Investigation&amp;rdquo; (Thursday at 9 p.m. on WBZ, Ch. 4): It&amp;rsquo;s a little awkward. Grissom (William Petersen) and Sara&amp;rsquo;s (Jorja Fox) relationship was a secret even to the show&amp;rsquo;s fans until last season&amp;rsquo;s kimono-wearing final moments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Guide </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/tv-guide-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/tv-guide-10/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
Question: There have been rumors swirling that Jorja Fox might not be back for Season 8 of CSI. Got any scoop on her contract status?- Laura
Ausiello: She&amp;rsquo;s in negotiations now. My guess? She&amp;rsquo;ll be back.
[&amp;hellip;]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yahoo! Finance </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/yahoo-finance-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/yahoo-finance-2/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Charlotte&amp;rsquo;s Web,&amp;rsquo; &amp;#8216;Happy Feet,&amp;rsquo; &amp;#8216;Fast Food Nation,&amp;rsquo; and &amp;#8216;Open Season&amp;rsquo; are Among the Nominees at The Humane Society of The United States&amp;rsquo; Annual Celebration of Animal-Friendly Media**
The Humane Society of the United States (HSUS) today announced nominees for its 21st Genesis Awards, honoring the news and entertainment media for showcasing animal protection issues. Winners in 18 categories will be presented on Saturday, March 24, 2007 at a gala ceremony at the Beverly Hilton in Beverly Hills, CA.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Guide </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/tv-guide-03/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/tv-guide-03/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
Question: Anything on the CSI front regarding Sara-Grissom? &amp;#8212; Penelope
Ausiello: There&amp;rsquo;s a big Sara episode coming up in April in which she gets a little too emotionally involved in a case. Complicating matters is the fact that, unlike most of the show&amp;rsquo;s victims, this one has a pulse. (For more on what&amp;rsquo;s ahead for Srissom, read [http://www.tvguide.com/Magazine/Cover-Story/ this excerpt] of the cover story in the new issue of TV Guide magazine, on sale Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Guardian Unlimited </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/guardian-unlimited/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/guardian-unlimited/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
12.34pm: &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;ll see your five-a-side football with Andy McCluskey and raise you five-a-sides with all the members of Teenage Fanclub followed by a few light refreshments in the bar afterwards,&amp;rdquo; writes Chris Black. Nice try, Chris, but you&amp;rsquo;re sunk now. I&amp;rsquo;ll see your footie with Scotland&amp;rsquo;s answer to the Beach Boys and raise you putting Johnny Vegas to bed after a session &amp;ldquo;and&amp;rdquo; asking Jorja Fox who plays Sara Sidle in CSI out for a drink.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Guide </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/tv-guide-33/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/tv-guide-33/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
Question: You haven&amp;rsquo;t said much regarding any of the CSI shows. Got any spoilers?- Kelly
Ausiello: Would you believe I have stuff on all three shows? Let&amp;rsquo;s start with the mother ship: Sara and Grissom are going to engage in an intimate act that involves her taking a sharp object to his neck. (Bonus scoop: This act takes place in Sara&amp;rsquo;s posh new pad).
[&amp;hellip;]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Woman Magazine UK</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/woman-magazine-uk/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/woman-magazine-uk/</guid>
      <description>Does being too popular do more harm than good? CSI star Jorja Fox says her blessing in disguise was Not Always Fitting In.
&amp;lsquo;Where I grew up, I wasn&amp;rsquo;t even close to being cool. My family lived in the smallest, most rural town in Florida, called Melbourne Beach, and it was an outdoors-y community where beauty was all about being tanned and blonde.
But I was chubby, awkward and fair-skinned with dark hair - and a 10p-sized gap between my teeth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yahoo! Finance </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/yahoo-finance-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/yahoo-finance-1/</guid>
      <description>Open Letter Demands Celebrities Withdraw Support for PETA
The Center for Consumer Freedom, a consumer watchdog group, is running a full-page open letter in Thursday&amp;rsquo;s Hollywood edition of Variety calling on Pamela Anderson, Alec Baldwin, Simon Cowell, James Cromwell, Jorja Fox, Moby, and other celebrities to stop their support of People for the Ethical Treatment of Animals (PETA). [&amp;hellip;]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MSN Sympatico </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/msn-sympatico/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/msn-sympatico/</guid>
      <description>The CSIer talks about her website, her beliefs, and the possibility that CSI may lose fans because of Liev Schreiber
Jorja Fox is refreshingly forthright, until you ask her about upcoming CSI storylines. But as long as we don&amp;rsquo;t, Fox is willing to talk about anything, including the possibility that fans may tune out while co-star William Petersen is gone from the forensic drama.
TV Guide: Hey Jorja, how are you doing?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KRO Mikro Guide </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/kro-mikro-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/kro-mikro-guide/</guid>
      <description>Every young actress with ambition hopes to make it in movies. But if it doesn&amp;rsquo;t work out the way you wanted, television can be a great alternative for a successful career. A great example of this is Jorja Fox (38).
She has appeared on the hit series [[CSI: Crime Scene Investigation]] for six years. Previous, she appeared on two other hit series: [[ER]] and [[The West Wing]].
Anyone who tries to remember her movies, probably comes up with [[Memento]].</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Defamer </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/defamer-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/defamer-1/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
Ellen DeGeneres focused on the word itself, telling Extra: &amp;ldquo;This particular word is thrown around all the time at the workplace, at the playground, on the sports field and no one gets outraged. Hopefully this incident will put an end to this and people will stop using this word and other hateful words once and for all.&amp;rdquo; Let&amp;rsquo;s hope the insanity stops here, and that Jorja Fox isn&amp;rsquo;t forced to drop by Ellen to tearfully recount the time Gil Grissom called her a &amp;ldquo;greedy rugmuncher&amp;rdquo; upon discovering she ate the last craft service banana.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Guide </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/tv-guide-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/tv-guide-02/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
Speaking of torches, what about the one Grissom carries for Sara? According to Mendelsohn, his departure will cause tension in that relationship, the source of which will become clear in a future episode &amp;#8212; when Grissom will try to make things right by &amp;ldquo;sending Sara (Jorja Fox) something. Fans may remember the last time he did that, it was a plant. So for longtime fans, this will have resonance.&amp;rdquo;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>News Articles (2007)</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/</guid>
      <description>Date Source    January 01 Series TV   January 01 TV &amp;amp; Satellite Week   January 04 TV Guide    January 19 Defamer    January 21 KRO Mikro Guide    January 23 MSN Sympatico    January 24 Yahoo! Finance    January 29 Woman Magazine UK   January 31 Guardian Unlimited    January 31 TV Guide    February 07 TV Guide    February 08 Yahoo!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Series TV</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/series-tv/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/series-tv/</guid>
      <description>Number one all around the world, CSI is apparently still at the top of its game. One could be forgiven for thinking that after seven seasons and two spin-offs, the genre would have completely lost steam, but that&amp;rsquo;s not taking into account the talent of the writers and the quality of the actors. We went to talk to the team behind the show to find out what they have in store for us in Season seven and how the show has managed to remain as fresh as ever.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV &amp; Satellite Week</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/tv-and-satellite-week-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/tv-and-satellite-week-1/</guid>
      <description>Jorja Fox takes time off from playing CSI&amp;rsquo;s forensics investigator Sara Sidle to show us around the set of the hit TV Show
###The crime lab###
&amp;ldquo;We have one of the best equipped labs in the US, even though it&amp;rsquo;s only TV. A lot of the equipment is given to us by the companies that make it, and there&amp;rsquo;s a technical expert with us every day. I could probably use the equipment to fingerprint and identify body fluids, but most other things vanish from my brain as soon as I do them.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>