<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>1997 on JFO Library</title>
    <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/tags/1997/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 1997 on JFO Library</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Sep 1997 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://jorjafox.net/library/tags/1997/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Gay TV</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/1997/gay-tv/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 1997 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/1997/gay-tv/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;FUN FACTOID&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jorja Fox is also the actress known as Jorjan Fox. They&amp;rsquo;re the same person, but when she joined the cast of &lt;em&gt;ER,&lt;/em&gt; Jorjan shortened her name to Jorja. Oh, those showbiz types.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All of America will be watching &lt;em&gt;ER&lt;/em&gt; tomorrow night as TV&amp;rsquo;s top-rated show is broadcast live for its fourth season premiere! Will Dr. Ross and Nurse Hathaway rekindle their romance? Will Dr. Greene finally get over his assault from last season? And, more importantly, will the actors royally flub those lines of long, complicated medical jargon they so convincingly bark out every week? Gay and lesbian viewers might also want to find out what&amp;rsquo;s next for &lt;em&gt;ER&lt;/em&gt;&amp;rsquo;s lesbian second-year resident, Maggie Doyle, played by the spunky young actress &lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When Fox joined the cast last season as the headstrong resident Doyle, it was readily apparent that, green as she may be, Doyle wasn&amp;rsquo;t one to take crap from anybody. She is a character full of contradictions. She drives a BMW but comes from a middle-class background (her dad&amp;rsquo;s a cop). She seemed flirty enough with handsome fellow resident John Carter (&lt;strong&gt;Noah Wyle&lt;/strong&gt;), but when taking some target practice with him on a shooting range she happened to see one of her ex-girlfriends in a nearby booth firing away. Needless to say that Carter, and &lt;em&gt;ER&lt;/em&gt;&amp;rsquo;s viewers, were surprised to hear this news. What will happen to Doyle this season? It&amp;rsquo;s hard to say, but the show&amp;rsquo;s writers seem eager to include her in the mad rush of every episode, so maybe this year we can get to know more about Doyle&amp;rsquo;s life outside the ER.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a fun gay-related item, Fox played up her newfound gay notoriety last spring, when she appeared at the end of the now infamous &lt;em&gt;Ellen&lt;/em&gt; coming-out episode as a woman who approaches Ellen at the lesbian coffeehouse, only to hit on Ellen&amp;rsquo;s pal, Paige.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Washington Post</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/1997/washington-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 1997 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/1997/washington-post/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With all the publicity when &amp;ldquo;Ellen&amp;rdquo; stepped out of the closet on ABC last spring, apparently no one noticed that the Maggie Doyle doctor character also came out on &amp;ldquo;ER&amp;rdquo; &amp;ndash; &amp;ldquo;There was absolutely no response to that story line,&amp;rdquo; [John] Wells [Executive Producer] said &amp;ldquo;&amp;hellip; She&amp;rsquo;ll be back in the fall, he said. &amp;ldquo;She is a doctor and a character who we like, who just happens to be gay &amp;hellip;. It doesn&amp;rsquo;t make her unusual in any way within the hospital environment&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Advocate</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/1997/the-advocate/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 1997 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/1997/the-advocate/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*&lt;strong&gt;ER* gets a lesbian&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;P&lt;/strong&gt;rime-time TV just got it&amp;rsquo;s 24th gay character. &lt;em&gt;ER&lt;/em&gt;&amp;rsquo;s Dr. Maggie Doyle, played by &lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt;, came out to fellow first-year resident, Dr. John Carter, played by &lt;strong&gt;Noah Wyle&lt;/strong&gt;, on the Feburary 6 episode of the hit NBC drama. To coproducer Dr. Neal Baer, who wrote the script, Maggie&amp;rsquo;s lesbian revelation is no big deal. &amp;ldquo;We also found out that she&amp;rsquo;s a vegetarian in that episode and that she collects guns,&amp;rdquo; Baer told The Buzz. &amp;ldquo;There are all kinds of stereotypes. I wanted to make sure this person doesn&amp;rsquo;t fit into any box.&amp;rdquo; Nor will Maggie lead with her lesbianism, says Baer. &amp;ldquo;We&amp;rsquo;re going to play her as a doctor who happens to be a lesbian. If it comes up, it comes up, just like in real life. Maybe someday there&amp;rsquo;ll be a patient who says &amp;lsquo;I don&amp;rsquo;t want her touching me.&amp;rsquo; That would be an interesting story, because that happens.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GLAAD</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/1997/glaad/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 1997 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/1997/glaad/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;On &amp;ldquo;Whose Appy Now?,&amp;rdquo; the February 6 episode of NBC-TV&amp;rsquo;s hit show E.R., the newly arrived Dr. Maggie Doyle (Jorjan Fox) came out to her sometimes nemesis and co-worker Dr. John Carter (Noah Wyle). Over this past season, the two characters have slowly made the transition from fighting over turf and authority to becoming friends. Near the end of the episode, Carter asks Maggie if she wants to go out that evening, but she declines, saying she already has plans. Offering to take him along, they go to a shooting range, where Maggie shows Carter how to aim and fire. At the range, Maggie spies her ex-girlfriend, with whom she just broke up a few months earlier. The ex is a cop, and, as Maggie says, &amp;ldquo;She&amp;rsquo;s jealous as hell.&amp;rdquo; Carter, startled, shoots out a light at the range.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;GLAAD Entertainment Media Director Chastity Bono said, &amp;ldquo;This new side of Dr. Maggie Doyle will hopefully develop into a strong plot line. GLAAD is eager to see where E.R. takes such a potentially exciting lesbian or bisexual supporting character on this critically acclaimed program.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>News Articles (1997)</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/1997/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 1997 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/1997/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>