<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Interviews on Fans of Le Fox Library</title>
    <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/categories/interviews/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Interviews on Fans of Le Fox Library</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://jorjafox.net/library/categories/interviews/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The Reluctant Entertainers</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2017/reluctant-entertainers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2017/reluctant-entertainers/</guid>
      <description>Ed Asner: Some of us love to entertain
Jorja Fox: But animals don&amp;rsquo;t get a choice.
Eric Roberts: Can you imagine?
Mindy Sterling: Can you imagine?
Eric Szmanda: Can you imagine?
Moby: Being stuck in a metal box.
Alexandra Paul: Seeing the world through bars.
Tonya Kay: No grass beneath your feet.
James Cromwell: No space to run.
Eric Szmanda: Tied up. Chained.
James Cromwell: Barely able to move.
Eric Roberts: Shouted at.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Transcripts (2017)</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2017/</guid>
      <description>  Date Source    March 27 The Reluctant Entertainers    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shark Allies</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2016/shark-allies/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2016/shark-allies/</guid>
      <description>Sharks are more important to our lives than we may imagine. It is time for us to appreciate their significance. We are grateful for the amazing job they do, every day, in all the oceans around the world to keep fish stock and the ocean healthy and vibrant.
Thank you, sharks, for making us feel awe and wonder, for connecting us to the wild, for being a fierce predator but not seeing us as prey.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Transcripts (2016)</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2016/</guid>
      <description>  Date Source    July 21 Shark Allies    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Extra at the EMA Awards Green Carpet</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2015/ema-awards/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Oct 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2015/ema-awards/</guid>
      <description>Renee Bargh: &amp;hellip; Ah but first up we&amp;rsquo;ve got Jorja Fox from CSI. Hi, how are you?
Jorja Fox: You look amazing.
Renee: You love wonderful.
Jorja: Thank you.
Renee: You look great. So tell me, why is it so important to be at this event?
Jorja: I think it&amp;rsquo;s one of the most important events that you could attend in Los Angeles. Bringing attention to environmental awareness, which is at such a critical, frightening stage right now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lylapalooza</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2015/lylapalooza/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2015/lylapalooza/</guid>
      <description>CSI star Jorja Fox takes time out to chat with Lyla about dogs, insects, and ice cream. Special guest appearance by Belle the puppy.
Lyla: This is Lylapalooza and we have Jorja Fox on our show today. Hello, Jorja, how are you today?
Jorja: I am very good, Lyla, how are you doing?
Lyla: Good. This is my shnuffler. Shnuffle. Do you have anything to say?
&amp;ldquo;Belle the Puppy:** *silence*</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shark Allies</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2015/shark-allies/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2015/shark-allies/</guid>
      <description>Jorja Fox talks about her personal connection to the ocean and her perception of trophy hunting and the misrepresentation of sharks in the media.
Our Connection to the Ocean
I spend as much time on the water as I can. I&amp;rsquo;ve been bodyboarding since I was about six and surfing for about the last fifteen years. So I&amp;rsquo;m there, you know, several times a week if I can be.
A long time ago, when you think of how mankind kind of evolved on earth, it was this battle</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ExtraTV</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2015/extra-tv/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2015/extra-tv/</guid>
      <description>On the Set of &amp;lsquo;CSI&amp;rsquo;! All the Scoop on the Series Finale *&amp;lsquo;Crime Watch Daily&amp;rsquo; host Matt Doran was the perfect &amp;lsquo;Extra&amp;rsquo; special correspondent to stop by the &amp;lsquo;CSI&amp;rsquo; set to get the scoop on the series finale. Watch!
Catch the final episode Sept. 27 at 9 PM on CBS.
[&amp;hellip;]
Matt Doran: (voice over) Jorja Fox, ready to put her work boots on one last time.
Matt Doran: What can you tell us about what we can expect from the finale?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Transcripts (2015)</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2015/</guid>
      <description>  Date Source    August 18 ExtraTV   September 29 Lylapalooza   September 29 Shark Allies   October 24 Extra at the EMA Awards Green Carpet    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RedCarpetReport TV</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2014/redcarpetreport-tv/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2014/redcarpetreport-tv/</guid>
      <description>Jorja Fox at the 30th Annual IDA Documentary Awards Gala #IDAawards
Quinn Marie: So what brings you out today? You are presenting, correct?
Jorja Fox: I am presenting best episodic series and best limited series, TV awards, which should be kind of fun.
QM: Very cool. And you recently narrated a documentary, correct?
JF: You know, I have actually. Thanks for knowing that! Actually a bit ago I narrated a documentary about Gidget.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Green with Tiffany</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2014/green-with-tiffany/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2014/green-with-tiffany/</guid>
      <description>Tiffany Paige: We&amp;rsquo;re here with actress Jorja Fox from CSI. What brings you here tonight?
Jorja Fox: I&amp;rsquo;m very excited about this event, it&amp;rsquo;s an event very close to my heart. I&amp;rsquo;m representing Artists &amp;amp; Athletes tonight. I&amp;rsquo;m on the advisory board and we&amp;rsquo;re a collective of artists and athletes that connect with Washington DC on issues that are close to everybody. Kind of create a dialogue between the different camps and bring us together to get things that we care about on the floor and up for conversation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Twitter Live Chat</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2014/twitter-live-chat/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Mar 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2014/twitter-live-chat/</guid>
      <description>Tweet
**&amp;#8212; Nikki @PenguinsFan87 **
Q: @JorjaFoxofficia How did you hear about CSI and how did u try auditioning for any of characters before you got Sara Sidle role? #CSI
&amp;#8212; LeFox @JorjaFoxofficia
A: .@PenguinsFan87 I had a birthday party at my house - someone at the party told me about it. Only auditioned for Sara. #CSI
&amp;#8212;-
Tweet
&amp;#8212; LeFox @JorjaFoxofficia
Everyone in here is telling me to be quiet so they can type.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SuperPopACCESS</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2014/superpopaccess/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2014/superpopaccess/</guid>
      <description>INTERVIEW - Eric Szmanda, Jorja Fox on the best part about Grammy weekend at Universal Music Group 2014 Post Grammy Party at The Ace Hotel Theater on 2014-01-26 in Los Angeles, California.
[&amp;hellip;]
Interviewer: [&amp;hellip;] this weekend?
Eric Szmanda: Well this was both of our first times going to the ceremony and I think it was one of the best ones that I&amp;rsquo;ve seen in recent years. One of my favorite artists kind of swept the awards.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Transcripts (2014)</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2014/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2014/</guid>
      <description>  Date Source    January 26 SuperPopACCESS   March 05 Twitter Live Chat   October 18 Green with Tiffany   December 05 RedCarpetReport TV    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ISSUES with Jane Velez-Mitchell</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2013/issues-with-jane-velez-mitchell/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2013/issues-with-jane-velez-mitchell/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
Jane Velez-Mitchell: CSI star Jorja Fox plays a determined crime scene investigator, who won&amp;rsquo;t let anything stand in her pursuit of the truth. When she&amp;rsquo;s off the set, she&amp;rsquo;s just as determined to free animals from captivity. I talked to Jorja about why she thinks Blackfish is a giant step for all animals in captivity.
[Clip of CSI]
Jane Velez-Mitchell: Jorja Fox, you play Sara Sidle on CSI and you do such a great job of investigating.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Talk (23 October 2013)</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2013/the-talk-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2013/the-talk-2/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
Sara Gilbert: I have to congratulate you guys on 300 episodes.
[audience cheers]
Jorja Fox: [pointing at Eric] He&amp;rsquo;s the only man in the pilot. Right here. All 300.
Sara Gilbert: You&amp;rsquo;ve been there since the first season, but I heard, Jorja, that you didn&amp;rsquo;t think the show was gonna take off.
Jorja Fox: No, and I can say that we&amp;rsquo;re [Jorja and Eric] getting old. [laughter] I can&amp;rsquo;t speak for you guys [Elisabeth and Ted] at all.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CBS CSI300 EPK</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2013/cbs-csi300-epk/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2013/cbs-csi300-epk/</guid>
      <description>&amp;hellip;
Jorja Fox: I was blown away by it, it was so different and I hadn&amp;rsquo;t seen anything ever like it. A show about death, on a Friday night? This is going to be canceled in six weeks, no one&amp;rsquo;s going to watch this! America&amp;rsquo;s not gonna watch this show! And boy was I &amp;hellip; that was extremely wrong about that! [breaks up laughing]
&amp;hellip;
Jorja Fox: It&amp;rsquo;s a great place to go back to.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mill Valley Film Festival Screening (05 October 2013)</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2013/mill-valley-film-festival-screening/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Oct 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2013/mill-valley-film-festival-screening/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Announcer: Please, before we start anything, give a big hand to Pacific Sun, who is responsible for letting Lion Ark be here today. The film is co-presented by Animal Defenders International, which had, obviously you&amp;rsquo;ll see, an integral part in the creation of Lion Ark. We&amp;rsquo;re very happy to have this film, it&amp;rsquo;s a powerful film, it&amp;rsquo;s an exciting film. It&amp;rsquo;s going to subvert a lot of your expectations about both seeing a documentary and about some of the assumptions we had growing up or seeing in our culture.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CableTV.com</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2013/cabletv-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2013/cabletv-1/</guid>
      <description>Monica Gleberman .. and just ask you, how did you get involved in acting to begin with?
Jorja Fox Oh my goodness. I wanted to act since I was probably four or five years old. I think that the television that sat in the living room of my house was one of the bigger influences in my life. It was definitely a babysitter for me. You know, I grew up in a small town, so there weren&amp;rsquo;t many acting programs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Talk (2 April 2013)</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2013/the-talk/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2013/the-talk/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
Sara Gilbert: Our first guest made a name for herself playing strong female characters on shows like ER and The West Wing, and has been solving crimes for more than a decade as analyst Sara Sidle on the most watched TV show in the world: CSI: Crime Scene Investigation. Take a look.
[Clip from &amp;ldquo;Sheltered&amp;rdquo;]
Gilbert: Please welcome Jorja Fox!
Jorja Fox: &amp;hellip; two hour The Talk special today?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CBS Live Chat</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2013/cbs-live-chat/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2013/cbs-live-chat/</guid>
      <description>[The following is saved quotes]
Q - @ThatIsNotAnExit
@CSI_CBS We&amp;rsquo;ve made a message page to jorja so were wondering if there&amp;rsquo;s a way she could get the link? It&amp;rsquo;s http://weloveyoujorjafox.tumblr.com/ #askjorja
A - @CSI_CBS
.@ThatIsNotAnExit We&amp;rsquo;re up and running in a few minutes. Send us your questions #AskJorja xx.
Q - @JulesSweetzer
working on the show for so long, do you feel like you could be a CSI in real life #AskJorja</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CSI Star Jorja Fox Spills Show Secrets - OMG Insider</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2013/csi-star-jorja-fox-spills-show-secrets-omg-insider/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2013/csi-star-jorja-fox-spills-show-secrets-omg-insider/</guid>
      <description>Thea Andrews: Oh dear! Jorja Fox, who plays Sara Sidle, seems to be in some hot water tonight on CSI
Kevin Fraizer: Jorja, welcome.
Jorja Fox: Hi.
Kevin Fraizer: And your character seems to be in a little bit of trouble. What&amp;rsquo;s going on?
Jorja Fox: You know, I don&amp;rsquo;t know what you&amp;rsquo;re talking about. It&amp;rsquo;s just a little misunderstanding!
Thea Andrews: What&amp;rsquo;d you get up to?
Jorja Fox: It gets completely blown out of proportion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Transcripts (2013)</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2013/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2013/</guid>
      <description>  Date Source    February 20 CBS Live Chat   February 20 CSI Star Jorja Fox Spills Show Secrets - OMG Insider   April 02 The Talk (2 April 2013)   September 24 CableTV.com   October 05 Mill Valley Film Festival Screening (05 October 2013)   October 22 CBS CSI300 EPK   October 23 ISSUES with Jane Velez-Mitchell   October 23 The Talk (23 October 2013)    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Marg Helgenberger&#39;s Star on Hollywood Boulevard</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2012/marg-helgenberger-star-on-hollywood-boulevard/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2012/marg-helgenberger-star-on-hollywood-boulevard/</guid>
      <description>Jorja Fox: Hello! Hi, I&amp;rsquo;m the one who&amp;rsquo;s going to have to read everything, as Marg knows.
Marg Helgenberger: It&amp;rsquo;s what you do.
Jorja Fox: Yeah. I&amp;rsquo;m so happy for you. I had the very good fortune of meeting Marg Helgenberger in July of 2000, just as we were embarking on what would prove to be one of the signature adventures of our lives. Over the course of these last twelve years, we&amp;rsquo;ve shared some of the best and most exciting times a person can have.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Transcripts (2012)</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2012/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2012/</guid>
      <description>  Date Source    January 23 Marg Helgenberger&amp;#39;s Star on Hollywood Boulevard    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ET Online</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2011/et-online/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2011/et-online/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
I like to think that I know Marg very well. And she&amp;rsquo;s one of the toughest, most stoic people &amp;lsquo; forget about woman or ladies &amp;lsquo; I mean one of the most stoic people I&amp;rsquo;ve ever met. And these moments where she&amp;rsquo;s kind of overcome are once in a blue moon. Probably the last time I ever saw that happen her dog died, probably six years ago. She&amp;rsquo;s got nerves of steel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AP Celebrity Extra</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2011/ap-celebrity-extra/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2011/ap-celebrity-extra/</guid>
      <description>When she&amp;rsquo;s not solving crimes on &amp;#8216;CSI,&amp;rsquo; you can find actress Jorja Fox on a surfboard. (Nov. 16)
I feel like I&amp;rsquo;m still learning to surf, you know? And that&amp;rsquo;s one of the things that I think makes it so fun, because it&amp;rsquo;s not really &amp;#8212; because I don&amp;rsquo;t do it competitively, I never feel like I&amp;rsquo;ve stopped learning. For me, it can lower my ambition, to go out and surf for a few hours, is so fulfilling and seems almost like an education.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ADI Jorja Fox Addresses Congress</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2011/adi-addresses-congress/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2011/adi-addresses-congress/</guid>
      <description>I do think that a question that some of you may be asking right now is &amp;ldquo;Well what about my kids? Can&amp;rsquo;t my kids have the same chance I did to go to these traveling circuses?&amp;rdquo; Or maybe these circuses your parents went to. And I thought about this at length, and I think the truth is that our kids look to us for what is right, and our kids look to us for what is fun.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Glittarazi</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2011/glittarazi/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2011/glittarazi/</guid>
      <description>Glittarazi: How does it feel to constantly be named one of PETA&amp;rsquo;s sexiest vegetarians?
Jorja Fox: It feels amazing and embarrassing at the same time. I&amp;rsquo;m thrilled that I get on the list, and I don&amp;rsquo;t even know how that happens. It may have to do with the little bit of green that I slip them to put me on it.
Glittarazi: Oh! Okay! I guess my other question is how would you like to expand or take this cause one step further?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Issues with Jane Velez-Mitchell</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2011/issues-with-jane-velez-mitchell-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2011/issues-with-jane-velez-mitchell-2/</guid>
      <description>(BEGIN VIDEO CLIP)
UNIDENTIFIED MALE: How do you train or break an elephant? That word, &amp;ldquo;break&amp;rdquo;.
UNIDENTIFIED FEMALE: Elephants are extremely social and they need the environment, they need movement, they need exercise.
UNIDENTIFIED FEMALE: Abused, 24 hours until the baby totally lost their mind. Many baby died.
Then the baby elephant fear the man. The man can control and the boy make baby elephant obey.
(END VIDEO CLIP)
VELEZ-MITCHELL: We&amp;rsquo;re talking about another kind of crime right now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Artists on Demand Radio</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2011/artists-on-demand-radio/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2011/artists-on-demand-radio/</guid>
      <description>ARTIST ON DEMAND: I&amp;rsquo;m Danni and I&amp;rsquo;ll be your host today. We have another very exciting show this afternoon. We&amp;rsquo;ll be talking to Jorja Fox who plays Sara Sidle on CSI. If you don&amp;rsquo;t know what CSI is, you must have been living under a rock. So. While we are waiting for her to call in, we&amp;rsquo;ll take a music break. So enjoy it. This is going to be Kimberly Cole, &amp;ldquo;Arrow through my Heart&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Talk</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2011/the-talk/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2011/the-talk/</guid>
      <description>Julie Chen: Welcome back to &amp;ldquo;The Talk&amp;rdquo;. Our first guest is best known for her role as Sara Sidle on the hit CBS drama &amp;ldquo;CSI: Crime Scene Investigation&amp;rdquo;. Take a look.
&amp;rdquo;(clip from CSI)&amp;rdquo;
Julie: Please welcome Jorja Fox.
Jorja Fox: (walks in, waves to audience) Oh wow! (hugs hosts, sits down on the couch with Julie Chen, Sharon Osbourne and Sara Gilbert) I am so honored to be here, thanks for having me&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Issues with Jane Velez-Mitchell</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2011/issues-with-jane-velez-mitchell-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2011/issues-with-jane-velez-mitchell-1/</guid>
      <description>(BEGIN VIDEO CLIP)
TIM PHILLIPS, ANIMAL DEFENDERS INTERNATIONAL: These lions have lived their life in a tiny, rusting, disgusting cage on the back of a lorry. Tomorrow they&amp;rsquo;re going to feel the wind blow in their face. They&amp;rsquo;re going to feel grass beneath their feet. They&amp;rsquo;re going to roam into the bushes. They&amp;rsquo;re going to do whatever they want. They&amp;rsquo;re going to be as lions, possibly for the first real time in their lives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pets In The City</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2011/pets-in-the-city/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2011/pets-in-the-city/</guid>
      <description>**Pets In The City: **For many of us, the circus brings back fond memories of lions, tigers, and other large, beautiful creatures performing incredible acts of courage and agility usually with their tamers and trainers on board. But in recent years, the ability of some circuses to properly care for these large beasts has been under scrutiny. This scrutiny has not been limited to the United States. Joining us today is Jorja Fox, who plays the popular character Sara Sidle on the mega hit *CSI *Las Vegas, to talk about her personal work on behalf of some very special and now globe-trotting lions that she and other notable stars have helped move from Bolivia to the U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Transcripts (2011)</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2011/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2011/</guid>
      <description>  Date Source    February 09 Pets In The City   February 23 Issues with Jane Velez-Mitchell   April 21 The Talk   September 21 Artists on Demand Radio   October 06 Issues with Jane Velez-Mitchell   November 02 ADI Jorja Fox Addresses Congress   November 02 Glittarazi   November 16 AP Celebrity Extra   December 07 ET Online    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Insider</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2010/the-insider/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2010/the-insider/</guid>
      <description>Watch Now: Trouble on the &amp;lsquo;CSI&amp;rsquo; Set
George Eads: For the last couple years I was a big fan of the &amp;ldquo;Hoarders&amp;rdquo; documentary program. And so I was telling everybody-
Jorja Fox: I think many of us are. George turned me on to it.
GE: I was telling you the other night!
JF: &amp;ldquo;I was watching this show the other night and you gotta check it out!&amp;rdquo; And I went and checked it out, and now it&amp;rsquo;s on my TiVo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CSI: Season Ten EPK</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2010/csi/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2010/csi/</guid>
      <description>Returning to CSI in Season 10 You can&amp;rsquo;t get rid of me. Everybody- I&amp;rsquo;ve had a couple of dramatic goodbyes here *laughter* like pretty dramatic! And it&amp;rsquo;s like oh, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna be- I&amp;rsquo;m probably going to be the last one standing. &amp;ldquo;Oh her? She&amp;rsquo;s saying goodbye again, whatever. She&amp;rsquo;ll be back in a few weeks.&amp;rdquo;
It is nice. You know, when I left I had cake in my mouth and I was crying.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Issues with Jane Velez-Mitchell</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2010/issues-with-jane-velez-mitchell/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jun 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2010/issues-with-jane-velez-mitchell/</guid>
      <description>JANE VELEZ-MITCHELL: In tonight&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Spotlight&amp;rdquo;, a fabulous mercy mission for four rescued circus lions. These magnificent animals were freed from their pitiful, abusive existence in a Bolivian circus last month. Bolivia recently did what every country should do &amp;#8212; banned the use of animals in circuses. These majestic animals will live out their lives at the amazing Paws Sanctuary in northern California.
Our guest tonight, CSI star, Jorja Fox, who was right there for their dramatic arrival.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ADI Press Update</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2010/adi-press-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 May 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2010/adi-press-update/</guid>
      <description>CSI&amp;rsquo;s Jorja Fox addresses the press on the morning of the release of four ex-circus lions rescued by ADI from Bolivia
Jorja Fox: Good morning everyone. I just wanted to thank you so very, very, very, very much for all being here today. I&amp;rsquo;m sure that, as Pat already said, you&amp;rsquo;re in for something quite extraordinary. Very few people get to see something like this. It&amp;rsquo;s magical. It&amp;rsquo;s special. It&amp;rsquo;s a good day to be a compassionate person.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ADI Rescue Diary</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2010/adi-rescue-diary-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 May 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2010/adi-rescue-diary-2/</guid>
      <description>Jorja Fox: Oh my gosh! Look! Look! We&amp;rsquo;ve heard from Jan and, I guess, close to landing the cats woke up. They started to brush themselves off, and they already checked them when they arrived at the gate. They&amp;rsquo;re doing great, so we may get a look at them tonight.
[&amp;hellip;]
Jorja: Hi, Jan. So how many hours have you been awake?
Jan Creamer: I think about 20 hours. Something like that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ADI Rescue Diary</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2010/adi-rescue-diary-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 May 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2010/adi-rescue-diary-3/</guid>
      <description>Although it has been a very, very, very long week, we have received news that the lions are finally on their way. They were boarded very early this morning in Bolivia, onto the back of a truck, where they headed off to the airport. The guys did really well, Camma was a little nervous but she settled down. When they arrived at the airport, the replacement aircraft had not shown up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ADI Rescue Diary</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2010/adi-rescue-diary/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 May 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2010/adi-rescue-diary/</guid>
      <description>Well! I&amp;rsquo;m here in San Francisco, working with the Animal Defenders International San Francisco team, and we&amp;rsquo;ve been on pins and needles waiting to get the go-ahead from Jan in Bolivia. I&amp;rsquo;ve just gotten off the phone with her, and it looks like all systems are a go. Mel, the vet, has checked the crates and has checked the lions &amp;#8212; everyone&amp;rsquo;s doing well. I think that we&amp;rsquo;re going to start boarding in a few hours.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KPIX - Rescued Lions from Bolivia Arrive at SFO (27 May 2010)</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2010/kpix-rescued-lions-from-bolivia-arrive-at-sfo/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 May 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2010/kpix-rescued-lions-from-bolivia-arrive-at-sfo/</guid>
      <description>Don Knapp And along for the trip tonight was Jorja Fox, of CSI, she&amp;rsquo;s lending her celebrity and her back.
[&amp;hellip;]
Jorja Fox I know I am, I&amp;rsquo;m sure all of us are very concerned about everything that&amp;rsquo;s going on in the gulf. The news is so bad, so devastating, and this is just a very small moment where we can look at ourselves as people and say, &amp;ldquo;You know, we&amp;rsquo;re doing something good.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lions Arrive At San Francisco Airport with &#34;CSI&#39;s&#34; Jorja Fox</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2010/adi-rescue-diary-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 May 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2010/adi-rescue-diary-4/</guid>
      <description>Jorja Fox: Well, here we are. It&amp;rsquo;s May 27th, 2010, at San Francisco International Airport, and we&amp;rsquo;re waiting for some spectacular cargo. Four retiring circus lions, from Bolivia, after fourteen hour flight, along with the head of ADI International, Animal Defenders International, Ms. Jan Creamer, and the vet, Mel, and Lisa, will be touching down, I think, within the hour.
[&amp;hellip;]
Jorja Fox: Lion number one, come on down!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Transcripts (2010)</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2010/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2010/</guid>
      <description>  Date Source    May 27 ADI Rescue Diary   May 27 ADI Rescue Diary   May 27 KPIX - Rescued Lions from Bolivia Arrive at SFO (27 May 2010)   May 27 Lions Arrive At San Francisco Airport with &amp;#34;CSI&amp;#39;s&amp;#34; Jorja Fox   May 28 ADI Press Update   May 28 ADI Rescue Diary   June 11 Issues with Jane Velez-Mitchell   July 01 CSI: Season Ten EPK   October 20 The Insider    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Kevin and Bean Show</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2009/the-kevin-and-bean-show/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2009/the-kevin-and-bean-show/</guid>
      <description>Host: &amp;hellip; It&amp;rsquo;s 9:15.
Host: And what a treat for us. CSI returns tonight at 9 on CBS. Ladies and gentlemen, Jorja Fox right now on the Kevin and Bean show.
Jorja: Aw, thank you!
Host: More importantly, Sara Sidle returns tonight. That&amp;rsquo;s what I care about.
Host 2: Yes! Yes yes yes.!
Jorja: Thank you so much!
Host: What your character has been put through in the course of this series, Jorja-</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Guest DJ Project on KCRW</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2009/guest-dj-project-on-kcrw/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2009/guest-dj-project-on-kcrw/</guid>
      <description>Michael Barnes: Hi, I&amp;rsquo;m Michael Barnes and I&amp;rsquo;m here with actress, Jorja Fox. Jorja has become a familiar face by playing major roles in three of the most successful television dramas in history: &amp;ldquo;ER&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;The West Wing&amp;rdquo; and, most recently, &amp;ldquo;CSI: Crime Scene Investigation&amp;rdquo;. Today we&amp;rsquo;ll be playing excerpts of songs she selected that have inspired her over the years, as part of KCRW&amp;rsquo;s Guest DJ Project.
Jorja Fox: Hi Michael.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NSF, The Humane Society And GQ Magazine Join Forces To Stop Puppy Mills</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2009/nsf/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2009/nsf/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
Reporter: &amp;hellip; tell us about puppy mills?
Jorja Fox: Well, probably a lot of things. I think that puppy mills - it&amp;rsquo;s a very easy issue. You know, if people were more aware, if they knew more, it would be a given issue. Just because we used to put asbestos in our walls, and we used to put lead in our paint, and it was a great idea at the time, doesn&amp;rsquo;t mean it&amp;rsquo;s still a great idea.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Today Show</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2009/the-today-show/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2009/the-today-show/</guid>
      <description>Jorja Fox: It was breathtaking, it was magic. There was so much going on on &amp;ldquo;ER&amp;rdquo; that I certainly had never seen on television before. I don&amp;rsquo;t think you&amp;rsquo;ve seen a lot of it in feature films. The use of steady-cams &amp;hellip; you could do almost an entire act of the show in one sweeping, sort of solid, motion. It was a dance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Transcripts (2009)</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2009/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2009/</guid>
      <description>  Date Source    April 02 The Today Show   September 12 Eyewitness News Video   September 22 NSF, The Humane Society And GQ Magazine Join Forces To Stop Puppy Mills   September 23 Guest DJ Project on KCRW   September 24 The Kevin and Bean Show    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ausiello TV</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2008/ausiello-tv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2008/ausiello-tv/</guid>
      <description>Michael Ausiello: You&amp;rsquo;re back this season
Jorja Fox: Maybe. Maybe I am, maybe I&amp;rsquo;m not.
Ausiello: I&amp;rsquo;ve already seen the first episode, and you were there.
Fox: Yeah, yeah. I&amp;rsquo;m definitely there for that.
Ausiello: And a couple more there.
Fox: Yeah, I&amp;rsquo;m visiting for a little bit. I&amp;rsquo;ll be in and out, so that&amp;rsquo;s kind of fun. I knew that might happen, I didn&amp;rsquo;t know it was gonna happen so soon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Entertainment Weekly 6th Annual Pre-Emmy Party</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2008/ew/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Sep 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2008/ew/</guid>
      <description>*Jorja Fox:** I think it&amp;rsquo;s my second or my third year at this party. I&amp;rsquo;m not the biggest party person. Yeah, no it&amp;rsquo;s super fun, it&amp;rsquo;s been super fun. I&amp;rsquo;ve even had a friend come in from out of town and she&amp;rsquo;s so excited.
Interviewer: Unintelligible
Jorja Fox: I think it&amp;rsquo;s a convergence of a lot of different people who almost never get to see each other. That&amp;rsquo;s number one. And because so many people are coming out tomorrow night anywhere, they&amp;rsquo;re here, they&amp;rsquo;re getting ready, they&amp;rsquo;re excited, they&amp;rsquo;re adrenaline is high.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Access Hollywood</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2008/access-hollywood/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2008/access-hollywood/</guid>
      <description>Interviewer: What are some tips you have to going green?
Jorja Fox: Going green? Oh, wow, I love it. Well, you know, start with the simple stuff. There&amp;rsquo;s some very simple things you can do. Recycling, obviously, I think we&amp;rsquo;re all doing that in California. I&amp;rsquo;m amazed. I go visit some of my family members across the country, and they don&amp;rsquo;t have recycling centers yet. And most of them are doing it themselves anyway.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SpinDaily</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2008/spindaily/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Feb 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2008/spindaily/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
Jorja Fox: You get &amp;ndash; you come into the theater and you&amp;rsquo;re like &amp;ldquo;Ah, I know that one song, it&amp;rsquo;ll be great&amp;rsquo; Never mind what an amazing colorful story she had, in what an amazing colorful times. Then you get in there and you actually know the songs, and you&amp;rsquo;re like &amp;ldquo;Oh wow!&amp;rsquo;
[&amp;hellip;]
Jorja Fox: It&amp;rsquo;s amazing to me that this story hasn&amp;rsquo;t been told before, 500 times already.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KTLA Morning Show</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2008/ktla-morning-show/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jan 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2008/ktla-morning-show/</guid>
      <description>Interviewer: All right, we&amp;rsquo;re gonna talk all about this play and everything Jorja related, but you, you made sort of a conscious decision - you know, you&amp;rsquo;ve been on this very successful show, and then, you left. What, what, what &amp;ndash; was that a real soul search, or was it &amp;ldquo;gee, it&amp;rsquo;s time&amp;rdquo;?
Jorja Fox: Oh, yeah. Yes, yeah, very very much. It was harder to leave than it was to stay, for sure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ian Harvie Show</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2008/ian-harvie-show/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jan 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2008/ian-harvie-show/</guid>
      <description>Jorja Fox: Ten and a half years of deaths -
Ian Harvie: Yes
Jorja Fox: - violence -
Ian Harvie: What is it with you -
Jorja Fox: I just had it of dead bodies -
Ian Harvie: Yeah, seriously!
Jorja Fox: I mean I&amp;rsquo;ve just had it.
Ian Harvie: Seriously, what is it with you and these roles, like these really hard, like, and the dialog is like really hard too!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Transcripts (2008)</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2008/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2008/</guid>
      <description>  Date Source    January 21 Ian Harvie Show   January 31 KTLA Morning Show   February 04 SpinDaily   May 04 Access Hollywood   September 20 Entertainment Weekly 6th Annual Pre-Emmy Party   September 21 Ausiello TV    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The View</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2007/the-view/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Nov 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2007/the-view/</guid>
      <description>Jorja Fox: Thank you, so honored to be here with all of you. &amp;ldquo;(to Whoopi)&amp;rdquo; And happy birthday to you, a day late.
Joy: You&amp;rsquo;ve been here a few times&amp;hellip;
Jorja Fox: This is my fourth round. Second time in the hot seat &amp;ldquo;(pats the table)&amp;rdquo;, and I&amp;rsquo;m just very excited. And awake.
Whoopi: Yeah. Well awake isn&amp;rsquo;t always important. Me, halfway. But let me ask you - you, you&amp;rsquo;re about to make a big change in your life, are you not?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RTL.de - Germany</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2007/rtl-de-germany/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2007/rtl-de-germany/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Why Sara decided to leave&amp;rdquo; Jorja Fox: &amp;hellip;you know, a series of events between the whole miniature killer thing and some other events, she&amp;rsquo;d had so many recent close calls. Um, the job was just too much for her to, it was too much with her, and I think she knew that if she asked Grissom to go with her, even if he said yes, that would be the end of him, you know &amp;ldquo;(very emotional)&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ET</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2007/et/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Oct 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2007/et/</guid>
      <description>Announcer: And sad news for &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; fans as a star says goodbye.
Jorja Fox: That&amp;rsquo;s the end of me for a while
Announcer: At the Frederick&amp;rsquo;s of Hollywood Fashion show last night Jorja Fox told &amp;ldquo;ET&amp;rdquo; the real reason she&amp;rsquo;s leaving CBS&amp;rsquo;s crime solving show
Jorja Fox: I just need to take a little break, and do some evaluating. Hopefully I will return.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ET Online</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2007/et-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Oct 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2007/et-2/</guid>
      <description>Jorja Fox: How fun is this, right? And what a tease for me!
Jann Carl: I know!
Fox: Such a tease! They tell &amp;ndash; I&amp;rsquo;m under the understanding that when I&amp;rsquo;m done today, they&amp;rsquo;re gonna let me take a little spin around the track.
[&amp;hellip;]
Carl: You&amp;rsquo;re back?
Fox: I made it! I made it. I survived. I know.
Carl: And you don&amp;rsquo;t look any worse off for it.
Fox: Well thank you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RTL.de - Germany</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2007/rtl-de-germany-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Sep 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2007/rtl-de-germany-2/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Jorja Fox &amp;ldquo;Sara Sidle&amp;rdquo; - Why Season 7 is so great&amp;rdquo; Jorja Fox: What separates season 7 from all the other seasons in &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; is for a very long time, we&amp;rsquo;re very content that our stories sort of had a beginning, a middle and an end within themselves, so if you watch a show from season 3 or season 1 or season 5 you kinda could watch them and they didn&amp;rsquo;t have to be in a particular order, you know.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VegTV (25 August 2007)</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2007/vegtv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Aug 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2007/vegtv/</guid>
      <description>Announcer: VegTV on the road with Marie Oser.
Marie Oser: I&amp;rsquo;m here with Jorja Fox from &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo;, a long time vegetarian, vegan. I asked you once what was your epiphany; it was a meatball sub in Brooklyn. And that was great!
Jorja Fox: &amp;ldquo;*laughing*&amp;rdquo; I told that story a couple of days ago to a friend! &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; &amp;rsquo;s out here in force tonight, there&amp;rsquo;s actually a little posse of us. There&amp;rsquo;s a couple vegetarians that I work with and a couple of vegans.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CSI season 7 DVD extras</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2007/csi-season-7-dvd-extras/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jul 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2007/csi-season-7-dvd-extras/</guid>
      <description>Jorja Fox &amp;ldquo;(on Billy Petersen leaving the show for four weeks in November of 2006)&amp;rdquo; I wasn&amp;rsquo;t disappointed at all, I think, you know, obviously as I met Billy he had come almost directly out of this excitement of theater he was doing in Chicago and he&amp;rsquo;s very famous for that theater that he&amp;rsquo;s done. I think that it&amp;rsquo;s been the heart of his work over the time of his career, he&amp;rsquo;s done some films that are ground-breaking and memorable and everybody, those, that&amp;rsquo;s probably the way that the most people know Billy Petersen, but I think that people who know Billy Petersen &amp;ldquo;know&amp;rdquo; that his heart and his soul has always been in the theater, so, and it&amp;rsquo;s almost as if in a sense odd that it took him six years to find his way into one, you know, and I think that it&amp;rsquo;s a testament to the show, how much &amp;ldquo;CSI:&amp;rdquo; has all this passion that he hasn&amp;rsquo;t felt like he could go do a play at the same time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wowow TV - Japan</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2007/wowow-tv-japan/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jun 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2007/wowow-tv-japan/</guid>
      <description>Question - about Sara Sidle(?) Jorja Fox: Uh, yes, well I think that Marg and I feel very very lucky to play the women we get to play on TV, you know. The character I get to play is &amp;ldquo;so&amp;rdquo; much smarter than I am, number one, &amp;ldquo;(laughs)&amp;rdquo; which is really fun, you never get tired of doing that, and they&amp;rsquo;re just, you know they&amp;rsquo;re strong women, and they&amp;rsquo;re professional, they&amp;rsquo;re completely intellectual and at the same time they feel very real, they feel like real people to me, they don&amp;rsquo;t feel, feels like a person that somebody could actually be.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CBS 2 Chicago Evening News (23 May 2007)</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2007/cbs-2-chicago-evening-news/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 May 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2007/cbs-2-chicago-evening-news/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
I know more about maggots that I really ever thought I would ever know. And I love them now! You know, the first four seasons it was a little creepy and they kind of scared me. And now I just enjoy their company when they&amp;rsquo;re on set.
[&amp;hellip;]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Early Show</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2007/the-early-show-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 May 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2007/the-early-show-2/</guid>
      <description>Jorja Fox: I&amp;rsquo;m not a big fan of Sara being in, in peril. I think that when you play a character as long as I have, what, it&amp;rsquo;s going on 36 years? No, 7 years, you become very, very, very, very, very close to that character in ways that, uh, are difficult to describe. So intrinsically as an artist, y&amp;rsquo;know, my desire is to protect that character and keep that character safe.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Early Show</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2007/the-early-show/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 May 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2007/the-early-show/</guid>
      <description>Chen&amp;rsquo;s &amp;lsquo;CSI&amp;rsquo; Investigation
Julie Chen gets an exclusive behind-the-scenes look at the hit crime drama &amp;ldquo;CSI.&amp;rdquo; She speaks with actors Marg Helgenberger, William Petersen, Paul Guilfoyle and Jorja Fox.
Julie Chen: This season, CSI has given us everything from Grissom and Sara big romance to the so-called &amp;lsquo;Miniature killer&amp;rsquo; who left scale model miniature of crime scenes. Cast members told me those models were as fascinating for them as they were for viewers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SpinDaily</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2007/spindaily/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2007/spindaily/</guid>
      <description>Katherine: Hi, I&amp;rsquo;m Katherine from SpinDaily.
Jorja Fox: Hi, I&amp;rsquo;m Jorja Fox from &amp;ldquo;CSI:&amp;ldquo;, and the only crime here is that we don&amp;rsquo;t have bicycles.
[&amp;hellip;]
Jorja Fox: I am looking for a recreational, kind of weekend bike. I surf, I would love to get a bicycle that I could put a rack on the side, and I could take my bike to the beach.
Katherine: Wait, can you put a surfboard, carry a surfboard on a bike?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Transcripts (2007)</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2007/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2007/</guid>
      <description>Date Source    March 16 SpinDaily   May 10 The Early Show   May 18 The Early Show   May 23 CBS 2 Chicago Evening News (23 May 2007)   June 29 Wowow TV - Japan   July 01 CSI season 7 DVD extras   August 25 VegTV (25 August 2007)   September 01 RTL.de - Germany   October 04 ET Online   October 25 ET   November 01 RTL.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PETA Vegetarian Thanksgiving</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2006/peta-vegetarian-thanksgiving/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2006/peta-vegetarian-thanksgiving/</guid>
      <description>Jorja Fox One of the most amazing things about today, not only is the food gonna be way better than it ever is at my place &amp;ldquo;(laughs)&amp;rdquo;, and, and, and, far more beautifully prepared, uh, I don&amp;rsquo;t have to cook or do any dishes I don&amp;rsquo;t think - maybe I do, but nobody&amp;rsquo;s told me yet so that&amp;rsquo;d be really fun. &amp;ldquo;(laughs)&amp;rdquo;
[&amp;hellip;]
Jorja Fox What a better way to spend this holiday that we really sorta celebrate peace and in a really peaceful way eating vegetarian.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Go Vegan with Bob Linden</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2006/go-vegan-with-bob-linden/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Sep 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2006/go-vegan-with-bob-linden/</guid>
      <description>Bob Linden: &amp;hellip;author of &amp;ldquo;When Elephants Weep&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;The Pig Who Sang to the Moon&amp;rdquo;, and &amp;ldquo;Dogs Never Lie About Love&amp;rdquo;. Um, now, uh, oh, I guess we have - is it, Jorja Fox is calling now? Okay, Jorja Fox is on the line, Chris DeRose I hope can hold on a little longer now, but Jorja Fox, I know, is in the midst of shooting right now, &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo;, and uh, taking a break.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Radio Times</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2006/radio-times/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2006/radio-times/</guid>
      <description>One Final Question - Jorja Fox
What&amp;rsquo;s it like to be upstaged by strange fibers and fluids?
*CSI: Crime Scene Investigation* is the top-rated drama in the US, but there are two spin-offs now. Does it annoy you that CSI: Miami and now CSI: NY are sponging off your ratings?
Well, they say it&amp;rsquo;s a great form of flattery, right? I think in the beginning we were all quite afraid. Our show in the States had barely got on its legs and already we were going to have competition from the inside.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Early Show</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2006/the-early-show-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2006/the-early-show-2/</guid>
      <description>Julie Chen: &amp;hellip; were wondering if there was more going on between Grissom and Sara than meets the eye. Well last night we found out, and the answer is definitely yes. Now we have even more questions, and so do the CSI stars. Last night&amp;rsquo;s episode was almost over when we heard Gil Grissom ruminating about the end of his own life.
William Petersen: And it&amp;rsquo;s a little scene, but it&amp;rsquo;s just a coda to the end of the season.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BBC 5</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2006/bbc-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2006/bbc-5/</guid>
      <description>Simon Mayo has a talk show called &amp;ldquo;*star studded&amp;rdquo; on the BBC radio 5 for news, sport and in-depth interviews. On May 18th, he talked with Jorja Fox about ER, The West Wing, CSI and Dear Bernard.
Simon Mayo: Jorja Fox has sidled in stage left. How are you doing?
Jorja Fox: I&amp;rsquo;m doing great Simon thank you so much for having me.
Simon Mayo: Well thank you for coming on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Early Show</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2006/the-early-show-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2006/the-early-show-1/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;] :Jorja Fox: It&amp;rsquo;s almost like we have these alter egos, y&amp;rsquo;know, and uh, and that started back in season one and now that it&amp;rsquo;s been six years, I totally do, I have hopes for her, and dreams for her, and I get upset for her- :Julie Chen: You&amp;rsquo;re more showier than her.  :Jorja Fox: -yeah, yeah, no it&amp;rsquo;s confusing sometimes. And ah, certain times of the year I&amp;rsquo;ll buy a piece of wardrobe and I&amp;rsquo;ll look at it in the summer and I&amp;rsquo;ll be like &amp;lsquo;Who bought that?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Early Show</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2006/the-early-show-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2006/the-early-show-3/</guid>
      <description>Julie Chen: What does it tell us about your character, the vision, the re-creation you had? What was that like?
Jorja Fox: It was a lot &amp;hellip; &amp;ldquo;(laughing uproariously)&amp;rdquo; It&amp;rsquo;s my character. &amp;ldquo;(laughter)&amp;rdquo; There was no acting involved for me on that episode. Ah, Sara&amp;rsquo;s a little intimacy-gun-shy, a little committment-phobic.
Jorja Fox: &amp;ldquo;(voiceover)&amp;rdquo; It&amp;rsquo;s one of my favorite episodes we&amp;rsquo;ve ever done. It&amp;rsquo;s also a complete direction change for us.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ET Online</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2006/et-online/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2006/et-online/</guid>
      <description>Go behind the scenes of the &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; wedding murder!
Voiceover by Jorja Fox:
We open the story with a beautiful wedding with 200. Beautiful grounds, it&amp;rsquo;s just a perfect day. The sun is shining. The bride and groom are driving away in their beautiful vintage car. Everything is glorious. And then we find out that the groom&amp;rsquo;s mother is tied to the back of the convertible. Things go sorta downhill from there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CTV eTalkDaily</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2006/ctv-etalkdaily/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Apr 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2006/ctv-etalkdaily/</guid>
      <description>Jorja Fox: The thing that surprises me is how much people just wanna be dead bodies on the show.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Genesis Awards</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2006/genesis-awards/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2006/genesis-awards/</guid>
      <description>Jorja was interviewed at the 20th anniversary Genesis Awards. This is a partial transcript.
Jorja Fox: Uh, yeah, this is my second time at the Genesis Awards, and I&amp;rsquo;m really excited to be invited back. They tend to spread the love around, so I think it&amp;rsquo;s, it&amp;rsquo;s a little special to be back a second time. Uh, I&amp;rsquo;m lucky enough tonight I&amp;rsquo;m going to be presenting a Genesis Award for &amp;lsquo;Dramatic Television Show&amp;rsquo; that &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; is winning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Transcripts (2006)</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2006/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2006/</guid>
      <description>  Date Source    March 18 Genesis Awards   April 13 CTV eTalkDaily   April 27 ET Online   April 28 The Early Show   May 11 The Early Show   May 18 BBC 5   May 19 The Early Show   June 06 Radio Times   September 03 Go Vegan with Bob Linden   November 01 PETA Vegetarian Thanksgiving    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Early Show</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2005/the-early-show-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2005/the-early-show-2/</guid>
      <description>Julie Chen: After six seasons and a pair of spin-offs, &amp;ldquo;CSI:&amp;rdquo; remains a true original. It&amp;rsquo;s still a ratings powerhouse too with nearly 30 million viewers tuning in every week. I sat down with some of the show&amp;rsquo;s stars inside the CSI autopsy room to dissect the secret of their success.
[&amp;hellip;]
Julie Chen: &amp;ldquo;(voiceover)&amp;rdquo; In tonight&amp;rsquo;s episode, the sexual tension also continues between Sara and Grissom.
Julie Chen: In season six you still kinda have a crush on Grissom, right?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Early Show</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2005/the-early-show/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2005/the-early-show/</guid>
      <description>Julie Chen: If you can&amp;rsquo;t get enough of TV&amp;rsquo;s hottest drama, CSI:, then you&amp;rsquo;re in luck. Every Friday, we&amp;rsquo;re going to take you behind the scenes to show you how they make it happen. In last night&amp;rsquo;s episode, called &amp;ldquo;Secrets and Flies&amp;rdquo;, star Jorja Fox came face to face with an actor&amp;rsquo;s big challenge: working with a baby. Or did she?
Jorja Fox: The camera comes in, you find a woman who&amp;rsquo;s obviously deceased, you don&amp;rsquo;t know what&amp;rsquo;s happened, there&amp;rsquo;s a pool of blood, and the only other sound in the house is of a baby crying.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Matters of the Heart</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2005/matters-of-the-heart/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2005/matters-of-the-heart/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s kind of a funny thing about our show, &amp;lsquo;cause I say that the audience is almost split down the middle, where about 50% of the audience really just wants to, they want the stories. They don&amp;rsquo;t wanna get into the characters personal lives all that much. And then the whole other 50% of the audience wants always to know more about the characters. It&amp;rsquo;s a unique conundrum for the writers, and I think they handle it very gracefully and &amp;hellip; they&amp;rsquo;re always disappointing someone and they&amp;rsquo;re always making someone happy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PETA Gala and Humanitarian Awards</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2005/peta-gala-and-humanitarian-awards/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Sep 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2005/peta-gala-and-humanitarian-awards/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
Jorja Fox I&amp;rsquo;ve been a vegetarian since I was nineteen. I come from like a French-Canadian family who ate meat and potatoes every day, three times a day for my entire youth, and I used to tease the heck out of my friends that were vegetarians, and I had a lot of &amp;lsquo;em, and then when I became a vegetarian I just decided that I was going to try and learn as much I could so that when people teased me, maybe I&amp;rsquo;d have a couple of things to say.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CSI Season 5 DVD extras</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2005/csi-season-5-dvd-extras/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2005/csi-season-5-dvd-extras/</guid>
      <description>Jorja Fox All bets are off, and on at the same time. Anything can happen to anybody, there&amp;rsquo;s lines that have been drawn, and uh, it does make it really fascinating.
[&amp;hellip;]
Jorja Fox It, we&amp;rsquo;re split almost down the middle, 50 percent of the people who watch &amp;ldquo;CSI:&amp;rdquo; want more character stuff, and 50 percent of the people who watch the show don&amp;rsquo;t want that much of it, they really like the stories and the science.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Land&#39;s Top Ten Sexiest Men</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2005/tv-land-s-top-ten-sexiest-men/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2005/tv-land-s-top-ten-sexiest-men/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;TV Land&amp;rsquo;s Top Ten&amp;rdquo; is a show about the top ten .
Jorja Fox was on the June 15, 2005 episode for &amp;lsquo;Sexiest Men&amp;rsquo;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My First Place: Celebrity Style</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2005/my-first-place-celebrity-style/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2005/my-first-place-celebrity-style/</guid>
      <description>HGTV, in a interesting move, released excerpts from it&amp;rsquo;s new show &amp;ldquo;&amp;lsquo;My First Place: Celebrity Style&amp;rdquo;&amp;rsquo; online.
Jorja Fox was filmed for an upcoming episode and her quote on the main page is as follows:
 I was a bad teenager. I had to get out of there. My family was very old-fashioned and I knew quite young that I needed to get my own place. I was 16. I moved in with my friends.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Transcripts (2005)</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2005/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2005/</guid>
      <description>  Date Source    January 01 My First Place: Celebrity Style   May 15 TV Land&amp;#39;s Top Ten Sexiest Men   July 01 CSI Season 5 DVD extras   September 10 PETA Gala and Humanitarian Awards   October 10 Matters of the Heart   November 04 The Early Show   November 17 The Early Show    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Huckleberry Fund Benefit</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2004/huckleberry-fund-benefit/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Dec 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2004/huckleberry-fund-benefit/</guid>
      <description>&amp;rdquo;&amp;lsquo;Jorja Fox:&amp;ldquo;&amp;rsquo; Um, the Huckleberry Fund is an amazing organization, they help a lot of teenagers in the Los Angeles area. It&amp;rsquo;s a very, uh, it&amp;rsquo;s a group that gets overlooked a lot and obviously a group with a lot of special needs, very specific needs, um, taking care of medical as well as psychological, developmental stuff. Um, I&amp;rsquo;m lucky enough to have a photograph inside, it&amp;rsquo;s one of my favorite things to get to do, it&amp;rsquo;s my second time doing it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Extra TV</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2004/extra-tv/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2004/extra-tv/</guid>
      <description>Interviewer: Let&amp;rsquo;s use the microphone. Now, what do you think keeps those thirty million people coming back each week?
Jorja Fox: Um. I think it&amp;rsquo;s just way, way, way too many TV stations, and we&amp;rsquo;re on number two, so when you turn on the television, it&amp;rsquo;s fist number that comes up. It&amp;rsquo;s much simpler than surfing
Interviewer: I think there&amp;rsquo;s a little bit more to do than that.
Jorja Fox: Uh, I just- we&amp;rsquo;ve been so blessed, so lucky and I hope we keep doing it for a long time and don&amp;rsquo;t take any single day for granted.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E! - Emmy Red Carpet</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2004/emmy-red-carpet/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Sep 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2004/emmy-red-carpet/</guid>
      <description>Star Jones: In the mean time my girl is here.
Jorja Fox: Hey. (hug)
Star Jones: Hey Jorja, nice to see you.
Jorja Fox: How are you?
Star Jones: So we are looking at one of the stars of one of the number one shows [[CSI]] &amp;hellip;they&amp;rsquo;re still watchin&amp;rsquo; Jorja.
Jorja Fox: Ahh, thank you.
Star Jones: You&amp;rsquo;ve got to show yourself off here Jorja, because everybody&amp;rsquo;s looking for you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Ellen Degeneres Show</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2004/the-ellen-degeneres-show/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 May 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2004/the-ellen-degeneres-show/</guid>
      <description>Ellen DeGeneres Our next guest is a star of the popular forensic drama, CSI. Watch her at work.
[&amp;hellip;]
Ellen Please welcome, Jorja Fox!
[&amp;hellip;]
Ellen Hi!
Jorja Fox: Hi! I brought you something.
Ellen Merci.
Jorja Oh, great.
Ellen Merci beaucoup.
Jorja That&amp;rsquo;s all I know.
Ellen What does that mean, what is this?
Jorja Well I know you&amp;rsquo;ve been studying a little French on the show, and so I thought these might help; they&amp;rsquo;re French art deco cosmetic labels.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The View</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2004/the-view/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2004/the-view/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The View&amp;rdquo; is a daytime television talk show on ABC which was created by Barbara Walters and premiered on August 11, 1997, to showcases women&amp;rsquo;s points of view on a variety of issues.
Star Jones: Please welcome Jorja Fox and George Eads!
Star: We&amp;rsquo;re out here in the sunshine&amp;hellip; you guys are used to being in Vegas because CSI is shot-
Jorja Fox: Not, not during daylight hours though. laughs, raises her hand to shade her eyes from the sun</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pulse</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2004/pulse/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2004/pulse/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Pulse&amp;rdquo; is a talk show.
Jorja appeared on the 15th episode, on 13 February 2004.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Transcripts (2004)</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2004/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2004/</guid>
      <description>  Date Source    February 13 Pulse   February 19 The View   May 18 The Ellen Degeneres Show   September 19 E! - Emmy Red Carpet   November 11 Extra TV   December 05 Huckleberry Fund Benefit    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>93.7 The Buzz</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2003/93.7-the-buzz/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2003/93.7-the-buzz/</guid>
      <description>93.7 BZZ is a top-40 station with all of today&amp;rsquo;s new music.
Bubba: Has it hit you yet that you&amp;rsquo;re on, like, the number one television show in the world?
Jorja Fox: No, absolutely not. I don&amp;rsquo;t know if it&amp;rsquo;ll ever really hit me. I don&amp;rsquo;t really know, I mean it&amp;rsquo;s kind of like fantastically overwhelming to think of.
Bubba: And it&amp;rsquo;s not like you&amp;rsquo;re a bit player in the show, that you like are taking credit for the whole show, you&amp;rsquo;re actually are the show.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Living TV</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2003/living-tv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2003/living-tv/</guid>
      <description>Living TV is &amp;ldquo;Women orientated entertainment&amp;rdquo; and is available on Sky, Telewest and NTL.
Marc: Looking quite glamorous is Jorja from CSI.
Jorja: Thank you very much.
Marc: Chewing gum on the red carpet.
Jorja: Well it&amp;rsquo;s better than a cigar right?
Marc: Ok, you heard it here first, this is a fashion statement, gum chewing, as they say. No let&amp;rsquo;s face it. CSI, the runaway hit, everyone&amp;rsquo;s talking about it, you guys have gotta be feeling pretty good about yourselves.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Love the &#39;70s</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2003/i-love-the-70s/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2003/i-love-the-70s/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;I Love the 70s&amp;rdquo; is a television mini-series shown on VH1, and was created after the success of &amp;ldquo;I Love the &amp;lsquo;80s&amp;rdquo;.
##Appearances##
Jorja appeared in 5 episodes of the miniseries:
 1970 - Original Airdate 08.18.2003
 1973 - Original Airdate 08.19.2003
 1974 - Original Airdate 08.20.2003
 1976 - Original Airdate 08.21.2003
 1977 - Original Airdate 08.21.2003  ##See Also##
VH1 - I Love the &amp;lsquo;70s</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CSI Season 3 DVD extras</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2003/csi_season_3_dvd_extras_2003/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2003/csi_season_3_dvd_extras_2003/</guid>
      <description>Crash and Burn Jorja Fox You know, Sara Sidle had a very dark year in season 3; she had a tough one, she really had a tough one. It really started, uh, I would say, in January, about midway through the season. Ah, the first thing that happens is, is, a very good friend of hers betrays her very personally. And the next time we see Sara, her boyfriend, it turns out, has a girlfriend and he also betrays her.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Guide Channel Insider</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2008/tv_guide_channel_insider_2003/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2008/tv_guide_channel_insider_2003/</guid>
      <description>Jorja Fox Wow, um. Thank you. I&amp;rsquo;m hearing that, people have been saying that. And that&amp;rsquo;s amazing, I think- You know, the other reason that I thought the show was going to flop was because it was about science. And I thought that was going to be a very hard thing to make to look fascinating and interesting and exciting to people. I thought it was very fascinating, like reading the script I had a tremendous amount of faith in the show and I just had no idea how we would pull it off.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The View</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2003/the-view/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2003/the-view/</guid>
      <description>The New York Times had run a story saying that Jorja would be appearing on the show &amp;ldquo;The Bachelorette&amp;rdquo; - she joked about in on &amp;ldquo;The View&amp;rdquo;.
Meredith: Welcome to &amp;ldquo;The View&amp;rdquo;, live from L.A. &amp;ldquo;CSI:&amp;rdquo; star Jorja Fox is our celebrity co-host today. Welcome to you, you look great.
Jorja Fox: Thank you so much. I feel like I&amp;rsquo;m in New York City right now, being with you guys, which is so nice for me, cause I&amp;rsquo;m from there-</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Early Show</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2003/the-early-show/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2003/the-early-show/</guid>
      <description>This particular article was about the music of &amp;ldquo;CSI:&amp;ldquo;; in the beginning was an interview with series creator Anthony Zuiker, discussing how music is chosen for various segments.
(brief clip of Jorja and Gary Dourdan jamming on the set with the crew, something they do on a regular basis. Jorja plays guitar while Gary plays bass)
 Julie Chen: But the music isn&amp;rsquo;t just fun, it&amp;rsquo;s theraputic, an escape from the disturbing drama.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Transcripts (2003)</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2003/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2003/</guid>
      <description>  Date Source    January 09 The Early Show   February 20 The View   April 22 TV Guide Channel Insider   July 01 CSI Season 3 DVD extras   August 18 I Love the &amp;#39;70s   September 21 Living TV   September 25 93.7 The Buzz    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CSI season 2 DVD extras</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2002/csi-season-2-dvd-extras/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2002/csi-season-2-dvd-extras/</guid>
      <description>Jorja Fox &amp;ldquo;(shot of the characters viewing a &amp;lsquo;corpse&amp;rsquo;; Jorja walks away holding her stomach)&amp;rdquo; Uh. It&amp;rsquo;s too early. &amp;ldquo;(to &amp;lsquo;corpse&amp;rsquo;)&amp;rdquo; I mean, I&amp;rsquo;m sure you&amp;rsquo;re a really nice guy&amp;hellip;
[&amp;hellip;]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Late Late Show</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2002/the-late-late-show/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2002/the-late-late-show/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Late Late Show with Craig Kilborn&amp;rdquo; was a TV Talk show/variety show, hosted by Craig Kilborn.
Transcript Jorja Fox Can I, can I just say something?
Craig Kilborn You may say something.
Jorja Fox Something that I&amp;rsquo;ve always wanted to say, perhaps on national television. Ding dong, you son of a bitch. Ding dong.
Craig Kilborn That was good, right?
Jorja Fox It was great!
Craig Kilborn That&amp;rsquo;s exciting, seeing Buddy Hackett.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ri:se</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2002/ri-se/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2002/ri-se/</guid>
      <description>Jorja Fox (Sara Sidle), Paul Guilfoyle (Jim Brass) and Robert David Hall (Dr. Al &amp;lsquo;David&amp;rsquo; Robbins) were on Ri:se, Channel 4(UK) to promote the season 1 DVD. There was a clip of Season 1 stuff with a voice over and lots of Gary Dourdan (Warrick Brown) clips. Then they showed an interview of Jorja in one hotel room Paul and Robert in another, interspersed with clips form various episodes. There was mention of CSI&amp;rsquo;s ratings success in the US and also for the UK&amp;rsquo;s Channel 5, and a way too enthusiastic commentary from the presenters about the TMI cam for a breakfast show.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Larry King Weekend</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2002/larry-king-weekend/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2002/larry-king-weekend/</guid>
      <description>LARRY KING, HOST: Tonight, unsolved mysteries, Jon Bonet Ramsey, Chandra Levy &amp;#8212; in the news. No wonder one of TV&amp;rsquo;s top drama&amp;rsquo;s is &amp;ldquo;CSI Crime Scene Investigation&amp;rdquo;. This phenomenal series is about following evidence and closing cases. Glory details, high tech twists, it got them all.
&amp;rdquo;(VIDEO CLIP)&amp;rdquo;
KING: But, how realistic are the corpses and the clues?
Joining us from LA, stars from the gripping show, killing the competition, and from Detroit, world renowned forensic expert Dr.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Early Show</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2002/the-early-show/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2002/the-early-show/</guid>
      <description>Bryant Gumbel: Although it now may seem hard to believe, it was just two years ago the hit drama &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; barely made it on to the primetime schedule. The show has since become a hit with an unusual look at forensic investigators who solve crimes with science.
[&amp;hellip;]
Bryant Gumbel The stars of &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; are William Petersen, Marg Helgenberger, Gary Dourdan, Jorja Fox and Paul Guilfoyle. Good morning, everybody.
(EVERYONE): Good morning, Bryant.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Channel 5 UK</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2002/channel-5-uk/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2002/channel-5-uk/</guid>
      <description>The character Sara is ten gazillion times more courageous than I am. You know, we do things sometimes and me, Jorja, in between takes is like &amp;lsquo;I&amp;rsquo;m not doing this, I can&amp;rsquo;t do this. Let&amp;rsquo;s make sure, we need to be careful, where&amp;rsquo;s the medic?&amp;rdquo; And then the camera&amp;rsquo;s start rolling and Sara Sidle kinda just goes in and does it. We did a helicopter scene. This year George Eads and I had a scene where we were rappelling out of a helicopter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Women Of ... Primetime Crime</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2002/women-of/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2002/women-of/</guid>
      <description>Intro Jorja Fox I never knew that I wasn&amp;rsquo;t equal to everyone else out there.
&amp;ldquo;Who was your favorite female crime fighter?&amp;rdquo;
Jorja Fox There were the pioneers out there, you know, like Angie Dickinson [&amp;hellip;] I grew up on Charlie&amp;rsquo;s Angels. Those women seemed, they were just incredible. They were so fierce. You know? &amp;lsquo;Cause they were doing karate chops and solving crimes and had the guns and yet they were still young and smart.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Golden Globes Red Carpet</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2002/golden-globes-red-carpet/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jan 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2002/golden-globes-red-carpet/</guid>
      <description>Melissa Rivers Thank you. I am here with the cast of CSI. Your show has taken off, like, y&amp;rsquo;know. A train, just steaming right out of the station.
Jorja Fox We&amp;rsquo;re dazed. We&amp;rsquo;re dazed and confused and so happy and yeah! It&amp;rsquo;s great.
Melissa Rivers I see Marg has gotten a lot of attention for the show for the last, what? For last season.
Jorja Fox Yeah.
Melissa Rivers But now the whole show is being acknowledged tonight.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Transcripts (2002)</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2002/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2002/</guid>
      <description>  Date Source    January 20 Golden Globes Red Carpet   March 08 Women Of ... Primetime Crime   April 19 Channel 5 UK   May 15 The Early Show   May 18 Larry King Weekend   May 29 Ri:se   June 26 The Late Late Show   July 01 CSI season 2 DVD extras    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Late Late Show</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2001/the-late-late-show/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jun 2001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2001/the-late-late-show/</guid>
      <description>The Late Late Show with Craig Kilborn is a TV Talk show/variety show, hosted by Craig Kilborn. Jorja Fox was the second guest, and introduced as a &amp;ldquo;beautiful actress &amp;hellip; helming the hit TV series CSI&amp;rdquo;.
Craig Kilborn: Welcome back, our next guest is a beautiful actress who has helped make CBS series &amp;ldquo;CSI.&amp;rdquo; the highest rated new drama on television. Please welcome Jorja Fox. &amp;ldquo;(cheers and applause)&amp;rdquo;
Jorja: I&amp;rsquo;m doing great.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Early Show</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2001/the-early-show/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2001/the-early-show/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Early Show&amp;rdquo; is a CBS morning show. On Thursday, April 26th, they aired a &amp;#8216;behind the scenes&amp;rsquo; sequence on CSI. Gary Dourdan, George Eads and Jorja Fox gave tours.
CSI is filmed in Santa Clarita, California, and Jorja Fox showed off Grissom&amp;rsquo;s Office, where they keep bugs, and other fun toys.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yahoo Chat</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2001/yahoo-chat/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Apr 2001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2001/yahoo-chat/</guid>
      <description>This chat log was cut short by technical difficulties (dialup connection crashed). Despite promises to provide the full log, Yahoo! never did.
&amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; star Jorja Fox It&amp;rsquo;s got to be a fabulous Spring for actress Jorja Fox. She&amp;rsquo;s in the coolest TV show of the season &amp;#8212; CSI: Crime Scene Investigation &amp;#8212; and one of the most talked about movies of the year &amp;#8212; Memento. But you know, the last few years couldn&amp;rsquo;t have sucked&amp;hellip; In the 99-00 season, she portrayed Secret Service Special Agent Gina Toscano on The West Wing, protecting President Bartlet&amp;rsquo;s youngest daughter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hollywood At Large</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2001/hollywood-at-large/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2001/hollywood-at-large/</guid>
      <description>In 2001, Court TV had a new show, Hollywood at Large, in which they look into various TV shows and how they portray the criminal justice system. CSI was featured in the pilot, on Feb 23, 2001.
Jorja Fox had a brief interview on the show (the CSI scene lasted for about five minutes). In her interview she stated that she has liked forensic TV shows (like &amp;lsquo;The New Detectives&amp;rsquo;) since before she started working on CSI, and that she still gets grossed out the easiest.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Inside Media at The Paley Center</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2001/inside-media-at-the-paley-center/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2001/inside-media-at-the-paley-center/</guid>
      <description>Actor/executive producer William Petersen (Gil Grissom) and executive producer Carol Mendelsohn point out the reasons they brought Jorja Fox (Sara Sidle) onto the show.
Why Jorja Fox? William Petersen: It was very interesting. Here was this young girl who was basically a rookie. And she comes out and we basically ignore her through out the night because we were too busy doing our stuff. And to have her get shot at the end of a pilot was somewhat profound.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Memento Premiere</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2001/memento-premiere/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2001/memento-premiere/</guid>
      <description>Jorja Fox was interviewed at the premiere of &amp;ldquo;Memento&amp;rdquo;
Interviewer: I saw the movie and it was fabulous-
Jorja Fox: Thank you.
Interviewer: -um, and it looked real scary to lay in that bag.
Jorja Fox: It was really scary, actually, &amp;ldquo;(laughs)&amp;rdquo; and, and the tile was very very cold, and there was water being spritzed on me occasionally, so I had a very&amp;hellip; I think I uh, I think I dozed off for a little while.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Transcripts (2001)</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2001/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2001/</guid>
      <description>  Date Source    January 01 Inside Media at The Paley Center   January 01 Memento Premiere   February 23 Hollywood At Large   April 24 The Test   April 24 Yahoo Chat   April 26 The Early Show   June 25 The Late Late Show   July 01 CSI Season 1 DVD extras   July 28 Animal Planet Radio    </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>