<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Filmography on Fans of Le Fox Library</title>
    <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/categories/filmography/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Filmography on Fans of Le Fox Library</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 16 Aug 2009 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://jorjafox.net/library/categories/filmography/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Drop Dead Diva</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/actor/drop-dead-diva/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Aug 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/actor/drop-dead-diva/</guid>
      <description>The series revolves around vapid aspiring model, Deborah &amp;ldquo;Deb&amp;rdquo; Dobkins, who is killed in a car crash on the way to an audition for The Price Is Right. As her soul enters the gates of Heaven, she finds herself being judged by a gatekeeper named Fred. As a result of her shallowness, Fred declares her a &amp;ldquo;zero-zero,&amp;rdquo; since she has performed zero good deeds and zero bad deeds during her time on Earth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3 Weeks to Daytona</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/actor/3-weeks-to-daytona/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/actor/3-weeks-to-daytona/</guid>
      <description>Recap Chuck Weber is a race car driver who is down on his luck and nothing has gone right in twenty years, which happens to be the last time he won a race. Divorced, struggling to pay for his car and the alimony for his son, Willy (aka Worm), the only bright spot in his life is racing at the Speedbowl, a lock stock-car track run by Sal.
After crashing into the wall and losing his sponsorship, Chuck fears his dreams are at an end when Sal loses his sponsorship from Rob&amp;rsquo;s furniture.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alchemy</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/actor/alchemy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/actor/alchemy/</guid>
      <description>This distinctly feminist drama chronicles three phases in the life of a young woman. The three phases are presented as distinct, titled vignettes, &amp;ldquo;Charity,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;Hope,&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Faith,&amp;rdquo; centered upon Louisa Garrison, a woman who translates folk tales. She is first seen working in a bookstore. Though involved with Ethan, she decides to break up with him because she strongly suspects that he is still in love with Kitty, his ex-girl friend.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CSI: Crime Scene Investigation</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/actor/csi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/actor/csi/</guid>
      <description>Premise The show follows the cases of the Crime Scene Investigation division of the Clark County (Nevada) Sheriff&amp;rsquo;s Department, usually referred to by officers as the &amp;ldquo;Las Vegas Crime Lab.&amp;rdquo; The division solves crimes almost entirely through the means of forensics evidence, which may or may not come to the conclusion of a murder or accidental death. Keeping in theme with the setting, investigations often lead to taboo subjects, such as sexual deviations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Courthouse</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/actor/courthouse/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/actor/courthouse/</guid>
      <description>Jorja Fox&amp;rsquo;s appearance in this is unverified. If you have information than can confirm, please contact us, and be sure to cite your source.
Character Jorja Fox played &amp;ldquo;Maureen Dawes&amp;rdquo; in the pilot episode.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dead Drunk: The Kevin Tunell Story</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/actor/dead-drunk/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/actor/dead-drunk/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Dead Drunk: The Kevin Tunell Story&amp;rdquo; was first aired on HBO in 1993. It is a compelling and cautionary tale of the choices and consequences of drinking and driving. On New Years Eve, 1981, Kevin Tunell went to a party to celebrate the coming new year and drank with his friends. He took his girlfriend home and although impaired, told her &amp;ldquo;nothing ever happens to me when I drink.&amp;rdquo; That might have been true, but that night Kevin&amp;rsquo;s life would change forever.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dead Funny</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/actor/dead-funny/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/actor/dead-funny/</guid>
      <description>Reggie has been skewered to the kitchen table with a Samurai sword, and Viv&amp;rsquo;s trying to remember what happened. After all, it was one hell of a party last night. Instead of calling the police, Louise, Viv&amp;rsquo;s best friend, takes charge, attempting to solve Reggie&amp;rsquo;s murder with the help of a list of suspects and a couple of bottles of champagne. Deep in memories of her last year with Reggie and continuously interrupted by a strange cast of characters, Viv wanders through her apartment in a daze.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dear Bernard</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/producer/dear-bernard/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/producer/dear-bernard/</guid>
      <description>Overview New York City - 1973. The city is awash in excess, playing host to the hottest parties and people of the moment. &amp;ldquo;Dear Bernard&amp;rdquo; tells the timeless tale of a small town English girl seeking fame and glamour in in America - with a twist.
Chelsea Mills - our exuberant English import - arrives in New York and is quickly discovered by the Liberace of fashion photographers, who propels her to the top of the &amp;ldquo;body part model&amp;rdquo; biz.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dodges City</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/actor/dodges-city/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/actor/dodges-city/</guid>
      <description>Jorja Fox&amp;rsquo;s appearance in this is unverified. If you have information than can confirm, please contact us, and be sure to cite your source.
Produced by Paramount, Eric Szmanda (who played Greg Sanders on CSI) starred as Johnny Dodge, a fearless, thrill seeking private investigator with a taste for fast cars and faster women.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Down With The Joneses</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/actor/down-with-the-joneses/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/actor/down-with-the-joneses/</guid>
      <description>While it is listed at IMDb as having been completed in 2003, this movie has no release information and there is no record of anyone having see the completed film.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ER</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/actor/er/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/actor/er/</guid>
      <description>Character Dr. Maggie Doyle arrived from a hospital that had been closed. A wonderful dichotomy, Doyle was a gun-toting, lesbian vegetarian. She was good friends with John Carter, and had enough attitude for everyone.
Doyle slogged through a fairly nasty piece of litigation, when surgeon Dr. Robert &amp;lsquo;Rocket&amp;rsquo; Romano blasted her on her evaluation when she threatened to tell about his harassment of her. While Doyle filed the report, the plot fell by the wayside, and Romano became the Chief of Emergency Medicine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ellen</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/actor/ellen/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/actor/ellen/</guid>
      <description>Episode: &amp;ldquo;The Puppy Episode (2)&amp;rdquo;  Aired 30 April 1997 Season 4, Episode 23  Ellen senses a kindred spirit when she meets a gay woman, who enlightens her to her own sexual identity. Confused by this startling self-discovery, Ellen seeks the guidance of a therapist and braces herself for yet another moment of truth-telling her friends about this personal revelation.
Character On the now infamous &amp;lsquo;Coming Out&amp;rsquo; episode of Ellen, Jorja Fox played the uncredited, unnamed, lesbian in the coffee house who walks up to Ellen, sits down next to her, smiles, and proceeds to hit on Ellen&amp;rsquo;s best friend (and good looking friend), Paige.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ellen: The Ellen Degeneres Show</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/self/ellen/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/self/ellen/</guid>
      <description> The Ellen DeGeneres Show, premiered September 08, 2003, and is a television talk show hosted by Ellen DeGeneres. The show features interviews with celebrities and comedic monologues by the host.
Jorja&amp;rsquo;s Apperances  18 May 2004  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Extinction Soup</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/producer/extinction-soup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/producer/extinction-soup/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Extinction Soup&amp;rdquo; follows documentary filmmaker Philip Waller on his quest for adventure as he sets out to tell the story of his larger-than-life friend and extreme sports legend, Jimmy Hall. The film quickly takes a surprise turn when Waller finds himself consumed with exposing to the world an environmental catastrophe in the making - the extinction of the oceans&amp;rsquo; shark population through the mass slaughter of these magnificent animals for their fins.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Food for the Heart</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/actor/food-for-the-heart/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/actor/food-for-the-heart/</guid>
      <description>Jorja Fox plays Delmar Youngblood; a divorcee with an abundant love of cooking and family raising a young son in a small town in anywhere, USA. Her cherished dream is to open a restaurant, The Hungry Bachelors Club, but this reality is deterred by her uninteresting and low-paying job as an insurance adjuster.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Forever Fabulous</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/actor/forever-fabulous/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/actor/forever-fabulous/</guid>
      <description>Loreli Daly (Jean Smart), beauty pageant organizer and Former Miss Texas Gal 1969, was run out of Paris, Texas ten years ago on the heels of a tabloid sex scandal. Living somewhere in Arizona with her long-term boyfriend and washed-up pageant MC, Lyle (Robert Wagner), and her daughter Corinne (Jennifer Elise Cox), holder of over 200 pageant titles and tiaras, Loreli is invited back, to Paris, to host the Miss Texas Tiara Quest &amp;ndash; but she can&amp;rsquo;t face the shame.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gidget: The Accidental Icon</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/actor/gidget/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/actor/gidget/</guid>
      <description>Narrated by Jorja Fox and produced by Brian L. Gillogly and Robert Masters, ACCIDENTAL ICON explores the largely untold story of the real “Gidget,” Kathy Kohner Zuckerman. Kathy’s account of surfing Malibu in the mid-50’s became the basis for a best-selling novel by her father Frederick Kohner and the hit 1959 “Gidget” movie, which introduced the modern sport of surfing to a world-wide audience. Surf legends and present-day “surfer girls” set the stage and take the Gidget story full circle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happy Hell Night</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/actor/happy-hell-night/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/actor/happy-hell-night/</guid>
      <description>25 years ago at Winfield College, psycho-priest Zachary Malius murdered seven frat boys and was put away in the local asylum. Now, however, the same fraternity stages a prank from which Malius is inadvertently set free and returns to the house to repeat his crime&amp;hellip;
As a prank for Rush Week, a couple of frat boys go to an insane asylum to take some pictures of an inmate there who supposedly killed a group of frat guys from their fathers&amp;rsquo; generation at the same college.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Honeypot Productions</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/honeypot/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/honeypot/</guid>
      <description>Honeypot Productions (also known as HoneyPot Productions) is an independent theater company in Los Angeles.
Jorja Fox and many of her friends are the founders, and through the company they write, produce and star in many of their own works. According to what she said a TV Guide interview, HoneyPot was formed in either 1998 or 1999; she met fellow Honeypot members Katherine Kendall and Suzanne Mara during the filming of Food for the Heart in 1998.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>House of Frankenstein 1997</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/actor/house-frankenstein/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/actor/house-frankenstein/</guid>
      <description>Distinctly mutilated bodies are being dropped all over Los Angeles like so much arcane propaganda. No one, however, knows how to read the message. The police are secretly baffled while the press has made the only stab at profiling the killer, calling the perpetrator The Midnight Raptor. Grace Dawkins is the Raptor&amp;rsquo;s latest victim, and the only one to have survived an attack, but she&amp;rsquo;s little help to the investigation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How I Became an Elephant</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/producer/how-became-elephant/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/producer/how-became-elephant/</guid>
      <description>How I Became An Elephant is more than just a film. It&amp;rsquo;s one girl&amp;rsquo;s story&amp;hellip; which led to a movement, which led to a continuing plan, to save a species.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Make the Cruelest Month</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/actor/how-make-crueslest-month/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/actor/how-make-crueslest-month/</guid>
      <description>Kip Koenig wrote and directed this comedy, set in a small college town, about neurotic Bell Bryant (Clea DuVall) who explains her problems directly to the camera: her older sister Sarah (Jorja Fox) has a happy marriage plus a baby on the way. Her other sister, beautiful Dot (Amy Smart), is involved in an affair with Bell&amp;rsquo;s ex, Leonard (Gabriel Mann). In a remote location, Bell makes love to Leonard and then departs, abandoning the nude Leonard who makes his way to the house of a married couple (Dennis Haysbert, Marianne Jean-Baptiste).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Love the &#39;70s</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/self/i-love-the-70s/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/self/i-love-the-70s/</guid>
      <description>I Love the 70s takes viewers on another fun-filled ride through the music, movies, TV shows, products, fashions, fads, trends and major events that defined pop culture each year of the decade. From Star Wars to Charlie&amp;rsquo;s Angels, leisure suits to underoos, mutton-chop sideburns to the Mod Squad&amp;hellip; we once again tap our collective memories to cover the sublime, the ridiculous, and everything in between.
Comics, rock stars, actors, writers and other celebs past and present weigh in on the 70s experience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>In Hell With Love</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/writer/in-hell-love/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/writer/in-hell-love/</guid>
      <description>Written by Jorja Fox, In Hell With Love is about nurses in Vietnam.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Law &amp; Order</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/actor/law-order/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/actor/law-order/</guid>
      <description>Episode: &amp;ldquo;Securitate&amp;rdquo;  Aired 5 May 1993 Season 3, Episode 20  When a Romanian immigrant kills, his lawyer announces he will plead his client &amp;ldquo;not guilty due to cultural insanity&amp;rdquo; claiming the man had been conditioned to violence in his homeland.
Character Paula Engren and a friend are on their way to a club when they&amp;rsquo;re witness to a man being dragged behind a car. They call the cops, but remember no useful information.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lion Ark</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/producer/lion-ark/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/producer/lion-ark/</guid>
      <description>More action adventure than traditional documentary, Lion Ark follows the world’s most ambitious and daring animal rescue, with a narrative compiled from film, interviews, conversations and reactions as events unfolded. How attitudes to animals were changed in Bolivia, illegal circuses pursued and closed, and 25 lions airlifted to freedom.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Loving Stanley</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/writer/loving-stanley/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/writer/loving-stanley/</guid>
      <description>Written by Jorja Fox, Loving Stanley is comedy about the Women&amp;rsquo;s Pro Bowling circuit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Memento</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/actor/memento/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/actor/memento/</guid>
      <description>Memento is a movie starring Guy Pearce (&amp;lsquo;The Adventures of Priscilla, Queen of the Desert&amp;rsquo; and &amp;lsquo;L.A. Confidential&amp;rsquo;) and Carrie Anne-Moss (&amp;lsquo;The Matrix&amp;rsquo; and &amp;lsquo;Red Planet&amp;rsquo;). Jorja Fox plays Catherine Shelby, the wife of Leonard Shelby (Pearce), who was raped and murdered in the couple&amp;rsquo;s home.
Recap Around 2:00 AM (Nov. 1997) police were called to the home of Leonard and Catherine Shelby, after two neighbors reported hearing gunshots. The front door was open, and they found the Shelbys in serious condition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Missing Persons</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/actor/missing-persons/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/actor/missing-persons/</guid>
      <description>The show aired from August 1993 through February 1994 on ABC at 8 p.m., apart from the feature-length pilot episode, which was broadcast as the Monday Night Movie from 9 p.m.-11 p.m. ET.
Episodes usually began with some sort of humorous exchange between the team as they all crowded round the coffee machine, eating doughnuts. Ray would then come out from his office and hand out the cases for the day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Next Exit</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/actor/next-exit/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/actor/next-exit/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Charles wants to become an actor and Jason wants to go only as far as Bakersfield, where he hopes to reunite with his estranged father. Upon arrival in Bakersfield, Charles gets sidetracked when he falls in love with Tracy Morris, a local teen, who is dating Jon Burroughs, a twenty something, small time drug dealer.
Jason finds his father, but the reunion is cut short when he realizes that his dad has moved on with a new family of his own and is not interested in making up for lost time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nineteen</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/actor/nineteen/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/actor/nineteen/</guid>
      <description>Nineteen filmed a pilot episode, produced by CBS, and was an angst ridden comedy about a couple getting married at 19. Noah Lee Margetts played Michael Spattavechia to Jorja Fox&amp;rsquo;s Ruth Manicotti, with Meredith Scott Lynn playing Ruth&amp;rsquo;s best friend.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Partners</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/actor/partners/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/actor/partners/</guid>
      <description>Jorja Fox&amp;rsquo;s appearance in this is unverified. If you have information than can confirm, please contact us, and be sure to cite your source.
Jorja Fox played &amp;ldquo;Alex&amp;rdquo; in episode 3 &amp;ldquo;My Sister, My Enemy&amp;rdquo;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seafox Productions</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/seafox/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/seafox/</guid>
      <description> Seafox Productions is an independent film, television and theater company based in Los Angeles, California. It is owned by Sea Turtle Inc.
Currently, Seafox Productions focuses on documentary and biographical projects that highlight the critical inter-connectedness between humans and the natural world.
Staff  Jorja Fox - President Jonathan Grant - Chief Operating Officer  Projects  Extinction Soup Lion Ark How I Became An Elephant Stay Forever: The Life and Music of Dusty Springfield  See Also  Seafox Productions  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Skin Trade</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/self/skin-trade/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/self/skin-trade/</guid>
      <description>Originally titled Pets on Your Plate, Skin Trade is a documentary.
Synopsis All of the dead animals in California &amp;ndash; including out pets &amp;ndash; along with their diseases, chemicals and drugs, toxins and bacteria, are cooked in a stew pot and rendered into protein meal and fat, and then fed to animals in the human food chain.
Review  The documentary film “Skin Trade”, an exposé of the fur industry, recently premiered in Los Angeles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stay Forever: The Life and Music of Dusty Springfield</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/producer/stay-forever/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/producer/stay-forever/</guid>
      <description>Originally shown at the L.A. Gay &amp;amp; Lesbian Center’s Lily Tomlin/Jane Wagner Cultural Arts Center, Jorja Fox produced this with Bunnyhop Productions in 2008.
In 2012, the show was revived off-Broadway.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Summer Stories: The Mall</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/actor/the-mall/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/actor/the-mall/</guid>
      <description>Experience summer at the mall with Sarah, Spinner, Marla, Diane (Jorja Fox), Teresa, Kwan, and their friends.
Episodes  Aired Summer 1993  As these brand-new high school graduates prepare to head in new directions, poised between the past and the future, they learn a few of each other&amp;rsquo;s secrets&amp;hellip;and a lot more about themselves. Some of the stories in the first program, First Impressions, continue in the second program, Second Chances, as well as in the third program, Temptations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Jerky Boys</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/actor/jerky-boys/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/actor/jerky-boys/</guid>
      <description>When a former high school classmate brags about his mob connections, the Jerky Boys &amp;ndash; a pair of thirty-something slackers who pride themselves on devious prank phone calls &amp;ndash; decide to have a little fun in the Mafia underworld. However, when a cop mistakes the Jerky Boys for actual hit men, their innocent game causes more trouble than they would&amp;rsquo;ve ever imagined.
Character Jorja Fox plays Lazarro&amp;rsquo;s Young Lady. Lazarro works for the Mafia, and his Young Lady is basically a hired call girl.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Kill-Off</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/actor/kill-off/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/actor/kill-off/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis In a small coastal community in New Jersey, the only action in town is a run-down nightclub called Pavillion. The club&amp;rsquo;s owner, Pete (Jackson Sims), can barely make the payroll for Rags the bartender (William Russell), Myra the barmaid (Jorjan Fox) (who is also Pete&amp;rsquo;s daughter), and clean-up man Ralph (Steve Monroe). In a bid to bring in more customers, Pete hires a stripper, Danny Lee (Cathy Haase). Danny Lee&amp;rsquo;s act soon turns Ralph&amp;rsquo;s head, which is not good news for his wife Luanne (Loretta Gross).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The True Story</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/actor/true-story/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/actor/true-story/</guid>
      <description>The True Story was to be produced by Tom Fontana and shown on UPN for the 1999&amp;frasl;2000 season. However for reasons unknown, it was reworked into a show named The Beat became about young, male, cops, one of whom was the son of a man who&amp;rsquo;d killed his wife 25 years ago. The Beat aired only 6 episodes and was marked as being one of the more foul-mouthed shows on the air.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The West Wing</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/actor/west-wing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/actor/west-wing/</guid>
      <description>Character Jorja Fox played Gina Toscano, the Secret Service agent assigned to protect the President&amp;rsquo;s youngest daughter, Zoey.
Special Agent Gina Toscano was a Secret Service agent assigned to protect the President&amp;rsquo;s daughter (Zoey), while Zoey was in college.
Gina attended University of Virginia (studying Criminology), and was in the Army ROTC (2nd Lt. in MP). She was the first agent to sign up for the detail or protecting Zoey and trained for 18 months before earning the assignment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unity</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/self/unity/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/self/unity/</guid>
      <description>Despite the advent of science, literature, technology, philosophy, religion, and so on &amp;ndash; none of these has assuaged humankind from killing one another, the animals, and nature. UNITY is a film about why we can&amp;rsquo;t seem to get along, even after thousands and thousands of years.
Jorja is one of the movie&amp;rsquo;s narrators.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Velocity Trap</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/actor/velocity-trap/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/actor/velocity-trap/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s high noon in deep space. It&amp;rsquo;s the year 2150, and electronic crime and interstellar piracy rule the galaxy. Facing unlawful murder charges, Police officer Raymond Stokes is reassigned to escort the Federal Banking Ship USF Atlantic and $40,000,000,000 through the Bermuda Triangle of space: The Velocity Run. With only Beth Sheffield, the ship&amp;rsquo;s navigator, to assist him, all his strength is put to the test when everything on board is threatened by an oncoming 600 million ton asteroid, and a well-armed team of thieves that have docked alongside the USF Atlantic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Your Mommy Kills Animals</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/self/mommy-kills-animals/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/self/mommy-kills-animals/</guid>
      <description>Your Mommy Kills Animals is a documentary.
An in-depth look at the animal rights movement and the FBI&amp;rsquo;s recent declaration calling them the number one domestic terrorist threat to the United States.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>