<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>1992 on JFO Library</title>
    <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/tags/1992/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 1992 on JFO Library</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Mar 1992 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://jorjafox.net/library/tags/1992/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>The Baltimore Sun</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/1992/baltimore-sun/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 1992 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/1992/baltimore-sun/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;During an earlier era on television, teens hung out at the malt shop or the burger joint. But today their meeting place is the mall &amp;#8212; and many of them work there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What better place to set an earnest new miniseries aimed at teen viewers?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Summer Stories: The Mall,&amp;rdquo; a three-part edition of the &amp;ldquo;ABC Afterschool Special,&amp;rdquo; premieres at 4 p.m. today (on Channel 13), with additional segments scheduled for the same time April 2 and 16 . The network calls it the first miniseries designed for this viewing period.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Like the Nanuet Mall of Rockland County, N.Y., where it was primarily filmed, &amp;ldquo;Summer Stories&amp;rdquo; has a scrubbed feeling, a vague artificiality. It falls somewhat short of conveying the grittiness of teen reality, particularly in language.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But bearing in mind its target audience, the miniseries does address some of the challenges facing young people today.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The third principal story involves Diane (Jorjan Fox), a former drug abuser struggling to stay clean while being pressured by a former drug-dealing boyfriend to resume their relationship.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The New York Times</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/1992/new-york-times/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 1992 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/1992/new-york-times/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In subsequent stories, Marla Clayton (Samaria Graham) will have to come to terms with her widowed mother&amp;rsquo;s pending remarriage, and Diane Dravecki (Jorjan Fox) will battle against slipping back into crack addiction.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beneath the usual television gloss there&amp;rsquo;s a new grittiness, evident even in the casting, which clearly has tried to avoid stereotypically pretty new faces. Some of the actors, especially the intriguingly offbeat Ms. Fox, impressively convey the value of pure talent.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Entertainment Weekly</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/1992/entertainment-weekly/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 1992 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/1992/entertainment-weekly/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Here&amp;rsquo;s something different and ambitious from ABC&amp;rsquo;s Afterschool Specials series: its first miniseries. For the next three weeks, &lt;strong&gt;Summer Stories: The Mall&lt;/strong&gt; will dole out tales of teens laboring in a suburban mall. (The Mall was filmed at the Nanuet Mall in Rockland County, N.Y.)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are also Marla (Samaria Graham) and Diane (Jorjan Fox), waitresses in one of the mall&amp;rsquo;s fast-food restaurants. Marla is perpetually cranky because her mom is remarrying without having consulted her, and because she has recently been passed over for a promotion to assistant manager. Diane is a recovering alcoholic and former drug addict whose will is being tested by the sudden reappearance of her old boyfriend (Todd Graff), who used to provide her with drugs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>News Articles (1992)</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/1992/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 1992 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/1992/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>