<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>1998 on JFO Library</title>
    <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/tags/1998/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 1998 on JFO Library</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 Feb 1998 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://jorjafox.net/library/tags/1998/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Variety</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/1998/variety/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 1998 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/1998/variety/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A Fugue State/Magnet Prods. presentation. Produced by Alison Dickey, Mark Lipson. Executive producer, James R. Hedges. Co-producer, Caitlin Abramoritz.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Directed, written by Kip Koenig. Camera (color), Julian Whatley; editor, Chris Figler; music, Jeff Martin; production design, Jodi Ginnever; set decoration, Melissa K. Frankel; costume design, Agnes NaDene Baddoo, Dalhia Schuette; sound (Dolby), Larry Blake; associate producers, Scott Kennedy, Luis Barajas, Alberto Gieco; assistant director, Marie O&amp;rsquo;Keefe; casting, Joseph Middleton. Reviewed at Sundance Film Festival (competing), Jan. 19, 1998. Running time: 99 MIN.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bell Bryant Clea DuVall&lt;br /&gt;
Leonard Crane Gabriel Mann&lt;br /&gt;
Uncle Jerry John David Souther&lt;br /&gt;
Mary Bryant Mary Kay Place&lt;br /&gt;
Christina Parks Marianne Jean-Baptiste&lt;br /&gt;
Manhattan Parks Dennis Haysbert&lt;br /&gt;
Fryer Crane John Voskamp&lt;br /&gt;
Dot Bryant Amy Smart&lt;br /&gt;
Westy James Duvall&lt;br /&gt;
Sarah Bryant Jorja Fox&lt;br /&gt;
Dr. Rutledge Christopher Gartin&lt;br /&gt;
Rickey Frederick Weller&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Though brimming with fresh ideas, zany humor and offbeat characters, the aptly titled comedy &amp;ldquo;How to Make the Cruelest Month&amp;rdquo; also displays the sheer audacity, messy structure and lack of discipline that often characterize first features. As writer and director, Kip Koenig exhibits a remarkable sensitivity to the raw energy and sexual and moral confusion of American youngsters today. Drastic cuts, particularly in the midsection, should improve theatrical prospects for a picture that&amp;rsquo;s vastly uneven but holds appeal for the twentysomething crowd, which is likely to connect emotionally with the vibrant ensemble onscreen.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pic recalls, in spirit and ambition, if not in execution, the early comedies of Woody Allen and, more recently, David O. Russell&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Flirting With Disaster.&amp;rdquo; In sharp contrast to the anomie and alienation that mark the youth movies of Gregg Araki and Richard Linklater, Koenig seems more forgiving and tolerant of the various anxieties that beset American youth of the 1990s.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Almost a female version of the young Woody Allen screen character, protagonist is Bell (Clea DuVall), a bright, neurotic, fast-talking, sexually confused woman. Like Allen&amp;rsquo;s protagonists, Bell periodically steps out of her role and addresses the camera directly, sharing with the audience her innermost feelings.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the first, rather deftly scripted monologue, Bell confides the impossibility of realizing New Year&amp;rsquo;s resolutions. Two goals high on her list are to quit smoking and to fall in love. Since the first resolution proves taxing, Bell channels all her energy into achieving the second one - against all odds.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It doesn&amp;rsquo;t help that she&amp;rsquo;s the least attractive and most problematic of three sisters. Sarah (Jorja Fox), the eldest, is happily married and about to give birth, whereas Dot (Amy Smart), a graceful blonde, is clearly the family&amp;rsquo;s beauty. To complicate matters, Dot has an affair with Bell&amp;rsquo;s ex, Leonard (Gabriel Mann), which increases Bell&amp;rsquo;s insecurities. In an early sequence, Bell takes Leonard to a remote place, begins making love to him in the car and then runs away, leaving the naked man stranded and bewildered.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finding his way back home, Leonard stumbles into the house of a married couple, Manhattan (Dennis Haysbert) and Christina (&amp;ldquo;Secrets &amp;amp; Lies&amp;rsquo; &amp;ldquo;Marianne Jean-Baptiste). In what are the film&amp;rsquo;s weakest scenes, Manhattan engages in endless monologues about fishing, while his unsatisfied wife acts upon her attraction to Leonard, who&amp;rsquo;s the type of handsome, vulnerable guy women find particularly appealing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the story progresses, it seems, as Bell says, &amp;ldquo;that I&amp;rsquo;m smoking more and falling in love less.&amp;rdquo; Out of desperation and confusion, she even entertains the idea that she might be a lesbian and goes on a date with a woman. Hysterically rushing from one encounter to another, Bell also deals with her eccentric Uncle Jerry (John David Souther), who&amp;rsquo;s also her teacher, and her laid-back room (Mary Kay Place).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Though the yarn is set in a small college town and the action is confined to a few buildings, &amp;ldquo;How to Make&amp;rdquo; assumes the logic of a zany road movie, populated by a large gallery of eccentric characters. Problem is, Koenig tries to do too much, throwing more balls in the air than he can possibly juggle. Result is a comedy that&amp;rsquo;s ultimately more exhausting than entertaining. Its happy ending is too cutesy and fake.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are not many quiet moments in the movie, but there are too many dull, static episodes that don&amp;rsquo;t pay off. As a comedy director, Koenig needs to learn how to modulate the pacing of the vignettes that form his episodic narrative. Too many scenes are off-key, with a tempo that either drifts lazily or rushes frantically.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the lead role, DuVall is well cast as the tomboyish, neurotic Bell, though her performance is occasionally too intensely mannered. The large ensemble is, for the most part, exuberant and enticing, with standout work from Place, Souther and Mann.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Regrettably, two of the cast&amp;rsquo;s most graceful pros, Jean-Baptiste and Haysbert, are burdened with stiff roles that highlight the weaknesses of the picture.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BTinternet</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/1998/btinternet/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 1998 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/1998/btinternet/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Written for the screen &amp;amp; directed by Maggie Greenwald.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Starring Loretta Gross, Jackson Sims, Cathy Haase, Steve Monroe, Andrew Lee Barrett and Jorjan Fox.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cinematography by Declan Quinn.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Grim but Worthy &amp;#8212; Low-Life Study&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Maggie Greenwald&amp;rsquo;s dark, low-budget adaptation of &lt;em&gt;The Kill-Off&lt;/em&gt; is considered one of the finest translations of a Jim Thompson novel from page to screen. Completed in 1989 the movie documents the sleazy lowlife of an East Coast nowheresville and its inhabitants who share a common hatred of monstrous bed-ridden gossip Luane (played by Loretta Gross) who terrorizes the town with her tales and accusations. ER semi-regular Jorja Fox features as the naive junkie daughter of the local bar-owner who has half-hopes of escaping to a better existence. Claustrophobic and very slow-paced, The Kill Off makes for grim but worthy viewing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It received a limited cinema release in New York City and was screened at the Sundance Festival. Reviews have been overwhelmingly favourable but the film remains largely unknown to most people. It was screened by Channel Four in the UK on May 13 1997. &lt;em&gt;The Kill-Off&lt;/em&gt; marks Irish-American cinematographer Declan Quinn&amp;rsquo;s first feature.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Several novels from hack pulp-meister Jim Thompson have now been made into films including * The Grifters*, *After Dark My Sweet, The Getaway *(twice!) and the French productions &lt;em&gt;Coup de Torchon&lt;/em&gt; , based on Pop.1280 and * Serie Noire*, adapted from A Hell of A Woman. Despite the additional dialogue credit, Thompson wrote the screenplay for Kubrick&amp;rsquo;s * The Killing *and had some kind of hand in adapting &lt;em&gt;Paths of Glory&lt;/em&gt; for the same director. Increasingly frustrated and shunned by Hollywood he later wrote scripts for TV sitcoms as his career hit the skids amid chronic alcoholism and illness. He died in 1977 before his books enjoyed a publishing renaissance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Reviews&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;The locations are appropriately weathered and run-down and the photography relentlessly grim. The cast, mainly composed of New York stage actors, captures the hopeless meanness of the characters with exceptional conviction, and the score is hauntingly sleazy.&amp;rdquo; -* Movie Guide*&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;For her second feature Greenwald almost gets it perfect&amp;hellip;she revels in the laconic dialogue, vicious motivations and downbeat mood beloved by Thompson fans&amp;hellip;As a thriller however, the movie is short of real suspense: comparison with &lt;em&gt;Blood Simple&lt;/em&gt; highlights Greenwald&amp;rsquo;s slow pace.&amp;rdquo; - &lt;em&gt;Time Out&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;One of the best adaptations of the work of pulp novelist Jim Thompson this is a film whose low budget works in its favour, evoking the oppressively fatalistic atmosphere at which Thompson excelled. A must-see for fans of film noir.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Source:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Kill-Off&lt;/em&gt; was out of print for several years but Vintage Crime published a new edition in 1998. The film version has significant differences from the novel but of course its always worth checking out the original source material.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Corgi edition 1988&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Checkout</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/1998/checkout/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 1998 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/1998/checkout/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Kip Koenig wrote and directed this comedy, set in a small college town, about neurotic Bell Bryant (Clea DuVall) who explains her problems directly to the camera: her older sister Sarah (Jorja Fox) has a happy marriage plus a baby on the way. Her other sister, beautiful Dot (Amy Smart), is involved in an affair with Bell&amp;rsquo;s ex, Leonard (Gabriel Mann). In a remote location, Bell makes love to Leonard and then departs, abandoning the nude Leonard who makes his way to the house of a married couple (Dennis Haysbert, Marianne Jean-Baptiste). Wondering if she&amp;rsquo;s a lesbian, the confused Bell dates a woman and then dashes around from one place to another, dropping in on her mom (Mary Kay Place), her uncle, John David Souther), and various eccentrics. Shown at the 1998 Sundance Film Festival.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#8212; Bhob Stewart, All Movie Guide&lt;br /&gt;
:Six stars (out of ten)&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>News Articles (1998)</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/1998/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 1998 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/1998/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>