<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Jorja Fox on Fans of Le Fox Library</title>
    <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/categories/jorja-fox/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Jorja Fox on Fans of Le Fox Library</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://jorjafox.net/library/categories/jorja-fox/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Musical Interests</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/music/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/music/</guid>
      <description>Jorja has always been interested in music, from attending events to performing. She often attends concerts, especially if her friends are performing, and has been to the Grammy&amp;rsquo;s once. She has also written and performed several songs for the cast and crew of CSI, which she sang at the &amp;lsquo;wrap&amp;rsquo; parties in 2003 and 2004.
A Dreamer&amp;rsquo;s Holiday Written by Kim Gannon and Mabel Wayne, the song was performed by Jorja Fox and Patti Welch in Food for the Heart.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Search Results</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/search/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/search/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to the Fans of Le Fox Library</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/</guid>
      <description>The goal of the Fans of Le Fox Library is to provide a comprehensive resource for information about the career and life of the actress, producer, humanitarian, activist and environmentalist that is Jorja Fox.
 Biographies - Various biographies Filmography - Her work as an actor, producer, and writer Advocacy - The good she does for the world Transcripts - Interviews, press releases, and online chats News Articles - News where she is mentioned Episode Recaps - Recaps of TV episodes in which she&amp;rsquo;s appeared  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>