<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>2015 on Fans of Le Fox Library</title>
    <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/tags/2015/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 2015 on Fans of Le Fox Library</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 30 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://jorjafox.net/library/tags/2015/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>World SCREEN</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2015/worldscreen/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2015/worldscreen/</guid>
      <description>[Translated from Chinese (Traditional) by Google]
Immortal classic album in the history of American crime series &amp;ldquo;CSI Crime Scene&amp;rdquo; (CSI: Crime Scene Investigation), to declare the whole fifteenth season after watching the film aired, and in particular to accompany fans through fifteen years of &amp;ldquo;CSI Crime Scene &amp;ldquo;Shooting finale - a two-hour special edition television movie&amp;rdquo; CSI: final return &amp;ldquo;(THE FINAL: CSI) draw a perfect ending ◦ AXN will be December 31, 2015 (iv) from 21:00 Release&amp;rdquo; AXN Taiwan Movies fifteen years crazy day special program &amp;ldquo;, in addition to Taiwan premiere of&amp;rdquo; CSI: final return &amp;ldquo;can relive William Petersen (William Petersen) and Lawrence Fishburne (Laurence Fishburne) in ninth season Even in the first hand to solve the case of great shots, and watch exclusive interviews behind closed producer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A.V. Club</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2015/avclub/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2015/avclub/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
AVC: So were you happy to come back in order for Gil and Sara to literally sail off into the sunset?
WP: Well, yeah, that was kind of… [Hesitates.] I mean, what are you going to do after all these years and everything, and you’re supposed to do a wrap-up in two hours? If they’d said, “Why don’t you do a wrap-up over several episodes?” we’d’ve done something different. But they sort of just sprang it on us after they canceled the show.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Extra at the EMA Awards Green Carpet</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2015/ema-awards/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Oct 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2015/ema-awards/</guid>
      <description>Renee Bargh: &amp;hellip; Ah but first up we&amp;rsquo;ve got Jorja Fox from CSI. Hi, how are you?
Jorja Fox: You look amazing.
Renee: You love wonderful.
Jorja: Thank you.
Renee: You look great. So tell me, why is it so important to be at this event?
Jorja: I think it&amp;rsquo;s one of the most important events that you could attend in Los Angeles. Bringing attention to environmental awareness, which is at such a critical, frightening stage right now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Insider</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2015/tvinsider/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Oct 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2015/tvinsider/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
In Praise of CSI&amp;rsquo;s Happy Ending Question: Several years ago, I wrote to you regarding my extreme disappointment in CSI for divorcing Grissom and Sara, the series&amp;rsquo; &amp;ldquo;long ship&amp;rdquo; known as GSR. Well, you were the voice of reason, saying that you hoped William Petersen would be back for the end. Thankfully, you were right. Although I still think they should not have been separated, the end of the finale was oh so satisfying.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lylapalooza </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2015/lylapalooza/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2015/lylapalooza/</guid>
      <description>CSI star Jorja Fox takes time out to chat with Lyla about dogs, insects, and ice cream. Special guest appearance by Belle the puppy.
Lyla: This is Lylapalooza and we have Jorja Fox on our show today. Hello, Jorja, how are you today?
Jorja: I am very good, Lyla, how are you doing?
Lyla: Good. This is my shnuffler. Shnuffle. Do you have anything to say?
&amp;ldquo;Belle the Puppy:** *silence*</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shark Allies</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2015/shark-allies/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2015/shark-allies/</guid>
      <description>Jorja Fox talks about her personal connection to the ocean and her perception of trophy hunting and the misrepresentation of sharks in the media.
Our Connection to the Ocean
I spend as much time on the water as I can. I&amp;rsquo;ve been bodyboarding since I was about six and surfing for about the last fifteen years. So I&amp;rsquo;m there, you know, several times a week if I can be.
A long time ago, when you think of how mankind kind of evolved on earth, it was this battle</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Channel Guide Magazine</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2015/channel-guide-magazine/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2015/channel-guide-magazine/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
At some point in the episode, another woman blows herself up, this time, it&amp;rsquo;s a Lady Heather doppleganger outside of the mistresses&amp;rsquo; house. When the lookalike&amp;rsquo;s car explodes, Brass catches on fire, but once he&amp;rsquo;s extinguished by a fast-acting Sara, he stands there like a total bad-ass, proving once again that the former captain&amp;rsquo;s cajones are made of â¦ well, brass.
Gil&amp;rsquo;s in Vegas, sees his ex-wife Sara (#Awkward), and runs into a chipper redhead who flummoxes him to no end.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CinemaBlend</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2015/cinemablend/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2015/cinemablend/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
Despite Lady Heather&amp;rsquo;s rivalry with Sara Sidle over the years, I don&amp;rsquo;t think anyone wanted her to be a true terrorist, and CSI obliges. It&amp;rsquo;s a frame job, and when the real terrorist shows up&amp;ndash;he&amp;rsquo;s played by frequent baddie Doug Hutchinson&amp;ndash;we know immediately where the episode is going. Regardless, it doesn&amp;rsquo;t matter, as this was an episode about bringing together the original team and sending them off in a way that pleased fans who showed up earlier in the show&amp;rsquo;s run as well as the fans who stuck around for the series over the long term.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E! Online</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2015/e-online-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2015/e-online-1/</guid>
      <description>Full disclosure: I haven&amp;rsquo;t watched &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; in years, but that didn&amp;rsquo;t mean tonight wasn&amp;rsquo;t a total emotional roller coaster for me.
I watched every single episode for the first nine seasons at least, and even stuck around for a couple more after Grissom left (and broke my heart in the process).
[&amp;hellip;]
I loved CSI, and I never really stopped loving it. I just kind of grew up and apart from the show, just as the original characters grew apart from each other (looking at you, Grissom and Sara).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E! Online (News)</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2015/e-online-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2015/e-online-2/</guid>
      <description>Confession: I have never purposefully watched an episode of CSI. Or any of its spinoffs.
[&amp;hellip;]
 Sarah and Catherine, are they frenemies? I feel tension? I feel history? Tempted to Google, but that feels like cheating.  [&amp;hellip;]
 Wait, Sarah and Petersen were MARRIED?! Is that why there was tension with her and Marg&amp;rsquo;s character?! Love it.  [&amp;hellip;]
 Sarah and Gil&amp;rsquo;s (I&amp;rsquo;ll call him that from now on, not Petersen) first encounter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LA Times</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2015/la-times-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2015/la-times-2/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
Jorja Fox, one of the show&amp;rsquo;s original cast members, has said in previous interviews that she didn&amp;rsquo;t think anyone would watch the series when it first premiered in 2000. She could not have been more wrong. The drama about a forensics investigation division in Las Vegas was an instant smash.
During its 15-year run, &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; spawned three spinoffs and became one of TV&amp;rsquo;s most popular series, in the U.S. and internationally.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LA Times (Review)</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2015/la-times-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2015/la-times-3/</guid>
      <description>In the end, &amp;lsquo;CSI: Crime Scene Investigation&amp;rsquo; died as it lived: fun, flabby, and altogether too invested in the undying love of two deeply sexless characters.
[&amp;hellip;]
Though Petersen&amp;rsquo;s return for the series finale gave the show a badly needed jolt of original &amp;lsquo;CSI&amp;rsquo; magic, it also meant that the love story of Gil Grissom and Sara Sidle returned to center stage.
Sidle, played by Jorja Fox, was another of the show&amp;rsquo;s originating characters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LostRemote</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2015/lostremote/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2015/lostremote/</guid>
      <description>While CSI has been one of the longest-running shows of the decade, its series finale drew almost no digital buzz. Amobee Brand Intelligence analyzed the engagements around the finale and found that just a few fans were called to action last night, which either means that CSI is more a of a VOD hit than anything else or that everyone was watching ABC, which premiered Quantico and Once Upon a Time last night.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Equals</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2015/tv-equals/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2015/tv-equals/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
Still, it was hard to complain about that, when the show not only brought back Catherine Willows (Marg Helgenberger) and Jim Brass (Paul Guilfoyle), but the long-since-gone Grissom (William Peterson) and- be still my heart- even Lady Heather, aka Dr. Kessler (Melinda Clarke). I certainly wasn&amp;rsquo;t. Grissom was as wonderfully grizzled and nerdy as ever, (Sara) sidling back into the role as if no time whatsoever had passed. As such, it was probably inevitable that he would get the most screen time, but I suppose that&amp;rsquo;s as it should be.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Washington Post</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2015/washington-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2015/washington-post/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
&amp;rdquo;&amp;lsquo;Grissom and Sara ended up together &amp;ndash; for good this time, we assume.&amp;ldquo;&amp;rsquo;
For a moment it seemed like the on-again, off-again lovers might go their separate ways, but come on. There&amp;rsquo;s no way that was happening. Instead, Sara left Vegas and flew to San Diego to join Gil on his boat. The pair literally sailed off into the sunset.&amp;lsquo;CSI&amp;rsquo; was never the subtlest show.
[&amp;hellip;]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zap2It</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2015/zap2it/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2015/zap2it/</guid>
      <description>After 15 years, 335 episodes and countless grisly death scenes, &amp;lsquo;CSI&amp;rsquo; said goodbye with a TV movie entitled &amp;lsquo;Immortality.&amp;rsquo; It was a chance to bid adieu to old friends, wrap up some loose ends, and watch a television institution ride off into the sunset.
But in true &amp;lsquo;Crime Scene Investigation&amp;rsquo; fashion, it was also an opportunity to bring some grisly drama. With Las Vegas itself under attack, would the return of Gil Grissom, Catherine Willows and Jim Brass help save the day?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deadline</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2015/deadline/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2015/deadline/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
DEADLINE: Let&amp;rsquo;s start with the final scene of Gil and Sara sailing off into the sunset. How did that ending come about?
ZUIKER: SixteenÂ years ago, William Petersen, (executive producers) Cindy Chvatal and Jonathan Littman and myself sat down at the Beverly Wilshire, that was the first time we got together.Â We actually met there 16 years later, same table, same party of four. And William Peterson pulled out this research folder that dealt with sea shepherd.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Entertainment Weekly</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2015/entertainment-weekly-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2015/entertainment-weekly-4/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
Still, it was interesting seeing this most coldly logical of mystery shows indulge its romantic side. At one point in the finale, a mysterious bad guy sends in a face-scrambling video message straight to Grissom: &amp;lsquo;The grand finale is specifically designed for you.&amp;rsquo; That vibed like a meta mission statement for &amp;lsquo;Immortality,&amp;rsquo; which worked best as an extremely melodramatic triangle between Grissom, longtime antagonist/ambiguous love interest Lady Heather, and even-longer-time ally/ex-wife Sara.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Inquirer.net</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2015/inquirer-net/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2015/inquirer-net/</guid>
      <description>How will the &amp;lsquo;CSI&amp;rsquo; special two-hour series finale address the romance between William Petersen&amp;rsquo;s Gil Grissom and Jorja Fox&amp;rsquo;s Sara Sidle?
[&amp;hellip;]
Will there be closure for Gil Grissom and Sara Sidle?
You have to watch. I don&amp;rsquo;t know how they edited it so who knows?
They are teasing a lot about it in the trailer.
Of course, they are. I am always leery of saying much about it. With the technology and everything, everybody is going to find out anyway.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Orlando Sentinel</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2015/orlando-sentinel/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2015/orlando-sentinel/</guid>
      <description>Gil Grissom (William Petersen) returned to &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; to talk to bees, lecture about whale songs and tell of a flower whose fragrance can make anyone lose control. For a final time, Grissom&amp;rsquo;s offbeat brilliance brightened the forensics work.
As the influential CBS crime procedural ended its 15-year run &amp;#8212; SPOILER ALERT &amp;#8212; Grissom also stopped a mad bomber and found personal happiness. Petersen&amp;rsquo;s return was a reminder that &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; had never been the same since Grissom left.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>People</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2015/people-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2015/people-2/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
Beyond being entranced by the newly sophisticated level of high-tech forensic investigation and the clever murder scenarios the show employed, fans also fell for the character&amp;rsquo;s personal dramas &amp;ndash; most specifically Grissom&amp;rsquo;s slow-simmering romance with Jorja Fox&amp;rsquo;s fellow investigator Sara Sidle.
&amp;ldquo;All we wanted to do was sort of have a real relationship that exists sometimes in the workplace where there&amp;rsquo;s a little thing that happens,&amp;rdquo; says Petersen. &amp;ldquo;And that becomes a little bit more of a thing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sidney Morning Herald</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2015/sidney-morning-herald/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2015/sidney-morning-herald/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
Sara Sidle &amp;ndash; CSI Forensic scientist Sara Sidle makes a living being up-close and personal with dead bodies, but she draws the line when it comes to animals. Sarah wasn&amp;rsquo;t always a vegetarian, instead she became one halfway through the show after spending a night with a dead, decomposing pig. Remarkably, Sara wasn&amp;rsquo;t the first vegetarian character played by actress Jorja Fox, who also gave up meat for Dr Maggie Doyle on E.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Variety</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2015/variety-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2015/variety-1/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
Without giving too much away what is the most important bit of closure that you&amp;rsquo;ll offer your die-hard fans?
This is the Super Bowl for (Jorja Fox&amp;rsquo;s) Sara Sidle. She&amp;rsquo;s applied for the directorship of running the lab. This is the one incident that brings back Grissom, and we see her being mentored by (Ted Danson&amp;rsquo;s) D.B. Russell. This is a case that paralyzes Vegas. One of the big burning questions of the finale is where (Grissom&amp;rsquo;s) heart will lie.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Variety (Columns)</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2015/variety-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2015/variety-2/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
Not surprisingly, there was a &amp;lsquo;the gang&amp;rsquo;s all here&amp;rsquo; quality to the finale (and SPOILER ALERT if you haven&amp;rsquo;t watched), which concocted an excuse to bring back Grissom (Petersen) to work a case alongside Catherine Willows (Marg Helgenberger) and ex-wife Sara Sidle (Jorja Fox), all in the ostensible service of solving a crime that tied into his past, involving the dominatrix Lady Heather (Melinda Clarke). Frankly, anyone who has watched TV in the last 20-some-odd years should have instantly known whodunit when Doug Hutchison (who has been playing a psycho as far back as Tombs in &amp;lsquo;The X-Files&amp;rsquo;) showed up, but that really wasn&amp;rsquo;t the issue.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LA Times</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2015/la-times-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2015/la-times-1/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Jorja Fox of &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; is preparing to face welcome uncertainty. &amp;ldquo;I think you kind of have to embrace the unknown if you&amp;rsquo;re an actor,&amp;rdquo; she says.&amp;rdquo;
After playing Las Vegas forensic scientist Sara Sidle on &amp;ldquo;CSI: Crime Scene Investigation&amp;rdquo; for 15 seasons, Jorja Fox is preparing to face &amp;ndash; even welcoming &amp;ndash; uncertainty. &amp;ldquo;I think you kind of have to embrace the unknown if you&amp;rsquo;re an actor,&amp;rdquo; she says. The show that launched the colossal franchise on CBS &amp;ndash; as well as career aspirations for forensics obsessives everywhere &amp;ndash; concludes Sunday with a two-hour finale.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Guide</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2015/tv-guide-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2015/tv-guide-3/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
Zuiker is staying pretty mum on the details of the finale, other than acknowledging that there is an explosion that &amp;ldquo;paralyzes Las Vegas&amp;rdquo; and hinting that the episode will deal with the resolution of Grissom&amp;rsquo;s relationships with both Lady Heather (Melinda Clarke) and fellow CSI Sara Sidle (Jorja Fox). In some ways, that feels ironic because of the show&amp;rsquo;s insistence early on, partially at Petersen&amp;rsquo;s behest, not to go home with its characters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NY Daily News</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2015/ny-daily-news/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2015/ny-daily-news/</guid>
      <description>&amp;lsquo;CSI&amp;rsquo; wraps up its final case Sunday (Sept. 27), with a two-hour movie (CBS, 9 p.m.) that allows one of the most influential and successful shows in TV history to take a well-deserved final bow.
&amp;lsquo;If any show ever earned this kind of sendoff, it&amp;rsquo;s &amp;lsquo;CSI&amp;rsquo;,&amp;rsquo; CBS Entertainment Chairman Nina Tassler said this summer.
The last show, modestly titled &amp;lsquo;Immortality,&amp;rsquo; doesn&amp;rsquo;t only let the CSI team save Las Vegas one final time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>USA Today</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2015/usa-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2015/usa-today/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
Fox, whose criminalist Sara Sidle renews contact with her ex, Grissom, says the finale resolves some relationship matters while characters solve a deadly mystery. “Anthony wrote a suspenseful, exhilarating, crazy, warped story, which is one of his specialties,” she says.
[&amp;hellip;]
Questions of legacy were hardly at the forefront when CSI started. The series was a late addition to the network&amp;rsquo;s fall schedule and was initially scheduled on Fridays, a low-wattage night.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yahoo</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2015/yahoo/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2015/yahoo/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;CSI: Crime Scene Investigation&amp;rdquo; was a last-minute pickup by CBS, plugged into a Friday lineup whose widely forecast surefire hit would be a reboot of &amp;ldquo;The Fugitive,&amp;rdquo; not a quirky little drama dwelling on hair fibers and blood spatter.
&amp;ldquo;I thought it was never going to succeed,&amp;rdquo; says Jorja Fox. At the time she had a recurring role on &amp;ldquo;The West Wing&amp;rdquo; as a Secret Service agent, &amp;ldquo;but I thought, &amp;lsquo;How fun would it be just to take this ride for a little while!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>People</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2015/people-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2015/people-1/</guid>
      <description>What happened in Vegas &amp;hellip;
When CSI prepares to wrap up its &amp;ldquo;historic and groundbreaking&amp;rdquo; CBS run on Sunday, many of the series&amp;rsquo;s favorites are returning, including charter cast members William Petersen as Gil Grissom and Marg Helgenberger as Catherine Willows, to join Ted Danson&amp;rsquo;s D.B. Russell for one last investigation.
[&amp;hellip;]
Says original cast member Jorja Fox (whose Sara Sidle returned in season 11 after a brief hiatus): &amp;ldquo;Obviously we left a lot of balls up in the air at the end of season 15.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EW</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2015/ew/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2015/ew/</guid>
      <description>Original &amp;lsquo;CSI&amp;rsquo; cast members reflect on the positive impact of the CBS show 15 years later
It&amp;rsquo;s the end of an era: after 15 years on the air, &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; is coming to a close on Sept. 27 with a two-hour movie finale. The creators, producers, and cast met up on closing night of this year&amp;rsquo;s PaleyFest Fall TV Preview for a farewell salute panel on Wednesday (moderated by EW&amp;rsquo;s own Lynette Rice), and we caught up with William Petersen and some of his costars on the red carpet before the event to get their thoughts about the end of &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Entertainment Weekly</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2015/entertainment-weekly-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2015/entertainment-weekly-3/</guid>
      <description>At the last event of this year&amp;rsquo;s PaleyFest Fall TV Previews at the Paley Center for Media, the cast and producers of CSI gathered Tuesday night in Los Angeles for a panel to say farewell to the groundbreaking series, which is ending its run after 15 seasons.
Though season 15 ended earlier this year, but the whole series is going out with a bang: It will conclude with a two-hour TV movie, which airs Sunday, Sept.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Line</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2015/tv-line-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2015/tv-line-2/</guid>
      <description>Brush up on your forensic jargon and crank the volume on The Who, because it&amp;rsquo;s nearly time to say goodbye to CSI.
After formally getting cancelled in May, the long-running mothership series will tie up loose ends with a two-hour movie event on Sunday, Sept. 27 (9/8c, CBS), which will involve almost every key player from the past 15 seasons.
Though some fans may be skeptical as to how Gil Grissom, Catherine Willows, et al.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mirror</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2015/mirror/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2015/mirror/</guid>
      <description>After 15 years on the air, it&amp;rsquo;s time to say goodbye - but it&amp;rsquo;s all hands on deck for the final mystery.
As CSI comes to an end after 15 years, a new trailer has been unveiled for it&amp;rsquo;s movie-length finale Immortality.
The band is back together for what is bound to be an emotional final episode, with William Petersen, Jorja Fox, Paul Guilfoyle and Marg Helgenberger being brought back.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Entertainment Weekly</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2015/entertainment-weekly-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2015/entertainment-weekly-2/</guid>
      <description>The original cast members reflect on the highs and lows of starring in the CBS drama
After 15 seasons and more than 300 episodes, the crime drama will bid farewell with a two-hour finale on Sept. 27. We asked some original cast members to reflect on their time behind the yellow tape.
[&amp;hellip;]
&amp;rdquo;&amp;lsquo;Jorja Fox&amp;rdquo;&amp;rsquo; (Sara Sidle): &amp;lsquo;I think Sara is the least-liked character on the show. As much as she has a lot of fans, I think she has more who dislike her.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Guide</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2015/tv-guide-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2015/tv-guide-1/</guid>
      <description>Gil Grissom&amp;rsquo;s back! The first teaser for CSI&amp;rsquo;s two-hour finale has arrived with our first glimpse of William Petersen and Marg Helgenberger joining Ted Danson and other CSI alums for one last hurrah.
We also catch just a hint of Grissom and Sara Sidle&amp;rsquo;s (Jorja Fox) relationship status, as guest star Melinda Clarke asks Sidle, &amp;ldquo;Do you love him?&amp;rdquo;
[&amp;hellip;]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Line</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2015/tv-line-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2015/tv-line-1/</guid>
      <description>&amp;lsquo;Let&amp;rsquo;s give the world something to remember,&amp;rsquo; indeed!
The first teaser trailer for &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo;&amp;rsquo;s two-hour finale event (CBS, Sept. 27) promises to tie up any loose ends from the procedural&amp;rsquo;s 15-season run &amp;ndash; including Sara Sidle and Gil Grissom&amp;rsquo;s uncertain romantic future.
&amp;lsquo;Do you love him?&amp;rsquo; Lady Heather (guest-star Melinda Clarke) asks Sidle, to which Sidle tearfully replies, &amp;lsquo;I do.&amp;rsquo; That exchange, coupled with a shot of Sidle approaching Grissom on a boat, should offer suffering fans quite a bit of hope.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Entertainment Weekly</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2015/entertainment-weekly-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2015/entertainment-weekly-1/</guid>
      <description>Longtime faves William Petersen, Marg Helgenberger, Paul Guilfoyle, and Melinda Clarke returned to the CSI set earlier this month to help wrap 15 seasons and more than 300 episodes of the CBS drama with the two-hour finale (Sept. 27). Newer stars, including Ted Danson and Elisabeth Harnois, team with the vets to investigate a catastrophic event that paralyzes all of Sin City, but the two-parter &amp;#8212; titled &amp;ldquo;Immortality, Parts I and II&amp;rdquo; &amp;#8212; also was one last excuse to reunite old friends.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Guide Magazine</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2015/tv-guide-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2015/tv-guide-2/</guid>
      <description>After 15 years and countless cases, CSI closes the lab for good with a two-hour send-off.
THE MOST POPULAR, groundbreaking and influential whodunit in TV history has to go out with a bang, right? CSI: Crime Scene Investigation ends its 15-season run with &amp;ldquo;Immortality,&amp;rdquo; a two-hour episode about an explosive attack on the Eclipse, the posh Las Vegas casino co-owned by former CSI Catherine Willows (Marg Helgenberger). This news-making calamity has Catherine, now working for the FBI in Los Angeles, returning to Sin City to lead the forensics investigation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ExtraTV</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2015/extra-tv/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2015/extra-tv/</guid>
      <description>On the Set of &amp;lsquo;CSI&amp;rsquo;! All the Scoop on the Series Finale *&amp;lsquo;Crime Watch Daily&amp;rsquo; host Matt Doran was the perfect &amp;lsquo;Extra&amp;rsquo; special correspondent to stop by the &amp;lsquo;CSI&amp;rsquo; set to get the scoop on the series finale. Watch!
Catch the final episode Sept. 27 at 9 PM on CBS.
[&amp;hellip;]
Matt Doran: (voice over) Jorja Fox, ready to put her work boots on one last time.
Matt Doran: What can you tell us about what we can expect from the finale?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>News Articles (2015)</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2015/</guid>
      <description>Date Source    August 27 TV Guide Magazine   September 04 Entertainment Weekly   September 14 Entertainment Weekly   September 14 TV Guide   September 14 TV Line   September 15 Mirror   September 17 EW   September 17 Entertainment Weekly   September 17 TV Line   September 23 People   September 24 USA Today   September 24 Yahoo   September 25 NY Daily News   September 26 LA Times   September 26 TV Guide   September 27 Deadline   September 27 Entertainment Weekly   September 27 Inquirer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Transcripts (2015)</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2015/</guid>
      <description>  Date Source    August 18 ExtraTV   September 29 Lylapalooza    September 29 Shark Allies   October 24 Extra at the EMA Awards Green Carpet    </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>