<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Red Carpet on Jorja Fox Library</title>
    <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/tags/red-carpet/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Red Carpet on Jorja Fox Library</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2006 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://jorjafox.net/library/tags/red-carpet/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Genesis Awards</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2006/genesis-awards/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2006/genesis-awards/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Jorja was interviewed at the 20th anniversary Genesis Awards. This is a partial transcript.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; Uh, yeah, this is my second time at the Genesis Awards, and I&amp;rsquo;m really excited to be invited back. They tend to spread the love around, so I think it&amp;rsquo;s, it&amp;rsquo;s a little special to be back a second time. Uh, I&amp;rsquo;m lucky enough tonight I&amp;rsquo;m going to be presenting a Genesis Award for &amp;lsquo;Dramatic Television Show&amp;rsquo; that &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; is winning. So I get to present the award to a very good friend of mine who&amp;rsquo;s, uh, co-executive producer and writer of the episode on &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Interviewer:&lt;/strong&gt; And why do you think they&amp;rsquo;re winning the award tonight?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; Um, well I think&amp;hellip; you know it&amp;rsquo;s cool, it&amp;rsquo;s- it&amp;rsquo;s sorta like getting recognized, you know what I mean?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Interviewer:&lt;/strong&gt; Right.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; It&amp;rsquo;s a great gift to receive for that show. Uh, it&amp;rsquo;s an issue that was very close to Josh Berman&amp;rsquo;s heart, the writer of the episode, and it deals with canned hunting, which is kind of a, a big, sort of widespread thing, particularly in rural America, obviously not so much in the cities. But people who have ranches and farms, um, there&amp;rsquo;s a lot of money to be made, you can ship in exotic animals and stage a hunt.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Interviewer:&lt;/strong&gt; Right.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; And uh, so this is an issue that he took a, he became sort of passionately interested in and he wrote it, and we rarely have shows, you know, in &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; where we take strong stands about things. And uh, so it was kinda nice that he did and it&amp;rsquo;s been recognized like this.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Interviewer:&lt;/strong&gt; So you credit him for doing that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; Yeah it&amp;rsquo;s cool.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Interviewer:&lt;/strong&gt; Now why do you think they invited you back again this year?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; Um, well I&amp;rsquo;m really excited, you know, I see Gretchen around from time to time at different events and uh, she had mentioned this to me a couple of months ago and when she mentioned it, actually, she said that we were nominated, but, uh, at that time who knew who was gonna win.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Interviewer:&lt;/strong&gt; Yeah, yeah.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; So this is her last Genesis Awards that she&amp;rsquo;s gonna be hosting, it&amp;rsquo;s the 20th anniversary, she&amp;rsquo;s retiring, I feel deeply honored to get to be here tonight and share it, a little bit of that with her, you know.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Interviewer:&lt;/strong&gt; Yeah. And then you&amp;rsquo;re going to go&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; Yeah, yeah. So I don&amp;rsquo;t know why I&amp;rsquo;m back, but I&amp;rsquo;m, I&amp;rsquo;m very glad to be back.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Interviewer:&lt;/strong&gt; Yeah. Thank you so much for-&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E! - Emmy Red Carpet</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2004/emmy-red-carpet/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Sep 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2004/emmy-red-carpet/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Star Jones:&lt;/strong&gt; In the mean time my girl is here.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; Hey. (hug)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Star Jones:&lt;/strong&gt; Hey Jorja, nice to see you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; How are you?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Star Jones:&lt;/strong&gt; So we are looking at one of the stars of one of the number one shows [[CSI]] &amp;hellip;they&amp;rsquo;re still watchin&amp;rsquo; Jorja.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; Ahh, thank you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Star Jones:&lt;/strong&gt; You&amp;rsquo;ve got to show yourself off here Jorja, because everybody&amp;rsquo;s looking for you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; I&amp;rsquo;ll try&amp;hellip;okay.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Star Jones:&lt;/strong&gt; Okay, got to tell you, great figure&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; Thanks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Star Jones:&lt;/strong&gt; I&amp;rsquo;m not going to pick on you and say if you ate a doughnut you&amp;rsquo;d look pregnant, but what did you eat today girl?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; (laughs) I had a half of a real Food Daily cheeseburger.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Star Jones:&lt;/strong&gt; You did!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; That&amp;rsquo;s all I had, yeah.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Star Jones:&lt;/strong&gt; Yeah, but you did have a little cheesburger. A little nourishment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; Yeah, vegetarian with the vege bacon and the vege cheese&amp;hellip;but it&amp;rsquo;s a cheeseburger.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Star Jones:&lt;/strong&gt; But it&amp;rsquo;s still a cheeseburger.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; Oh yeah.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Star Jones:&lt;/strong&gt; You didn&amp;rsquo;t do that stalk and cellery and lettuce thing?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; No, no, no, I gave up on all that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Star Jones:&lt;/strong&gt; You did?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; No, I can&amp;rsquo;t maintain all that. And I had a little bit of vodka and 7Up in the car. But don&amp;rsquo;t tell anyone, shh.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Star Jones:&lt;/strong&gt; That&amp;rsquo;s my girl, so you&amp;rsquo;re drinking vodka and 7Up in the car, shh, don&amp;rsquo;t tell anyone&amp;hellip; what are you listening to on the radio?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; Radio didn&amp;rsquo;t work, my goodness, so we listened to you know, sky, the sky sounds, that kind of thing. Sometimes I bring CDs, but I bring em&amp;rsquo;, then I forget em&amp;rsquo;. So I try to leave them at home and I should have today because the radio was broken.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Star Jones:&lt;/strong&gt; So all over limos in Los Angeles have like a stock of Jorja Fox CDs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; (laughs) Yeah.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Star Jones:&lt;/strong&gt; You won&amp;rsquo;t have any left. Are you excited about tonight?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; I am. I love this award show.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Star Jones:&lt;/strong&gt; It&amp;rsquo;s a lot of fun.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; I&amp;rsquo;m like a little kid. And it&amp;rsquo;s so nice you know, the movie people and the TV people are together&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Star Jones:&lt;/strong&gt; Absolutely&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; And it&amp;rsquo;s kind of a small space&amp;hellip; and it feels I know it&amp;rsquo;s weird to say but kind of family, like there&amp;rsquo;s a family feel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Star Jones:&lt;/strong&gt; You know why? Because it&amp;rsquo;s actors honouring other actors, and you all are a family.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; Yes, exactly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Star Jones:&lt;/strong&gt; And I just want to tell you&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; A happy family.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Star Jones:&lt;/strong&gt; A little dysfunctional, but a family none the less. Well, we wish you the best for CSI this year.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; Thank you. You are wonderful.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Star Jones:&lt;/strong&gt; Thank you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; I love seeing you here.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Star Jones:&lt;/strong&gt; Yes, keep watchin&amp;rsquo; baby, keep watchin&amp;rsquo;, we&amp;rsquo;ll see you next time.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Golden Globes Red Carpet</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2002/golden-globes-red-carpet/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jan 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2002/golden-globes-red-carpet/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Melissa Rivers&lt;/strong&gt; Thank you. I am here with the cast of CSI. Your show has taken off, like, y&amp;rsquo;know. A train, just steaming right out of the station.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; We&amp;rsquo;re dazed. We&amp;rsquo;re dazed and confused and so happy and yeah! It&amp;rsquo;s great.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Melissa Rivers&lt;/strong&gt; I see Marg has gotten a lot of attention for the show for the last, what? For last season.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; Yeah.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Melissa Rivers&lt;/strong&gt; But now the whole show is being acknowledged tonight.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Robert David Hall&lt;/strong&gt; It&amp;rsquo;s the great chemistry. It&amp;rsquo;s a lot of fun to go to work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Melissa Rivers&lt;/strong&gt; Now did anyone, did any of you get offers, or did everyone have to sort of go through the whole process?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; They actually made us all audition, I think. Anyone-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mrs. Hall&lt;/strong&gt; Except for Billy Petersen.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;rdquo;(everyone laughs)&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Melissa Rivers&lt;/strong&gt; How many times- How many times did you have to come back?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Paul Guilfoyle&lt;/strong&gt; Twice.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; Two times, yeah.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Eric Szmanda&lt;/strong&gt; Two.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Gary Dourdan&lt;/strong&gt; Oh they already hired me like months before, yeah.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Melissa Rivers&lt;/strong&gt; Now, and you shoot on location in Vegas.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; Yes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Melissa Rivers&lt;/strong&gt; How much fun is Vegas?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; It&amp;rsquo;s hard to concentrate sometimes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Gary Dourdan&lt;/strong&gt; Vegas is it&amp;rsquo;s own character, you know. Vegas, Vegas- We don&amp;rsquo;t have to do anything, it does itself, so&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Melissa Rivers&lt;/strong&gt; Do you still, like, walk to the casinos and go &amp;lsquo;Oh, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna go out tonight,&amp;rsquo; or is it more is it just like &amp;lsquo;eh it&amp;rsquo;s Vegas&amp;rsquo;? Cause I spent a lot of time there, growing up, when my mom was working there, and you kind of get numb to the whole thing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; There are certain ones of us here who have to have their money held for them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Melissa Rivers&lt;/strong&gt; Ahhh.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; I won&amp;rsquo;t mention any names &amp;ldquo;(points to Gary, George and herself)&amp;rdquo; but they&amp;rsquo;re here.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Melissa Rivers&lt;/strong&gt; We&amp;rsquo;ll save that for the ending interview, how about that? Cause I have a feeling you guys are all going to be nominated for that. Thank you so much for stopping and best of luck tonight.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Memento Premiere</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2001/memento-premiere/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2001/memento-premiere/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Jorja Fox was interviewed at the premiere of &amp;ldquo;Memento&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Interviewer:&lt;/strong&gt; I saw the movie and it was fabulous-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; Thank you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Interviewer:&lt;/strong&gt; -um, and it looked real scary to lay in that bag.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; It was really scary, actually, &amp;ldquo;(laughs)&amp;rdquo; and, and the tile was very very cold, and there was water being spritzed on me occasionally, so I had a very&amp;hellip; I think I uh, I think I dozed off for a little while.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Interviewer:&lt;/strong&gt; What was it like working with Chris Nolan [director of &amp;ldquo;Memento&amp;rdquo;]?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; Amazing. He&amp;rsquo;s very generous, really intelligent, whip smart&amp;hellip; I read the script like three times and I still didn&amp;rsquo;t know what the movie was about, and he very simply sat down and sort of explained to me, and it did &amp;ldquo;change&amp;rdquo;, there were several incarnations of what the movie might be, and that&amp;rsquo;s one of the most exciting things I think about working with him, because it&amp;rsquo;s like a &amp;#8216;lightning mind&amp;rsquo; syndrome, and um, yet very communcative at the same time. So it&amp;rsquo;s kinda rare in a movie.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Interviewer:&lt;/strong&gt; What was it like working with Guy Pearce?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;ldquo;(smiling)&amp;rdquo; I &amp;ldquo;love&amp;rdquo; Guy Pearce, yeah. Um&amp;hellip; he&amp;rsquo;s&amp;hellip; incredibly handsome, an incredible actor, so very kind and sweet, and uh, grounded, he has a very grounded presence. Because so much of the movie is so dark, and yet here he had this sort of light, ethereal energy that he brought with him to the whole cast. Cause you can start to get a little, you know, after a long day you can start to drag down and you&amp;rsquo;re like &amp;#8216;why am I depressed?&amp;lsquo;, you know, and he brought that energy and enthusiasm with him all the time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Interviewer:&lt;/strong&gt; What other projects are you working on, what are you working on next?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; Uh, currently I&amp;rsquo;m working on a show called &amp;ldquo;CSI:&amp;ldquo;, uh, and that&amp;rsquo;s really, there&amp;rsquo;s no &amp;#8216;next&amp;rsquo; at the moment, we finish in May and we&amp;rsquo;ve been working since last July, so next might be a slow trip somewhere, far away, from you know, once we make hiatus, I might just do that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Interviewer:&lt;/strong&gt; What&amp;rsquo;s the show about?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; Uh, it&amp;rsquo;s about crime scene investigators, actually, so I feel like I have made a complete circle; I played a victim in this movie and on &amp;ldquo;CSI:&amp;rdquo; I&amp;rsquo;m a forensic scientist and a criminalist who investigates what happened to people like me in &amp;ldquo;Memento&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Interviewer:&lt;/strong&gt; Well thank you so much. We love-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[[Category:Red Carpet]]&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>