<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Movies on JFO Library</title>
    <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/tags/movies/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Movies on JFO Library</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="http://jorjafox.net/library/tags/movies/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>3 Weeks to Daytona</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/actor/3-weeks-to-daytona/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/actor/3-weeks-to-daytona/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;recap:49b2d895cc86225af703d16ec08e2f89&#34;&gt;Recap&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Chuck Weber is a race car driver who is down on his luck and nothing has gone right in twenty years, which happens to be the last time he won a race. Divorced, struggling to pay for his car and the alimony for his son, Willy (aka Worm), the only bright spot in his life is racing at the Speedbowl, a lock stock-car track run by Sal.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After crashing into the wall and losing his sponsorship, Chuck fears his dreams are at an end when Sal loses his sponsorship from Rob&amp;rsquo;s furniture. In a desperate grab to save his track, Sal convinces Rob to fund one driver to the Daytona 500. Rob balks at the idea of supporting Sal&amp;rsquo;s driver, Buddy, so Sal suggests a race - winner takes all.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cheryl, Chuck&amp;rsquo;s pit crew and girlfriend (called &amp;lsquo;Trenton trash&amp;rsquo; by Katie, Chuck&amp;rsquo;s ex-wife), spends her days working at a machine shop. Unlike Chuck, Cheryl saves her money with the hope of making her own speed shop. Still, she bets on Chuck, and when she finds out about the race, she funds Chuck&amp;rsquo;s repairs. Katie demands the money for alimony instead, which makes Chuck unable to pay for his car, and pisses Cheryl off to no end.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After being kicked out by Cheryl, Chuck takes his son to his old trailer, filled with his old trophies, which Worm had never seen before. Chuck finally tells Worm that he started losing races when his father stepped in to be his pit boss, replacing Sal. Young Chuck was so frustrated with his father&amp;rsquo;s ways, he intentionally crashed his car, and hasn&amp;rsquo;t won a race since.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of Chuck coworkers, Steve, harasses him at work and happens to be dating Katie. Finally he challenges Chuck to a race to the airport: whomever picks up the customer first wins the race, and the car. Now armed with the money, Chuck retrieves his car and apologizes to Cheryl, who refuses to go help him. The only person who will go to the track with Chuck is his son, who now insists on being called Willy and has been failing math since he spends his time trying to fix Chuck&amp;rsquo;s car. Katie, however, blackmails Chuck for all of his winnings just to let Willy go to the race.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Just as the race starts, Cheryl arrives to manage the pit and works with Willy to improve the speed and performance of the car. When Chuck starts to waver, Willy provides the emotional stimulus to win, and the trio finally move forward to Daytona.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;character:49b2d895cc86225af703d16ec08e2f89&#34;&gt;Character&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cheryl constantly bets on Chuck, losing money every race by literally betting on him. She loses her cool when he spends money meant for the car on his alimony, but accepts his apology and helps him at the end. Cheryl has a remarkable eye for the track, spotting a crash before it happens, and is innovative, using a hair clip for the car&amp;rsquo;s missing hood pin. While it&amp;rsquo;s clear she and Chuck have feelings for each other, they only kiss after he wins the Speedbowl race.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alchemy</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/actor/alchemy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/actor/alchemy/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This distinctly feminist drama chronicles three phases in the life of a young woman. The three phases are presented as distinct, titled vignettes, &amp;ldquo;Charity,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;Hope,&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Faith,&amp;rdquo; centered upon Louisa Garrison, a woman who translates folk tales. She is first seen working in a bookstore. Though involved with Ethan, she decides to break up with him because she strongly suspects that he is still in love with Kitty, his ex-girl friend. Ethan swears his innocence, but it&amp;rsquo;s to no avail. Somewhat obsessed with Kitty, Louisa begins investigating her and then learns that Ethan died in a car wreck. She goes to Kitty and becomes her friend. The grieving Kitty has no idea that Louisa was ever involved with Ethan. In the next segment, Louisa goes to see Jane, her older sister, who has just learned that she has cancer. Louisa is surprised to learn her sister is a lesbian. It also hurts her to realize that while Jane is gentle and giving to everyone around her, she is cold and remote from Louisa. In the last vignette, Louisa moves to a remote artists&amp;rsquo; colony and there falls in love with Duncan, a man she used to work with.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jorja Fox plays Josie (credited as Jorjan Fox).&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dead Drunk: The Kevin Tunell Story</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/actor/dead-drunk/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/actor/dead-drunk/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Dead Drunk: The Kevin Tunell Story&amp;rdquo; was first aired on HBO in 1993. It is a compelling and cautionary tale of the choices and consequences of drinking and driving. On New Years Eve, 1981, Kevin Tunell went to a party to celebrate the coming new year and drank with his friends. He took his girlfriend home and although impaired, told her &amp;ldquo;nothing ever happens to me when I drink.&amp;rdquo; That might have been true, but that night Kevin&amp;rsquo;s life would change forever. Driving impaired and distracted by images on the side of the road Kevin had a head on collision with a young woman who was driving home from her friends house. He walked away with barely a scratch. The young woman, Maggie Glendon was not as fortunate and died as a result of her injuries.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jorja Fox plays Maggie Glendon, credited as Jorjan Fox.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dead Funny</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/actor/dead-funny/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/actor/dead-funny/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;Reggie has been skewered to the kitchen table with a Samurai sword, and Viv&amp;rsquo;s trying to remember what happened. After all, it was one hell of a party last night. Instead of calling the police, Louise, Viv&amp;rsquo;s best friend, takes charge, attempting to solve Reggie&amp;rsquo;s murder with the help of a list of suspects and a couple of bottles of champagne. Deep in memories of her last year with Reggie and continuously interrupted by a strange cast of characters, Viv wanders through her apartment in a daze. Still desperately hoping that Reggie&amp;rsquo;s body in the kitchen is another of his tasteless pranks, she slowly begins to recall the bizarre events of the last 24 hours.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;character:766a739f3bc523507071cad86f06798a&#34;&gt;Character&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jorja Fox plays one of the three fates (Fate 3); one of three women that Reggie knows who show up at odds moments in the movie. First they&amp;rsquo;re at the painting party Viv had hosted the night before, and second as three cops showing up in a hallucination around Reggie&amp;rsquo;s dead body. Fox doesn&amp;rsquo;t have many speaking lines, and they&amp;rsquo;re all in the background noise.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Down With The Joneses</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/actor/down-with-the-joneses/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/actor/down-with-the-joneses/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;While it is listed at IMDb as having been completed in 2003, this movie has no release information and there is no record of anyone having see the completed film.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Filmography</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/pages/Filmography/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/pages/Filmography/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;A filmography is, in essence, the resume of a performer, listing all their cinematic achievements. This filmography has been broken down by section, to aid in sorting her work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jorja is credited as Jorja Fox unless otherwise noted.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;TOC
{:toc}&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;{% for role in page.roles %}
{% assign credits = 0 %}
{% for item in site.data.filmography %}{% if item.role == role %}{% assign credits = credits | plus: 1 %}
{% endif %}{% endfor %}&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;role-capitalize-credits-credit-if-credits-1-s-endif:f98b6fda71393b193c0e7c84256f94c9&#34;&gt;{{role | capitalize }} ( {{credits}} Credit{% if credits != 1 %}s{% endif %})&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;table class=&#34;jfotable&#34; width=&#34;100%&#34;&gt;&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
    &lt;th&gt; Title &lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;th&gt; Date(s)&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
{% for item in site.data.filmography %}{% if item.role == role %}
&lt;tr&gt;
    &lt;td&gt;&lt;strong&gt;{% if item.slug %}&lt;a href=&#34;{{ site.baseurl }}/{{ item.role }}/{{ item.slug }}/&#34;&gt;{{ item.title }}&lt;/a&gt;{% else %}{{ item.title }}{% endif %}&lt;/strong&gt; ({{ item.type }})
        {% if item.character %}&lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;{{ item.character }}&lt;/strong&gt; {% if item.jorjan %}&lt;small&gt;[Credited as Jorjan Fox]&lt;/small&gt;{% endif %}{% endif %}
        {% if item.notes %}&lt;br /&gt;&lt;small&gt;{{ item.notes }}&lt;/small&gt;{% endif %}
    &lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;td valign=&#34;top&#34;&gt;{{ item.dates }}&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
{% endif %}{% endfor %}
&lt;/tbody&gt;&lt;/table&gt;
{% endfor %}&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;see-also:f98b6fda71393b193c0e7c84256f94c9&#34;&gt;See Also&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.imdb.com/name/nm0289080/&#34;&gt;IMDb&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;{{ site.baseurl }}/honeypot/&#34;&gt;Honeypot Productions&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;{{ site.baseurl }}/seafox/&#34;&gt;Seafox Productions&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Food for the Heart</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/actor/food-for-the-heart/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/actor/food-for-the-heart/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Jorja Fox plays Delmar Youngblood; a divorcee with an abundant love of cooking and family raising a young son in a small town in anywhere, USA. Her cherished dream is to open a restaurant, The Hungry Bachelors Club, but this reality is deterred by her uninteresting and low-paying job as an insurance adjuster.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Forever Fabulous</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/actor/forever-fabulous/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/actor/forever-fabulous/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;Loreli Daly (Jean Smart), beauty pageant organizer and Former Miss Texas Gal 1969, was run out of Paris, Texas ten years ago on the heels of a tabloid sex scandal. Living somewhere in Arizona with her long-term boyfriend and washed-up pageant MC, Lyle (Robert Wagner), and her daughter Corinne (Jennifer Elise Cox), holder of over 200 pageant titles and tiaras, Loreli is invited back, to Paris, to host the Miss Texas Tiara Quest &amp;ndash; but she can&amp;rsquo;t face the shame. Corinne, who dreams of fleeing her stifling mother and the pageant world to pluck starlets&amp;rsquo; eyebrows in Hollywood, sees the redemptive trip home as her means for escape.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Together with former childhood pageant-mates Liz Guild (Jorja Fox), currently a lovelorn prison guard, and Tiffany (Emily Procter), a bored but ambitious local news reporter who sees the story of Loreli&amp;rsquo;s return as her ticket to &lt;sup&gt;20&lt;/sup&gt;&amp;frasl;&lt;sub&gt;20&lt;/sub&gt; or Dateline, the three gals convince Loreli to go home to Texas and confront her past. The four women and Lyle embark on a fateful road trip, during which they will comically and poignantly come to terms with their own limitations, buried truths and each other.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Guided by the book &amp;ldquo;Valley of the Dolls,&amp;rdquo; an addiction to the soft drink Tab, and having Lyle choke to death on a fake eyelash are just some of the things they encounter during their trip back to Texas, only to find that event is actually a drag queen beauty pageant&amp;hellip; and so Loreli has the best drag queen pageant you will ever see!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;character:759e9b97004a1d421177a56180c93e75&#34;&gt;Character&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Liz Guild is the loyal, but plain and ordinary, friend of Corrine&amp;rsquo;s. There&amp;rsquo;s never been any surprise or defiance or star power in Liz, but for some reason she can&amp;rsquo;t fathom and is grateful for, Corrine has always let her hang around.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nothing at Liz&amp;rsquo;s job as a guard in the local women&amp;rsquo;s prison could ever hold a candle to the glamor and drama she&amp;rsquo;s privy to at the Daly house. She isn&amp;rsquo;t even glamorous enough herself to hold onto her boyfriend, Barry, who has left her and run off to Texas with all her clothes. So, when Corrine mentioned finding her mother&amp;rsquo;s invitation in the trash and her plan to use it as her own ticket out, and then Tiffany came on board with her plan to help Corrine by convincing Loreli to accept the invitation and use it as her ticket out, there was no question that Liz would be on board &amp;ndash; even if she had to buy her own ticket just to go along with them for the ride. And she would find Barry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If only she hadn&amp;rsquo;t tried to fit in with all the glamor. If only she hadn&amp;rsquo;t been crying over Barry again. If only she&amp;rsquo;d used better eyelash glue.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Forever Fabulous Biography</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/biographies/forever-fabulous/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/biographies/forever-fabulous/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Jorja Fox (Liz) co-stars in the new CBS breakout series C.S.I.: CRIME SCENE INVESTIGATION. She has also been featured as a Secret Service agent on NBC&amp;rsquo;s popular, Emmy-winning series THE WEST WING. She played the recurring role of Doyle on the NBC&amp;rsquo;s long-running ER, where she happily appeared for a number of seasons. She has made several made-for-TV films and mini-series including HOUSE OF FRANKENSTEIN, DEAD DRUNK and SUMMER STORIES. Film credits include MEMENTO, THE JERKY BOYS, THE HUNGRY BACHELORS&amp;rsquo; CLUB, VELOCITY TRAP, HOW TO MAKE THE CRUELEST MONTH, ALCHEMY, DEAD FUNNY, HAPPY HELL NIGHT and KILL OFF.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gidget: The Accidental Icon</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/actor/gidget/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/actor/gidget/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;Narrated by Jorja Fox and produced by Brian L. Gillogly and Robert Masters, ACCIDENTAL ICON explores the largely untold story of the real “Gidget,” Kathy Kohner Zuckerman. Kathy’s account of surfing Malibu in the mid-50’s became the basis for a best-selling novel by her father Frederick Kohner and the hit 1959 “Gidget” movie, which introduced the modern sport of surfing to a world-wide audience. Surf legends and present-day “surfer girls” set the stage and take the Gidget story full circle. Prominent actors and directors, many of whom brought Gidget to the big and small screen, provide an often enlightening behind-the-scenes perspective.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;fundraiser-05-sept-2008:ca11c76d99b94874c3c69bc39068a0bf&#34;&gt;Fundraiser (05 Sept. 2008)&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Surfrider West LA/Malibu Chapter and the Malibu Surfing Association celebrated Gidget&amp;rsquo;s story and the history of Malibu surfing with a special screening at Duke&amp;rsquo;s Malibu. Attendees met Kathy &amp;lsquo;Gidget&amp;rsquo; Kohner Zuckerman and other legends of the surf community, participated in a silent auction of artwork from top Malibu and LA artists, and attended an after party with live music.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://surfriderwlam.org/cleanthebu/?p=125&#34;&gt;Event Website&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happy Hell Night</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/actor/happy-hell-night/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/actor/happy-hell-night/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;25 years ago at Winfield College, psycho-priest Zachary Malius murdered seven frat boys and was put away in the local asylum. Now, however, the same fraternity stages a prank from which Malius is inadvertently set free and returns to the house to repeat his crime&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a prank for Rush Week, a couple of frat boys go to an insane asylum to take some pictures of an inmate there who supposedly killed a group of frat guys from their fathers&amp;rsquo; generation at the same college. One of them, after removing a huge cross that&amp;rsquo;s barring the door, gets dragged into the cell and killed. They inadvertently have unleashed the Satan Preacher on their college campus once again to continue the bloody reign of terror that he began decades ago.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;character:41b411eb7d3758d88d91265d41d8d77f&#34;&gt;Character&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jorja Fox plays a Kappa Sig Sorority Girl who &lt;em&gt;doesn&amp;rsquo;t&lt;/em&gt; sleep with a frat boy. Sadly, she does get killed.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>House of Frankenstein 1997</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/actor/house-frankenstein/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/actor/house-frankenstein/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;Distinctly mutilated bodies are being dropped all over Los Angeles like so much arcane propaganda. No one, however, knows how to read the message. The police are secretly baffled while the press has made the only stab at profiling the killer, calling the perpetrator The Midnight Raptor. Grace Dawkins is the Raptor&amp;rsquo;s latest victim, and the only one to have survived an attack, but she&amp;rsquo;s little help to the investigation. Grace insists she was attacked by some sort of wolf, and Detective Vernon Coyle, although he is intrigued by her beauty and animal magnetism, thinks she&amp;rsquo;s just terribly confused.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;character:f4556362dc85ff2b1be955f2f8e5b766&#34;&gt;Character&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jorja Fox plays Felicity, Grace&amp;rsquo;s roommate. The Raptor goes to the apartment searching for Grace, but finds Felicity instead, and bites her, turning her into a vampire.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Make the Cruelest Month</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/actor/how-make-crueslest-month/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/actor/how-make-crueslest-month/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Kip Koenig wrote and directed this comedy, set in a small college town, about neurotic Bell Bryant (Clea DuVall) who explains her problems directly to the camera: her older sister Sarah (Jorja Fox) has a happy marriage plus a baby on the way. Her other sister, beautiful Dot (Amy Smart), is involved in an affair with Bell&amp;rsquo;s ex, Leonard (Gabriel Mann). In a remote location, Bell makes love to Leonard and then departs, abandoning the nude Leonard who makes his way to the house of a married couple (Dennis Haysbert, Marianne Jean-Baptiste). Wondering if she&amp;rsquo;s a lesbian, the confused Bell dates a woman and then dashes around from one place to another, dropping in on her mom (Mary Kay Place), her uncle (John David Souther), and various eccentrics.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Shown at the 1998 Sundance Film Festival.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hungry Bachelors Club Biography</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/biographies/hungry-bachelors-club/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/biographies/hungry-bachelors-club/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Note: This biography was released before The Hungry Bachelors Club was renamed.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jorja Fox (Delmar Youngblood) is the lead in THE HUNGRY BACHELORS CLUB, playing a single mother with an unusual offer that may make her dreams come true. She had a recurring role as Dr. Maggie Doyle on NBC&amp;rsquo;s hit series ER. Her television credits also include guest leads on Law and Order and most recently, a pilot for Barry Levinson and Tom Fontana, Flesh and Blood. While THE HUNGRY BACHELORS CLUB marks Fox&amp;rsquo;s theatrical debut in a leading role, she is no stranger to film, having appeared in VELOCITY TRAP, ALCHEMY, HOW TO MAKE THE CRUELEST MONTH and TIARA TANGO, among others. Fox studied theatre and appeared onstage in New York and Los Angeles. She formed Honeypot Productions, a theatrical troupe in Los Angeles that presents one-act plays. Fox recently completed the feature MOMENTO, a dark suspense-mystery with Guy Pierce and Carrie Anne-Moss.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Memento</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/actor/memento/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/actor/memento/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Memento&lt;/strong&gt; is a movie starring Guy Pearce (&amp;lsquo;The Adventures of Priscilla, Queen of the Desert&amp;rsquo; and &amp;lsquo;L.A. Confidential&amp;rsquo;) and Carrie Anne-Moss (&amp;lsquo;The Matrix&amp;rsquo; and &amp;lsquo;Red Planet&amp;rsquo;). Jorja Fox plays Catherine Shelby, the wife of Leonard Shelby (Pearce), who was raped and murdered in the couple&amp;rsquo;s home.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;recap:35210f06cf016a5d9a2f20e7c327cfcf&#34;&gt;Recap&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Around 2:00 AM (Nov. 1997) police were called to the home of Leonard and Catherine Shelby, after two neighbors reported hearing gunshots. The front door was open, and they found the Shelbys in serious condition. Catherine (age 32) was brought to the hospital and listed in critical condition, having been sexually assaulted and having received a number of serious injuries to her head, neck and upper body. Leonard was stable, after receiving several severe blows to the head. Catherine later died from her injuries, while her husband suffers from &amp;lsquo;severe anterograde memory dysfunction as a result of head trauma&amp;rsquo; and recovers &amp;lsquo;almost none of his ability to convert short-term experiences to long term memory&amp;rsquo;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Over the course of the movie - which is told in reverse chronological order - Leonard tries to find out who killed his wife, and extract revenge with the help of Natalie and a lot of tattoos.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Though the character of Catherine Shelby is supposedly murdered, at the end of the movie we see the couple in bed together, with Leonard sporting all of his tattoos. This makes it appear as if he&amp;rsquo;s completed his revenge quest, yet his wife is still alive.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;character:35210f06cf016a5d9a2f20e7c327cfcf&#34;&gt;Character&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Catherine is the dead wife of Leonard Shelby, appearing only in flashbacks throughout the movie.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The circumstances of her death are murky, and either she was raped and murdered during a home invasion, or she died later due to an overdose of insulin medication.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>