<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Recaps on Jorja Fox Library</title>
    <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Recaps on Jorja Fox Library</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 27 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Immortality (Part 1)</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/immortality-part-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/immortality-part-1/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;synopsis:411c18cf4606f6caccf8d8cd9402d421&#34;&gt;Synopsis##&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We start with a &amp;lsquo;normal&amp;rsquo; episode of CSI. Finn is dead, D.B. Russell is leaving to work for the CSI: Cyber people, Sara is applying for a &amp;lsquo;key position&amp;rsquo; And then it all goes to hell with a suicide bomber.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We find Grissom working on a boat in San Diego, helping catch people illegally trapping sharks for shark fin soup. The CSIs that show up don&amp;rsquo;t mention Nick, who is their head last we heard.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While Grissom is arrested for illegal trespassing, Catherine shows up from Quanitco and wants in. DB and Sara try to keep her off the case, but it&amp;rsquo;s Catherine. When they find evidence pointing to Lady Heather, it&amp;rsquo;s Conrad Ecklie who has the brass balls to ask Sara for Grissom&amp;rsquo;s number. This gets Grissom out of hot water with San Diego at least.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When Grissom shows up in Vegas, he&amp;rsquo;s accosted by Lindsey Willows, Catherine&amp;rsquo;s daughter, a new level 1 CSI, starting her first day. It&amp;rsquo;s deja vu all over again. Grissom isn&amp;rsquo;t any less discombobulated when he sees Sara.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At Heather&amp;rsquo;s house they find evidence of bomb making, which doesn&amp;rsquo;t make anyone happy. Sara and Brass chase down a woman on the grounds, believing it to be Heather, but she blows up and injures Brass enough that he&amp;rsquo;s sent to the hospital.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And the woman? Isn&amp;rsquo;t Heather. Alive and well, Heather comes to the lab and turns herself in, saying she&amp;rsquo;s the one behind the bombings.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;sara-sidle-review:411c18cf4606f6caccf8d8cd9402d421&#34;&gt;Sara Sidle Review##&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While she&amp;rsquo;s moved on with her life and is trying to professionally make it through, Sara is not happy about Grissom and Heather, and really who can blame her? She kept Grissom&amp;rsquo;s number but they hadn&amp;rsquo;t been talking, even before the divorce, to the point that she didn&amp;rsquo;t know he was talking to Heather.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;character-notes:411c18cf4606f6caccf8d8cd9402d421&#34;&gt;Character Notes##&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sara and Grissom are divorced&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Communication issues led to the divorce&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sara is applying for lab director&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;quotes:411c18cf4606f6caccf8d8cd9402d421&#34;&gt;Quotes&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sara Sidle&lt;/strong&gt; Look, we both went our separate ways. You&amp;rsquo;re doing your Jacques Cousteau thing. I&amp;rsquo;m out in the field. Things end. I get it. But you and I are professionals. And as professionals, I think it&amp;rsquo;s in the best interest of my case to put our game faces on&amp;hellip; and keep it&amp;hellip; professional&amp;hellip; See&amp;hellip; Mine&amp;rsquo;s on. Ready to go in?&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Gil Grissom&lt;/strong&gt; Seeing you again left me speechless.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Immortality (Part 2)</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/immortality-part-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/immortality-part-2/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;synopsis:d7ca8c350c2b49405d241256b9943625&#34;&gt;Synopsis&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Unlike the last time Grissom was mentioned in the lab , this time everyone is angry at Grissom because of Lady Heather. However they allow him in the room when Heather is interrogated.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She claims there was an intruder in her home whom she attacked and then ran off, not calling the cops because of recent experiences. Heather needles Sara until Sara breaks and leaves the room, promising to get Heather. It&amp;rsquo;s Heather who says &amp;lsquo;you mean him&amp;rsquo;, indicating Grissom. Heather explains that while she&amp;rsquo;s certainly the &amp;lsquo;cause&amp;rsquo; for the killings, she&amp;rsquo;s not behind them. She&amp;rsquo;s being framed by one of the thirteen people who had a key to her special room.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Of the thirteen people, only five are male and alive. They include Dalton Barrow, Heather&amp;rsquo;s first client. But none of their blood matches. As they mull that over, Lindsey Willows brings in Grissom&amp;rsquo;s suitcase. Only it&amp;rsquo;s not Grissom&amp;rsquo;s. It&amp;rsquo;s a dead body in a suitcase. In the body is a MicroSD card with a video message for Grissom. All the killings are being done for him.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The body is identified as Jacob Wolfowitz, the man who killed Heather&amp;rsquo;s daughter. While they manage to clear Heather as the person in the video, she&amp;rsquo;s still detained as a suspect while the CSIs hunt down more evidence, but all they find is Mr. Synthetic Cadaver with a bee in him.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Grissom and Sara study the bee, which Grissom thinks was planted just for him. He sends out sniffer bees to find the where the bee in the fake body came from, and hopefully find the killer: Dalton Barron.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Meanwhile D.B. Russell tracks down the prints from the cadaver and sends Catherine, Greg, and Morgan Brody off to collect the man: Dalton Barron. The trio don&amp;rsquo;t make it out there, finding bombs in their cars instead. Catherine is able to help everyone defuse the car bombs safely.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dalton&amp;rsquo;s entire apartment is wired to blow, and as Grissom and Sara find him in the forest, so is he. Somehow he managed to trick them with his DNA. Since Dalton is dying of lymphoma, the blood he left at the scene matches his stem cell treatment, not his bucal swab. Dalton&amp;rsquo;s motive was because Grissom ruined Heather, taking her away from him. Grissom is able to talk him into delaying, disconnecting his suicide vest.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the case closes, Russell leaves for the Cyber team while Catherine returns to Las Vegas and Sara gets the Director&amp;rsquo;s position. Grissom heads back out to the ocean and Heather is free to go. Before she does, Grissom thanks Heather for opening his heart so he could love.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As Sara leaves for San Diego, she leaves her director&amp;rsquo;s badge for Catherine. In the end, she chooses Grissom.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;End of Series&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;sara-sidle-review:d7ca8c350c2b49405d241256b9943625&#34;&gt;Sara Sidle Review&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sara is anything but happy to see Heather, and blows up at Grissom. She keeps it together until the interrogation, and has to leave then. Catherine calls her out on still being in love with Grissom, but admits she herself would like to kill Heather too. Heather asks Sara if she loves Grissom, and Sara admits she still does.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While still smarting over Heather, Sara apologizes to Grissom and asks if they can be friends, to which he agrees. They work on the bees together, just like old times.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the end, Sara gets the position she wants but refuses to say goodbye to Grissom. They&amp;rsquo;re two ships passing in the night. When Grissom thanks Heather, he says his heart belongs to one woman, meaning Sara, she hears all but the end. Meaning she doesn&amp;rsquo;t know that until she reads the transcript of Heather&amp;rsquo;s final interview with Grissom.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And she gives it all up for Grissom, sailing off into the ocean with him.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;character-notes:d7ca8c350c2b49405d241256b9943625&#34;&gt;Character Notes##&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sara is promoted to Lab Director (the role Grissom had in season one)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sara chooses Grissom in the end.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;quotes:d7ca8c350c2b49405d241256b9943625&#34;&gt;Quotes&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sara Sidle&lt;/strong&gt; Lady Heather, as much as I&amp;rsquo;d like to roll out the voluntary red carpet and welcome you here to your own bombing party, I can&amp;rsquo;t find it in my bone marrow to overrule my gut. But I&amp;rsquo;m sure you&amp;rsquo;re having a blast with the blasts, so I&amp;rsquo;ll just ask the question&amp;hellip; are you the one behind the bombings?&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Lady Heather&lt;/strong&gt; Your hostility connotes jealousy and resentment. It doesn&amp;rsquo;t suit&lt;br /&gt;
you, Sara.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Sara Sidle&lt;/strong&gt; Mrs. Sidle to you.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Lady Heather&lt;/strong&gt; Ms. Sidle, isn&amp;rsquo;t it?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lady Heather&lt;/strong&gt; Do you love him?&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Sara Sidle&lt;/strong&gt; I do.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The End Game</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/the-end-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/the-end-game/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;George Eads&amp;rsquo; final episode*&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;synopsis:03701490ea43aa3ee32b3e79dca173de&#34;&gt;Synopsis##&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The CSI unit faces the final showdown with the Gig Harbor killer whose motives are finally revealed. Also, Nick makes a decision that will affect the entire team moving forward.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With Nick being courted by San Diego to lead up their lab, Finn gets a package from her mother that is actually from Paul Winthrop, the Gig Harbor Killer, last seen limping away from the fatal shooting of his brother, Jared Briscoe  can help. Larson, who did provide women for the boys, had nothing to do with the killings, and suspects Collin Winthrop, Paul&amp;rsquo;s father, as the third partner to the killings.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;David Hodges traces the ink in Winthrop&amp;rsquo;s severed finger to a specific tattoo artist in Vegas. Winthrop has taken on the tattoos of his brother in order to become both of them. On the trail of Collin, Nick goes down to San Diego where they find him and Paul Winthrop&amp;rsquo;s new base of operations. When Winthrop spots them, he kills his father and Shaw, who jumps between Finn and a bullet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Brother Larson also talked to Collin Winthrop shortly before he died, contrary to what he claimed when questioned by Finn. Larson was also the father of the brothers. Mae was Collin&amp;rsquo;s daughter and mother of the killers. She was also Sister Alice, the woman at the convent where the boys where born. Alice is on the run, however, and Winthrop attacks Finn, locking her in the trunk of a car with plans to dump her in the desert. D.B. Russell interrupts him, coming to pick up Finn and take her to Seattle to find Alice.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Winthrop is shot when the police burst in and Finn is left in critical condition. Finn remains in a coma as the episode ends while Winthrop will recover and pay for his crimes. Nick takes the job in San Diego.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;sara-sidle-review:03701490ea43aa3ee32b3e79dca173de&#34;&gt;Sara Sidle Review&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nick asks Sara if he should take the job in San Diego.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While Nick is in San Diego, Sara is left in charge of the lab as DB and Finn are headed to Seattle. She proves herself more than capable, reading the situation and sending out the CSIs to the right places at the right time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;quotes:03701490ea43aa3ee32b3e79dca173de&#34;&gt;Quotes&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Stokes:&lt;/strong&gt; You know, Sara, after all these years, I&amp;rsquo;ve finally learned what&amp;rsquo;s important to me, and it&amp;rsquo;s not a promotion.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Sidle:&lt;/strong&gt; Well. You know what Grissom would say. You gotta go where you can do the most good.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Under My Skin</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/under-my-skin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/under-my-skin/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;synopsis:ae64acb46450138a39128eee3f448f56&#34;&gt;Synopsis##&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The CSI team investigates a murder with ties to two teenaged kidnapped girls.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cara and Lexi Nolan are in Vegas with their dad&amp;rsquo;s credit card. When Pete Corday (aged 23), a young man who went off with the younger sister, Cara (aged 13), turns up dead, the hunt is on for the girls, who happen to the the daughters of John Nolan, director for the crime lab in San Diego. Lexi (aged 17) had ditched her sister to hook up with a sex trafficker named Axel Vargas (aged 25).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lexi is found dead in a dumpster, still in Vegas, killed from a rare scorpion sting which, when combined with the video she took on her phone, is tracked back to Kieran Clark. Clark had been stalking a woman who looked incredibly like Cara. Clark kidnapped her because she looked just like the woman he obsessed over.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;sara-sidle-review:ae64acb46450138a39128eee3f448f56&#34;&gt;Sara Sidle Review&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sara doesn&amp;rsquo;t appreciate people who abuse women in any way. She&amp;rsquo;s aggressive towards Axel but kinder to Tori when explaining the graphic photos found on Lexi&amp;rsquo;s phone.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;character-notes:ae64acb46450138a39128eee3f448f56&#34;&gt;Character Notes##&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Parents fighting make Sara uncomfortable&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Last Ride</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/the-last-ride/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/the-last-ride/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;synopsis:4d97a7272d61d3c5a528929d1710fe0b&#34;&gt;Synopsis##&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A woman, Eva Montrose, is found dead of asphyxiation from being painted solid silver and swallowing it. The paint used was special, eco-friendly, car chrome paint. Based on the bruise pattern on her back and the shards of headlamp in her arm, the CSIs track down a classic Packard car and it&amp;rsquo;s owner&amp;hellip; Eva&amp;rsquo;s ex-boyfriend, Carlo Derosa.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sara and Finn talk to Carlo and his brother, Aron, who own a collection of classic cars, including the Packard. They find evidence that Eva was killed there, but a classic Cadillac is missing, used to transport her body. The Caddy was also the car where their father, Vegas legend Alfonso Derosa, was murdered, and it&amp;rsquo;s worth around $1 million.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The find the car in a storage unit rented by Eva, along with Aron who tracked the car down. The brothers blame each other for the murder but it&amp;rsquo;s Eva&amp;rsquo;s mother, Ruth, who is a suspect. She was attempting to buy the Caddy from Carlo for a man from Dubai, while Aron refused to sell, so she asked Eva to help her steal it. Except Ruth&amp;rsquo;s boyfriend, Duncan Ridell, is the son of the man who killed Alfonso and was, oddly enough, not her buyer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But the killer was the car appraiser, Ken Bixler, who was also the real killer of Alfonso. He was there to kill Vera, Alfonso&amp;rsquo;s mistress and Ken&amp;rsquo;s fiancée. Eva asked Ken to help her steal the car, knowing him from her drug days, and Ken stole the headrest to cover his murder of Vera and Alfonso. Eva stumbled on him and he killed her.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;sara-sidle-review:4d97a7272d61d3c5a528929d1710fe0b&#34;&gt;Sara Sidle Review##&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sara gives the death notification to Eva&amp;rsquo;s parents and goes with Finn to find the cars. When Carlo&amp;rsquo;s a bit of a dick and tries to ignore them, she bumps his expensive car and sets off the alarm.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;character-notes:4d97a7272d61d3c5a528929d1710fe0b&#34;&gt;Character Notes##&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sara hates when people lie to her&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;quotes:4d97a7272d61d3c5a528929d1710fe0b&#34;&gt;Quotes##&lt;/h2&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hero to Zero</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/hero-to-zero/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/hero-to-zero/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;synopsis:7988bbb62b4e417d2d8d29befdd313c7&#34;&gt;Synopsis##&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A homeless man is harassed by some masked street thugs, only to be saved by a young man dressed as a superhero. Sara and Nick find the hero, beaten to death, but are able to identify the barefoot homeless man when he returns to try and get his cart, and learn that the assailants drove off in a red truck.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While looking for more evidence, Morgan Brody and Greg stumble across two more heroes. They ID the dead man as &amp;lsquo;Dominion&amp;rsquo; (aka Brad Jeffries). Their number one suspect, Tony Agraro, had tangled with the three heroes before, but is found dead, and one of the heroes is the suspect. He&amp;rsquo;s innocent, but the homeless man, Roger, is found with Brad&amp;rsquo;s custom bat, claiming to be &amp;lsquo;the real Batman.&amp;rsquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The killer turns out to be Seth, Brad&amp;rsquo;s stepfather.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;sara-sidle-review:7988bbb62b4e417d2d8d29befdd313c7&#34;&gt;Sara Sidle Review##&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sara makes sure the homeless man, Roger, is fed and clothed back at the station before talking to him.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;character-notes:7988bbb62b4e417d2d8d29befdd313c7&#34;&gt;Character Notes##&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sara&amp;rsquo;s escape as a child was science and math.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;quotes:7988bbb62b4e417d2d8d29befdd313c7&#34;&gt;Quotes&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sidle:&lt;/strong&gt; I guess I just don&amp;rsquo;t get it. You know, my childhood &amp;hellip; the fantasy was never my escape. I lost myself in science and numbers. It&amp;rsquo;s all I needed, I guess.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Russell:&lt;/strong&gt; Well you liked things that were clear or proven. Right or wrong. Black or white.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Sidle:&lt;/strong&gt; Maybe.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Merchants of Menace</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/merchants-of-menace/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/merchants-of-menace/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;synopsis:7db4e9a654f3334a409ba36da5d0c6f9&#34;&gt;Synopsis##&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The CSI team investigates a homicide at a convention for people who collect macabre murder memorabilia. Morgan Brody and D.B. Russell are first on the scene to investigate a man found dead in the car at his own own convention. Damon Harlow, a student of the psychology of serial killers, was dating the sister of a victim of the killer whose car he was found dead in.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Damon was found dead in the car of Lucas Reem, the killer who&amp;rsquo;d killed Nora Water&amp;rsquo;s sister, stabbed to death by a bone from Lucas, sharpened into a blade. Bruce Waters, Nora&amp;rsquo;s father, was killed by the same man who killed Damon. The killer was wearing Lucas Reem&amp;rsquo;s fringed leather jacket for both crimes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It turns out one of the young kids at the convention was the killer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;sara-sidle-review:7db4e9a654f3334a409ba36da5d0c6f9&#34;&gt;Sara Sidle Review&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sara interviews Nora Waters and goes with Nick to try and catch Bruce Waters before he&amp;rsquo;s able to buy Lucas Reems&amp;rsquo; bones.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;character-notes:7db4e9a654f3334a409ba36da5d0c6f9&#34;&gt;Character Notes##&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;One of the models from the Miniature Crime Scene killer is used by Nick to gain entry in a memorabilia back alley meeting.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Greater Good</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/the-greater-good/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/the-greater-good/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;synopsis:5050a07062978e06196218d782d3dc5e&#34;&gt;Synopsis&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Russell&amp;rsquo;s daughter, Maya (the mother of Kaitlyn who was once kidnapped&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hodges finds out that Rebecca was not just a kidnapped victim turned Stockholm, but the maker of the fake evidence strings the Gig Harbor boys used. In addition, she ran an escort service, from which the killers selected their victims. He and Morgan discover the bodies of the missing girls and Shaw&amp;rsquo;s prints.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Shaw, working with the brothers, picks up Maya at the Russell house, but doesn&amp;rsquo;t know Maya&amp;rsquo;s wearing a wire. Maya had agreed to play bait. He plays the CSIs and absconds with Maya. Shaw turns out to be blackmailed by the Gig Harbor Brothers. He&amp;rsquo;d had a daughter (Amy) with Rebecca Lowell&amp;rsquo;s sister, an escort, and Winthrope kidnapped her.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Shaw double crosses the brothers and kills Brisco, saving Maya and his daughter, but Winthrope was smarter and shoots him. As he&amp;rsquo;s about to kill Shaw, Maya stabs Winthrope with a crowbar, brutally wounding him. But she doesn&amp;rsquo;t kill him and Winthrope escapes. Shaw is arrested for his crimes, his daughter moving to live with her grandmother.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;sara-sidle-review:5050a07062978e06196218d782d3dc5e&#34;&gt;Sara Sidle Review##&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sara is a little aghast at DB using his own daughter for bait.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;character-notes:5050a07062978e06196218d782d3dc5e&#34;&gt;Character Notes##&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;quotes:5050a07062978e06196218d782d3dc5e&#34;&gt;Quotes&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sara Sidle&lt;/strong&gt; You came close, DB. The greater good. Brisco&amp;rsquo;s dead and Winthrope&amp;rsquo;s on the run, a fugitive. You can plaster his face everywhere. Freeze his accounts. You&amp;rsquo;re in the driver&amp;rsquo;s seat.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;DB Russell&lt;/strong&gt; Then why doesn&amp;rsquo;t it feel like that?&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dead Woods</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/dead-woods/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/dead-woods/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;synopsis:499e4832cce5e2bb2f8a3f4a096089fd&#34;&gt;Synopsis&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Abby Fisher, the sole survivor of a mass murder when her father, Barry. killed the family on a camping trip, is involved in a robbery gone bad with her bad-boy-boyfriend, Slade. While &lt;strong&gt;Sara&lt;/strong&gt;, who worked the case a decade ago, is upset (she hates Slade), she&amp;rsquo;s stunned to learn that Abby now remembers details about the case. Abby remembers that someone picked her up and put her in the sleeping bag, not knowing she was still alive, but the man had a beard and a smell that was not her father&amp;rsquo;s.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An autopsy and blood test of the exhumed body of the father shows he&amp;rsquo;d been drugged with a knockout drug. It&amp;rsquo;s enough to reopen the case, and fingerprints belonging to registered sex offender Garth Fogel are found in the tent. Fogel&amp;rsquo;s also the biological father of Hannah, Abby&amp;rsquo;s older sister. Cathy, the mom, had told everyone that Hannah&amp;rsquo;s father died in a car accident.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fogel claims innocence. He found in about Hannah while in prison and looked them up. He saw them packing to go camping and he talked to Cathy about letting him see Hannah, but she told him to go to hell. He touched the sleeping bags then, but did not hurt anyone.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Abby IDs a hunter, Donald Wraith, as the man who shot her parents, but when the CSIs go to arrest him, Donald is dead. Shot in the head the same way the Fishers had been. Randy Pruitt, president of Wraith&amp;rsquo;s hunting club, had killed him, and his prints match the unknowns found in the Fishers&amp;rsquo; tent. Randy and Donald wanted to rape the wife, so the drugged the husband but she fought back and Donald killed her. He and Randy had done this before.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;sara-sidle-review:499e4832cce5e2bb2f8a3f4a096089fd&#34;&gt;Sara Sidle Review##&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sara does not initially believe Abby, but after looking at the evidence, starts digging into the case. This ruffles a lot of feather, including Doc Robbins and Ecklie.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;character-notes:499e4832cce5e2bb2f8a3f4a096089fd&#34;&gt;Character Notes##&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sara has kept in touch with Abby, enough to know she&amp;rsquo;s still in foster care and who Slade is.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sara empathizes with Abby, sharing the pain of a family member murdering another.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sara talks about her past with Greg, the first time she&amp;rsquo;s told anyone besides Grissom.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sara was not allowed to attend her father&amp;rsquo;s funeral.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sara admits to missing her father.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;quotes:499e4832cce5e2bb2f8a3f4a096089fd&#34;&gt;Quotes&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sanders:&lt;/strong&gt; We&amp;rsquo;ve worked a lot of cases where kids lost their parents.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Sidle:&lt;/strong&gt; Yeah. But one parent killing another, getting shipped off to foster care. Something I know a little bit about.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Sanders:&lt;/strong&gt; In all the years we&amp;rsquo;ve been friends, you&amp;rsquo;ve never really talked about what happened with your dad. And I don&amp;rsquo;t mean to pry, but&amp;ndash;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Sidle:&lt;/strong&gt; You know what happened. They had a &amp;hellip; volatile relationship. And&amp;hellip; &lt;em&gt;[Sara&amp;rsquo;s phone rings, ending the conversation]&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Pruit&lt;/strong&gt; We hunt animals. Not human beings.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Sidle:&lt;/strong&gt; Yeah? Well &amp;hellip; Some people can&amp;rsquo;t tell the difference.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sidle:&lt;/strong&gt; Oh. 1D&amp;rsquo;s playing at the Hard Rock tomorrow night.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Abby Fisher&lt;/strong&gt; One Direction? Are you kidding?&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Sidle:&lt;/strong&gt; Nah, it&amp;rsquo;s Lourde. I&amp;rsquo;ll pick you up at seven.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sanders:&lt;/strong&gt; You look like your dad.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Sidle:&lt;/strong&gt; He used to read to me when I was a kid. &lt;em&gt;Charlotte&amp;rsquo;s Web&lt;/em&gt;, my favorite. Must have read it a hundred times.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Sanders:&lt;/strong&gt; It&amp;rsquo;s a nice memory.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Sidle:&lt;/strong&gt; I have a lot of nice memories of him. My mom too. They were toxic when they were together, though.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Sanders:&lt;/strong&gt; Your mom said your dad was abusive? Kill him in self defense?&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Sidle:&lt;/strong&gt; That&amp;rsquo;s what she said.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Sanders:&lt;/strong&gt; You don&amp;rsquo;t believe her?&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Sidle:&lt;/strong&gt; Look, I know my dad wasn&amp;rsquo;t a saint, but my mom was an alcoholic who suffered from mental illness. I&amp;rsquo;m just not sure that things were as black and white as she made them out to be.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Sanders:&lt;/strong&gt; You did say they had a volatile relationship.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Sidle:&lt;/strong&gt; Yeah. The fact is, I&amp;rsquo;ll never know what happened that night. This is gonna sound horrible, but I&amp;rsquo;m kinda jealous of Abby. She gets to rewrite her whole family history. Nothing will ever change what my mother did.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Sanders:&lt;/strong&gt; Well&amp;hellip; You can&amp;rsquo;t change the past. But you always have the future. Your mom&amp;rsquo;s still alive. It&amp;rsquo;s not too late for you to start over.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Sidle:&lt;/strong&gt; I don&amp;rsquo;t know if I could.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Angle of Attack</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/angle-of-attack/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/angle-of-attack/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;synopsis:db52268f4fed9845ce5e9c90191576b1&#34;&gt;Synopsis##&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A &amp;lsquo;hit and run&amp;rsquo; is found on the streets of Vegas, but curiously matches none of the markers one would expect. The case only gets odder when they determine the man fell from a building blocks away, being thrown through glass thick enough to take a bullet. At first the lab suspects a missile, but they determine it&amp;rsquo;s a Squirrel Suit and manage to ID the deceased: Captain Robert Holland, Air Force.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Capt. Holland had taken an experimental suit without full permission from the R&amp;amp;D lab: TRD. Unbeknownst to him the suit had been tampered with so the emergency parachute would never fire. One of the TRD workers, another pilot, dies in the middle of an interrogation of a cerebral edema.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Holland was having an affair with his CO, who killed him to cover up their homosexual relationship. He killed the other pilot because he thought Holland told him.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;sara-sidle-review:db52268f4fed9845ce5e9c90191576b1&#34;&gt;Sara Sidle Review&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sara talks to Morgan about her initial theory involving a Columbian cartel.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dead Rails</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/dead-rails/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/dead-rails/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;synopsis:78545c7ab432fbf13eb2176502ad3f46&#34;&gt;Synopsis##&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After digging his way out of a shallow grave, Jimmy Turelli stumbled out of the desert and to a road, only to be hit by a speeding car and killed. The trace evidence puts him as a billiards player, likely a member of a tournament run by Elise Massey (special guest Sharon Osbourne), but instead he paid for the entry of a player named &amp;lsquo;The Hornet&amp;rsquo; for Elise Massey (who neglected to mention this before). Cal Tate, a hustler at The Rails, had been in an argument with Jimmy, and his wife Zoe pinned Jimmy&amp;rsquo;s murder on Cal. Of course, Cal&amp;rsquo;s found dead, shot in the head at home.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They manage to match DNA at the scene to the most unlikely suspect, Mary Haymond. Mary was the driver of the car that hit and killed Jimmy on the road. Mary had been working with Zoe and her blackmail scam on hustlers. When Mary tried to bring Jimmy in on the deal, he balked and she killed him. Twice.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;sara-sidle-review:78545c7ab432fbf13eb2176502ad3f46&#34;&gt;Sara Sidle Review&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sara goes with Morgan Brody to the after hours club &amp;lsquo;The Rails&amp;rsquo; and find blood and snakeskin matching that which was found on the scene.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;character-notes:78545c7ab432fbf13eb2176502ad3f46&#34;&gt;Character Notes&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sara learns not to play pool with Morgan.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;quotes:78545c7ab432fbf13eb2176502ad3f46&#34;&gt;Quotes&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sidle:&lt;/strong&gt; Same with this glass.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Brody&lt;/strong&gt; Confirms the Hornet&amp;rsquo;s trick shot.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Sidle:&lt;/strong&gt; Somebody used it for a different sort of trick.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Brody&lt;/strong&gt; You ready for another weird?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;sidle-it-s-what-keeps-me-coming-back:78545c7ab432fbf13eb2176502ad3f46&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sidle:&lt;/strong&gt; It&amp;rsquo;s what keeps me coming back.&lt;/h2&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Let&#39;s Make A Deal</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/lets-make-a-deal/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/lets-make-a-deal/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;synopsis:c17f229bd0527ca8c07da6696e0f99fc&#34;&gt;Synopsis##&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The CSIs investigate a murder at the Clark County jail after an inmate stumbles upon a body while running away from officers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;sara-sidle-review:c17f229bd0527ca8c07da6696e0f99fc&#34;&gt;Sara Sidle Review##&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sara Sidle&lt;/strong&gt; does not appear in this episode.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rubbery Homicide</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/rubbery-homicide/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/rubbery-homicide/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;synopsis:c74c3467e3ad79ebe49da87d8f75d794&#34;&gt;Synopsis##&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A man, Nelson Kern, is found stripped to his boxers in an alley, having been slashed to death. But with so little blood on his person, the scene is very odd. It gets odder when they find a life sized rubber outfit in the dumpster. An outfit that fits Mr. Kern.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The outfit is based on a model from the 80s named Charlene, which is the same name Kern used when dressed up. Charlene died of an aneurysm years ago.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Kern wasn&amp;rsquo;t Charlene, however. He was a rival vulcanized vixen, Lexie, who broken into the home of the &lt;em&gt;real&lt;/em&gt; Charlene&amp;rsquo;s widower, Stan, to steal the outfit and the doll. But Stan didn&amp;rsquo;t kill Kern. His daughter, April, did, in order to protect the image of her father, mother, and the company they created.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;sara-sidle-review:c74c3467e3ad79ebe49da87d8f75d794&#34;&gt;Sara Sidle Review##&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sara works the case, however there is little notable this episode. She&amp;rsquo;s quick to come up with a slightly out-there theory again (like she did with spontaneous human combustion).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;character-notes:c74c3467e3ad79ebe49da87d8f75d794&#34;&gt;Character Notes&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sara is quick to theorize about a rape gone wrong, identifying with the theoretical woman.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;quotes:c74c3467e3ad79ebe49da87d8f75d794&#34;&gt;Quotes##&lt;/h2&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Road To Recovery</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/road-to-recovery/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/road-to-recovery/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;synopsis:38dc8e636a07a9c872d42ed5bf2ac488&#34;&gt;Synopsis##&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The CSI team investigates the death of a woman full of alcohol and drugs in a pool at a rehab facility&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;sara-sidle-review:38dc8e636a07a9c872d42ed5bf2ac488&#34;&gt;Sara Sidle Review##&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sara Sidle&lt;/strong&gt; does not appear in this episode.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Twin Paradox</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/the-twin-paradox/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/the-twin-paradox/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;synopsis:5fd0411d87a0b9a1f8b04e67f1731d71&#34;&gt;Synopsis##&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Gig Harbor Killer is back. Twin brothers Jared Brisco (the confessed killer) and Paul Winthrope (the free lawyer) both argue that Jared is innocent.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This time he calls 911 before he murders a woman, and like before, stages the crime scene. Sara and Nick are first on the scene and collect the evidence. Since D.B. Russell believes the initial killing was done by the brothers together, they now feel than the one un-jailed brother has a new partner. Working with DB, Sara suspects Jared&amp;rsquo;s apparent insanity is not an act. After his time in foster care, Jared was susceptible to a stronger influence, especially one that reflected himself: i.e. his twin brother.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Up in Seattle, Finn works with a local PI (and ex-boyfriend) and investigate Jared and Paul&amp;rsquo;s birth, subsequent abandonment at a church, and adoption. While Jared was adopted, Paul is listed as dying shortly after birth. The infant body at the church turns out to be a doll with a photo of the possible mother tucked inside, and a hair.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They&amp;rsquo;re able to find the Gig Harbor Killer&amp;rsquo;s lair, but at the cost of the life of his latest victim. When rescued, she attacks Greg and hits him with a pipe, taking his gun. Finn is forced to shoot and kill her to protect him. It turns out that the woman was a post-surgery transgendered man who was used by the Gig Harbor Killer, however the city exonerates Finn for killing what appears to be the Gig Harbor Killer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;sara-sidle-review:5fd0411d87a0b9a1f8b04e67f1731d71&#34;&gt;Sara Sidle Review##&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Listening to the audio, Sara is able to identify two people walking, implying the killer has a partner. When Sara and DB listen to interviews with Jared Brisco, and he says how after foster care how could he be anything &lt;em&gt;but&lt;/em&gt; a serial killer, Sara is pained.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;character-notes:5fd0411d87a0b9a1f8b04e67f1731d71&#34;&gt;Character Notes##&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sara is understanding of people in foster care.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sara checks on Greg after he&amp;rsquo;s injured on the scene.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;quotes:5fd0411d87a0b9a1f8b04e67f1731d71&#34;&gt;Quotes&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Stokes:&lt;/strong&gt; reading &amp;lsquo;People Lie, Follow the Evidence&amp;rsquo;?&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Sidle:&lt;/strong&gt; We&amp;rsquo;re really good at that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sidle:&lt;/strong&gt; You did the best you could. You need to know that. In time, you will know that. As for how you live with what happened, I wish I knew the answer to that.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>