<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Human Rights on Fans of Le Fox Library</title>
    <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/tags/human-rights/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Human Rights on Fans of Le Fox Library</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 05 Dec 2004 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://jorjafox.net/library/tags/human-rights/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Huckleberry Fund Benefit</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2004/huckleberry-fund-benefit/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Dec 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2004/huckleberry-fund-benefit/</guid>
      <description>&amp;rdquo;&amp;lsquo;Jorja Fox:&amp;ldquo;&amp;rsquo; Um, the Huckleberry Fund is an amazing organization, they help a lot of teenagers in the Los Angeles area. It&amp;rsquo;s a very, uh, it&amp;rsquo;s a group that gets overlooked a lot and obviously a group with a lot of special needs, very specific needs, um, taking care of medical as well as psychological, developmental stuff. Um, I&amp;rsquo;m lucky enough to have a photograph inside, it&amp;rsquo;s one of my favorite things to get to do, it&amp;rsquo;s my second time doing it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Have a Dream Foundation</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/i-have-a-dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/i-have-a-dream/</guid>
      <description>The &amp;ldquo;I Have a Dream&amp;rdquo; Program helps children from low-income areas reach their education and career goals by providing a long-term program of mentoring, tutoring, and enrichment with an assured opportunity for higher education.
Jorja Fox attended their 6th annual brunch on 18 January 2004.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Five Acres</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/five-acres/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/five-acres/</guid>
      <description>Five Acres has served vulnerable children and families since 1888. They provide family-centered support services on campus and through outreach programs in homes, at schools and in off-site offices.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Huckleberry Foundation</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/huckleberry/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/huckleberry/</guid>
      <description>The Huckleberry Foundation is named after Huckleberry Finn, an 11-year-old who ran away from home to escape the abuse of his alcoholic father.
This Foundation supports the youth programs of the Division of Adolescent Medicine, Childrens&amp;rsquo; Hospital Los Angeles, which reach out to the &amp;lsquo;Huckleberry Finns&amp;rsquo; of today. For 20 years, the Division has led the way in providing integrated medical and psychological services to disadvantaged and disconnected youth of Los Angeles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Penny Lane</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/penny-lane/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/penny-lane/</guid>
      <description>Penny Lane Org cares for over 1,500 abused, neglect and abandoned children each year in the Los Angeles area and Antelope Valley, and Jorja For is one of the number one supporters.
Voices of Our Children They have an annual celebrity fund raiser called Voices of Our Children, which entails celebrities reading what those beautiful children have written about their life experiences. Jorja is one of the emotional and powerful celebrities who reads and has helped them now for several years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Friends of El Faro</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/el-faro/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/el-faro/</guid>
      <description>Friends of El Faro has a simple mission &amp;#8212; to help improve the lives of the orphans at El Faro (in Mexico) in any way possible. El Faro 2 (The Lighthouse) was founded in the 1990, when Carmen and Jorge Gonzales opened the doors of their home to a few abandoned children living on the streets. Word spread and in a very short amount of time children were being dropped off in the middle of the night by relatives who could not care for them, or were frightened because of a history of abuse.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Campaign for Burma</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/us-campaign-for-burma/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/us-campaign-for-burma/</guid>
      <description>30 Hollywood celebrities ran a campaign from May 1 through May 30 to seek the release of Myanmar&amp;rsquo;s democracy icon Aung San Suu Kyi and push for freedom in the military-ruled nation.
The 30-day campaign will see stars such as Will Ferrell, Ellen Page, Judd Apatow, Anjelica Huston, Jennifer Aniston and Rosanna Arquette appearing in video clips on the Internet highlighting human rights issues in Myanmar.
Jorja filmed a video with Eric Szmanda which aired on May 11th (day 11).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Until the Violence Stops: Los Angeles</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/until-violence-stops/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/until-violence-stops/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Until the Violence Stops: Los Angeles&amp;rdquo; (aka UTVS:LA) is the LA organization who organizes and promotes V-Day. A coalition of activists, artists, entertainers, educators, civic leaders and concerned citizens who reside in Los Angeles County, UTVS:LA wants to see Los Angeles become the safest city on earth for women and girls.
 V-Day is a global movement to stop violence against women and girls. V-Day is a catalyst that promotes creative events to increase awareness, raise money and revitalize the spirit of existing anti-violence organizations.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>