<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Er on Fans of Le Fox Library</title>
    <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/categories/er/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Er on Fans of Le Fox Library</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://jorjafox.net/library/categories/er/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>ER</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/actor/er/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/actor/er/</guid>
      <description>Character Dr. Maggie Doyle arrived from a hospital that had been closed. A wonderful dichotomy, Doyle was a gun-toting, lesbian vegetarian. She was good friends with John Carter, and had enough attitude for everyone.
Doyle slogged through a fairly nasty piece of litigation, when surgeon Dr. Robert &amp;lsquo;Rocket&amp;rsquo; Romano blasted her on her evaluation when she threatened to tell about his harassment of her. While Doyle filed the report, the plot fell by the wayside, and Romano became the Chief of Emergency Medicine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>List of ER episodes</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/actor/er-episodes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/actor/er-episodes/</guid>
      <description>The following is a list of episodes from the CBS television series, &amp;ldquo;ER&amp;rdquo; in which Jorja Fox appeared or was credited. Episodes are rated based on quality and volume of Jorja&amp;rsquo;s scenes. Episodes in which she is listed in the credits but does not appear are rated with zero stars.
Jorja appeared as a regular guest in seasons three, four and five. In season 15, the final season of ER, her character&amp;rsquo;s nameplate can be seen in two episodes, on the wall of doctors who have left the ER.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>