<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Politics on Fans of Le Fox Library</title>
    <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/tags/politics/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Politics on Fans of Le Fox Library</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://jorjafox.net/library/tags/politics/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Artists &amp; Athletes Alliance</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/artists-athletes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/artists-athletes/</guid>
      <description>The &amp;lsquo;Artists and Athletes Alliance&amp;rsquo; assists artists and athletes in navigating the halls of government, as well as helping them better understand the political process. By providing top-line educational information to artists and athletes through one-on-one meetings, private briefings, roundtable discussions, forums and other related events on the specific public policies and political issues of interest to them, the Alliance hopes to engage in productive dialogue with lawmakers, policymakers and opinion-leaders so the voices of the artistic and athletic community can be heard on the many important issues facing our nation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Campaign for Burma</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/us-campaign-for-burma/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/us-campaign-for-burma/</guid>
      <description>30 Hollywood celebrities ran a campaign from May 1 through May 30 to seek the release of Myanmar&amp;rsquo;s democracy icon Aung San Suu Kyi and push for freedom in the military-ruled nation.
The 30-day campaign will see stars such as Will Ferrell, Ellen Page, Judd Apatow, Anjelica Huston, Jennifer Aniston and Rosanna Arquette appearing in video clips on the Internet highlighting human rights issues in Myanmar.
Jorja filmed a video with Eric Szmanda which aired on May 11th (day 11).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>