<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>2002 on Fans of Le Fox Library</title>
    <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/tags/2002/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 2002 on Fans of Le Fox Library</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2002 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://jorjafox.net/library/tags/2002/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Guide</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2002/tv-guide-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2002/tv-guide-5/</guid>
      <description>Showbiz Buzz + Celebrity Scoop
Jorja Fox loves playing Sara Sidle, the lab rat on CBS&amp;rsquo;s CSI: Crime Scene Investigation. &amp;ldquo;She&amp;rsquo;s brave, smart, obsessed with doing the right thing. I aspire to be this person,&amp;rdquo; Fox says. &amp;ldquo;Being a little less squeamish would be a good thing.&amp;rdquo; That won&amp;rsquo;t be easy. Some story lines are so &amp;ldquo;psycholigically horrifying,&amp;rdquo; Fox has nightmares if she reads scripts before going to bed. &amp;ldquo;I keep thinking they [bad dreams] are going away!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About.com</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2002/about-com/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2002/about-com/</guid>
      <description>Are you surprised at the popularity of the show and the amount of young people who are going to college now to learn more about forensics?
JORJA FOX: I&amp;rsquo;m enormously surprised at the success of ?C.S.I.? I think that even in all of our wildest dreams that we could have imagined as great a run as we are having and I&amp;rsquo;m just thrilled about it. I feel blessed every day. I&amp;rsquo;m also surprised that, yes, there seems to be an increase in kids wanting to study forensics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ET Online</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2002/et-online-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2002/et-online-2/</guid>
      <description>A permanent disappearance during a magic trick means it&amp;rsquo;s time to call in the &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; crew. Inhuman blood droplets and the discovery of a razor sharp knife just magnify the mystery for investigators. And as star JORJA FOX told ET, tonight&amp;rsquo;s episode on CBS is so realistic that it frightened her. Meanwhile, over at &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rsquo;s&amp;rdquo; sister show, &amp;ldquo;CSI: Miami,&amp;rdquo; a decision has been made regarding an episode that features a sniper.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Guide</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2002/tv-guide-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2002/tv-guide-4/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
Question: I am a huge CSI fan. I was wondering if you have heard anything about if the show is going to put Grissom (William Petersen) and Sara (Jorja Fox) together? You can see that they&amp;rsquo;re attracted to each other! Do you think that Grissom and Sara should date despite their age difference? ? Karen
Matt: I think dating would be a huge mistake for CSI, but not because I&amp;rsquo;m an ageist or anything.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ET Online</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2002/et-online-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2002/et-online-1/</guid>
      <description>Not since &amp;#8216;The Wizard of Oz&amp;rsquo; have so many little people gathered together for a production, but this week&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; earns that distinction when the team investigates the death of one of the members attending the International Organization of Little People&amp;rsquo;s convention in Las Vegas.
&amp;ldquo;There are two storylines,&amp;rdquo; JORJA FOX tells ET about tonight&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;A Little Murder&amp;rdquo; episode of &amp;ldquo;CSI.&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;One of the them is very touching and affects Catherine Willows (MARG HELGENBERGER) and Warrick Brown (GARY DOURDAN).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Gal</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2002/tv-gal-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2002/tv-gal-3/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
I know the big thing about &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; (Thursday, CBS, 9 p.m.) is that we don&amp;rsquo;t know much about the personal life of the characters, but I do love the subtle tension that is building between Grissom and Sara. He&amp;rsquo;s obviously fighting his attraction to her and she&amp;rsquo;s obviously angry about his announcement that she needs to get a life. The really amazing thing is how much more vibrant and interesting the characters on &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; are versus the characters on &amp;ldquo;CSI: Miami.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>People</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2002/people-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2002/people-2/</guid>
      <description>As crime-solving wizards on TV&amp;rsquo;s top-rated drama, the stars of CSI steep themselves in blood, bullet holes and (very) gross anatomy.
This past summer the cast of CSI: Crime Scene Investigation did what you&amp;rsquo;d expect anyone from a major hit series to do. They kicked back and forgot about the inanimate parade of bruised, gouged, mutilated and (on one memorable occasion) liquefied corpses that form the dramatic center of the CBS show&amp;rsquo;s high-tech forensic sleuthing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mantra Online</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2002/mantra-online/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2002/mantra-online/</guid>
      <description>Actress Jorja Fox poses as she arrives at the Macy&amp;rsquo;s and American Express Passport 20&amp;frasl;02 20th anniversary HIV/AIDS fundraiser in Santa Monica, California, September 28, 2002. The annual event features a celebrity auction and fashion show.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>People</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2002/people-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2002/people-1/</guid>
      <description>Someone must have forgotten to tell CSI: Crime Scene Investigation&amp;rsquo;s Jorja Fox that it&amp;rsquo;s still summer: The actress (whose show is an Emmy contender for outstanding drama series) opts to pair her spaghetti-strapped dress with calf-high leather boots.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Post Dispatch</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2002/post-dispatch/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2002/post-dispatch/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
CSI: Crime Scene Investigation CBS
Last season ended with the revelation that Grissom (William Petersen) is losing his hearing. But producers say we shouldn&amp;rsquo;t expect his condition to dominate the season; instead, look for Sara (Jorja Fox) to strike up a romance with the cute guy she met last season who didn&amp;rsquo;t mind her smell.
[&amp;hellip;]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Extra TV</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2002/extra-tv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2002/extra-tv/</guid>
      <description>Those crafty crime scene investigators of &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; are back on the case for another season of murder and mayhem, shifting into high gear for the third season of CBS? runaway hit. And only &amp;ldquo;Extra&amp;rdquo; was on location in Las Vegas with the ratings grabbing gumshoes as they shot an upcoming episode with a crime ripped from the headlines.
Star William Petersen and his team of criminalists are called in to investigate a young movie star accused of murder.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>In Style Magazine</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2002/in-style-magazine-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2002/in-style-magazine-2/</guid>
      <description>She&amp;rsquo;s a dressed-down, seriously smart cookie in &amp;#8216;CSI: Crime Scene Invesigation&amp;rsquo;, but off-screen, Jorja Fox loves to get glammed-up for big nights out in Hollywood.
Brains and beauty can mix. That&amp;rsquo;s if vivacious American actress Jorja Fox, 34, is anything to go by. The ex-model plays Sara Sidle, a bookishly sexy forensic scientist in Channel 5&amp;rsquo;s number-one show, CSI: Crime Scene Invesigation, which also has the second biggest TV ratings in the US.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Self</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2002/self/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2002/self/</guid>
      <description>Love Match
One advantage of tennis: it&amp;rsquo;s an amazing exercise. Just ask actress Jorja Fox.
When Jorja Fox isn&amp;rsquo;t busy playing a forensic scientist on the CBS Drama CSI: Crime Scene Investigation, she&amp;rsquo;s sleuthing out new ways to stay fit. Her latest fitness foray: adding tennis to her repertoire, which already includes running, boogie boarding and hiking. Fox hadn&amp;rsquo;t played since her teens, so she started by having a coaching session with Sue Whiteside, tennis director at Rancho Valencia in Rancho Santa Fe, California.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Entertainment Tonight</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2002/entertainment-tonight/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2002/entertainment-tonight/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; star JORJA FOX tells ET that even though she hasn&amp;rsquo;t received a script for the upcoming season of the CBS drama, she can guarantee it&amp;rsquo;s going to be scary. While Fox was enjoying her summer hiatus from show, she took time to help out a cause dear to her heart: the environment. Fox posed for the Environmental Communications Office&amp;rsquo;s educational campaign about global warming. Long an advocate of the cause, Fox hopes that the effort will help preserve the earth for generations to come.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CSI season 2 DVD extras</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2002/csi-season-2-dvd-extras/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2002/csi-season-2-dvd-extras/</guid>
      <description>Jorja Fox &amp;ldquo;(shot of the characters viewing a &amp;lsquo;corpse&amp;rsquo;; Jorja walks away holding her stomach)&amp;rdquo; Uh. It&amp;rsquo;s too early. &amp;ldquo;(to &amp;lsquo;corpse&amp;rsquo;)&amp;rdquo; I mean, I&amp;rsquo;m sure you&amp;rsquo;re a really nice guy&amp;hellip;
[&amp;hellip;]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Veronica Magazine</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2002/veronica-magazine/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2002/veronica-magazine/</guid>
      <description>One person&amp;rsquo;s death is another person&amp;rsquo;s breath. That&amp;rsquo;s something Jorja Fox knows everything about. The part of a forensic investigator on the television show C.S.I. has introduced her to a large audience. We talked to the American actress about her own life and her love/hate-relationship with death.
That she would ever be standing next to dead bodies that aren&amp;rsquo;t even cold yet, for a living, surprises Jorja more than anyone. The thirty-three year old actress slowly but surely made her way up to Hollywood.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Late Late Show</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2002/the-late-late-show/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2002/the-late-late-show/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Late Late Show with Craig Kilborn&amp;rdquo; was a TV Talk show/variety show, hosted by Craig Kilborn.
Transcript Jorja Fox Can I, can I just say something?
Craig Kilborn You may say something.
Jorja Fox Something that I&amp;rsquo;ve always wanted to say, perhaps on national television. Ding dong, you son of a bitch. Ding dong.
Craig Kilborn That was good, right?
Jorja Fox It was great!
Craig Kilborn That&amp;rsquo;s exciting, seeing Buddy Hackett.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Guide</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2002/tv-guide-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2002/tv-guide-3/</guid>
      <description>Within six years, Jorja Fox has graced three top 10 shows - ER, The West Wing, and now CSI. She&amp;rsquo;s the kind of Hollywood Success Story that seems, well, almost suspect.
They call her the lucky charm. First, Jorja Fox was gun-toting intern Dr. Maggie Doyle on ER. Then she was Secret Service Agent Gina Toscano, who protected the president&amp;rsquo;s daughter on The West Wing. When both of those story lines ended, Fox went on to play forensic-science hotshot Sara Sidle on CBS&amp;rsquo;s smash hit CSI: Crime Scene Investigation (Thursdays, 9 P.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>De Telegraaf</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2002/de-telegraaf/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2002/de-telegraaf/</guid>
      <description>[CSI] has an outstanding cast with William Petersen, Jorja Fox and Eric Szmanda.
[&amp;hellip;]
Actress Jorja Fox, also known for her roles in ER and West Wing, who conducts her murder investigations detatched and focused on tv: &amp;ldquo;Actually I&amp;rsquo;m an absolute pascifist. The show gives me nightmares. When the shootings are over [for the season]. I&amp;rsquo;m relieved that I can escape for a couple of months. It&amp;rsquo;s all just so realistic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contents Magazine</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2002/contents-magazine/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2002/contents-magazine/</guid>
      <description>Who better than Eric Szmanda of the #1 television drama C.S.I. to investigate his beautiful co-star Jorja Fox? Eric says that when filming wraps for the summer he plans on &amp;ldquo;travelling to Europe and hitting the film festivals&amp;rdquo;. May we suggest a less violent approach, say a handshake, when arriving in Berlin?
Jorja Fox, actor interviewed by Eric Szmanda
Eric Szmanda: Has working on CSI changed your outlook on life?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Emmy Magazine</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2002/emmy-mag-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2002/emmy-mag-2/</guid>
      <description>CSI  the series that makes forensic science look sexy  wraps a very successful second season. Bring on the spinoff and the next victim &amp;hellip;
[&amp;hellip;]
With the two leads set, casting centered on a trio of supporting characters, a veritable neoMod Squad of sexy, edgy forensics flunkies. As criminalist Sara Sidle, Jorja Fox, thirty-three, a bohemian type whose backstory includes recurring roles on ER and West Wing, would be the neoPeggy Lipton.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ri:se</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2002/ri-se/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2002/ri-se/</guid>
      <description>Jorja Fox (Sara Sidle), Paul Guilfoyle (Jim Brass) and Robert David Hall (Dr. Al &amp;lsquo;David&amp;rsquo; Robbins) were on Ri:se, Channel 4(UK) to promote the season 1 DVD. There was a clip of Season 1 stuff with a voice over and lots of Gary Dourdan (Warrick Brown) clips. Then they showed an interview of Jorja in one hotel room Paul and Robert in another, interspersed with clips form various episodes. There was mention of CSI&amp;rsquo;s ratings success in the US and also for the UK&amp;rsquo;s Channel 5, and a way too enthusiastic commentary from the presenters about the TMI cam for a breakfast show.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Larry King Weekend</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2002/larry-king-weekend/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2002/larry-king-weekend/</guid>
      <description>LARRY KING, HOST: Tonight, unsolved mysteries, Jon Bonet Ramsey, Chandra Levy &amp;#8212; in the news. No wonder one of TV&amp;rsquo;s top drama&amp;rsquo;s is &amp;ldquo;CSI Crime Scene Investigation&amp;rdquo;. This phenomenal series is about following evidence and closing cases. Glory details, high tech twists, it got them all.
&amp;rdquo;(VIDEO CLIP)&amp;rdquo;
KING: But, how realistic are the corpses and the clues?
Joining us from LA, stars from the gripping show, killing the competition, and from Detroit, world renowned forensic expert Dr.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NYSE</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2002/nyse/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2002/nyse/</guid>
      <description>CBS Television Network, a division of Viacom, Inc. (NYSE-Listed VIA, VIA.B), visits the NYSE to celebrate the success of CSI and to promote CBS&amp;rsquo; new Fall lineup. In honor of the occasion, Les Moonves, CBS President and CEO, rings The Closing BellSM. He is joined on the bell podium by CSI cast members William Peterson, Mark Helgenberger, Jorja Fox, Gary Dourdan, and Paul Guilfoyle and CSI executive producers Carol Mendelsohn, Ann Donahue and Anthony Zuiker.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stuff Magazine</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2002/stuff-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2002/stuff-2/</guid>
      <description>BEST IN SHOWS:
After stints on ER and The West Wing, Jorja is now riding high atop the crest of the hit CBS series CSI: Crime Scene Investigation.
READ THIS BACKWARDS AND IT&amp;rsquo;LL MAKE MORE SENSE:
Jorja had a role in the indie-film sensation Memento.
OUR WEIRD-RADAR WAS IMPOUNDED:
&amp;ldquo;I might have that weird-radar, because the people who talk to me are almost never creepy. You&amp;rsquo;ve gotta wonder what kind of vibe you&amp;rsquo;re putting out there if you&amp;rsquo;re having really creepy people come talk to you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stuff Magazine</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2002/stuff-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2002/stuff-3/</guid>
      <description>We go &amp;ldquo;undercover&amp;rdquo; with C.S.I&amp;rsquo;s Jorja Fox. By which we mean we dress her in crazy getups and ask her silly questions. It&amp;rsquo;s our m.o.!
Silver Lake, California, 3:19 on a sunny afternoon at the dog park, about a softball pitch away from downtown L.A.: I was scheduled to meet Jorja Fox at 3 P.M. and follow her around with a tape recorder while she walked her dogs. Just when I start to think, This sucks, I see a sprightly, tank-topped, ponytailed woman come bounding through the gates.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Early Show</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2002/the-early-show/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2002/the-early-show/</guid>
      <description>Bryant Gumbel: Although it now may seem hard to believe, it was just two years ago the hit drama &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; barely made it on to the primetime schedule. The show has since become a hit with an unusual look at forensic investigators who solve crimes with science.
[&amp;hellip;]
Bryant Gumbel The stars of &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; are William Petersen, Marg Helgenberger, Gary Dourdan, Jorja Fox and Paul Guilfoyle. Good morning, everybody.
(EVERYONE): Good morning, Bryant.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Guide</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2002/tv-guide-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2002/tv-guide-2/</guid>
      <description>CSI Star MIA at ER Funeral
On tonight&amp;rsquo;s ER ? airing 10 pm/ET on NBC ? many ex-cast members are expected to return for the farewell of Dr. Mark Greene (Anthony Edwards). Who? Exec producer John Wells has kept that info under tight wraps. But we can tell you who won&amp;rsquo;t be there: CSI star Jorja Fox, who played lesbian lady doc Maggie Doyle from 1996-99.
&amp;ldquo;They did call a couple of weeks ago asking if Maggie Doyle could go to Dr.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Star Magazine</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2002/stuff-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2002/stuff-1/</guid>
      <description>Jorja Fox of TVs &amp;ldquo;C.S.I&amp;rdquo; is killer! She sparkles in a $2,000 marcasite beaded gown with gold lace accents by designer Christina Perrin &amp;#8212; and crystal baubles by Daniel Swarovski Paris.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Channel 5 UK</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2002/channel-5-uk/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2002/channel-5-uk/</guid>
      <description>The character Sara is ten gazillion times more courageous than I am. You know, we do things sometimes and me, Jorja, in between takes is like &amp;lsquo;I&amp;rsquo;m not doing this, I can&amp;rsquo;t do this. Let&amp;rsquo;s make sure, we need to be careful, where&amp;rsquo;s the medic?&amp;rdquo; And then the camera&amp;rsquo;s start rolling and Sara Sidle kinda just goes in and does it. We did a helicopter scene. This year George Eads and I had a scene where we were rappelling out of a helicopter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>In Style Magazine</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2002/in-style-magazine-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2002/in-style-magazine-1/</guid>
      <description>She said &amp;hellip; Jorja Fox
33-year-old co-star of CBS&amp;rsquo;s CSI.
I am (in five words) &amp;hellip; &amp;ldquo;Present, light, compulsive, idealistic and revolutionary.
nickname: &amp;ldquo;Foxy. When I was young, I was very chubby and had buckteeth. I could fit a quarter between my two front teeth. Stull, my mom went out and got Foxy Girl T-shirts for me to wear every day of the week. I was not foxy at all.&amp;rdquo;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Channel 5</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2002/channel-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2002/channel-5/</guid>
      <description>Jorja Fox appears to have the golden touch, having starred in three of the biggest US TV hits of the last decade! She played Dr Maggie Doyle in ER, guest-starred as Special Agent Maggie Toscano in The West Wing, and now plays ambitious forensic investigator Sara Sidle in CSI: Crime Scene Investigation, which begins its second series on 5 this week. Jorja&amp;rsquo;s taste in film roles is just as inspired, having played Guy Pearce&amp;rsquo;s wife in critically acclaimed psychological thriller Memento.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>&#39;Women Of ... Primetime Crime</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2002/women-of/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2002/women-of/</guid>
      <description>Intro Jorja Fox I never knew that I wasn&amp;rsquo;t equal to everyone else out there.
&amp;ldquo;Who was your favorite female crime fighter?&amp;rdquo;
Jorja Fox There were the pioneers out there, you know, like Angie Dickinson [&amp;hellip;] I grew up on Charlie&amp;rsquo;s Angels. Those women seemed, they were just incredible. They were so fierce. You know? &amp;lsquo;Cause they were doing karate chops and solving crimes and had the guns and yet they were still young and smart.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Gal</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2002/tv-gal-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2002/tv-gal-2/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
Grissom and Sarah on &amp;ldquo;C.S.I.&amp;rdquo; are quickly becoming my new favorite uncouple. I loved it when he told her he&amp;rsquo;s only been interested in beauty since he met her. This week (Thursday, CBS, 9 p.m.), Grissom and crew investigate a murder at a Buddhist temple.
[&amp;hellip;]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Evening Times</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2002/evening-times/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Feb 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2002/evening-times/</guid>
      <description>Jorja Fox appears to have the golden touch, having starred in three of the biggest US TV hits of the last decade!
She played Dr Maggie Doyle in ER, guest-starred as Special Agent Maggie Toscana in The West Wing, and now plays ambitious forensic investigator Sara Sidle in CSI: Crime Scene Investigation, which begins its second series on 5 tonighy.
Jorja&amp;rsquo;s taste in film roles is just as inspired, having played Guy Pearce&amp;rsquo;s wife in critically acclaimed psychological thriller Memento.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Emmy Magazine</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2002/emmy-mag-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2002/emmy-mag-1/</guid>
      <description>As forensic detective Sarah Sidle on the CBS Series CSI, Jorja Fox works with the dead, searching for clues that will help solve the mystery of their demise. She has made some discoveries among the living, too.
&amp;ldquo;I was a jaded New Yorker with this idea that everyone in L.A. sells their soul,&amp;rdquo; says Fox, thirty-three. &amp;ldquo;And I don&amp;rsquo;t think I&amp;rsquo;ve met people with more soul than the ones I&amp;rsquo;ve worked with out here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Guide</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2002/tv-guide-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jan 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2002/tv-guide-1/</guid>
      <description>Maybe they should rename the show CSI: Celibate Scientists Investigating. The brainchild behind CBS&amp;rsquo;s Thursday night smash says he&amp;rsquo;s in no rush to see Catherine (Marg Helgenberger) and Gil (William L. Petersen) throw down their ion detectors and electrothermal atomizers and acknowledge the mountain of evidence piling up right before their eyes: They want each other bad. In fact, creator-executive producer Anthony Zuiker seems content portraying all of CSI&amp;rsquo;s sexy sleuths as poster children for abstinence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Gal</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2002/tv-gal-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jan 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2002/tv-gal-1/</guid>
      <description>Okay people, clearly I&amp;rsquo;m going to have to fly to LA and apply for a job at the E! channel.
I know that standing on the red carpet and recognizing all the stars can&amp;rsquo;t be as easy as it looks. But last night the people behind-the-scenes were saying incorrect things into Joan&amp;rsquo;s ear. That Andie MacDowell was on &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; (confusing her with Jorja Fox perhaps?) That Christine Lahti was on &amp;ldquo;The West Wing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Golden Globes Red Carpet</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2002/golden-globes-red-carpet/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jan 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2002/golden-globes-red-carpet/</guid>
      <description>Melissa Rivers Thank you. I am here with the cast of CSI. Your show has taken off, like, y&amp;rsquo;know. A train, just steaming right out of the station.
Jorja Fox We&amp;rsquo;re dazed. We&amp;rsquo;re dazed and confused and so happy and yeah! It&amp;rsquo;s great.
Melissa Rivers I see Marg has gotten a lot of attention for the show for the last, what? For last season.
Jorja Fox Yeah.
Melissa Rivers But now the whole show is being acknowledged tonight.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>News Articles (2002)</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2002/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2002/</guid>
      <description>Date Source    January 01 Series Mania   January 21 TV Gal   January 28 TV Guide   February 01 Emmy Magazine   February 02 Evening Times   March 04 TV Gal   March 19 Channel 5   April 01 In Style Magazine   April 20 Star Magazine   May 09 TV Guide   May 16 Stuff Magazine   May 16 Stuff Magazine   May 17 NYSE   June 01 Contents Magazine   June 01 Emmy Magazine   June 21 De Telegraaf   June 22 TV Guide   July 01 Veronica Magazine   July 24 Entertainment Tonight   September 01 In Style Magazine   September 01 Self   September 07 Extra TV   September 17 Post Dispatch   September 23 People   September 28 Mantra Online   October 03 People   October 14 TV Gal   October 17 ET Online   October 21 TV Guide   October 31 ET Online   November 01 About.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Series Mania</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2002/series-mania/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2002/series-mania/</guid>
      <description>If you&amp;rsquo;ve already seen an episode of CSI, perhaps someone pointed out the face of Jorja Fox. Remember in 1996 when Maggie Doyle made her debut in Cook County in ER. It is with this role that she allured the public by accuratly protraying an intern who, after a fashion, tried to make her place among the doctors and befriended Carter (Noah Wyle), before acknowledging her homosexuality. In real life, Jorja is truly passionate, her talents touching everything she does : playing the guitar, singing, writing plays and working with a group with which she co-founded (Honey Pot Productions).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>