<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Er on Fans of Le Fox Library</title>
    <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/tags/er/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Er on Fans of Le Fox Library</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2009 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://jorjafox.net/library/tags/er/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Retrospective</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/retrospective/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/retrospective/</guid>
      <description>Note: This episode is a clip show/retrospective and introduces no new material. All appearances include the actors as themselves.
Summary Clips from memorable episodes; interviews with past and present cast members.
Jorja returned to talk about being on the show.
Quotes On watching the show:
Jorja: When you watched the show, you felt smarter.
On filming the show:
Jorja: It was absolutely terrifying for me.
What it felt like:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shifting Equilbrium</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/shifting-equilbrium/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/shifting-equilbrium/</guid>
      <description>Note: Jorja Fox does not appear in this episode.
Summary It&amp;rsquo;s Neela&amp;rsquo;s last day and everyone in the ER seems to have forgotten that she is leaving. Neela proves she is ready to be an attending when she and Dr. Dubenko argue about the treatment of two surgical cases. Meanwhile, Brenner has an epiphany about his troubled past.
Character Review Doyle&amp;rsquo;s name is seen when Neela puts her nameplate on the wall of departed doctors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Book Of Abby</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/the-book-of-abby/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/the-book-of-abby/</guid>
      <description>Note: Jorja Fox does not appear in this episode.
Summary Neela finds out Abby&amp;rsquo;s good news second hand. Catherine Banfield and Abby butt heads on how to treat the victim of a gun shot wound, that has just been admitted into the ER. Finally, Abby comes to Sam&amp;rsquo;s defense before a nurses&amp;rsquo; disciplinary board.
Character Review Doyle&amp;rsquo;s name is seen when Abby puts her nameplate on the wall of departed doctors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sticks and Stones</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/sticks-and-stones/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Mar 1999 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/sticks-and-stones/</guid>
      <description>Note: This is Maggie Doyle&amp;rsquo;s last appearance on ER.
Summary During a paramedic ride-along, Carter is forced to drive the ambulance while fleeing a riot scene and inadvertently runs over a teenage boy. Later, a paramedic is shot by an angry mob looking for the driver of the ambulance. Carol is despondent following Doug&amp;rsquo;s departure. She later discloses that she&amp;rsquo;s pregnant. Kerry is intrigued by an injured pro wrestler and his relationship with his father.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Storm, Part II</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/the-storm-part-ii/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Feb 1999 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/the-storm-part-ii/</guid>
      <description>Summary Greene assists paramedics in treating injured children at a school bus accident. En route, Doug and Jeanie survive their own accident. Kerry stops Doug from treating Jeanie&amp;ndash;or any other patient. Doug decides to resign and leave Chicago for the Northwest and asks Carol to come with him. She decides against it, but he leaves anyway. Carol steps down from running the clinic so that Anspaugh will keep it open.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Storm, Part I</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/the-storm-part-i/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Feb 1999 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/the-storm-part-i/</guid>
      <description>Summary Doug faces possible criminal charges after Ricky Abbott dies when Ross shows Joi how to bypass system lockouts to give Ricky a lethal dosage of dilaudin. Doug is delegated to desk duty, Carol&amp;rsquo;s clinic is shut down for acquiring the P.C.A. machine for Ricky, and Greene and Weaver face future disciplinary action for not reporting Doug&amp;rsquo;s tampering with the double blind study. Carter and Lucy discover a mutual attraction.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Double Blind</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/double-blind/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 1999 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/double-blind/</guid>
      <description>Summary Doug jeopardizes future federal grants for the entire ER when he breaks a double blind study by giving a sample drug to an ailing patient. Doyle lodges a sexual harassment complaint against Romano, hoping Dr. Corday will lend support. Lucy begins her surgery rotation under Benton&amp;rsquo;s tutelage. The two of them treat a man claiming to be 140-years-old. Mark declines to proceed in the NASA program. Carol questions Lynette&amp;rsquo;s intentions when she hosts a women&amp;rsquo;s health clinic for African American women only.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Good Luck, Ruth Johnson</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/good-luck-ruth-johnson/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 1998 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/good-luck-ruth-johnson/</guid>
      <description>Note: This was ER&amp;rsquo;s 100th episode
Summary Carter plays tour guide for Ruth Johnson, who was born in the hospital 100 years ago to the day, and her large family. Carol treats a boy who was hit by a car and tells a story of being chased, his friend being shot in the process. Peter observes Kotlowitz install a cochlear implant and decides to wait before scheduling an operation for Reese.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Good Fight</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/the-good-fight/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Nov 1998 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/the-good-fight/</guid>
      <description>Summary A girl and her father are brought into the ER after a car accident. Her father abandons her in the ER, and he is the only match for her rare blood type. This forces Benton to operate on her without blood and Carter and Lucy to travel all through the city to find the father. They encounter a number of obstacles including Carter dislocating his shoulder, and end up across the street from the hospital.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hazed and Confused</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/hazed-and-confused/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Nov 1998 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/hazed-and-confused/</guid>
      <description>Summary Corday commits a deadly error after being on-call for nearly 36 hours straight. Peter visits Dr. Kotlowitz and receives encouragement regarding a cochlear implant for Reese. Dr. Amanda Lee, a prospective new ER chief, visits. In the wake of a failed pregnancy attempt, Carol lashes out at a mother using abortion as a means of selective birth control. Carter and Lucy feud when Carter accidentally uses her palm computer and finds out what she thinks of him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day For Knight</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/day-for-knight/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 1998 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/day-for-knight/</guid>
      <description>Summary Third-year med student Lucy Knight reports to the ER. Doug hits the nail on the head when he describes her as a &amp;lsquo;hit-the-book&amp;rsquo; student. Lucy&amp;rsquo;s first day finds her informing a wife of her husbands terminal condition, comforting a pregnant woman, getting locked on the roof and trying to figure out Kerry Weaver&amp;rsquo;s &amp;lsquo;Tour on Tape.&amp;rsquo; Greene extends a protective wing over Lucy, who&amp;rsquo;s forced to endure Carter&amp;rsquo;s irritation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Of Past Regret and Future Fear</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/of-past-regret-and-future-fear/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Apr 1998 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/of-past-regret-and-future-fear/</guid>
      <description>Summary It&amp;rsquo;s another busy night in the ER, as case after case comes through the doors. Hathaway comforts a burn victim in his dying hours. Carter and Anna struggle with a man afflicted with cerebral palsy. Dr. Ross deals with an infant&amp;rsquo;s heroin addiction and its drug-addicted mother. Weaver cares for an elderly couple who may have AIDS. Peter and Elizabeth decide to keep their relationship a secret. Anna&amp;rsquo;s old boyfriend comes to town.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Brother&#39;s Keeper</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/my-brothers-keeper/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 1998 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/my-brothers-keeper/</guid>
      <description>Summary Several heroin ODs are brought into the ER, including Chase Carter. Mark tries to track down Cynthia. Anna treats a John Doe sent from another hospital because he had no insurance. Doug accuses two parents of child abuse, but finds out that their child is disturbed. Benton and Corday run into his sister Jackie. Scott Anspaugh finishes his chemotherapy.
Character Review Doyle is working the night shift, and is seen briefly at the beginning and end of the episode.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Obstruction of Justice</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/obstruction-of-justice/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 1997 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/obstruction-of-justice/</guid>
      <description>Summary Carter is arrested when he refuses to honor a warrant seeking evidence in a domestic abuse incident. Corday is overjoyed to be able to perform a rare femoral transplant. Doug returns from California. Benton and Corday discover that they have a lot in common. Cynthia takes Rachel to the dentist and other places. Jeanie threatens to sue to get her job back, to Kerry&amp;rsquo;s dismay. Anspaugh rehires her, and Al leaves for Atlanta without her.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Freak Show</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/freak-show/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 1997 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/freak-show/</guid>
      <description>Summary Benton takes advantage of a grieving father for a chance to write a paper on a boy with reversed internal organs. George Henry returns to complete his clerkship and suffers a near fatal attack. Jeanie confronts Kerry and Anspaugh over what she perceives as wrongful termination. Cynthia&amp;rsquo;s error forces the free clinic to open a week early; Carol enlists new ER nurse Yosh to help out. Mark strikes a deal with attorney Herb Spivak for legal representation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Good Touch, Bad Touch</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/good-touch-bad-touch/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 1997 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/good-touch-bad-touch/</guid>
      <description>Summary Mark undergoes deposition with the Law family for their lawsuit. Jeanie and Al are involved in a barroom brawl. Carol mulls the idea of opening a free health care clinic. Carter successfully diagnoses a serious injury, only to have Edson steal the credit. Benton&amp;rsquo;s familial duties earn him a waist-high stack of back paperwork. Dr. Romano returns from a European sabbatical, pioneering the latest in robotics technology. Anna treats a young man with testicular cancer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Friendly Fire</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/friendly-fire/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 1997 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/friendly-fire/</guid>
      <description>Summary Carol&amp;rsquo;s trust in Doug is strained when she overhears an errant comment. Weaver puts her newfound power to use immediately. Jerry commits a large-scale blunder with a patient&amp;rsquo;s rocket launcher; Weaver advises him to take some vacation time. Carter suspects Doyle of giving Anna preferential treatment. Cynthia Hooper works her first day as a desk clerk. Benton and Carla argue over circumcision. Mark can&amp;rsquo;t get it up with Heather Morgan.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Something New</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/something-new/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 1997 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/something-new/</guid>
      <description>Summary Greene hires a new desk clerk. High on morphine, Dr. Morganstern gives Weaver increased authority while he recuperates from his heart attack. Doug asks Carol for a drawer at her place. Dr. Corday adjusts to the differences between British and U.S. ERs. Dr. Greene is served with a wrongful death suit from the Law family. Carter trains a med student who is better at research than treating patients. Mark and Carol interview applicants for a vacant desk clerk position.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>One More For The Road</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/one-more-for-the-road/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 1997 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/one-more-for-the-road/</guid>
      <description>Summary Mark, still recovering from the attack, vents his emotions in a violent fit in the break room and buys a gun for protection. Carter decides his future lies in emergency medicine, not surgery, and tries to convince an irate Anspaugh likewise. Drs. Ross and Del Amico work together when Charlie is brought back into the ER. Peter&amp;rsquo;s child strengthens. Doug and Carol share a kiss. Jeanie and Al are back together.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Make A Wish</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/make-a-wish/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 1997 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/make-a-wish/</guid>
      <description>Summary Mark returns to work, scarred both physically and emotionally. Carla goes in labor again, four weeks prematurely, and delivers a baby boy. Doug thwarts Carol&amp;rsquo;s efforts to quietly celebrate her birthday. Carter begins to doubt that his future lies in surgery.
Character Review Doyle tries to help Mark feel better by bringing him a small arsenal of weapons from her family stash, including handguns, tasers and pepper spray. Carter sprays his own face with the spray.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Random Acts</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/random-acts/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 1997 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/random-acts/</guid>
      <description>Summary The staff springs into action when Dr. Greene is violently beaten by an unknown assailant. Dr. Ross treats the son of a wealthy man, leading Carol to suspect Doug of giving the child special treatment. Greg demands that Jeanie choose between him and Al. Speculation runs rampant when a torrid novella, author unknown, is found at the admit desk. A new pediatrician arrives from Philadelphia. Olbes shows up out of uniform for a change, bringing in her grandfather, who has suffered a stroke.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Calling Dr. Hathaway</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/calling-dr-hathaway/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 1997 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/calling-dr-hathaway/</guid>
      <description>Summary Carol finds herself at a career crossroads when her MCAT results come back. She&amp;rsquo;s torn between nursing and becoming a doctor, with Kerry grooming her for medicine, while Carol tries to care for a mother with a dying child. Carter debates whether to report Edson for falsifying a patient&amp;rsquo;s chart. Benton takes a personal day to care for Carla. Dr. Greene treats a couple concocting odd situations to see how quickly the staff finds a solution.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Bet Your Life</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/you-bet-your-life/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 1997 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/you-bet-your-life/</guid>
      <description>Summary Carter goes behind Anspaugh&amp;rsquo;s back to get a gambler admitted for surgery, earning Anspaugh and Hicks&amp;rsquo; wrath and jeopardizing his residency. Carol clashes with Doyle, angered that a 25-year-old intern is able to order her around. Peter illegally obtains Carla&amp;rsquo;s ultrasound to look for abnormalities. Doug treats an ill teenager who doesn&amp;rsquo;t want to miss her prom. Greene deals with a patient who feigns symptoms because she likes having surgeries.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tribes</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/tribes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 1997 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/tribes/</guid>
      <description>Summary Mark examines his prejudices when he&amp;rsquo;s accused of neglecting a black gunshot victim, Kenny Law, in favor of a white victim. Jeanie discovers Peter&amp;rsquo;s impending parenthood when Carla comes into the ER. Carter spends the entire day treating a hopeless case. Kerry tries to persuade a disabled junkie to enter a rehab program. Carol treats a college student who was drugged with roofies. After Jenn&amp;rsquo;s mother has a stroke, Rachel comes to stay with Mark for a while.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Faith</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/faith/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 1997 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/faith/</guid>
      <description>Summary Mark examines his prejudices when he&amp;rsquo;s accused of neglecting a black gunshot victim, Kenny Law, in favor of a white victim. Jeanie discovers Peter&amp;rsquo;s impending parenthood when Carla comes into the ER. Carter spends the entire day treating a hopeless case. Kerry tries to persuade a disabled junkie to enter a rehab program. Carol treats a college student who was drugged with roofies. After Jenn&amp;rsquo;s mother has a stroke, Rachel comes to stay with Mark for a while.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Whose Appy Now?</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/whose-appy-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 1997 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/whose-appy-now/</guid>
      <description>Summary A gleeful Carter removes Benton&amp;rsquo;s appendix. Dr. Ross treats a 17-year-old cystic fibrosis patient who wants to die, but isn&amp;rsquo;t old enough to sign a DNR. Mark juggles dates with three women, including psychiatrist Nina Pomerantz. Jeanie and Greg team up to find the culprit behind a rash of staph infections. Haleh has a tough time filling Carol&amp;rsquo;s shoes.
Character Review Yet again, Carter and Doyle&amp;rsquo;s friendly rivalry rears its head, as the two clash over some early cases.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fortune&#39;s Fools</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/fortunes-fools/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 1997 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/fortunes-fools/</guid>
      <description>Summary Carol takes an interest in an ailing police sergeant who&amp;rsquo;s hiding a degenerative ailment. She also meets with a newspaper reporter to air the complete story on her fatal mistake and is subsequently suspended. Peter runs into a pregnant Carla, upsetting the rest of his day. Carter, already fed up with Benton&amp;rsquo;s lackluster attitude, accepts a transfer to Hicks&amp;rsquo; team after Peter fails to show up at a lecture the two were to give.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Night Shift</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/night-shift/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 1997 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/night-shift/</guid>
      <description>Summary A long, cold night finds ER staffers with hours of time to kill. Kerry recruits staffers to participate in a study on sleep deprivation combined with physical activity. Gant appeals to Anspaugh after a public scolding from Benton. Carter ditches Dennis again to escape his whining, only to discover deadly results. Peter is denied a recommendation from Keaton one last time before she leaves for Pakistan. Mark and Chuny discover that they have a lot in common.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Homeless For The Holidays</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/homeless-for-the-holidays/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 1996 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/homeless-for-the-holidays/</guid>
      <description>Summary Rumors sweep the ER when Kerry and Mark cloister themselves to discuss policy regarding HIV-positive employees, prompting Jeanie to publicize her illness. Charlie brings the child she has been caring for into the ER. Doug treats the child and feels obligated to report the child&amp;rsquo;s mother for neglect. Doyle treats an abused woman, and conspires to help her escape her husband. Carter blows off an evening with Gant to spend the night with Keaton.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Union Station</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/union-station/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 1996 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/union-station/</guid>
      <description>Note: Jorja Fox credited as Jorjan Fox
Summary Susan&amp;rsquo;s last day in the ER finds Mark unsure of himself. Despite Doug&amp;rsquo;s urgings, Mark still finds himself afraid to admit his feelings for her. He chases her all over the city until he finds her at the train station. He declares his love for her, but she decides to leave for Phoenix anyway. Grabarsky and Lydia finally get married. Carol agrees to become &amp;lsquo;management&amp;rsquo; in exchange for an end to the policy of floating ER nurses elsewhere.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>No Brain, No Gain</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/no-brain-no-gain/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 1996 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/no-brain-no-gain/</guid>
      <description>Note: Jorja Fox credited as Jorjan Fox
Summary Benton fights to save the life of a gangbanger already declared dead by Doug. Nurse Rhonda Sterling floats down to the ER again and makes another critical mistake. Carter fights Edson for the rights of an incompetent patient and bonds with Anspaugh in the meantime. E. Ray worries that an MRI test gave him negative karma. Carter and Keaton get closer. Mark fears Susan is dating Morganstern; she tells him that she&amp;rsquo;s moving to Phoenix.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fear of Flying</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/fear-of-flying/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Nov 1996 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/fear-of-flying/</guid>
      <description>Note: Jorja Fox credited as Jorjan Fox
Summary Mark and Susan take to the air for helicopter flight rotation, which brings to the ER an entire family injured in an accident. Benton&amp;rsquo;s overconfidence during Keaton&amp;rsquo;s absence results in a dire mistake. Carol deals with a &amp;lsquo;floater&amp;rsquo; nurse who can&amp;rsquo;t cope with the speed of the ER. Jeanie and Maggie are given the task of keeping a dead man on ice in anticipation of cryogenic storage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ghosts</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/ghosts/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 1996 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/ghosts/</guid>
      <description>Note: Jorja Fox credited as Jorjan Fox
Summary Doug and Carol man the Healthmobile, a roving medical van that caters to the homeless. Benton tries to be more warm and friendly towards children, even taking a group of hospitalized youngsters trick-or-treating. Gant demands more respect from Benton. Mark anxiously waits for Susan to return from vacation.
Character Review Doyle and Jeanie treat Sophie Jennings, an elderly woman, suffering from end stage Lou Gehrig&amp;rsquo;s disease.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Last Call</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/last-call/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 1996 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/last-call/</guid>
      <description>Note: Jorja Fox credited as Jorjan Fox
Summary Dr. Ross brings a one-night-stand into the hospital when she has an epileptic seizure, earning him the stares of his colleagues when he can&amp;rsquo;t remember her name. Carter screws up Benton&amp;rsquo;s lecture when he realizes his presentation materials were in his apartment fire. Keaton takes a shine to Carter, meanwhile, when he persuades a teenage girl to undergo surgery. Carter also finds a place to live, with Dennis Gant.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Don&#39;t Ask, Don&#39;t Tell</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/dont-ask-dont-tell/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 1996 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/dont-ask-dont-tell/</guid>
      <description>Note: Jorja Fox credited as Jorjan Fox
Summary Mark is befuddled by an invitation from Susan to go on a joint vacation to Hawaii. The ER is filled with more refugees from South Side, Drs. Maggie Doyle and Abby Keaton among them. Peter decides to join Keaton&amp;rsquo;s pediatric surgery team. Carter gets on Anspaugh&amp;rsquo;s bad side when he exaggerates a patient&amp;rsquo;s condition to book an operating room. Jeanie tries to keep her HIV status a secret in the face of Weaver&amp;rsquo;s queries.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>