<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Index on Fans of Le Fox Library</title>
    <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/tags/index/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Index on Fans of Le Fox Library</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://jorjafox.net/library/tags/index/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Advocacy</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/main/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/main/</guid>
      <description>Advocacy is an umbrella term for organized activism related to a particular set of issues. Advocacy is expected to be non-deceptive and in good faith, though it is sometimes tainted by use of propaganda. It is almost always organized into or by an advocacy group or special interests. In other instances, an individual may act as a lobbyist, on their own account, or on behalf of a corporation or industry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Biography</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/biographies/main/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/biographies/main/</guid>
      <description> Jorja Fox is an actress, producer, humanitarian, activist and environmentalist. She has been seen on such hit TV shows as CSI: Crime Scene Investigation, ER, The West Wing and Law &amp;amp; Order, as well as indie movies like Memento and Food for the Heart. She has been in numerous other television shows and movies.
Vital Statistics  Birth Name: Jorja-An Fox Nicknames: Jorja, Jorj, Jorjan, Horha (the Spanish pronunciation of her name, used by her &amp;ldquo;CSI Miami&amp;rdquo; friend Emily Procter) Date of Birth: 07 July 1968 Place of Birth: New York City, NY (raised in Melbourne Beach, FL) Eye Color: Brown Hair Color: Brown Height: 5&amp;rsquo;9&amp;rdquo; Pets: Bexar (dog - adopted 2012)  Other Biographies </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FAQs</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/faq/main/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/faq/main/</guid>
      <description>FAQ stands for frequently asked questions, and refers to listed questions and answers, all supposedly frequently asked in some context, and pertaining to a particular topic.
Which is to say, here is what people ask the most:
Most Frequently Asked Questions Is this FAQ up to date? You&amp;rsquo;re probably trying to ask if the contact information is up to date. Yes, yes it is. That&amp;rsquo;s the official, public, contact information.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>News</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/main/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/main/</guid>
      <description>News articles are presented, in whole or in part, with as much accuracy as can be found in the original article. Even in the case that an article is grossly inaccurate, information will be presented honestly in reference to its source. We do not correct articles for spelling or grammar and assume no responsibility over the accuracy or validity of any news documents you may read in this section of the website.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Politics</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/politics/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/politics/</guid>
      <description>In addition to her Advocacy, Jorja is very politically active. She spends time with the Artists &amp;amp; Athletes Alliance, fights for legislation for the protection of animals, and has spoken out against candidates like George W. Bush.
eGreetings: Vote in November (2004) In 2004, a webmedia ad showed up, narrated by Jorja, urging people to get out and vote in November.
Specifically, this ad, which was available online in the fall and winter of 2004, spoke openly against voting for President George W.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recaps</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/</guid>
      <description>Television show recaps have been made available after hours and years of watching.
The follow shows are currently recapped here:
 Missing Persons ER The West Wing CSI: Crime Scene Investigation  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Search Results</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/search/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/search/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Transcripts</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/main/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/main/</guid>
      <description>Interviews, press announcements, and live chat transcripts are presented, in whole or in part, with as much accuracy as can be found in the source media. Even in the case that an interview is grossly inaccurate, information will be presented honestly in reference to its source. There has been no attempt to correct grammar and while every best effort is put forth, assume no responsibility over the accuracy or validity of any transcripts you may read in this section of the website.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to the Fans of Le Fox Library</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/</guid>
      <description>The goal of the Fans of Le Fox Library is to provide a comprehensive resource for information about the career and life of the actress, producer, humanitarian, activist and environmentalist that is Jorja Fox.
 Biographies - Various biographies Filmography - Her work as an actor, producer, and writer Advocacy - The good she does for the world Transcripts - Interviews, press releases, and online chats News Articles - News where she is mentioned Episode Recaps - Recaps of TV episodes in which she&amp;rsquo;s appeared  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>