<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Filmography on JFO Library</title>
    <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/categories/filmography/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Filmography on JFO Library</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 16 Aug 2009 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://jorjafox.net/library/categories/filmography/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Drop Dead Diva</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/actor/drop-dead-diva/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Aug 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/actor/drop-dead-diva/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The series revolves around vapid aspiring model, Deborah &amp;ldquo;Deb&amp;rdquo; Dobkins, who is killed in a car crash on the way to an audition for The Price Is Right. As her soul enters the gates of Heaven, she finds herself being judged by a gatekeeper named Fred. As a result of her shallowness, Fred declares her a &amp;ldquo;zero-zero,&amp;rdquo; since she has performed zero good deeds and zero bad deeds during her time on Earth. While he&amp;rsquo;s distracted, Deb presses the &amp;ldquo;return&amp;rdquo; key before Fred can stop her and is brought back to life in the body of a recently deceased lawyer named Jane Bingum , who died protecting her boss, Jay Parker.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jane is the complete opposite of Deb; she is brilliant, hard-working, charitable, and plus size. Deb finds that Jane also works in the same law firm, Harrison-Parker, as Deb&amp;rsquo;s fiancé Grayson Kent. After immediately telling her best friend, Stacy, of her predicament, Deb prepares herself to tell Grayson the truth about her new body. However, Fred’s assignment as Deb’s guardian angel serves as punishment for letting her leave heaven. His purpose on Earth is to prevent Deb from telling Grayson the truth and insisting that no one else can know that it is really Deb in Jane&amp;rsquo;s body.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Deb struggles to learn more about her inherited life, learning lessons about self-esteem and personal acceptance. Eventually, the real Jane Bingum reappears in another person&amp;rsquo;s body after having pressed the return key, leading Deb to finally reveal the truth to Grayson, now one of Jane&amp;rsquo;s closest friends. Grayson, after grieving and moving on from Deb&amp;rsquo;s passing, becomes conflicted, but finally accepts Deb in her new body, saying that he wants her to be her and no one else.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In addition to working with Grayson at the law firm, Deb (as Jane) also contends with her professional rival, Kim Kaswell, who briefly dates Grayson after Deb&amp;rsquo;s passing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;##Episode: &amp;ldquo;Second Chances&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Aired 16 August 2009&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Season 1, Episode 6&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;MaryAnn Neely comes to see Jane in her office, having met her a few years prior when Jane worked a pro-bono case for the St. Jude&amp;rsquo;s Hospital, where MaryAnn worked as a nurse.  Scared and needing help, MaryAnn doesn&amp;rsquo;t get to explain much before the police arrive and arrest her for murder.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At 18, MaryAnn&amp;rsquo;s boyfriend had her stay in the car while, unknown to her, he robbed a continence store.  The robbery went bad, he killed the clerk, and MaryAnn was culpable for not only accessory to murder, but also murder in the second degree.  Hearing the DA was pushing for the death sentence, MaryAnn ran once she got out on bail, changed her name and started a new life.  She fell in love, got married and had two children.  When the hospital started fingerprinting everyone for security, MaryAnn knew she&amp;rsquo;d be caught, so she wrote a note to her husband, Phillip, and went to Jane&amp;rsquo;s office so she wouldn&amp;rsquo;t be arrested in front of her children.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Upset at the deception, Phillip has trouble putting aside his feelings of betrayal, and in a case where the law isn&amp;rsquo;t on their side, Jane has to humanize MaryAnn, and prove she&amp;rsquo;s not the same person she was 20 years ago.  While MaryAnn&amp;rsquo;s coworkers extol her virtues, the most the DA is willing to offer is a reduction. Ten years for manslaughter.  At first, MaryAnn is more concerned that Phillip won&amp;rsquo;t testify, but then the idea of ten years, away from her children, scares her.  Jane suggests that MaryAnn take the stand, and tell the jury what she never told her husband.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;MaryAnn&amp;rsquo;s testimony sways her husband, and he wants to testify but it&amp;rsquo;s after the Defense rests and no further testimony can be heard.  Instead, Jane quotes a letter from him in her closing argument, arguing for MaryAnn&amp;rsquo;s rehabilitation as service enough.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;MaryAnn is found guilty of accessory, innocent of murder, and sentence to time served for the community.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;##Character##
Jorja plays the soccer mom, MaryAnn Neely (formerly Fay Greene), whose criminal past comes back to haunt her.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3 Weeks to Daytona</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/actor/3-weeks-to-daytona/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/actor/3-weeks-to-daytona/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;recap:49b2d895cc86225af703d16ec08e2f89&#34;&gt;Recap&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Chuck Weber is a race car driver who is down on his luck and nothing has gone right in twenty years, which happens to be the last time he won a race. Divorced, struggling to pay for his car and the alimony for his son, Willy (aka Worm), the only bright spot in his life is racing at the Speedbowl, a lock stock-car track run by Sal.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After crashing into the wall and losing his sponsorship, Chuck fears his dreams are at an end when Sal loses his sponsorship from Rob&amp;rsquo;s furniture. In a desperate grab to save his track, Sal convinces Rob to fund one driver to the Daytona 500. Rob balks at the idea of supporting Sal&amp;rsquo;s driver, Buddy, so Sal suggests a race - winner takes all.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cheryl, Chuck&amp;rsquo;s pit crew and girlfriend (called &amp;lsquo;Trenton trash&amp;rsquo; by Katie, Chuck&amp;rsquo;s ex-wife), spends her days working at a machine shop. Unlike Chuck, Cheryl saves her money with the hope of making her own speed shop. Still, she bets on Chuck, and when she finds out about the race, she funds Chuck&amp;rsquo;s repairs. Katie demands the money for alimony instead, which makes Chuck unable to pay for his car, and pisses Cheryl off to no end.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After being kicked out by Cheryl, Chuck takes his son to his old trailer, filled with his old trophies, which Worm had never seen before. Chuck finally tells Worm that he started losing races when his father stepped in to be his pit boss, replacing Sal. Young Chuck was so frustrated with his father&amp;rsquo;s ways, he intentionally crashed his car, and hasn&amp;rsquo;t won a race since.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of Chuck coworkers, Steve, harasses him at work and happens to be dating Katie. Finally he challenges Chuck to a race to the airport: whomever picks up the customer first wins the race, and the car. Now armed with the money, Chuck retrieves his car and apologizes to Cheryl, who refuses to go help him. The only person who will go to the track with Chuck is his son, who now insists on being called Willy and has been failing math since he spends his time trying to fix Chuck&amp;rsquo;s car. Katie, however, blackmails Chuck for all of his winnings just to let Willy go to the race.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Just as the race starts, Cheryl arrives to manage the pit and works with Willy to improve the speed and performance of the car. When Chuck starts to waver, Willy provides the emotional stimulus to win, and the trio finally move forward to Daytona.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;character:49b2d895cc86225af703d16ec08e2f89&#34;&gt;Character&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cheryl constantly bets on Chuck, losing money every race by literally betting on him. She loses her cool when he spends money meant for the car on his alimony, but accepts his apology and helps him at the end. Cheryl has a remarkable eye for the track, spotting a crash before it happens, and is innovative, using a hair clip for the car&amp;rsquo;s missing hood pin. While it&amp;rsquo;s clear she and Chuck have feelings for each other, they only kiss after he wins the Speedbowl race.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alchemy</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/actor/alchemy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/actor/alchemy/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This distinctly feminist drama chronicles three phases in the life of a young woman. The three phases are presented as distinct, titled vignettes, &amp;ldquo;Charity,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;Hope,&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Faith,&amp;rdquo; centered upon Louisa Garrison, a woman who translates folk tales. She is first seen working in a bookstore. Though involved with Ethan, she decides to break up with him because she strongly suspects that he is still in love with Kitty, his ex-girl friend. Ethan swears his innocence, but it&amp;rsquo;s to no avail. Somewhat obsessed with Kitty, Louisa begins investigating her and then learns that Ethan died in a car wreck. She goes to Kitty and becomes her friend. The grieving Kitty has no idea that Louisa was ever involved with Ethan. In the next segment, Louisa goes to see Jane, her older sister, who has just learned that she has cancer. Louisa is surprised to learn her sister is a lesbian. It also hurts her to realize that while Jane is gentle and giving to everyone around her, she is cold and remote from Louisa. In the last vignette, Louisa moves to a remote artists&amp;rsquo; colony and there falls in love with Duncan, a man she used to work with.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jorja Fox plays Josie (credited as Jorjan Fox).&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CSI: Crime Scene Investigation</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/actor/csi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/actor/csi/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;premise:76426f91c68ef01caf8f95fe8e34a3df&#34;&gt;Premise&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The show follows the cases of the Crime Scene Investigation division of the Clark County (Nevada) Sheriff&amp;rsquo;s Department, usually referred to by officers as the &amp;ldquo;Las Vegas Crime Lab.&amp;rdquo; The division solves crimes almost entirely through the means of forensics evidence, which may or may not come to the conclusion of a murder or accidental death. Keeping in theme with the setting, investigations often lead to taboo subjects, such as sexual deviations. The bizarre conclusions of these cases often force one to question morals and beliefs and possibly human nature in general.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;character:76426f91c68ef01caf8f95fe8e34a3df&#34;&gt;Character&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jorja Fox plays Sara Sidle, who hails from San Francisco, and was brought in by personal request of CSI Supervisor Gil Grissom to investigate the shooting (and subsequent death of) Holly Gribbs. Since then, Sara remained on the team and proved her worth while solving crimes. Sidle&amp;rsquo;s relationship with many of her teammates is contentious and layered, as she does not often open up to them. Sara doesn&amp;rsquo;t really have any friends or interests outside of work, which can occasionally cause problems; she can also be obsessive about certain types of cases.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Over time, her relationship with Grissom develops into one of romance, which suffers a setback when, after being kidnapped by a serial killer and nearly dying of exposure, Sara leaves Las Vegas. Sara returns briefly to mourn the death of Warrick Brown, but leaves for Costa Rica. Grissom comes after her when, shortly there after, he too leaves the lab. After a year away, Sara returns yet again, married to Grissom, although he remains in Paris while she works in Las Vegas. Their relationship suffers from the distance and they end up divorcing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the series finale, Sara is promoted to Lab Director following a convoluted and deeply personal case which brings Grissom back to Las Vegas not for her, but for Lady Heather. However when Grissom confesses his love for Sara to Heather, she gives up Las Vegas to be with him.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;see-also:76426f91c68ef01caf8f95fe8e34a3df&#34;&gt;See Also&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
    {% for post in site.actor %}
        {% if post.categories == &#39;csi&#39; %}
            &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;{{ site.baseurl }}{{ post.url }}&#34;&gt;{{ post.title }}&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
        {% endif %}
    {% endfor %}
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Courthouse</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/actor/courthouse/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/actor/courthouse/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Jorja Fox&amp;rsquo;s appearance in this is unverified. If you have information than can confirm, please &lt;a href=&#34;http://jorjafox.net/contact/&#34;&gt;contact us&lt;/a&gt;, and be sure to cite your source.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;character:b6560e5ae47b2057087e12e286e6e684&#34;&gt;Character&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jorja Fox played &amp;ldquo;Maureen Dawes&amp;rdquo; in the pilot episode.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dead Drunk: The Kevin Tunell Story</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/actor/dead-drunk/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/actor/dead-drunk/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Dead Drunk: The Kevin Tunell Story&amp;rdquo; was first aired on HBO in 1993. It is a compelling and cautionary tale of the choices and consequences of drinking and driving. On New Years Eve, 1981, Kevin Tunell went to a party to celebrate the coming new year and drank with his friends. He took his girlfriend home and although impaired, told her &amp;ldquo;nothing ever happens to me when I drink.&amp;rdquo; That might have been true, but that night Kevin&amp;rsquo;s life would change forever. Driving impaired and distracted by images on the side of the road Kevin had a head on collision with a young woman who was driving home from her friends house. He walked away with barely a scratch. The young woman, Maggie Glendon was not as fortunate and died as a result of her injuries.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jorja Fox plays Maggie Glendon, credited as Jorjan Fox.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dead Funny</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/actor/dead-funny/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/actor/dead-funny/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;Reggie has been skewered to the kitchen table with a Samurai sword, and Viv&amp;rsquo;s trying to remember what happened. After all, it was one hell of a party last night. Instead of calling the police, Louise, Viv&amp;rsquo;s best friend, takes charge, attempting to solve Reggie&amp;rsquo;s murder with the help of a list of suspects and a couple of bottles of champagne. Deep in memories of her last year with Reggie and continuously interrupted by a strange cast of characters, Viv wanders through her apartment in a daze. Still desperately hoping that Reggie&amp;rsquo;s body in the kitchen is another of his tasteless pranks, she slowly begins to recall the bizarre events of the last 24 hours.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;character:766a739f3bc523507071cad86f06798a&#34;&gt;Character&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jorja Fox plays one of the three fates (Fate 3); one of three women that Reggie knows who show up at odds moments in the movie. First they&amp;rsquo;re at the painting party Viv had hosted the night before, and second as three cops showing up in a hallucination around Reggie&amp;rsquo;s dead body. Fox doesn&amp;rsquo;t have many speaking lines, and they&amp;rsquo;re all in the background noise.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dear Bernard</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/producer/dear-bernard/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/producer/dear-bernard/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;overview:e68cc6f7f5c86bfeb26b20bb6b06f4d5&#34;&gt;Overview&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;New York City - 1973. The city is awash in excess, playing host to the hottest parties and people of the moment. &amp;ldquo;Dear Bernard&amp;rdquo; tells the timeless tale of a small town English girl seeking fame and glamour in in America - with a twist.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Chelsea Mills - our exuberant English import - arrives in New York and is quickly discovered by the Liberace of fashion photographers, who propels her to the top of the &amp;ldquo;body part model&amp;rdquo; biz. Her legs light up the hosiery billboards in Times Square and her sparkling teeth adorn the bus stops across Queens and Brooklyn, hawking the latest toothpaste flavor. Caught up in the swirl of glamour and money, fragmented in both her personal and professional life, Chelsea strives for success at any price.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Real &amp;ldquo;success&amp;rdquo; seems just beyond Chelsea&amp;rsquo;s reach. But how do you know when you&amp;rsquo;re there? Who congratulates you upon your arrival? And if the people congratulating you are strangers - have you succeeded?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These answers, high kicks, sexy body part models and great songs can be found in the new musical &amp;ldquo;Dear Bernard,&amp;rdquo; written by Heather Reid of The Murmurs and Gush.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dodges City</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/actor/dodges-city/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/actor/dodges-city/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Jorja Fox&amp;rsquo;s appearance in this is unverified. If you have information than can confirm, please &lt;a href=&#34;http://jorjafox.net/contact/&#34;&gt;contact us&lt;/a&gt;, and be sure to cite your source.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Produced by Paramount, Eric Szmanda (who played Greg Sanders on CSI) starred as Johnny Dodge, a fearless, thrill seeking private investigator with a taste for fast cars and faster women.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Down With The Joneses</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/actor/down-with-the-joneses/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/actor/down-with-the-joneses/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;While it is listed at IMDb as having been completed in 2003, this movie has no release information and there is no record of anyone having see the completed film.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ER</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/actor/er/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/actor/er/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;character:6626a93c6b492822270aeeaea0d79467&#34;&gt;Character&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dr. Maggie Doyle&lt;/strong&gt; arrived from a hospital that had been closed. A wonderful dichotomy, Doyle was a gun-toting, lesbian vegetarian. She was good friends with John Carter, and had enough attitude for everyone.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Doyle slogged through a fairly nasty piece of litigation, when surgeon Dr. Robert &amp;lsquo;Rocket&amp;rsquo; Romano blasted her on her evaluation when she threatened to tell about his harassment of her. While Doyle filed the report, the plot fell by the wayside, and Romano became the Chief of Emergency Medicine. According to one news report, Doyle was going to leave the ER with the last line &amp;ldquo;File that yourself, bastard.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It never happened, and February 18, 1999 Maggie Doyle made her last appearance on ER. It wasn&amp;rsquo;t until two years later that it was mentioned Doyle had left the hospital. In 2008, when Abby Lockhart left the ER, we finally see Doyle&amp;rsquo;s nameplate, saved in the back with all the others who have left the ER. It&amp;rsquo;s intimated that she hung her own nameplate when she left.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;see-also:6626a93c6b492822270aeeaea0d79467&#34;&gt;See Also&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
    {% for post in site.actor %}
        {% if post.categories == &#39;er&#39; %}
            &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;{{ site.baseurl }}{{ post.url }}&#34;&gt;{{ post.title }}&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
        {% endif %}
    {% endfor %}
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ellen</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/actor/ellen/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/actor/ellen/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;episode-the-puppy-episode-2:fe558eee30085a456516179075531c8b&#34;&gt;Episode: &amp;ldquo;The Puppy Episode (2)&amp;rdquo;&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Aired 30 April 1997&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Season 4, Episode 23&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ellen senses a kindred spirit when she meets a gay woman, who enlightens her to her own sexual identity. Confused by this startling self-discovery, Ellen seeks the guidance of a therapist and braces herself for yet another moment of truth-telling her friends about this personal revelation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;character:fe558eee30085a456516179075531c8b&#34;&gt;Character&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the now infamous &amp;lsquo;Coming Out&amp;rsquo; episode of Ellen, Jorja Fox played the uncredited, unnamed, lesbian in the coffee house who walks up to Ellen, sits down next to her, smiles, and proceeds to hit on Ellen&amp;rsquo;s best friend (and good looking friend), Paige. To quote Ellen &amp;ldquo;Well, it&amp;rsquo;s good to see some things never change.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ellen: The Ellen Degeneres Show</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/self/ellen/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/self/ellen/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;The Ellen DeGeneres Show, premiered September 08, 2003, and is a television talk show hosted by Ellen DeGeneres. The show features interviews with celebrities and comedic monologues by the host.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;jorja-s-apperances:fe558eee30085a456516179075531c8b&#34;&gt;Jorja&amp;rsquo;s Apperances&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;{{site.baseurl}}transcript/2004/the-ellen-degeneres-show/&#34;&gt;18 May 2004&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Extinction Soup</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/producer/extinction-soup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/producer/extinction-soup/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Extinction Soup&amp;rdquo; follows documentary filmmaker Philip Waller on his quest for adventure as he sets out to tell the story of his larger-than-life friend and extreme sports legend, Jimmy Hall. The film quickly takes a surprise turn when Waller finds himself consumed with exposing to the world an environmental catastrophe in the making - the extinction of the oceans&amp;rsquo; shark population through the mass slaughter of these magnificent animals for their fins. Waller documents the efforts of conservationist Stefanie Brendl as she fights to educate lawmakers and help pass ground-breaking legislation that will curb the consumption of shark fin soup, considered a delicacy in many Eastern cultures, and the impetus behind 70 million sharks being killed per year.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Food for the Heart</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/actor/food-for-the-heart/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/actor/food-for-the-heart/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Jorja Fox plays Delmar Youngblood; a divorcee with an abundant love of cooking and family raising a young son in a small town in anywhere, USA. Her cherished dream is to open a restaurant, The Hungry Bachelors Club, but this reality is deterred by her uninteresting and low-paying job as an insurance adjuster.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>