<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Faqs on JFO Library</title>
    <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/faq/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Faqs on JFO Library</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="http://jorjafox.net/library/faq/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>About Jorja Fox</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/faq/jorja/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/faq/jorja/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;Questions here are about Jorja Fox&amp;rsquo;s personal life and, in broad terms, her career, including how to get in touch with her.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;who-is-jorja-fox:8031039bd2efb244b8ebc9d0ca550f27&#34;&gt;Who is Jorja Fox?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jorja Fox is an actor, producer, activist and musician.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She is most well known for her TV work, having played the recurring role of Dr. Maggie Doyle on the NBC show ER from 10/10/1996 through 01/21/1999, the guest role of Secret Service Agent Gina Toscano on NBC&amp;rsquo;s The West Wing from 02/24/2000 through 09/2000, and the regular role of Sara Sidle on CBS&amp;rsquo;s CSI: Crime Scene Investigation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She has also been seen in movies and award shows, and is an environmentalist and humanitarian who attends many outreach causes. For her other roles, see her filmography. For more about her background, read her biography.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-s-the-deal-with-her-name:8031039bd2efb244b8ebc9d0ca550f27&#34;&gt;What&amp;rsquo;s the deal with her name?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This question arises since Jorja Fox was listed as &amp;lsquo;Jorjan Fox&amp;rsquo; in her first few movies, on Missing Persons, and on her first few episodes of ER. After a few episodes, her listing changed to &amp;lsquo;Jorja Fox&amp;rsquo;. The confusion was compounded by the following rumor &amp;ldquo;When [Jorja] joined the cast of ER, her name was shortened back to Jorja after a couple episodes, hence the confusion. In an interview she said that one day she woke up and wanted her name back.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The rumor is arguable, and not verifiable. The truth of the matter is that her birth name is &amp;lsquo;Jorja-An&amp;rsquo; and Jorja is a shortening. Jorjan was bastardization of Jorja-An that was done when she was on Missing Persons.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today, both personally and professionally, she is known as &amp;lsquo;Jorja Fox&amp;rsquo;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;how-old-is-jorja:8031039bd2efb244b8ebc9d0ca550f27&#34;&gt;How old is Jorja?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She was born July 7, 1968.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;how-do-you-pronounce-her-name:8031039bd2efb244b8ebc9d0ca550f27&#34;&gt;How do you pronounce her name?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jorja is pronounced just like the US state or the Eurasian country &amp;lsquo;Georgia.&amp;rsquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;where-does-jorja-live:8031039bd2efb244b8ebc9d0ca550f27&#34;&gt;Where does Jorja live?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jorja lives around the Los Angeles area in California.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;how-do-i-contact-her:8031039bd2efb244b8ebc9d0ca550f27&#34;&gt;How do I contact her?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Studio Fan Mail&lt;br /&gt;
1048 Irvine Ave #624&lt;br /&gt;
Newport Beach, CA 92660&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;how-do-i-get-an-autographed-picture-of-her:8031039bd2efb244b8ebc9d0ca550f27&#34;&gt;How do I get an autographed picture of her?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Send a letter to the above address. It may take a long time to get a reply though. All her fan mail is checked before it gets to her.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;will-you-forward-my-email-too-her:8031039bd2efb244b8ebc9d0ca550f27&#34;&gt;Will you forward my email too her?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I would if I could, but as I can&amp;rsquo;t, please don&amp;rsquo;t email personal letters to me. It&amp;rsquo;s very embarrassing for me to read the reeeeally personal details of total strangers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-s-her-official-website:8031039bd2efb244b8ebc9d0ca550f27&#34;&gt;What&amp;rsquo;s her official website?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://jorjafox.com&#34;&gt;jorjafox.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;does-jorja-have-a-twitter-myspace-facebook-account:8031039bd2efb244b8ebc9d0ca550f27&#34;&gt;Does Jorja have a Twitter/Myspace/Facebook account?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.facebook.com/JorjaFoxworldwide&#34;&gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/JorjaFoxofficia&#34;&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-movies-and-tv-shows-has-she-been-in:8031039bd2efb244b8ebc9d0ca550f27&#34;&gt;What movies and TV shows has she been in?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jorja Fox most recently starred in the CBS drama CSI. For more information, please check her filmography.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;is-jorja-fox-gay-bisexual-or-straight:8031039bd2efb244b8ebc9d0ca550f27&#34;&gt;Is Jorja Fox gay, bisexual or straight?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don&amp;rsquo;t know, and until Jorja herself states her sexuality, it&amp;rsquo;s not a topic open for discussion. Please respect her privacy as much as you value your own.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;is-jorja-fox-single-is-she-dating:8031039bd2efb244b8ebc9d0ca550f27&#34;&gt;Is Jorja Fox single? Is she dating?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In 2001, Jorja told USA Today she was seeing someone: &amp;ldquo;Involved, but not married. I&amp;rsquo;m not allowed to talk about it at all. I&amp;rsquo;ve been sworn to secrecy &amp;ndash; the whole theory that it&amp;rsquo;s more special. I&amp;rsquo;m very happy and living under a shroud until further notice.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However in a 2003 interview with People Magazine, she was reported as being single, and that was why she took her brother to the Emmys that year.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;is-jorja-fox-pregnant:8031039bd2efb244b8ebc9d0ca550f27&#34;&gt;Is Jorja Fox pregnant?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No. Regardless of what you read online elsewhere and hear in rumors, she is not, and has never been, pregnant.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;does-jorja-have-any-children-does-she-want-any:8031039bd2efb244b8ebc9d0ca550f27&#34;&gt;Does Jorja have any children? Does she want any?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jorja has no children, but she has cats and dogs. I don&amp;rsquo;t know if she wants any children (though she did mention it when talking about why she left CSI).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;is-jorja-fox-a-smoker:8031039bd2efb244b8ebc9d0ca550f27&#34;&gt;Is Jorja Fox a smoker?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yes and no. She has smoked, and has tried to quit many times. As of February 2010, she still smoked.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;is-she-a-vegetarian:8031039bd2efb244b8ebc9d0ca550f27&#34;&gt;Is she a vegetarian?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jorja Fox became a vegetarian at the age of 19, sometime around her modeling days, and discovered PETA in New York City at about the same time. Jorja told the PETA spokesperson that she took part in a few protests, and enjoyed their &amp;ldquo;confrontational&amp;rdquo; attitude. She describes herself as an aspiring vegan.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-political-party-is-jorja-affiliated-with:8031039bd2efb244b8ebc9d0ca550f27&#34;&gt;What political party is Jorja affiliated with?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Emphatically not Republican. She&amp;rsquo;s done work with Libertarians and Democrats, but most recently she attended the 2008 Democratic National Convention and supported Barak Obama.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;does-she-wear-corrective-lenses:8031039bd2efb244b8ebc9d0ca550f27&#34;&gt;Does she wear corrective lenses?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jorja wore glasses in a Support SAG PSA in 2008, and in bonus material on CSI DVDs, she wore glasses while re-doing lines in a recording studio. It&amp;rsquo;s likely she just needs reading lenses.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;does-she-have-any-tattoos:8031039bd2efb244b8ebc9d0ca550f27&#34;&gt;Does she have any tattoos?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yes. She has a flower on her left ankle (seen in the CSI season five episode 4x4 and in various award show and charity photographs).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A temporary/henna tattoo was spotted on &amp;ldquo;The Early Show&amp;rdquo; for April 28, 2006. On that show, she had what looked like a stylized turtle tattoo high up on her right shoulder. This has not been seen since.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;does-she-have-any-piercings:8031039bd2efb244b8ebc9d0ca550f27&#34;&gt;Does she have any piercings?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jorja has pierced ears.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-pets-does-she-have:8031039bd2efb244b8ebc9d0ca550f27&#34;&gt;What pets does she have?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She had two cats and a dog (Ali (dog, female, Boxer), Rumplestiltskin (cat), and Sid Poitier (cat, male, formerly named Sid Vicious)), all of whom have passed away of old age. In 2012, she adopted a new dog: Bexar County Rodeo Princess.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-kind-of-music-does-jorja-like:8031039bd2efb244b8ebc9d0ca550f27&#34;&gt;What kind of music does Jorja like?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Everything. As she said in a Yahoo! Chat &amp;ldquo;Soul, rock n roll and jazz are probably my favorites.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-kind-of-tv-does-jorja-watch:8031039bd2efb244b8ebc9d0ca550f27&#34;&gt;What kind of TV does Jorja watch?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She watched the first season of Survivor, and she also is a fan of Lost.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;does-she-play-music:8031039bd2efb244b8ebc9d0ca550f27&#34;&gt;Does she play music?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While Jorja is disparaging about her musical talents, she sings and plays the guitar. CSI co-star Gary Dourdan says she plays well. You can hear her sing in the CSI episode Too Tough To Die and also in the movie Food for the Heart. Jorja also wrote and performed a song for the short movie, Traveling Companions, as well as some songs written with the CSI cast and crew. She has performed her music at the several wrap parties for CSI, including after season Four and Season Five. At various times she has had songs that she has written and played on her personal web site.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In 2005 she reportedly acquired a drum set and was learning to play, and according to an L.A. Times article, she often takes part in a &amp;lsquo;drum circle&amp;rsquo; at Malibu Beach.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;does-jorja-play-sports:8031039bd2efb244b8ebc9d0ca550f27&#34;&gt;Does Jorja play sports?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yes. Jorja and fellow CSI cast member Eric Szmanda were members of the &amp;ldquo;Royal Blue Balls&amp;rdquo;, which is a team in the Adult Kickball League. To stay in shape she jogs, and for personal enjoyment she plays tennis, surfs, swims, hikes, kayaks and goes camping.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;does-jorja-really-surf:8031039bd2efb244b8ebc9d0ca550f27&#34;&gt;Does Jorja really surf?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jorja has been surfing since she was little and was a self-professed &amp;lsquo;surfer girl&amp;rsquo; in high school. She&amp;rsquo;s surfed in Florida and California, and during the Christmas break in 2006 she went surfing in Puerto Rico. After leaving CSI, Jorja mentioned wanting to surf in South America.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once CSI ended, she started surfing more often.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-kind-of-car-does-jorja-drive:8031039bd2efb244b8ebc9d0ca550f27&#34;&gt;What kind of car does Jorja drive?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A Toyota Hybrid. She also has a bicycle and multiple surfboards.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Jorja Fox&#39;s Career</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/faq/career/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/faq/career/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-movies-and-tv-shows-has-she-been-in:7e6e72851422b97b7259805ca91208dc&#34;&gt;What movies and TV shows has she been in?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jorja Fox most recently starred in the CBS drama CSI. For a complete list, please check her &lt;a href=&#34;http://jorjafox.net/library/filmography/&#34;&gt;filmography&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-was-her-first-role:7e6e72851422b97b7259805ca91208dc&#34;&gt;What was her first role?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She first played the Rooster, in a children production of Chicken Little. Her first professional role was as Myra Pavlov in The Kill-Off.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;why-did-jorja-fox-leave-er:7e6e72851422b97b7259805ca91208dc&#34;&gt;Why did Jorja Fox leave ER?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since she wasn&amp;rsquo;t a main cast member, Jorja Fox had the freedom to film a pilot for a UPN series, The True Story. The pilot ep was reworked into The Beat, which was sans Fox and was canceled after a handful of episodes. She was then in two movies, The Hungry Bachelors Club and Velocity Trap, which accounts for her time between ER and The West Wing, which became her next TV project.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;why-did-jorja-fox-leave-the-west-wing:7e6e72851422b97b7259805ca91208dc&#34;&gt;Why did Jorja Fox leave the West Wing?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Her role on The West Wing was only a guest-starring role, so when she got the call for CSI, she was able to audition for it - twice. Originally it had been hoped that she would continue to be a guest star on The West Wing, however her commitment to CSI kept her too busy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;was-she-really-run-over-on-the-west-wing:7e6e72851422b97b7259805ca91208dc&#34;&gt;Was she really run over on The West Wing?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yes. During the filming of the final episode for the season, a limousine ran over her legs. Thankfully, there were no broken bones or other permanent damage, but when she auditioned for CSI she did so on crutches.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;does-jorja-fox-like-her-csi-co-stars-in-real-life:7e6e72851422b97b7259805ca91208dc&#34;&gt;Does Jorja Fox like her CSI co-stars in real life?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Off camera they&amp;rsquo;re all friends, though Jorja&amp;rsquo;s probably friendlier with Eric Szmanda, Gary Dourdan and George Eads, as they&amp;rsquo;re closer to her age. By all reports, Jorja&amp;rsquo;s friendly with everyone on the set, including William Peteresen and Marg Helgenberger.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;jorja-fox-makes-all-these-cute-innuendos-in-interviews-with-her-csi-co-stars-do-they-mean-anything:7e6e72851422b97b7259805ca91208dc&#34;&gt;Jorja Fox makes all these cute innuendos in interviews with her CSI co-stars. Do they mean anything?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Probably not, she&amp;rsquo;s just good friends with her co-stars. Go re-read the answer to &amp;lsquo;Is Jorja dating anyone?&amp;rsquo; She&amp;rsquo;s not dating Gary Dourdan, George Eads, or Eric Szmanda. I&amp;rsquo;m not going to dignify the questions of if she&amp;rsquo;s dating any of the co-stars who are happily married to other people. Please get your heads out of the gutter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;was-jorja-really-fired-from-csi:7e6e72851422b97b7259805ca91208dc&#34;&gt;Was Jorja really fired from CSI?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yes she was, for &amp;lsquo;breach of contract&amp;rsquo; on July 16, 2004. Basically, CBS sent her a letter, asking her to sign it, that stated she wouldn&amp;rsquo;t form a sick-out to bargain for the raise she asked for. Jorja sent the letter back via registered mail, while everyone else used a Fax. CBS claimed not to have received the letter, however the sign-for date on the registered mail supports otherwise. Jorja was hired back once this was resolved, however refused to return until CBS also re-hired George Eads, who had been fired at the same time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Of note, Jorja also did not agree to sign the contract extension (to remain on the show past season seven), which caused her not to receive a raise, like the rest of her co-workers. This may be related to why she chose to leave the show in season eight.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As of July 23, 2004 Jorja was officially rehired on CSI. If you want to follow the fun, go check the 2004 news section. There&amp;rsquo;s a lot to read.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;why-did-jorja-leave-csi:7e6e72851422b97b7259805ca91208dc&#34;&gt;Why did Jorja leave CSI?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are all these things I want to do. Some are personal. Some are professional. And I really need to do some of them before I get too old. If I thought the show were on its last legs, I would have tried harder to stay the course. But I feel like its going to be around for a while, so if I don’t want some of those dreams to pass me by, I have to get off the ride for a while.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;why-did-jorja-come-back-to-csi:7e6e72851422b97b7259805ca91208dc&#34;&gt;Why did Jorja come back to CSI?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In season nine, Jorja came back to give William Petersen a great send off when he left the show.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In season ten, she came back because CBS asked if she&amp;rsquo;d be interested in coming back part-time, and she said yes. She stuck around for season eleven as a part time main cast member, returning to the credits, and stayed till the end.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;has-she-been-nominated-for-any-awards:7e6e72851422b97b7259805ca91208dc&#34;&gt;Has she been nominated for any awards?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She was in the first round of nominations for the 2007 primetime Emmys in the category &amp;ldquo;Supporting Actress, Drama&amp;rdquo; (for her work in the CSI episode Empty Eyes). However, she was removed from subsequent rounds of the nomination process. CSI has been nominated (and has won) several times.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;where-can-i-find-her-movies-and-tv-shows:7e6e72851422b97b7259805ca91208dc&#34;&gt;Where can I find her movies and TV shows?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The TV shows ER, The West Wing and CSI have all been released on DVD. You can also find the movie Memento on DVD, however many of her other films are difficult to find on DVD or VHS. Her guest appearances on Ellen and Law &amp;amp; Order are both available on DVD.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;is-it-true-she-did-a-movie-for-free:7e6e72851422b97b7259805ca91208dc&#34;&gt;Is it true she did a movie for free?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The independent film Next Exit was looking to cast no-name actors for the small buget movie. Jorja knew the director and offered to play the role for no pay. The film aired at a Los Angeles area film festival in January 2005.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FAQs</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/faq/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;FAQ stands for &lt;strong&gt;frequently asked questions&lt;/strong&gt;, and refers to listed questions and answers, all supposed to be frequently asked in some context, and pertaining to a particular topic.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;most-frequently-asked-questions:d680e8a854a7cbad6d490c445cba2eba&#34;&gt;Most Frequently Asked Questions&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;is-this-faq-up-to-date:d680e8a854a7cbad6d490c445cba2eba&#34;&gt;Is this FAQ up to date?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You&amp;rsquo;re probably trying to ask if the contact information is up to date. Yes, yes it is. That&amp;rsquo;s the official, public, contact information.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;is-this-the-official-jorja-fox-site-are-you-jorja-fox:d680e8a854a7cbad6d490c445cba2eba&#34;&gt;Is this the official Jorja Fox site? Are you Jorja Fox?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No, this is not, nor has it ever claimed to be an official Jorja Fox website. Nor has anyone who works on the site ever been or claimed to be Jorja.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jorja Fox: Online (JFO) is NOT an official Jorja Fox website. JFO is run by fans for the purpose of sharing information about Jorja Fox&amp;rsquo;s career. Jorja&amp;rsquo;s official site is &lt;a href=&#34;http://jorjafox.org/&#34;&gt;jorjafox.org&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;how-can-i-contact-jorja:d680e8a854a7cbad6d490c445cba2eba&#34;&gt;How can I contact Jorja?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Studio Fan Mail&lt;br /&gt;
1048 Irvine Ave #624&lt;br /&gt;
Newport Beach, CA 92660&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;can-you-get-me-in-touch-with-jorja:d680e8a854a7cbad6d490c445cba2eba&#34;&gt;Can you get me in touch with Jorja?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No, I cannot get you in touch with Jorja. Use the above info to contact her yourself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;does-jorja-have-a-social-media-account:d680e8a854a7cbad6d490c445cba2eba&#34;&gt;Does Jorja have a Social Media account?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yes!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.facebook.com/JorjaFoxworldwide&#34;&gt;Facebook - JorjaFoxworldwide&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/jorjafoxofficia&#34;&gt;Twitter - @jorjafoxofficia&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If she has anything else, she&amp;rsquo;s keeping it private. That means &lt;strong&gt;anyone&lt;/strong&gt; you see claiming to be her probably isn&amp;rsquo;t.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;is-jorja-fox-pregnant:d680e8a854a7cbad6d490c445cba2eba&#34;&gt;Is Jorja Fox pregnant?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No, Jorja is not pregnant. No, she wasn&amp;rsquo;t pregnant. No. No. No.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;###Is Jorja Fox gay?###&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jorja&amp;rsquo;s sexuality is her own business. Until Jorja says &amp;ldquo;I am &lt;whatever&gt;.&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;I am dating &lt;whomever&gt;.&amp;ldquo;, discussion about her dating life and sexuality is not permitted on this website.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;###Have you met Jorja?###&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yes. She&amp;rsquo;s just as cool as you think.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;why-wasn-t-jorja-in-every-episode-of-csi:d680e8a854a7cbad6d490c445cba2eba&#34;&gt;Why wasn&amp;rsquo;t Jorja in every episode of CSI?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Because she didn&amp;rsquo;t want to be.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;what-s-she-doing-now-that-csi-is-over:d680e8a854a7cbad6d490c445cba2eba&#34;&gt;What&amp;rsquo;s she doing now that CSI is over?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mostly advocacy work, but we&amp;rsquo;ll see what&amp;rsquo;s next! Isn&amp;rsquo;t it exciting?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;see-also:d680e8a854a7cbad6d490c445cba2eba&#34;&gt;See Also&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
{% for faq in site.faq %}{% if faq.title != &#39;FAQs&#39; %}
    &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;{{ site.baseurl }}{{ faq.url }}&#34;&gt;{{ faq.title }}&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
{% endif %}{% endfor %}
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grading</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/faq/grading/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/faq/grading/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Grading is a fairly subjective way of rating a TV show or movie by way of how much is Jorja Fox&amp;rsquo;s character involved, and how much screen time does she get.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The objective is to give the highest &amp;lsquo;score&amp;rsquo; to anything that someone should watch if looking for a great representation of Jorja Fox&amp;rsquo;s work as an actor. This is not an attempt to grade how good a movie or TV show is. In fact, Memento is a highly acclaimed movie and only has a &amp;lsquo;score&amp;rsquo; of 2, because Jorja Fox&amp;rsquo;s role is quite minor. Rating also may not reflect how much screen time Jorja has. For example, in the CSI episode A La Cart, she&amp;rsquo;s in three scenes, however a great deal of characterization is developed in those scenes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Grades are given on a loose scale of 0 to 5 stars, with a rough guideline as follows:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;i style=&#34;color:red;&#34; class=&#34;fa fa-star-o fa-rotate-normal&#34; name=&#34;empty star&#34;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i style=&#34;color:red;&#34; class=&#34;fa fa-star-o fa-rotate-normal&#34; name=&#34;empty star&#34;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i style=&#34;color:red;&#34; class=&#34;fa fa-star-o fa-rotate-normal&#34; name=&#34;empty star&#34;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i style=&#34;color:red;&#34; class=&#34;fa fa-star-o fa-rotate-normal&#34; name=&#34;empty star&#34;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i style=&#34;color:red;&#34; class=&#34;fa fa-star-o fa-rotate-normal&#34; name=&#34;empty star&#34;&gt;&lt;/i&gt; - Not yet rated due to lack of media.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Example: Anything that has not yet aired or been seen.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;i style=&#34;color:grey;&#34; class=&#34;fa fa-star fa-rotate-normal&#34; name=&#34;grey star&#34;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i style=&#34;color:grey;&#34; class=&#34;fa fa-star fa-rotate-normal&#34; name=&#34;grey star&#34;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i style=&#34;color:grey;&#34; class=&#34;fa fa-star fa-rotate-normal&#34; name=&#34;grey star&#34;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i style=&#34;color:grey;&#34; class=&#34;fa fa-star fa-rotate-normal&#34; name=&#34;grey star&#34;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i style=&#34;color:grey;&#34; class=&#34;fa fa-star fa-rotate-normal&#34; name=&#34;grey star&#34;&gt;&lt;/i&gt; - Cameo appearance with no lines, or an episode where she is credited but does not appear.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Example: &lt;a href=&#34;http://jorjafox.net/library/library/actor/west-wing/&#34;&gt;The West Wing&lt;/a&gt; episode &amp;ldquo;In the Shadow of Two Gunmen: Part II&amp;rdquo; or the &lt;a href=&#34;http://jorjafox.net/library/library/actor/csi/&#34;&gt;CSI&lt;/a&gt; episode &amp;ldquo;Jackpot&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;i style=&#34;color:gold;&#34; class=&#34;fa fa-star fa-rotate-normal&#34; name=&#34;gold star&#34;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i style=&#34;color:grey;&#34; class=&#34;fa fa-star fa-rotate-normal&#34; name=&#34;grey star&#34;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i style=&#34;color:grey;&#34; class=&#34;fa fa-star fa-rotate-normal&#34; name=&#34;grey star&#34;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i style=&#34;color:grey;&#34; class=&#34;fa fa-star fa-rotate-normal&#34; name=&#34;grey star&#34;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i style=&#34;color:grey;&#34; class=&#34;fa fa-star fa-rotate-normal&#34; name=&#34;grey star&#34;&gt;&lt;/i&gt; - Very brief scene or two, no more than 2 minutes total. Often as a guest actor.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Example: The CSI episode &amp;ldquo;High and Low&amp;rdquo; or the movie &lt;a href=&#34;http://jorjafox.net/library/library/actor/jerky-boys&#34;&gt;The Jerky Boys&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;i style=&#34;color:gold;&#34; class=&#34;fa fa-star fa-rotate-normal&#34; name=&#34;gold star&#34;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i style=&#34;color:gold;&#34; class=&#34;fa fa-star fa-rotate-normal&#34; name=&#34;gold star&#34;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i style=&#34;color:grey;&#34; class=&#34;fa fa-star fa-rotate-normal&#34; name=&#34;grey star&#34;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i style=&#34;color:grey;&#34; class=&#34;fa fa-star fa-rotate-normal&#34; name=&#34;grey star&#34;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i style=&#34;color:grey;&#34; class=&#34;fa fa-star fa-rotate-normal&#34; name=&#34;grey star&#34;&gt;&lt;/i&gt; - Some dialogue, acting as a supporting character.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Example: The movie &lt;a href=&#34;http://jorjafox.net/library/library/actor/memento/&#34;&gt;Memento&lt;/a&gt; or the CSI episode &amp;ldquo;Burked&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;i style=&#34;color:gold;&#34; class=&#34;fa fa-star fa-rotate-normal&#34; name=&#34;gold star&#34;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i style=&#34;color:gold;&#34; class=&#34;fa fa-star fa-rotate-normal&#34; name=&#34;gold star&#34;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i style=&#34;color:gold;&#34; class=&#34;fa fa-star fa-rotate-normal&#34; name=&#34;gold star&#34;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i style=&#34;color:grey;&#34; class=&#34;fa fa-star fa-rotate-normal&#34; name=&#34;grey star&#34;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i style=&#34;color:grey;&#34; class=&#34;fa fa-star fa-rotate-normal&#34; name=&#34;grey star&#34;&gt;&lt;/i&gt; - Multiple scenes of varying degrees of importance, not the main character, but carries a subplot. On camera for a third of the running time and/or some new information about her character is revealed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Example: The movie &lt;a href=&#34;http://jorjafox.net/library/library/actor/velocity-trap/&#34;&gt;Velocity Trap&lt;/a&gt; or the CSI episode &amp;ldquo;Friends and Lovers&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;i style=&#34;color:gold;&#34; class=&#34;fa fa-star fa-rotate-normal&#34; name=&#34;gold star&#34;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i style=&#34;color:gold;&#34; class=&#34;fa fa-star fa-rotate-normal&#34; name=&#34;gold star&#34;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i style=&#34;color:gold;&#34; class=&#34;fa fa-star fa-rotate-normal&#34; name=&#34;gold star&#34;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i style=&#34;color:gold;&#34; class=&#34;fa fa-star fa-rotate-normal&#34; name=&#34;gold star&#34;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i style=&#34;color:grey;&#34; class=&#34;fa fa-star fa-rotate-normal&#34; name=&#34;grey star&#34;&gt;&lt;/i&gt; - One of the primary characters, but not necessarily the main character. Her character likely has noticeable development and information about her character is revealed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Example: The CSI episodes &amp;ldquo;Snuff&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;Gum Drops&amp;rdquo;, or the movie &lt;a href=&#34;http://jorjafox.net/library/library/actor/food-heart/&#34;&gt;Food for the Heart&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;i style=&#34;color:gold;&#34; class=&#34;fa fa-star fa-rotate-normal&#34; name=&#34;gold star&#34;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i style=&#34;color:gold;&#34; class=&#34;fa fa-star fa-rotate-normal&#34; name=&#34;gold star&#34;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i style=&#34;color:gold;&#34; class=&#34;fa fa-star fa-rotate-normal&#34; name=&#34;gold star&#34;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i style=&#34;color:gold;&#34; class=&#34;fa fa-star fa-rotate-normal&#34; name=&#34;gold star&#34;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i style=&#34;color:gold;&#34; class=&#34;fa fa-star fa-rotate-normal&#34; name=&#34;gold star&#34;&gt;&lt;/i&gt; - The main character and/or is central to the plot, or if her character has significant development. If you want to watch a movie/episode for Jorja, this is the one.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Example: The CSI episodes &amp;ldquo;Empty Eyes&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;Nesting Dolls&amp;rdquo;, Committed&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;Living Doll.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>