<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Talk Shows on Fans of Le Fox Library</title>
    <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/tags/talk-shows/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Talk Shows on Fans of Le Fox Library</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2013 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://jorjafox.net/library/tags/talk-shows/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>CableTV.com</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2013/cabletv-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2013/cabletv-1/</guid>
      <description>Monica Gleberman .. and just ask you, how did you get involved in acting to begin with?
Jorja Fox Oh my goodness. I wanted to act since I was probably four or five years old. I think that the television that sat in the living room of my house was one of the bigger influences in my life. It was definitely a babysitter for me. You know, I grew up in a small town, so there weren&amp;rsquo;t many acting programs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ET Online</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2011/et-online/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2011/et-online/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
I like to think that I know Marg very well. And she&amp;rsquo;s one of the toughest, most stoic people &amp;lsquo; forget about woman or ladies &amp;lsquo; I mean one of the most stoic people I&amp;rsquo;ve ever met. And these moments where she&amp;rsquo;s kind of overcome are once in a blue moon. Probably the last time I ever saw that happen her dog died, probably six years ago. She&amp;rsquo;s got nerves of steel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Issues with Jane Velez-Mitchell</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2011/issues-with-jane-velez-mitchell-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2011/issues-with-jane-velez-mitchell-2/</guid>
      <description>(BEGIN VIDEO CLIP)
UNIDENTIFIED MALE: How do you train or break an elephant? That word, &amp;ldquo;break&amp;rdquo;.
UNIDENTIFIED FEMALE: Elephants are extremely social and they need the environment, they need movement, they need exercise.
UNIDENTIFIED FEMALE: Abused, 24 hours until the baby totally lost their mind. Many baby died.
Then the baby elephant fear the man. The man can control and the boy make baby elephant obey.
(END VIDEO CLIP)
VELEZ-MITCHELL: We&amp;rsquo;re talking about another kind of crime right now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Talk</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2011/the-talk/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2011/the-talk/</guid>
      <description>Julie Chen: Welcome back to &amp;ldquo;The Talk&amp;rdquo;. Our first guest is best known for her role as Sara Sidle on the hit CBS drama &amp;ldquo;CSI: Crime Scene Investigation&amp;rdquo;. Take a look.
&amp;rdquo;(clip from CSI)&amp;rdquo;
Julie: Please welcome Jorja Fox.
Jorja Fox: (walks in, waves to audience) Oh wow! (hugs hosts, sits down on the couch with Julie Chen, Sharon Osbourne and Sara Gilbert) I am so honored to be here, thanks for having me&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Issues with Jane Velez-Mitchell</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2011/issues-with-jane-velez-mitchell-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2011/issues-with-jane-velez-mitchell-1/</guid>
      <description>(BEGIN VIDEO CLIP)
TIM PHILLIPS, ANIMAL DEFENDERS INTERNATIONAL: These lions have lived their life in a tiny, rusting, disgusting cage on the back of a lorry. Tomorrow they&amp;rsquo;re going to feel the wind blow in their face. They&amp;rsquo;re going to feel grass beneath their feet. They&amp;rsquo;re going to roam into the bushes. They&amp;rsquo;re going to do whatever they want. They&amp;rsquo;re going to be as lions, possibly for the first real time in their lives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pets In The City</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2011/pets-in-the-city/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2011/pets-in-the-city/</guid>
      <description>**Pets In The City: **For many of us, the circus brings back fond memories of lions, tigers, and other large, beautiful creatures performing incredible acts of courage and agility usually with their tamers and trainers on board. But in recent years, the ability of some circuses to properly care for these large beasts has been under scrutiny. This scrutiny has not been limited to the United States. Joining us today is Jorja Fox, who plays the popular character Sara Sidle on the mega hit *CSI *Las Vegas, to talk about her personal work on behalf of some very special and now globe-trotting lions that she and other notable stars have helped move from Bolivia to the U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Insider</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2010/the-insider/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2010/the-insider/</guid>
      <description>Watch Now: Trouble on the &amp;lsquo;CSI&amp;rsquo; Set
George Eads: For the last couple years I was a big fan of the &amp;ldquo;Hoarders&amp;rdquo; documentary program. And so I was telling everybody-
Jorja Fox: I think many of us are. George turned me on to it.
GE: I was telling you the other night!
JF: &amp;ldquo;I was watching this show the other night and you gotta check it out!&amp;rdquo; And I went and checked it out, and now it&amp;rsquo;s on my TiVo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Issues with Jane Velez-Mitchell</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2010/issues-with-jane-velez-mitchell/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jun 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2010/issues-with-jane-velez-mitchell/</guid>
      <description>JANE VELEZ-MITCHELL: In tonight&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Spotlight&amp;rdquo;, a fabulous mercy mission for four rescued circus lions. These magnificent animals were freed from their pitiful, abusive existence in a Bolivian circus last month. Bolivia recently did what every country should do &amp;#8212; banned the use of animals in circuses. These majestic animals will live out their lives at the amazing Paws Sanctuary in northern California.
Our guest tonight, CSI star, Jorja Fox, who was right there for their dramatic arrival.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Kevin and Bean Show</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2009/the-kevin-and-bean-show/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2009/the-kevin-and-bean-show/</guid>
      <description>Host: &amp;hellip; It&amp;rsquo;s 9:15.
Host: And what a treat for us. CSI returns tonight at 9 on CBS. Ladies and gentlemen, Jorja Fox right now on the Kevin and Bean show.
Jorja: Aw, thank you!
Host: More importantly, Sara Sidle returns tonight. That&amp;rsquo;s what I care about.
Host 2: Yes! Yes yes yes.!
Jorja: Thank you so much!
Host: What your character has been put through in the course of this series, Jorja-</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Today Show</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2009/the-today-show/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2009/the-today-show/</guid>
      <description>Jorja Fox: It was breathtaking, it was magic. There was so much going on on &amp;ldquo;ER&amp;rdquo; that I certainly had never seen on television before. I don&amp;rsquo;t think you&amp;rsquo;ve seen a lot of it in feature films. The use of steady-cams &amp;hellip; you could do almost an entire act of the show in one sweeping, sort of solid, motion. It was a dance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Access Hollywood</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2008/access-hollywood/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2008/access-hollywood/</guid>
      <description>Interviewer: What are some tips you have to going green?
Jorja Fox: Going green? Oh, wow, I love it. Well, you know, start with the simple stuff. There&amp;rsquo;s some very simple things you can do. Recycling, obviously, I think we&amp;rsquo;re all doing that in California. I&amp;rsquo;m amazed. I go visit some of my family members across the country, and they don&amp;rsquo;t have recycling centers yet. And most of them are doing it themselves anyway.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ian Harvie Show</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2008/ian-harvie-show/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jan 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2008/ian-harvie-show/</guid>
      <description>Jorja Fox: Ten and a half years of deaths -
Ian Harvie: Yes
Jorja Fox: - violence -
Ian Harvie: What is it with you -
Jorja Fox: I just had it of dead bodies -
Ian Harvie: Yeah, seriously!
Jorja Fox: I mean I&amp;rsquo;ve just had it.
Ian Harvie: Seriously, what is it with you and these roles, like these really hard, like, and the dialog is like really hard too!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ET</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2007/et/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Oct 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2007/et/</guid>
      <description>Announcer: And sad news for &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; fans as a star says goodbye.
Jorja Fox: That&amp;rsquo;s the end of me for a while
Announcer: At the Frederick&amp;rsquo;s of Hollywood Fashion show last night Jorja Fox told &amp;ldquo;ET&amp;rdquo; the real reason she&amp;rsquo;s leaving CBS&amp;rsquo;s crime solving show
Jorja Fox: I just need to take a little break, and do some evaluating. Hopefully I will return.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Early Show</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2007/the-early-show-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 May 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2007/the-early-show-2/</guid>
      <description>Jorja Fox: I&amp;rsquo;m not a big fan of Sara being in, in peril. I think that when you play a character as long as I have, what, it&amp;rsquo;s going on 36 years? No, 7 years, you become very, very, very, very, very close to that character in ways that, uh, are difficult to describe. So intrinsically as an artist, y&amp;rsquo;know, my desire is to protect that character and keep that character safe.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Early Show</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2007/the-early-show/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 May 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2007/the-early-show/</guid>
      <description>Chen&amp;rsquo;s &amp;lsquo;CSI&amp;rsquo; Investigation
Julie Chen gets an exclusive behind-the-scenes look at the hit crime drama &amp;ldquo;CSI.&amp;rdquo; She speaks with actors Marg Helgenberger, William Petersen, Paul Guilfoyle and Jorja Fox.
Julie Chen: This season, CSI has given us everything from Grissom and Sara big romance to the so-called &amp;lsquo;Miniature killer&amp;rsquo; who left scale model miniature of crime scenes. Cast members told me those models were as fascinating for them as they were for viewers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Radio Times</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2006/radio-times/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2006/radio-times/</guid>
      <description>One Final Question - Jorja Fox
What&amp;rsquo;s it like to be upstaged by strange fibers and fluids?
*CSI: Crime Scene Investigation* is the top-rated drama in the US, but there are two spin-offs now. Does it annoy you that CSI: Miami and now CSI: NY are sponging off your ratings?
Well, they say it&amp;rsquo;s a great form of flattery, right? I think in the beginning we were all quite afraid. Our show in the States had barely got on its legs and already we were going to have competition from the inside.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Early Show</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2006/the-early-show-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2006/the-early-show-2/</guid>
      <description>Julie Chen: &amp;hellip; were wondering if there was more going on between Grissom and Sara than meets the eye. Well last night we found out, and the answer is definitely yes. Now we have even more questions, and so do the CSI stars. Last night&amp;rsquo;s episode was almost over when we heard Gil Grissom ruminating about the end of his own life.
William Petersen: And it&amp;rsquo;s a little scene, but it&amp;rsquo;s just a coda to the end of the season.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BBC 5</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2006/bbc-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2006/bbc-5/</guid>
      <description>Simon Mayo has a talk show called &amp;ldquo;*star studded&amp;rdquo; on the BBC radio 5 for news, sport and in-depth interviews. On May 18th, he talked with Jorja Fox about ER, The West Wing, CSI and Dear Bernard.
Simon Mayo: Jorja Fox has sidled in stage left. How are you doing?
Jorja Fox: I&amp;rsquo;m doing great Simon thank you so much for having me.
Simon Mayo: Well thank you for coming on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Early Show</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2006/the-early-show-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2006/the-early-show-3/</guid>
      <description>Julie Chen: What does it tell us about your character, the vision, the re-creation you had? What was that like?
Jorja Fox: It was a lot &amp;hellip; &amp;ldquo;(laughing uproariously)&amp;rdquo; It&amp;rsquo;s my character. &amp;ldquo;(laughter)&amp;rdquo; There was no acting involved for me on that episode. Ah, Sara&amp;rsquo;s a little intimacy-gun-shy, a little committment-phobic.
Jorja Fox: &amp;ldquo;(voiceover)&amp;rdquo; It&amp;rsquo;s one of my favorite episodes we&amp;rsquo;ve ever done. It&amp;rsquo;s also a complete direction change for us.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ET Online</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2006/et-online/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2006/et-online/</guid>
      <description>Go behind the scenes of the &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; wedding murder!
Voiceover by Jorja Fox:
We open the story with a beautiful wedding with 200. Beautiful grounds, it&amp;rsquo;s just a perfect day. The sun is shining. The bride and groom are driving away in their beautiful vintage car. Everything is glorious. And then we find out that the groom&amp;rsquo;s mother is tied to the back of the convertible. Things go sorta downhill from there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CTV eTalkDaily</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2006/ctv-etalkdaily/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Apr 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2006/ctv-etalkdaily/</guid>
      <description>Jorja Fox: The thing that surprises me is how much people just wanna be dead bodies on the show.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Early Show</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2005/the-early-show-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2005/the-early-show-2/</guid>
      <description>Julie Chen: After six seasons and a pair of spin-offs, &amp;ldquo;CSI:&amp;rdquo; remains a true original. It&amp;rsquo;s still a ratings powerhouse too with nearly 30 million viewers tuning in every week. I sat down with some of the show&amp;rsquo;s stars inside the CSI autopsy room to dissect the secret of their success.
[&amp;hellip;]
Julie Chen: &amp;ldquo;(voiceover)&amp;rdquo; In tonight&amp;rsquo;s episode, the sexual tension also continues between Sara and Grissom.
Julie Chen: In season six you still kinda have a crush on Grissom, right?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Early Show</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2005/the-early-show/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2005/the-early-show/</guid>
      <description>Julie Chen: If you can&amp;rsquo;t get enough of TV&amp;rsquo;s hottest drama, CSI:, then you&amp;rsquo;re in luck. Every Friday, we&amp;rsquo;re going to take you behind the scenes to show you how they make it happen. In last night&amp;rsquo;s episode, called &amp;ldquo;Secrets and Flies&amp;rdquo;, star Jorja Fox came face to face with an actor&amp;rsquo;s big challenge: working with a baby. Or did she?
Jorja Fox: The camera comes in, you find a woman who&amp;rsquo;s obviously deceased, you don&amp;rsquo;t know what&amp;rsquo;s happened, there&amp;rsquo;s a pool of blood, and the only other sound in the house is of a baby crying.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Land&#39;s Top Ten Sexiest Men</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2005/tv-land-s-top-ten-sexiest-men/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2005/tv-land-s-top-ten-sexiest-men/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;TV Land&amp;rsquo;s Top Ten&amp;rdquo; is a show about the top ten .
Jorja Fox was on the June 15, 2005 episode for &amp;lsquo;Sexiest Men&amp;rsquo;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Extra TV</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2004/extra-tv/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2004/extra-tv/</guid>
      <description>Interviewer: Let&amp;rsquo;s use the microphone. Now, what do you think keeps those thirty million people coming back each week?
Jorja Fox: Um. I think it&amp;rsquo;s just way, way, way too many TV stations, and we&amp;rsquo;re on number two, so when you turn on the television, it&amp;rsquo;s fist number that comes up. It&amp;rsquo;s much simpler than surfing
Interviewer: I think there&amp;rsquo;s a little bit more to do than that.
Jorja Fox: Uh, I just- we&amp;rsquo;ve been so blessed, so lucky and I hope we keep doing it for a long time and don&amp;rsquo;t take any single day for granted.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Ellen Degeneres Show</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2004/the-ellen-degeneres-show/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 May 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2004/the-ellen-degeneres-show/</guid>
      <description>Ellen DeGeneres Our next guest is a star of the popular forensic drama, CSI. Watch her at work.
[&amp;hellip;]
Ellen Please welcome, Jorja Fox!
[&amp;hellip;]
Ellen Hi!
Jorja Fox: Hi! I brought you something.
Ellen Merci.
Jorja Oh, great.
Ellen Merci beaucoup.
Jorja That&amp;rsquo;s all I know.
Ellen What does that mean, what is this?
Jorja Well I know you&amp;rsquo;ve been studying a little French on the show, and so I thought these might help; they&amp;rsquo;re French art deco cosmetic labels.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The View</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2004/the-view/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2004/the-view/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The View&amp;rdquo; is a daytime television talk show on ABC which was created by Barbara Walters and premiered on August 11, 1997, to showcases women&amp;rsquo;s points of view on a variety of issues.
Star Jones: Please welcome Jorja Fox and George Eads!
Star: We&amp;rsquo;re out here in the sunshine&amp;hellip; you guys are used to being in Vegas because CSI is shot-
Jorja Fox: Not, not during daylight hours though. laughs, raises her hand to shade her eyes from the sun</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pulse</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2004/pulse/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2004/pulse/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Pulse&amp;rdquo; is a talk show.
Jorja appeared on the 15th episode, on 13 February 2004.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>93.7 The Buzz</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2003/93.7-the-buzz/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2003/93.7-the-buzz/</guid>
      <description>93.7 BZZ is a top-40 station with all of today&amp;rsquo;s new music.
Bubba: Has it hit you yet that you&amp;rsquo;re on, like, the number one television show in the world?
Jorja Fox: No, absolutely not. I don&amp;rsquo;t know if it&amp;rsquo;ll ever really hit me. I don&amp;rsquo;t really know, I mean it&amp;rsquo;s kind of like fantastically overwhelming to think of.
Bubba: And it&amp;rsquo;s not like you&amp;rsquo;re a bit player in the show, that you like are taking credit for the whole show, you&amp;rsquo;re actually are the show.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Living TV</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2003/living-tv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2003/living-tv/</guid>
      <description>Living TV is &amp;ldquo;Women orientated entertainment&amp;rdquo; and is available on Sky, Telewest and NTL.
Marc: Looking quite glamorous is Jorja from CSI.
Jorja: Thank you very much.
Marc: Chewing gum on the red carpet.
Jorja: Well it&amp;rsquo;s better than a cigar right?
Marc: Ok, you heard it here first, this is a fashion statement, gum chewing, as they say. No let&amp;rsquo;s face it. CSI, the runaway hit, everyone&amp;rsquo;s talking about it, you guys have gotta be feeling pretty good about yourselves.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Love the &#39;70s</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2003/i-love-the-70s/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2003/i-love-the-70s/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;I Love the 70s&amp;rdquo; is a television mini-series shown on VH1, and was created after the success of &amp;ldquo;I Love the &amp;lsquo;80s&amp;rdquo;.
##Appearances##
Jorja appeared in 5 episodes of the miniseries:
 1970 - Original Airdate 08.18.2003
 1973 - Original Airdate 08.19.2003
 1974 - Original Airdate 08.20.2003
 1976 - Original Airdate 08.21.2003
 1977 - Original Airdate 08.21.2003  ##See Also##
VH1 - I Love the &amp;lsquo;70s</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Guide Channel Insider</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2008/tv_guide_channel_insider_2003/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2008/tv_guide_channel_insider_2003/</guid>
      <description>Jorja Fox Wow, um. Thank you. I&amp;rsquo;m hearing that, people have been saying that. And that&amp;rsquo;s amazing, I think- You know, the other reason that I thought the show was going to flop was because it was about science. And I thought that was going to be a very hard thing to make to look fascinating and interesting and exciting to people. I thought it was very fascinating, like reading the script I had a tremendous amount of faith in the show and I just had no idea how we would pull it off.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The View</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2003/the-view/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2003/the-view/</guid>
      <description>The New York Times had run a story saying that Jorja would be appearing on the show &amp;ldquo;The Bachelorette&amp;rdquo; - she joked about in on &amp;ldquo;The View&amp;rdquo;.
Meredith: Welcome to &amp;ldquo;The View&amp;rdquo;, live from L.A. &amp;ldquo;CSI:&amp;rdquo; star Jorja Fox is our celebrity co-host today. Welcome to you, you look great.
Jorja Fox: Thank you so much. I feel like I&amp;rsquo;m in New York City right now, being with you guys, which is so nice for me, cause I&amp;rsquo;m from there-</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Early Show</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2003/the-early-show/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2003/the-early-show/</guid>
      <description>This particular article was about the music of &amp;ldquo;CSI:&amp;ldquo;; in the beginning was an interview with series creator Anthony Zuiker, discussing how music is chosen for various segments.
(brief clip of Jorja and Gary Dourdan jamming on the set with the crew, something they do on a regular basis. Jorja plays guitar while Gary plays bass)
 Julie Chen: But the music isn&amp;rsquo;t just fun, it&amp;rsquo;s theraputic, an escape from the disturbing drama.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Late Late Show</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2002/the-late-late-show/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2002/the-late-late-show/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Late Late Show with Craig Kilborn&amp;rdquo; was a TV Talk show/variety show, hosted by Craig Kilborn.
Transcript Jorja Fox Can I, can I just say something?
Craig Kilborn You may say something.
Jorja Fox Something that I&amp;rsquo;ve always wanted to say, perhaps on national television. Ding dong, you son of a bitch. Ding dong.
Craig Kilborn That was good, right?
Jorja Fox It was great!
Craig Kilborn That&amp;rsquo;s exciting, seeing Buddy Hackett.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ri:se</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2002/ri-se/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2002/ri-se/</guid>
      <description>Jorja Fox (Sara Sidle), Paul Guilfoyle (Jim Brass) and Robert David Hall (Dr. Al &amp;lsquo;David&amp;rsquo; Robbins) were on Ri:se, Channel 4(UK) to promote the season 1 DVD. There was a clip of Season 1 stuff with a voice over and lots of Gary Dourdan (Warrick Brown) clips. Then they showed an interview of Jorja in one hotel room Paul and Robert in another, interspersed with clips form various episodes. There was mention of CSI&amp;rsquo;s ratings success in the US and also for the UK&amp;rsquo;s Channel 5, and a way too enthusiastic commentary from the presenters about the TMI cam for a breakfast show.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Larry King Weekend</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2002/larry-king-weekend/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2002/larry-king-weekend/</guid>
      <description>LARRY KING, HOST: Tonight, unsolved mysteries, Jon Bonet Ramsey, Chandra Levy &amp;#8212; in the news. No wonder one of TV&amp;rsquo;s top drama&amp;rsquo;s is &amp;ldquo;CSI Crime Scene Investigation&amp;rdquo;. This phenomenal series is about following evidence and closing cases. Glory details, high tech twists, it got them all.
&amp;rdquo;(VIDEO CLIP)&amp;rdquo;
KING: But, how realistic are the corpses and the clues?
Joining us from LA, stars from the gripping show, killing the competition, and from Detroit, world renowned forensic expert Dr.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Early Show</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2002/the-early-show/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2002/the-early-show/</guid>
      <description>Bryant Gumbel: Although it now may seem hard to believe, it was just two years ago the hit drama &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; barely made it on to the primetime schedule. The show has since become a hit with an unusual look at forensic investigators who solve crimes with science.
[&amp;hellip;]
Bryant Gumbel The stars of &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; are William Petersen, Marg Helgenberger, Gary Dourdan, Jorja Fox and Paul Guilfoyle. Good morning, everybody.
(EVERYONE): Good morning, Bryant.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Channel 5 UK</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2002/channel-5-uk/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2002/channel-5-uk/</guid>
      <description>The character Sara is ten gazillion times more courageous than I am. You know, we do things sometimes and me, Jorja, in between takes is like &amp;lsquo;I&amp;rsquo;m not doing this, I can&amp;rsquo;t do this. Let&amp;rsquo;s make sure, we need to be careful, where&amp;rsquo;s the medic?&amp;rdquo; And then the camera&amp;rsquo;s start rolling and Sara Sidle kinda just goes in and does it. We did a helicopter scene. This year George Eads and I had a scene where we were rappelling out of a helicopter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Animal Planet Radio</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2001/animal-planet-radio/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jul 2001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2001/animal-planet-radio/</guid>
      <description>Introduction [&amp;hellip;] TV star Jorja Fox of &amp;ldquo;Crime Scene Investigation: CSI&amp;rdquo; talked about how she plays with her pooch while she has time between scenes. She also talked about her roles on &amp;ldquo;The West Wing&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;E/R.&amp;rdquo; Jorja says her dream job would be appearing on TV on Animal Planet. Were the bosses listening that day?
Animal Planet Radio - (10 min) Steve Dale We&amp;rsquo;ll be right back with Jorja Fox on Animal Planet Radio!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Late Late Show</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2001/the-late-late-show/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jun 2001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2001/the-late-late-show/</guid>
      <description>The Late Late Show with Craig Kilborn is a TV Talk show/variety show, hosted by Craig Kilborn. Jorja Fox was the second guest, and introduced as a &amp;ldquo;beautiful actress &amp;hellip; helming the hit TV series CSI&amp;rdquo;.
Craig Kilborn: Welcome back, our next guest is a beautiful actress who has helped make CBS series &amp;ldquo;CSI.&amp;rdquo; the highest rated new drama on television. Please welcome Jorja Fox. &amp;ldquo;(cheers and applause)&amp;rdquo;
Jorja: I&amp;rsquo;m doing great.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Early Show</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2001/the-early-show/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2001/the-early-show/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Early Show&amp;rdquo; is a CBS morning show. On Thursday, April 26th, they aired a &amp;#8216;behind the scenes&amp;rsquo; sequence on CSI. Gary Dourdan, George Eads and Jorja Fox gave tours.
CSI is filmed in Santa Clarita, California, and Jorja Fox showed off Grissom&amp;rsquo;s Office, where they keep bugs, and other fun toys.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hollywood At Large</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2001/hollywood-at-large/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2001/hollywood-at-large/</guid>
      <description>In 2001, Court TV had a new show, Hollywood at Large, in which they look into various TV shows and how they portray the criminal justice system. CSI was featured in the pilot, on Feb 23, 2001.
Jorja Fox had a brief interview on the show (the CSI scene lasted for about five minutes). In her interview she stated that she has liked forensic TV shows (like &amp;lsquo;The New Detectives&amp;rsquo;) since before she started working on CSI, and that she still gets grossed out the easiest.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ellen: The Ellen Degeneres Show</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/self/ellen/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/self/ellen/</guid>
      <description> The Ellen DeGeneres Show, premiered September 08, 2003, and is a television talk show hosted by Ellen DeGeneres. The show features interviews with celebrities and comedic monologues by the host.
Jorja&amp;rsquo;s Apperances  18 May 2004  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>