<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>2004 on Fans of Le Fox Library</title>
    <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/tags/2004/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 2004 on Fans of Le Fox Library</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 Dec 2004 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://jorjafox.net/library/tags/2004/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The Age</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/the-age/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Dec 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/the-age/</guid>
      <description>Here are 10 good reasons why the babe factor plays a big part in solving crimes, writes David Campbell.
What is it about women and crime that kept blokes glued to their TV sets night after night watching the many American whodunits that dominated our screens (and our most-watched lists) during 2004?
A shapely lab coat looming over a blood-spattered corpse? A cotton bud in feminine fingers seeking a DNA sample from a tattooed tough?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Defamer</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/defamer-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Dec 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/defamer-3/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
 My friend and I sat next to Jorja Fox while dining at Eagle &amp;ldquo;Silverlake-in-Training&amp;rdquo; Rock vegetarian eatery Fatty&amp;rsquo;s at about 2pm on Sunday. (which makes sense since Jorja is a well-known vegetarian.) She was with a female, Punky Brewster looking non-famous friend. Jorja wasn&amp;rsquo;t wearing makeup, looking pretty, but very normal. She was dressed in a khaki sweater, black tshirt and jeans, Tall and very skinny in a non-anorexic, super metabolism way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Huckleberry Fund Benefit</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2004/huckleberry-fund-benefit/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Dec 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2004/huckleberry-fund-benefit/</guid>
      <description>&amp;rdquo;&amp;lsquo;Jorja Fox:&amp;ldquo;&amp;rsquo; Um, the Huckleberry Fund is an amazing organization, they help a lot of teenagers in the Los Angeles area. It&amp;rsquo;s a very, uh, it&amp;rsquo;s a group that gets overlooked a lot and obviously a group with a lot of special needs, very specific needs, um, taking care of medical as well as psychological, developmental stuff. Um, I&amp;rsquo;m lucky enough to have a photograph inside, it&amp;rsquo;s one of my favorite things to get to do, it&amp;rsquo;s my second time doing it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Guide</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/tv-guide-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/tv-guide-4/</guid>
      <description>Hey, CSI fans! You die-hards may remember Sarah Buxton from the &amp;ldquo;Eleven Angry Jurors&amp;rdquo; episode that aired last January. She played Lana, a Las Vegas stripper who served her jury duty with a heapin&amp;rsquo; helping of sass on the side. In fact, Ms. Buxton&amp;rsquo;s resum&amp;amp;e reads like a laundry list of shady-lady roles &amp;#8212; go-go girls, hookers, home-wreckers and other miscellaneous temptresses &amp;#8212; in films, prime-time TV and daytime soaps like Sunset Beach and Days of our Lives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Extra TV</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2004/extra-tv/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2004/extra-tv/</guid>
      <description>Interviewer: Let&amp;rsquo;s use the microphone. Now, what do you think keeps those thirty million people coming back each week?
Jorja Fox: Um. I think it&amp;rsquo;s just way, way, way too many TV stations, and we&amp;rsquo;re on number two, so when you turn on the television, it&amp;rsquo;s fist number that comes up. It&amp;rsquo;s much simpler than surfing
Interviewer: I think there&amp;rsquo;s a little bit more to do than that.
Jorja Fox: Uh, I just- we&amp;rsquo;ve been so blessed, so lucky and I hope we keep doing it for a long time and don&amp;rsquo;t take any single day for granted.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E! - Emmy Red Carpet</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2004/emmy-red-carpet/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Sep 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2004/emmy-red-carpet/</guid>
      <description>Star Jones: In the mean time my girl is here.
Jorja Fox: Hey. (hug)
Star Jones: Hey Jorja, nice to see you.
Jorja Fox: How are you?
Star Jones: So we are looking at one of the stars of one of the number one shows [[CSI]] &amp;hellip;they&amp;rsquo;re still watchin&amp;rsquo; Jorja.
Jorja Fox: Ahh, thank you.
Star Jones: You&amp;rsquo;ve got to show yourself off here Jorja, because everybody&amp;rsquo;s looking for you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MSNBC</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/msnbc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Sep 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/msnbc/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
Both Jorja Fox and Drea de Matteo went shopping for their vintage
gowns at The Paper Bag Princess, with de Matteo picking a black chiffon
1930s gown with gold embroidery along the neckline and waist, and Fox
wearing a vintage Christian Dior pink slip gown with lingerie
details.
[&amp;hellip;]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>People Magazine</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/people-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Sep 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/people-2/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
2 OF 6
At least CSI star Jorja Fox got her lipstick right. Other than that, she looks better suited for a prom than the red carpet in this lace-trimmed pink dress and what seem to be faux pearls.
[&amp;hellip;]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sign On San Diego</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/sign-on-san-diego/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Sep 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/sign-on-san-diego/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
Earlier on the carpet, Jorja Fox of the Emmy-nominated &amp;ldquo;CSI: Crime
Scene Investigation&amp;rdquo; knew it would be hours before guests at the retro-
&amp;lsquo;60s official Governor&amp;rsquo;s Ball - where TV clips were being shown on 72
plasma screens - gorged on Steak Au Poivre with Rock Shrimp and
Television de Chocolat. A veggie, Fox had fortified herself with a soy
sausage omelet &amp;ldquo;because there&amp;rsquo;s booze offered every 3 feet in there and</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Star Magazine</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/star-magazine/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Sep 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/star-magazine/</guid>
      <description>For three years, CSI investigators Sara Sidle (played by Jorja Fox, 34) and Warrick Brown (Gary Dourdan, 37) have worked side by side, exchanging polite professional words. But at the People&amp;rsquo;s Choice Awards on Jan 11, the actors Fox and Dourdan snuck off repeatedly to hold hands and share smokes. The couple was spotted kissing by several backstage guests. &amp;#8216;They couldn&amp;rsquo;t keep their hands off each other,&amp;rsquo; a backstage photographer tell Star.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Star Online</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/star-online/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Sep 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/star-online/</guid>
      <description>Glamour mixes with relaxed attitudes as stars enter the Shrine
Auditorium
&amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; star Jorja Fox gave a lot of thought to
preparing for the Emmy Awards&amp;rsquo; red carpet, but that did not save her
from some minor embarrassment.
&amp;ldquo;I told my stylist I had to wear pink. I brought out 13 dresses,&amp;rdquo;
Fox said in an interview Sunday just a few yards from the doors of the
Shrine Auditorium.
&amp;ldquo;It took me one-and-one-half hours to get ready and 15 minutes to</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Paper Bag Princess</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/the-paper-bag-princess/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Sep 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/the-paper-bag-princess/</guid>
      <description>September 19, 2004 (Los Angeles) In support of her Emmy-nominated series CSI: Crime Scene Investigation, this raven-haired beauty will hit the red carpet at tomorrow night&amp;rsquo;s Emmys ceremony in a glamorous pale pink vintage Christian Dior slip gown with ivory lace insets from The Paper Bag Princess. Jorja will accessorize her gorgeous gown with a vintage ivory floral beaded pouch bag with gold edge and handle, also from The Paper Bag Princess.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Northwest Herald</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/northwest-herald/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Aug 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/northwest-herald/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;CSI: Crime Scene Investigation&amp;rdquo; actress Jorja Fox is looking back on her and cast mate George Eads&amp;rsquo; temporary firing from the show as &amp;ldquo;a very bad dream that lingered. You think, &amp;#8216;This can&amp;rsquo;t really be happening,&amp;rsquo; but it is.&amp;rdquo;
In her first interview since the highly publicized souring of the actors&amp;rsquo; contract renegotiations, Fox tells us she feels she and Eads have been unfairly slammed by some of the media  and that much of what has been reported about the dispute and its resolution has been inaccurate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New York City</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/new-york-city-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Aug 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/new-york-city-2/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;It&amp;rsquo;s like if you have a large rock fall on your head &amp;hellip; you absolutely don&amp;rsquo;t want another rock to fall on you!&amp;rdquo;
That&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; actress Jorja Fox, talking tentatively for the first time about the shocking firing of her and co-star George Eads, and then the equally startling turnaround when CBS rehired them. &amp;ldquo;CSI,&amp;rdquo; a gritty, graphic forensic drama, is TV&amp;rsquo;s top-rated series and has spawned a successful spinoff, &amp;ldquo;CSI: Miami.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AZ Central</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/az-central-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jul 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/az-central-2/</guid>
      <description>Jorja Fox, the CSI: Crime Scene Investigation star who was fired for skipping work in a salary dispute, is returning to the hit CBS drama at her old $100,000-per-episode salary.
Fox reached an agreement with the network and will be back on the set next week, the Associated Press reports.
Apparently, Fox did a better job cleaning CBS chief **Leslie Moonves&amp;rsquo; **floors with her toothbrush than did fellow *CSI *firee George Eads.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Detroit Free Press</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/detroit-free-press-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jul 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/detroit-free-press-2/</guid>
      <description>Reinstated: Jorja Fox, the actress fired with George Eads from CBS&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; show reportedly because they wanted more money. E! reports she has been un-fired, with both sides acknowledging a misunderstanding.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IndyStar</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/indystar/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jul 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/indystar/</guid>
      <description>Actors George Eads and Jorja Fox will both be back on the job next week at &amp;ldquo;CSI: Crime Scene Investigation.&amp;rdquo;
Eads reached an agreement Friday to return to television&amp;rsquo;s most popular drama after he was fired for skipping work in what CBS believed was a contract dispute, CBS entertainment spokesman Chris Ender said. Eads rejoins Fox, who came to her own agreement to come back on Thursday after being fired. A spokeswoman for Eads did not immediately return a call seeking comment Friday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lexington Herald-Leader</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/lexington-herald-leader/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jul 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/lexington-herald-leader/</guid>
      <description>The Sopranos won&amp;rsquo;t air again until 2006, and George Eads and Jorja Fox, who were fired from the top-rated CSI: Crime Scene Investigation for skipping work, will return to their hit show.
[&amp;hellip;]
Eads and Fox will both be back on the job next week at *CSI *after learning a lesson in hardball network politics. Eads reached an agreement yesterday to return to television&amp;rsquo;s most popular drama after he was fired for skipping work in what CBS thought was a contract dispute, CBS entertainment spokesman Chris Ender said.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seattle Post Inteligencer</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/seattle-post-inteligencer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jul 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/seattle-post-inteligencer/</guid>
      <description>Half of the &amp;ldquo;CSI: Crime Scene Investigation&amp;rdquo; team that was axed last week won&amp;rsquo;t have to collect unemployment after all: Jorja Fox, who plays investigator Sara Sidle, will return to the set after reaching an agreement with CBS Thursday, says The Associated Press. Fox originally was canned for skipping work in a salary dispute. George Eads, who played Nick Stokes and joined Fox in the dispute, is still on the outs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zap2it</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/zap2it-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jul 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/zap2it-2/</guid>
      <description>LOS ANGELES (Zap2it.com) It looks like we can finally close the book on the past week of &amp;ldquo;As &amp;#8216;CSI&amp;rsquo; Turns.&amp;rdquo;
CBS and &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; star George Eads reached an agreement Friday (July 23) that will allow Eads back on the series, a little more than a week after he was fired in a contract dispute.
So, despite much back-and-forth talk about contracts and oversleeping and the like, it turns out television&amp;rsquo;s highest-rated drama series will begin its fifth season with cast intact.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Defamer Business</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/defamer-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jul 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/defamer-2/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
 Les Moonves is a huge pussy: Jorja Fox allowed back on &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo;, and badly-timed &amp;ldquo;oversleeper&amp;rdquo; George Eads may also return. [&amp;hellip;]
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New York Post</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/new-york-post-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jul 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/new-york-post-2/</guid>
      <description>Fox, who plays Sara Sidle, says a &amp;ldquo;misunderstanding&amp;rdquo; caused her not to show up for work last week.
According to published reports, Fox was axed after she failed to meet a CBS-imposed deadline pledging, in writing, that she would continue to report for work despite whatever contractual issues she might have.
Fox was said to be &amp;ldquo;mystified&amp;rdquo; because she believed she&amp;rsquo;d mailed her &amp;ldquo;pledge&amp;rdquo; letter in on time.
&amp;ldquo;E! News Live&amp;rdquo; was the first to update the Fox situation when it reported that she will definitely return to the show.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zap2it</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/zap2it-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jul 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/zap2it-1/</guid>
      <description>LOS ANGELES (Zap2it.com) &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; will resume production next week with, at most, one fewer regular than in past seasons.
Television&amp;rsquo;s top-rated drama brought Jorja Fox back to its cast Thursday (July 22), the AP reports. George Eads, the other cast member who was dumped late last week in an apparent salary dispute, remained out of a job.
Fox&amp;rsquo;s rehiring ends, at least for her, a well-documented week in which she was booted from the show in an apparent salary dispute.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Backstage</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/backstage/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jul 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/backstage/</guid>
      <description>In his first public appearance since being fired from CBS&amp;rsquo; hit drama &amp;ldquo;CSI: Crime Scene Investigation,&amp;rdquo; George Eads called his dismissal &amp;ldquo;a misunderstanding.&amp;rdquo;
Meanwhile, sources said CBS was in talks with Jorja Fox, the other &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; co-star who was let go last week after what CBS executives characterized as their failure to show up for work as scheduled after they&amp;rsquo;d made demands for salary increases (HR 7&amp;frasl;16).
[&amp;hellip;]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Broadcasting Cable</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/broadcasting-cable/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jul 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/broadcasting-cable/</guid>
      <description>Abstract: CBS has rehired CSI actor Jorja Fox, and George Eads is likely to come back as well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CBS 2 Chicago</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/cbs-2-chicago/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jul 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/cbs-2-chicago/</guid>
      <description>LOS ANGELES (AP)
Jorja Fox, the &amp;ldquo;CSI: Crime Scene Investigation&amp;rdquo; star who was fired for skipping work in a salary dispute, is returning to the hit CBS drama.
Fox reached an agreement with the network and will be back on the set next week, a source close to the production said Thursday, speaking on condition of anonymity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Digital Spy</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/digital-spy-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jul 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/digital-spy-2/</guid>
      <description>George Eads and Jorja Fox have been sacked from C.S.I.: Crime Scene Investigation for breach of contract.
The pair were sacked after they failed to show up for work on Thursday (15th), the first day of production on the crime drama&amp;rsquo;s fifth season.
According to reports, the no-show was a deliberate tactic as part of an ongoing pay dispute with CBS.
The duo were seeking raises from their previous salary, estimated at $100,000 an episode.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Entertainment Weekly</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/entertainment-weekly/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jul 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/entertainment-weekly/</guid>
      <description>Can fired &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; actors get their jobs back? George Eads and Jorja Fox insist that they were fired over misunderstandings and weren&amp;rsquo;t holding out for more money by Gary Susman
George Eads appeared at the Television Critics Association&amp;rsquo;s summer conclave in Los Angeles on Wednesday to promote TNT&amp;rsquo;s July 30 movie &amp;ldquo;Evel Knievel,&amp;rdquo; in which he stars as the famed daredevil, but Eads&amp;rsquo; biggest hurdle these days is getting his job back as detective Nick Stokes on &amp;ldquo;CSI: Crime Scene Investigation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reuters TV</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/reuters-tv/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jul 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/reuters-tv/</guid>
      <description>LOS ANGELES (Hollywood Reporter) - In his first public appearance since being fired from CBS&amp;rsquo; hit drama &amp;ldquo;CSI: Crime Scene Investigation,&amp;rdquo; George Eads called his dismissal &amp;ldquo;a misunderstanding.&amp;rdquo;
Meanwhile, sources said CBS was in talks with Jorja Fox (news), the other &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; co-star who was let go last week after what CBS executives characterized as their failure to show up for work as scheduled after they&amp;rsquo;d made demands for salary increases.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Guide</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/tv-guide-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jul 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/tv-guide-3/</guid>
      <description>Although there&amp;rsquo;s no official confirmation from CBS, sources confirm that fired CSI actress Jorja Fox has been given her job back - but at her old $100,000-per-episode salary. (Poor thing.) &amp;ldquo;There will be no renegotiation,&amp;rdquo; says a source close to the show. Ditto Fox&amp;rsquo;s co-star George Eades, who apparently did just enough groveling at the TCA press tour on Wednesday. &amp;ldquo;Let me tell you, I&amp;rsquo;ve apologized nine ways to Sunday,&amp;rdquo; he told reporters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Variety</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/variety-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jul 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/variety-3/</guid>
      <description>CBS has rehired &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; star Jorja Fox and is talking to George Eads about a reprieve as well.
Fox will be back on the set of &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; when the show resumes production next week, insiders said. The actress was axed last week when CBS execs believed she had failed to comply with a request to sign a letter stating she had no plans to skip work while she and several other thesps sought raises.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coming Soon!</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/coming-soon/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jul 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/coming-soon/</guid>
      <description>Both George Eads and Jorja Fox are expecting to still be part of the CSI: Crime Scene Investigation cast for the fifth season, stating their firings last week was one big misunderstanding. CBS reportedly let the two actors go for breach of contract. Reports said they had asked for more money to stay on the show.
Eads, who played Nick Stokes on the popular show, tells the Associated Press that the reason he didn&amp;rsquo;t show up on-time the first day of filming was because he overslept.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E! Online</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/e-online-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jul 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/e-online-3/</guid>
      <description>BACK ON THE JOB: Exclusive sources telling E! News Live that Jorja Fox will report back to work at CSI and it was just a misunderstanding with CBS.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E! Online</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/e-online-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jul 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/e-online-4/</guid>
      <description>Are CSI&amp;rsquo;s casualties about to return from the dead?
Jorja Fox, axed last week from TV&amp;rsquo;s top-rated drama, will return to the scene of the crime and rejoin the show, sources tell E! News Live.
Fellow fired costar George Eads will stage a similar comeback-or so he hopes. Speaking to TV critics in Los Angeles Wednesday, Eads called his dismissal &amp;ldquo;a big misunderstanding,&amp;rdquo; the Associated Press reported.
CBS had no comment Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Variety</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/variety-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jul 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/variety-2/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
CBS execs may be ready to let fired &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; thesp Jorja Fox (news) have her job back, but it&amp;rsquo;s unclear if colleague George Eads will be so lucky &amp;#8212; despite making a public apology of sorts.
[&amp;hellip;]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Guide</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/tv-guide-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jul 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/tv-guide-2/</guid>
      <description>ALARM CLOCKS ARE EXPENSIVE: Fired CSI actor George Eads claims he missed work last week because he simply overslept. &amp;ldquo;They think it&amp;rsquo;s about money and it&amp;rsquo;s not,&amp;rdquo; Eads told reporters at the TCA press tour in L.A., where he was promoting TNT&amp;rsquo;s Evel Knievel film. &amp;ldquo;I overslept. I woke up white as a sheet three-and-a-half hours after I was supposed to be on the set.&amp;rdquo; Eads adds that he called CSI to say he&amp;rsquo;d be coming in late, and was told &amp;ldquo;Don&amp;rsquo;t bother.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ContraCostaTimes.com</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/contracostatimes-com/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jul 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/contracostatimes-com/</guid>
      <description>Two dismissed &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo;ers learned the hard way:
Everybody really does love &amp;ldquo;Raymond.&amp;rdquo;
The firing of two &amp;ldquo;CSI: Crime Scene Investigation&amp;rdquo; stars in a salary dispute was fair and intended to help the TV industry draw the fiscal line, CBS chief Les Moonves said Sunday.
Actors Jorja Fox and George Eads, who play investigators Sara Sidle and Nick Stokes on the hit CBS crime drama, were dumped last week when they failed to report for work on the upcoming season, he said.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Detroit Free Press</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/detroit-free-press-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jul 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/detroit-free-press-1/</guid>
      <description>&amp;#8216;CSI&amp;rsquo; SOAP OPERA: When &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; regulars George Eads and Jorja Fox tried to hold out for more money and failed to report for work last week, CBS abruptly fired them for breach of contract. Moonves isn&amp;rsquo;t exactly shedding tears. &amp;ldquo;It&amp;rsquo;s time to realize a contract is a contract,&amp;rdquo; he said. &amp;ldquo;When somebody doesn&amp;rsquo;t show up for work, that tells us that, OK, they don&amp;rsquo;t want to work for us anymore. That&amp;rsquo;s our attitude.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E! Online</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/e-online-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jul 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/e-online-2/</guid>
      <description>From Jean_Jenegan: Please tell me that Jorja and George will be back on CSI!!
I wish I could! The past two days at Press Tour have been CBS, and everyone, including pres Les Moonves and EP Anthony Zucker, says they are fired, for good. Me sad. You?
From larrypigtails: What the f-k is CBS thinking firing George and Jorja?
That has been the question at Press Tour. I have a very long quote from Les Moonves with his take on what happened, just for you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Elites TV</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/elites-tv/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jul 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/elites-tv/</guid>
      <description>Walking off the set or halting production of a new season is nothing new to the television industry. It&amp;rsquo;s a right of passage, a game to play, in the struggle of actor contract negotiations. Just this year, the six principal voices of the Simpson&amp;rsquo;s characters halted production demanding an increase in salary from $125,000 per episode to $360,000.
[&amp;hellip;]
However last week, the balance of power shifted back to CBS and all the studios with the firing of actors George Eads and Jorja Fox who play play investigators Nick Stokes and Sara Sidle on the hit CBS crime drama CSI, as Les Moonves, CBS chief, called the duo&amp;rsquo;s bluff.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Guide</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/tv-guide-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jul 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/tv-guide-1/</guid>
      <description>George and Jorja are no longer on CBS exec Leslie Moonves&amp;rsquo; mind
We can already picture the opening scene for the fifth-season premiere of CSI this fall. Lifeless prosthetic versions of George Eads and Jorja Fox will be laid out on the examining table in the morgue. Robert David Hall will shake his head as he writes down the cause of death: breach of contract.
Eads and Fox are the first victims in Viacom co-president Leslie Moonves&amp;#8216; war on rising programming cost.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Variety</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/variety-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jul 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/variety-1/</guid>
      <description>In his first major news conference since being elevated to Viacom co-prexy/co-chief operating officer, Eye topper Leslie Moonves left little doubt that he and CBS Entertainment prexy Nancy Tellem had tired of the annual salary dance, in which thesps seeking more coin often call in sick to make a point.
Issue has come to a head in recent days following the Eye&amp;rsquo;s decision to ax &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; co-stars George Eads and Jorja Fox.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Digital Spy</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/digital-spy-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jul 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/digital-spy-1/</guid>
      <description>Axed CSI actors George Eads and Jorja Fox look set to be reinstated on the cast of the crime drama, according to reports today.
The duo were both dropped by the show&amp;rsquo;s broadcast network CBS last week after failing to show for the first day of filming on the upcoming fifth season. Network chief Leslie Moonves cited an ongoing dispute over pay as the reason for their no-show and subsequent dismissal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Herald Sun</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/herald-sun/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jul 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/herald-sun/</guid>
      <description>ACTOR Jorja Fox has been sacked from the hit TV drama CSI just a day before filming was due to begin on a new series.
It is thought she was fired after a dispute over her pay.
Fox, who played Sara Sidle in the drama, was five years into a seven-year contract with the CBS network. CSI is regularly Australia&amp;rsquo;s most watched TV show.
Fox, 36, previously starred in ER as Dr Maggie Doyle and in a season of The West Wing as Gina Toscano.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New York City</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/new-york-city-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jul 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/new-york-city-1/</guid>
      <description>A new, New York-focused &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; is due on CBS this fall, but the &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; making headlines last week is the original, Las Vegas version.
Two popular regulars, George Eads and Jorja Fox, prominent since the beginning, were dismissed when they sought salary increases and declined to report for work.
The man who said, &amp;ldquo;You&amp;rsquo;re fired,&amp;rdquo; Leslie Moonves, co-president and co-chief operating officer of Viacom, CBS&amp;rsquo; parent, was blunt Sunday.
&amp;ldquo;We feel it&amp;rsquo;s very important that it&amp;rsquo;s time people realize that a contract is a contract,&amp;rdquo; he said.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New York Post</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/new-york-post-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jul 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/new-york-post-1/</guid>
      <description>CBS has axed &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; stars George Eads and Jorja Fox for demanding more money to stay on the show.
Eads and Fox, who played Nick Stokes and Sara Sidle, were fired by CBS for breach of contract. Eads failed to show up for work Thursday, the first day of filming for the new season and was fired soon after. Jorja was understood have been sent a letter of termination on Wednesday, according to published reports.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Philadelphia Inquirer</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/philadelphia-inquirer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jul 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/philadelphia-inquirer/</guid>
      <description>We have disquieting news for CSI: Crime Scene Investigation fans.
Jorja Fox and George Eads, two of the stars of CBS&amp;rsquo;s hyper-literate police drama, have been fired for breach of contract. According to the Hollywood Reporter, the actors had been in a dispute over their salaries.
We find CBS&amp;rsquo;s move particularly lame, not only because we find Fox to be charming (she&amp;rsquo;s got an exquisitely complex face whose slightest gesture tells a whole story), but also because her character, Sara Sidle, has had some serious chemistry with head CSI dude Gil Grissom (William L.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AIM Today</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/aim-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jul 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/aim-today/</guid>
      <description>Two stars of the CBS hit television series &amp;ldquo;CSI: Crime Scene Investigation&amp;rdquo; were fired for breach of contract, KCBS-TV and Variety reported Thursday.
Actors Jorja Fox and George Eads, who play investigators Sara Sidle and Nick Stokes, were fired after asking for more money to stay on the show, according to the reports.
Danica Smith, publicist for both Fox and Eads, told The Associated Press that Fox was fired Wednesday but did not have details.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BBC News</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/bbc-news/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jul 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/bbc-news/</guid>
      <description>One of the stars of the Emmy-nominated drama CSI has been fired in what is thought to be a dispute over salaries.
Actress Jorja Fox was fired over a contractual dispute on the day filming was due to begin on a new series.
Co-star George Eads has also reportedly been sacked after a pay row, according to Variety newspaper.
CSI is the US&amp;rsquo; top-rated show, drawing up to 26 million viewers, and has spawned a number of spin-offs including CSI: Miami and CSI: New York.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Defamer Business</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/defamer-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jul 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/defamer-1/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
 Pink slips on the set of CSI. Supporting actors George Eads and Jorja Fox are the sacrificial lambs in a salary debate, serving as an example to other castmembers that hey, this show is about visual effects and death, you can be replaced. [&amp;hellip;]
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Florida Today</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/florida-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jul 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/florida-today/</guid>
      <description>Two stars of the CBS hit television series &amp;ldquo;CSI: Crime Scene Investigation&amp;rdquo; - one who grew up in Brevard County - were fired for breach of contract, KCBS-TV and Variety reported.
Jorja Fox attended Melbourne High School.
Actors Jorja Fox, who attended elementary and high school in Melbourne, Fla., and George Eads, who play investigators Sara Sidle and Nick Stokes, were fired after asking for more money to stay on the show, according to the reports.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fox 23</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/fox-23/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jul 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/fox-23/</guid>
      <description>Hit TV show &amp;ldquo;CSI: Crime Scene Investigation&amp;rdquo; is in crisis after two stars of the series were fired for breach of contract.
Actors Jorja Fox and George Eads - who play detectives Sara Sidle and Nick Stokes respectively - were axed from the show after demanding a bigger pay package.
The pair&amp;rsquo;s publicist Danica Smith confirmed Fox was fired on Wednesday and did not have details on Eads&amp;rsquo; position.
However, reports claim Eads did not show up for work Thursday, the first day of production for the next season.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hollywood.com</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/hollywood-com-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jul 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/hollywood-com-2/</guid>
      <description>CSI: Crime Scene Investigation stars George Eads and Jorja Fox were fired from the show amid a salary dispute with the show&amp;rsquo;s producers. Sources told Reuters Eads and Fox, who have been on the show since its debut four years ago, had approached CBS about a salary increase for the 2004-2005 season. CBS reportedly offered a modest take-it-or-leave-it raise, and asked the cast to send in a formal letter assuring the network they would report to work as scheduled for the start of production on the show&amp;rsquo;s fifth season.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KESQ News</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/kesq-news/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jul 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/kesq-news/</guid>
      <description>The executive producer of &amp;ldquo;CSI: Crime Scene Investigation&amp;rdquo; says he&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;very saddened and deeply disappointed&amp;rdquo; over the firing of two stars on the show.
Williams Petersen issued the statement today after Jorja Fox and George Eads, who play investigators Sara Sidle and Nick Stokes on the show, were fired.
KCBS-TV and Variety reported they were fired after asking for more money to stay on the show.
Petersen, who also stars in the show, says he hopes &amp;ldquo;cooler heads will prevail and everything will be rectified and restored in due course.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KLAS TV</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/klas-tv/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jul 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/klas-tv/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
In other &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; news, according to the Hollywood Reporter, two supporting actors on the show, George Eads and Jorja Fox, have been let go amid a salary scuffle with the series&amp;rsquo; producers.
Eads and Fox, both of whom have been with the hit forensic drama since its debut in fall 2000, had approached the network about a salary increase for the coming season, sources said. CBS is said to have responded with what industry sources described as a modest take-it-or-leave-it offer of an increase.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SF Gate</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/sf-gate/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jul 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/sf-gate/</guid>
      <description>&amp;#8216;CSI&amp;rsquo; STARS FIRED AFTER PAY REQUESTS
Hit TV show &amp;ldquo;CSI: Crime Scene Investigation&amp;rdquo; is in crisis after two stars of the series were fired for breach of contract.
Actors Jorja Fox and George Eads &amp;#8212; who play detectives Sara Sidle and Nick Stokes respectively &amp;#8212; were axed from the show after demanding a bigger pay package.
The pair&amp;rsquo;s publicist Danica Smith confirmed Fox was fired on Wednesday, but did not have details on whether Eads&amp;rsquo; was fired.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sacbee.com</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/sacbee-com/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jul 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/sacbee-com/</guid>
      <description>William Petersen, star and executive producer of &amp;ldquo;CSI: Crime Scene Investigation,&amp;rdquo; issued a statement Friday concerning reports that co-stars Jorja Fox and George Eads were fired.
Fox and Eads, who play investigators Sara Sidle and Nick Stokes, were fired after asking for more money to stay on the show, according to reports from KCBS-TV and Variety.
Petersen said he is &amp;ldquo;very saddened and deeply disappointed that this is the turn of events,&amp;rdquo; and that he hopes &amp;ldquo;cooler heads will prevail and everything will be rectified and restored in due course.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scotsman.com News</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/scotsman-com-news/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jul 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/scotsman-com-news/</guid>
      <description>TWO stars of the American hit television series CSI: Crime Scene Investigation have reportedly been sacked for breach of contract.
Jorja Fox and George Eads, who play investigators Sara Sidle and Nick Stokes, were apparently fired after asking for more money to stay on the Emmy-nominated show.
Eads didn&amp;rsquo;t show up for work yesterday, the first day of production for the next season, according to Variety.
The actors were in the fifth of their seven-year contracts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Futon Critic</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/the-futon-critic/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jul 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/the-futon-critic/</guid>
      <description>In one of the industry&amp;rsquo;s most surprising moves in recent memory, actors George Eads and Jorja Fox have been fired from CBS&amp;rsquo; top-rated drama &amp;ldquo;C.S.I.: Crime Scene Investigation&amp;rdquo; over breach of contract.
The duo was sacked after neither appeared for work yesterday, the first day of production on the show&amp;rsquo;s fifth season. Both Eads and Fox had reportedly been looking for a pay raise from their current estimated salaries of $100,000 per episode.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AZ Central</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/az-central-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jul 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/az-central-1/</guid>
      <description>A Los Angeles TV station reports two of the stars of &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; are off the case.
KCBS reports George Eads and Jorja Fox have been fired from the series &amp;ldquo;CSI: Crime Scene Investigation.&amp;rdquo; hey play investigators Nick Stokes and Sara Sidle on the show.
The report cites a source who says the two wanted more money.
The report of the cast changes comes the day CSI received four Emmy nominations, including one for best drama.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CBS 4 Denver</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/cbs-4-denver/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jul 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/cbs-4-denver/</guid>
      <description>Search Is Underway For Replacements
Two stars of the CBS hit television series &amp;ldquo;CSI: Crime Scene Investigation&amp;rdquo; were fired for breach of contract and one failed to show up for work, KCBS-TV and Variety reported Thursday.
Actors Jorja Fox and George Eads, who play investigators Sara Sidle and Nick Stokes, were fired after asking for more money to stay on the show, according to the reports.
Danica Smith, publicist for both Fox and Eads, told The Associated Press that Fox was fired Wednesday but did not have details.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CNN</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/cnn/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jul 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/cnn/</guid>
      <description>Fox and Eads let go for breach of contract, sources say
Two stars of the CBS hit television series &amp;ldquo;CSI: Crime Scene Investigation&amp;rdquo; were fired for breach of contract, KCBS-TV and Variety reported Thursday.
Actors Jorja Fox and George Eads, who play investigators Sara Sidle and Nick Stokes, were fired after asking for more money to stay on the show, according to the reports.
Danica Smith, publicist for both Fox and Eads, told The Associated Press that Fox was fired Wednesday but did not have details.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E! Online</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/e-online-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jul 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/e-online-1/</guid>
      <description>It could be another gruesome CSI crime scene. Except this one doesn&amp;rsquo;t involve dead bodies. Just axed actors.
George Eads and Jorja Fox, who played two of the younger, hotter forensics experts you&amp;rsquo;ll find poking around a corpse, have been whacked from TV&amp;rsquo;s top-rated drama series, Daily Variety first reported on its Website Thursday.
The firings came after both Eads and Fox reportedly made it known to their bosses that, in the tradition of employees everywhere, they&amp;rsquo;d like to make more money.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Mercury News</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/the-mercury-news/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jul 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/the-mercury-news/</guid>
      <description>Two stars of the CBS hit television series &amp;ldquo;CSI: Crime Scene Investigation&amp;rdquo; were fired for breach of contract and one failed to show up for work, KCBS-TV and Variety reported Thursday.
Actors Jorja Fox and George Eads, who play investigators Sara Sidle and Nick Stokes, were fired after asking for more money to stay on the show, according to the reports.
Danica Smith, publicist for both Fox and Eads, told The Associated Press that Fox was fired Wednesday but did not have details.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>USA Today</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/usa-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jul 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/usa-today/</guid>
      <description>They&amp;rsquo;ve gone from looking for clues to looking for jobs: CSI stars George Eads and Jorja Fox played hardball and lost during a salary dispute.
CSI has fired two cast members after they didn&amp;rsquo;t show up for work in a salary dispute.
George Eads, who plays Nick Stokes, and Jorja Fox, who plays Sara Sidle, were dismissed by CBS Thursday, the first day of scheduled filming on the show&amp;rsquo;s fifth season.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yahoo News</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/yahoo-news/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jul 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/yahoo-news/</guid>
      <description>Blood is on the floor at &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo;: CBS has fired thesps George Eads and Jorja Fox from the hit Eye drama for breach of contract.
Eye toppers Leslie Moonves and Nancy Tellem, apparently drawing a line in their sand, made the decision after Eads &amp;#8212; looking for a pay hike &amp;#8212; failed to show up to work Thursday, the first day of production on the new season of the skein. Fox reported to duty, but insiders said her reps had been asking for more coin, and the Eye acted after Fox failed to reply to a letter asking her if she had any plans to not show up to work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hollywood Reporter</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/hollywood-reporter/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/hollywood-reporter/</guid>
      <description>Stage fright: Jorja Fox and Heather Reid are getting nervous, but it&amp;rsquo;s more of that superexcited, can&amp;rsquo;t-wait-for-people-to-see kind of nervous. On Thursday, they&amp;rsquo;re hoping lots of people will see their new show, &amp;ldquo;Dear Bernard.&amp;rdquo; It&amp;rsquo;s an original musical the duo is presenting courtesy of Honeypot Prods., a grass-roots theater company they launched with a group of friends eight years ago. It&amp;rsquo;s the biggest production yet and the first one to hit a real stage (the previous productions played to backyard audiences at the homes of generous friends, off-limits to agents, managers and attorneys).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Ellen Degeneres Show</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2004/the-ellen-degeneres-show/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 May 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2004/the-ellen-degeneres-show/</guid>
      <description>Ellen DeGeneres Our next guest is a star of the popular forensic drama, CSI. Watch her at work.
[&amp;hellip;]
Ellen Please welcome, Jorja Fox!
[&amp;hellip;]
Ellen Hi!
Jorja Fox: Hi! I brought you something.
Ellen Merci.
Jorja Oh, great.
Ellen Merci beaucoup.
Jorja That&amp;rsquo;s all I know.
Ellen What does that mean, what is this?
Jorja Well I know you&amp;rsquo;ve been studying a little French on the show, and so I thought these might help; they&amp;rsquo;re French art deco cosmetic labels.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>In Touch</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/in-touch/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 May 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/in-touch/</guid>
      <description>Call it the case of the missing cast member. &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; star Jorja Fox didn&amp;rsquo;t show up to film a pivotal cliff-hanger scene in LA on April 20 in which her character, Sara, is in a car wreck, claims an insider. &amp;ldquo;Producers were unable to find her,&amp;rdquo; claims an insider, adding that the scene had to be shot with a &amp;ldquo;blood-covered stand-in.&amp;rdquo; Jorja was fired &amp;#8212; and quickly rehired &amp;#8212; from &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; in 2004 when she held out for a pay increase right before the show&amp;rsquo;s fifth season.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scarlet Carpet</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/scarlet-carpet/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 May 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/scarlet-carpet/</guid>
      <description>CSI CAST OUT FOR BLOOD OVER CSI: NEW YORK: The original CSI cast is up in arms over CBS&amp;rsquo;s decision to add a third edition of the franchise to its 2004-05 schedlue. At the Golden Globes, Marg Helgenberger refused to comment on the record about the new show, but castmate Jorja Fox didn&amp;rsquo;t hold back: &amp;ldquo;When you do something, you&amp;rsquo;re lucky if people are interested in it, and audiences are very fickle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Guide (Brisbane Australia)</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/tv-guide-bisbane-australia/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Apr 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/tv-guide-bisbane-australia/</guid>
      <description>Jorja Fox once starred as a rooster in the children&amp;rsquo;s classics Chicken Little. She was five years old and liked being on stage so much that she became fixated on an acting career. Three decades down the track and New York City-born Fox,36, now ranks among the most popular TV actors in the US. The rooster role, she says, will never be reprised. &amp;ldquo;I dropped out of the play, actually,&amp;rdquo; a giggling Fox told TV Guide in Los Angeles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The View</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2004/the-view/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2004/the-view/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The View&amp;rdquo; is a daytime television talk show on ABC which was created by Barbara Walters and premiered on August 11, 1997, to showcases women&amp;rsquo;s points of view on a variety of issues.
Star Jones: Please welcome Jorja Fox and George Eads!
Star: We&amp;rsquo;re out here in the sunshine&amp;hellip; you guys are used to being in Vegas because CSI is shot-
Jorja Fox: Not, not during daylight hours though. laughs, raises her hand to shade her eyes from the sun</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pulse</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2004/pulse/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2004/pulse/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Pulse&amp;rdquo; is a talk show.
Jorja appeared on the 15th episode, on 13 February 2004.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New York Daily News</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/new-york-daily-news/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/new-york-daily-news/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
In a recent episode of CBS &amp;ldquo;CSI: Crime Scene Investigation,&amp;rdquo; when team members split up to investigate a large suite of hotel rooms, Jorja Fox&amp;rsquo;s Sara Sidle announced, &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;ll take the west wing.&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;A few seasons back, Jorja Fox played a Secret Service agent guarding the President&amp;rsquo;s youngest daughter on &amp;#8216;The West Wing,&amp;ldquo;] wrote Ray Carroll of Queens, who along with Richard Lejman of Staten Island and Linda Rodriguez of Manhattan caught the joke.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>People Magazine</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/people-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/people-1/</guid>
      <description>BLUE CRUSH: Panned at past Golden Globes for lackluster looks, Jorja Fox (of the nominated drama CSI) turned heads in a good way this year in this striking blue Monique Lhullier ensemble and simple gold accessories.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hollywood.com</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/hollywood-com-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/hollywood-com-1/</guid>
      <description>It was a red carpet explosion of diamonds, designer frocks, cleavage, tuxes and legions of journalists screaming for Nicole, Jennifer, Charlize, Uma and J-Lo, among others, and Hollywood.com caught a smattering of chatter as the biggest stars of the last year descended on the Golden Globes.
[&amp;hellip;]
&amp;ldquo;We had a last minute freak-out,&amp;rdquo; said CSI&amp;rsquo;s Jorja Fox. &amp;ldquo;We all met around the corner at the Four Seasons today, so the freak out happened there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>News Articles (2004)</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/</guid>
      <description>Date Source    January 26 Hollywood.com   January 27 People Magazine   January 30 New York Daily News   April 01 TV Guide (Brisbane Australia)   May 01 Scarlet Carpet   May 14 In Touch   July 12 Hollywood Reporter   July 15 AZ Central   July 15 CBS 4 Denver   July 15 CNN   July 15 E!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>