<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Er on JFO Library</title>
    <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/tags/er/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Er on JFO Library</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Oct 2015 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://jorjafox.net/library/tags/er/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>ER Recaps</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Oct 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Retrospective</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/retrospective/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/retrospective/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Note: This episode is a clip show/retrospective and introduces no new material. All appearances include the actors as themselves.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;summary:e67abe3f7f62d6347cf72c49eb91a80d&#34;&gt;Summary&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Clips from memorable episodes; interviews with past and present cast members.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jorja returned to talk about being on the show.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;quotes:e67abe3f7f62d6347cf72c49eb91a80d&#34;&gt;Quotes&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;On watching the show:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; When you watched the show, you felt smarter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;On filming the show:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; It was absolutely terrifying for me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;What it felt like:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; I just remember just Fridays. Fridays were insane. The show would air Thursday night, across America, and people who were going to work on Fridays or getting to work on Friday, would spend a good part of their morning talking about &amp;lsquo;ER&amp;rsquo; and what had happened the night before.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;On the cast and friends:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; This is a collection of people with an amazing sense of humor. George Clooney is legendary for it, legendary.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shifting Equilbrium</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/shifting-equilbrium/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/shifting-equilbrium/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;Note: Jorja Fox does not appear in this episode.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;summary:329de6fa695be1046dca671a57f0335b&#34;&gt;Summary&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s Neela&amp;rsquo;s last day and everyone in the ER seems to have forgotten that she is leaving. Neela proves she is ready to be an attending when she and Dr. Dubenko argue about the treatment of two surgical cases. Meanwhile, Brenner has an epiphany about his troubled past.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;character-review:329de6fa695be1046dca671a57f0335b&#34;&gt;Character Review&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Doyle&amp;rsquo;s name is seen when Neela puts her nameplate on the wall of departed doctors.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Book Of Abby</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/the-book-of-abby/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/the-book-of-abby/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Note: Jorja Fox does not appear in this episode.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;summary:84b9e4adf90817e879c2a1d80fc9aacd&#34;&gt;Summary&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Neela finds out Abby&amp;rsquo;s good news second hand. Catherine Banfield and Abby butt heads on how to treat the victim of a gun shot wound, that has just been admitted into the ER. Finally, Abby comes to Sam&amp;rsquo;s defense before a nurses&amp;rsquo; disciplinary board.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;character-review:84b9e4adf90817e879c2a1d80fc9aacd&#34;&gt;Character Review&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Doyle&amp;rsquo;s name is seen when Abby puts her nameplate on the wall of departed doctors.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sticks and Stones</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/sticks-and-stones/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Mar 1999 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/sticks-and-stones/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Note: This is Maggie Doyle&amp;rsquo;s last appearance on ER.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;summary:41700f887d0af7176224cfbb4d8cc23d&#34;&gt;Summary&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;During a paramedic ride-along, Carter is forced to drive the ambulance while fleeing a riot scene and inadvertently runs over a teenage boy. Later, a paramedic is shot by an angry mob looking for the driver of the ambulance. Carol is despondent following Doug&amp;rsquo;s departure. She later discloses that she&amp;rsquo;s pregnant. Kerry is intrigued by an injured pro wrestler and his relationship with his father. Lucy tangles with an Asian family that requests their matriarch not be told of a cancerous tumor. Jeanie turns down dates with both Dr. Baker and Reggie, telling each she&amp;rsquo;s seeing someone else.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;character-review:41700f887d0af7176224cfbb4d8cc23d&#34;&gt;Character Review&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the beginning of the episode, Carter shares stories with Maggie and Jerry about his night shift ride-along with the paramedics. Later on, Maggie supervises Lucy with an elderly Chinese woman who has lung cancer that has spread to her brain and is causing seizures. Lucy offers to speak to the family instead of having Maggie do it, and is stunned to find out the family knew, and wasn&amp;rsquo;t telling the older lady because it would just depress her. Lucy tells her anyway, which proceeds another seziure. Maggie helps Lucy control the seizure, and when the woman comes to, she can&amp;rsquo;t remember a thing about the day, though the family want a new doctor. In the end, Lucy tells the woman that she has epilepsy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Throughout the entire ordeal, Maggie supports Lucy, as a good teacher should.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Storm, Part II</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/the-storm-part-ii/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Feb 1999 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/the-storm-part-ii/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;summary:b613c666a8012863bc5d8c5331668fae&#34;&gt;Summary&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Greene assists paramedics in treating injured children at a school bus accident. En route, Doug and Jeanie survive their own accident. Kerry stops Doug from treating Jeanie&amp;ndash;or any other patient. Doug decides to resign and leave Chicago for the Northwest and asks Carol to come with him. She decides against it, but he leaves anyway. Carol steps down from running the clinic so that Anspaugh will keep it open. Jeanie discovers she may have contracted hepatitis. Hospital janitor Mobalage&amp;rsquo;s wife is stabbed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;character-review:b613c666a8012863bc5d8c5331668fae&#34;&gt;Character Review&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Doyle can be seen, briefly, in this episode, working on a trauma patient.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Storm, Part I</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/the-storm-part-i/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Feb 1999 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/the-storm-part-i/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;summary:62bb582ccf357d9acdde61f714602f16&#34;&gt;Summary&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Doug faces possible criminal charges after Ricky Abbott dies when Ross shows Joi how to bypass system lockouts to give Ricky a lethal dosage of dilaudin. Doug is delegated to desk duty, Carol&amp;rsquo;s clinic is shut down for acquiring the P.C.A. machine for Ricky, and Greene and Weaver face future disciplinary action for not reporting Doug&amp;rsquo;s tampering with the double blind study. Carter and Lucy discover a mutual attraction. Benton studies with a sign language instructor.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;character-review:62bb582ccf357d9acdde61f714602f16&#34;&gt;Character Review&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Romano is made acting ER chief, much to the irritation of Kerry, Mark and, yes, Maggie Doyle. Romano tells Doyle he&amp;rsquo;s looking forward to working with her again.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Note: A few seasons later we learn that Romano had the whole &amp;lsquo;Doyle incident&amp;rsquo; filed away and shoved under the rug.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;character-notes:62bb582ccf357d9acdde61f714602f16&#34;&gt;Character Notes&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Doyle still doesn&amp;rsquo;t like Romano. Can you blame her?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Double Blind</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/double-blind/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 1999 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/double-blind/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;summary:185bfd4903aaa3140bde8e9f2af01c8e&#34;&gt;Summary&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Doug jeopardizes future federal grants for the entire ER when he breaks a double blind study by giving a sample drug to an ailing patient. Doyle lodges a sexual harassment complaint against Romano, hoping Dr. Corday will lend support. Lucy begins her surgery rotation under Benton&amp;rsquo;s tutelage. The two of them treat a man claiming to be 140-years-old. Mark declines to proceed in the NASA program. Carol questions Lynette&amp;rsquo;s intentions when she hosts a women&amp;rsquo;s health clinic for African American women only. Mark goes to bat for Pickman when she inadvertently leaves a severely injured man at an accident scene.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;character-review:185bfd4903aaa3140bde8e9f2af01c8e&#34;&gt;Character Review&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Initially Corday is asked, by Kerry, if she wants to file a complaint against Romano, since it&amp;rsquo;s been mentioned he&amp;rsquo;s a bit much with her. Corday brushes it off and says that some people have thin skin. Well as it turns out, the person who complained was Doyle. After being harassed by Romano, Doyle told him (off camera) to knock it off and in return, Romano threatened to &amp;lsquo;blast her on her eval.&amp;rsquo; So Doyle went to Kerry to file a complaint and mentioned Corday. While Corday doesn&amp;rsquo;t want to file a complaint, Doyle&amp;rsquo;s unwillingness to back down, even at the cost of her job, seems to win Corday over, and at the end of the episode, she talks to Kerry again.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;character-notes:185bfd4903aaa3140bde8e9f2af01c8e&#34;&gt;Character Notes&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Doyle&amp;rsquo;s integrity and her stubbornness of doing the right thing is not lip service, as we see her willing to risk her career to take on Romano.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;quotes:185bfd4903aaa3140bde8e9f2af01c8e&#34;&gt;Quotes&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Doyle:&lt;/strong&gt; Guess he thought anything goes with the gay chick.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Doyle :&lt;/strong&gt; Self-respect is a bitch.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Good Luck, Ruth Johnson</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/good-luck-ruth-johnson/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 1998 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/good-luck-ruth-johnson/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Note: This was ER&amp;rsquo;s 100th episode&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;summary:6c671fb4d5a9c504d08594147f4fd4b8&#34;&gt;Summary&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Carter plays tour guide for Ruth Johnson, who was born in the hospital 100 years ago to the day, and her large family. Carol treats a boy who was hit by a car and tells a story of being chased, his friend being shot in the process. Peter observes Kotlowitz install a cochlear implant and decides to wait before scheduling an operation for Reese. Mark dines with Dr. Lee, new ER chief. Dr. Corday proposes radical changes in scheduling at an M&amp;amp;M conference, and later decides to break off her relationship with Benton.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;character-review:6c671fb4d5a9c504d08594147f4fd4b8&#34;&gt;Character Review&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Doyle gives a drunk guy two doses of Ativan, however he persists in singing &amp;lsquo;One Hundred Bottles of Beer On the Wall.&amp;rsquo;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Good Fight</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/the-good-fight/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Nov 1998 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/the-good-fight/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;summary:b1063ce69619d366123db59714267453&#34;&gt;Summary&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A girl and her father are brought into the ER after a car accident. Her father abandons her in the ER, and he is the only match for her rare blood type. This forces Benton to operate on her without blood and Carter and Lucy to travel all through the city to find the father. They encounter a number of obstacles including Carter dislocating his shoulder, and end up across the street from the hospital.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;character-review:b1063ce69619d366123db59714267453&#34;&gt;Character Review&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Doyle works on the girl while she&amp;rsquo;s in the ER.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hazed and Confused</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/hazed-and-confused/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Nov 1998 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/hazed-and-confused/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;summary:9802e16a5ea8bfe3a67d951bec8b2b83&#34;&gt;Summary&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Corday commits a deadly error after being on-call for nearly 36 hours straight. Peter visits Dr. Kotlowitz and receives encouragement regarding a cochlear implant for Reese. Dr. Amanda Lee, a prospective new ER chief, visits. In the wake of a failed pregnancy attempt, Carol lashes out at a mother using abortion as a means of selective birth control. Carter and Lucy feud when Carter accidentally uses her palm computer and finds out what she thinks of him. Mark panics during a paramedic initation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;character-review:9802e16a5ea8bfe3a67d951bec8b2b83&#34;&gt;Character Review&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s Doyle who pages Corday at 6:30 AM (after Corday as been on for 24 hours) to pick up another patient.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;character-notes:9802e16a5ea8bfe3a67d951bec8b2b83&#34;&gt;Character Notes&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Doyle is as unsympathetic to her coworkers as she is to her patients.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;quotes:9802e16a5ea8bfe3a67d951bec8b2b83&#34;&gt;Quotes&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Doyle:&lt;/strong&gt; We&amp;rsquo;ve all been there!&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Corday:&lt;/strong&gt; Shut up.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day For Knight</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/day-for-knight/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 1998 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/day-for-knight/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;summary:0321b9b08f670f7c5886e53558c81c1b&#34;&gt;Summary&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Third-year med student Lucy Knight reports to the ER. Doug hits the nail on the head when he describes her as a &amp;lsquo;hit-the-book&amp;rsquo; student. Lucy&amp;rsquo;s first day finds her informing a wife of her husbands terminal condition, comforting a pregnant woman, getting locked on the roof and trying to figure out Kerry Weaver&amp;rsquo;s &amp;lsquo;Tour on Tape.&amp;rsquo; Greene extends a protective wing over Lucy, who&amp;rsquo;s forced to endure Carter&amp;rsquo;s irritation. However, asked to insert an IV, Lucy requires Carol&amp;rsquo;s help.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;character-review:0321b9b08f670f7c5886e53558c81c1b&#34;&gt;Character Review&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Doyle is seen suturing a drunk guy. Near the end of the episode, Lucy&amp;rsquo;s fellow student, Bernard, is assigned to work with Doyle, while Lucy is assigned to Carter.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Of Past Regret and Future Fear</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/of-past-regret-and-future-fear/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Apr 1998 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/of-past-regret-and-future-fear/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;summary:5f9d9cacab27a0b611564b449ea4289f&#34;&gt;Summary&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s another busy night in the ER, as case after case comes through the doors. Hathaway comforts a burn victim in his dying hours. Carter and Anna struggle with a man afflicted with cerebral palsy. Dr. Ross deals with an infant&amp;rsquo;s heroin addiction and its drug-addicted mother. Weaver cares for an elderly couple who may have AIDS. Peter and Elizabeth decide to keep their relationship a secret. Anna&amp;rsquo;s old boyfriend comes to town.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;character-review:5f9d9cacab27a0b611564b449ea4289f&#34;&gt;Character Review&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Doyle works with Kerry, and delivers lab results for a older woman who turns out to be HIV+. Doyle also works with Jeanie on a case of a 21-year-old man who jumped 75 feet from a bridge into the river. The fellow insists he was just goofing off with some friends, but beer was involved and it&amp;rsquo;s more likely he did jump. Doyle is less than sympathetic.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;character-notes:5f9d9cacab27a0b611564b449ea4289f&#34;&gt;Character Notes&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;No-nonsense Maggie is her usual self to her broken-ankle patient.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;quotes:5f9d9cacab27a0b611564b449ea4289f&#34;&gt;Quotes&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Young Guy :&lt;/strong&gt; I had a couple of beers.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Maggie :&lt;/strong&gt; Well, now you have a couple of broken ankles.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Brother&#39;s Keeper</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/my-brothers-keeper/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 1998 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/my-brothers-keeper/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;summary:647e4e9109e0c914c895f77530b1f805&#34;&gt;Summary&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Several heroin ODs are brought into the ER, including Chase Carter. Mark tries to track down Cynthia. Anna treats a John Doe sent from another hospital because he had no insurance. Doug accuses two parents of child abuse, but finds out that their child is disturbed. Benton and Corday run into his sister Jackie. Scott Anspaugh finishes his chemotherapy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;character-review:647e4e9109e0c914c895f77530b1f805&#34;&gt;Character Review&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Doyle is working the night shift, and is seen briefly at the beginning and end of the episode.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Obstruction of Justice</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/obstruction-of-justice/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 1997 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/obstruction-of-justice/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;summary:36da19d610ec2da48c4a6ee53751fcb4&#34;&gt;Summary&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Carter is arrested when he refuses to honor a warrant seeking evidence in a domestic abuse incident. Corday is overjoyed to be able to perform a rare femoral transplant. Doug returns from California. Benton and Corday discover that they have a lot in common. Cynthia takes Rachel to the dentist and other places. Jeanie threatens to sue to get her job back, to Kerry&amp;rsquo;s dismay. Anspaugh rehires her, and Al leaves for Atlanta without her. Ellis West invites Kerry to St. Bart&amp;rsquo;s.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;character-review:36da19d610ec2da48c4a6ee53751fcb4&#34;&gt;Character Review&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Doyle meets with Jeanie at Doc Magoos to introduce her to the G/L Defense Lawyers mentioned the previous week.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;character-notes:36da19d610ec2da48c4a6ee53751fcb4&#34;&gt;Character Notes&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maggie likes Jeanie, and is willing to help.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>