<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Psa on JFO Library</title>
    <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/tags/psa/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Psa on JFO Library</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="http://jorjafox.net/library/tags/psa/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>CBS Cares</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/cbs-cares/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/cbs-cares/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;While on CSI: Crime Scene Investigation, Jorja Fox and many of her cast members filmed Public Service Announcements for CBS.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;peace-2002:548a11d8667fee7c206a085a9284381e&#34;&gt;Peace (2002)&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These days, good communication takes more than phones or computers. It means getting along with people from every race or foreign culture. CBS Cares.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;mentoring-2005:548a11d8667fee7c206a085a9284381e&#34;&gt;Mentoring (2005)&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A little time with a caring adult makes a huge difference in a child&amp;rsquo;s life &amp;ndash; and you&amp;rsquo;ll be amazed at what a huge difference it makes in your life as well. Become a mentor. CBS Cares.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Orangutan Outreach</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/orangutan-outreach/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/orangutan-outreach/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Orangutan Outreach is part of BOS International. The purpose of Orangutan Outreach is:&lt;br /&gt;
* To conserve orangutans in their native habitat.&lt;br /&gt;
* To raise and promote public awareness of, and participation in, conservation strategies for orangutans through grassroots campaigns, community involvement and global communication.&lt;br /&gt;
* To collaborate with Indonesian conservationists in the running of orangutan rehabilitation centers.&lt;br /&gt;
* To fund rescue efforts of orangutans confiscated on palm oil plantations.&lt;br /&gt;
* To fund rescue efforts of orangutans held illegally by private owners, whether commercial or individual, who are in direct violation of CITES.&lt;br /&gt;
* To collaborate with zoos and animal parks in North America to promote awareness of orangutan conservation efforts.&lt;br /&gt;
* To use the Internet to provide orangutan-related curriculum materials free of charge.&lt;br /&gt;
* To fundraise locally and globally to support these goals.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;##PSA##&lt;br /&gt;
Jorja Fox recorded a PSA for Orangutan Outreach in the spring of 2008.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jorja Fox: Can you hear that? The Earth. Home to millions of species. Take a moment. Listen. In the rainforests of Borneo, orphan orangutans are being given a second chance, but they need out help. Or we&amp;rsquo;ll be left here all alone. Save the forest, save the planet, reach out and save the orangutans. To find out how you can help, please visit us online at redapes.org.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>