<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Internet on JFO Library</title>
    <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/tags/internet/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Internet on JFO Library</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="http://jorjafox.net/library/tags/internet/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>All Movie Guide Biography</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/biographies/allmovieguide/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/biographies/allmovieguide/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The lithe and attractive brunette American actress Jorja Fox entered the public eye in the late &amp;lsquo;90s and early 2000s, given her involvement as a recurrent cast member in three consecutive, top-ranked U.S. television series: ER (1994), The West Wing (1999), and CSI: Crime Scene Investigation (2000). Fox is perhaps most familiar to fans of CSI, appearing in well over 150 episodes and numerous seasons.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Born Jorja-An Fox on July 7, 1968, in New York, NY, but raised in Melbourne Beach, FL, Fox moved back to Manhattan in her teens and began a modeling career after winning a local modeling contest, then subsequently enrolled as a drama student at the Lee Strasberg Institute, where she studied acting under the aegis of legendary actor William Hickey (Prizzi&amp;rsquo;s Honor, Forget Paris). Fox&amp;rsquo;s early roles were minor and somewhat forgettable, though she debuted onscreen under the tutelage one of the finest American indie filmmakers &amp;#8212; Maggie Greenwald &amp;#8212; in that director&amp;rsquo;s well-received film noir debut The Kill-Off (1991). She followed it up with an equally dark turn, as Fate 3 (alongside future West Wing co-star Allison Janney), in John Feldman&amp;rsquo;s little-seen black comedy thriller Dead Funny (1995), and joined mentor Hickey and Alan Arkin for the best-forgotten Jerky Boys (1995) &amp;#8212; a loud, rude and obnoxious farce about a couple of prank phone callers. The film bombed with critics and the public, and disappeared instantly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fox joined the cast of the blockbuster series ER in 1996, during its third season on the air. She played Maggie Doyle, a lesbian intern at County General Hospital who launches a sexual harassment suit against a seemingly invincible administrator. The role lasted for three seasons, wrapping in 1999; that same year, Fox signed for a supporting role on The West Wing, mega-producer Aaron Sorkin&amp;rsquo;s blockbuster series drama about life in the Oval Office. In that series, Fox played Gina Toscano, the Secret Service agent hired to protect first daughter Zoey Bartlet (Elisabeth Moss) during the first and second seasons (1999-2001).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fox&amp;rsquo;s prominence rose with her comparatively higher billing in the hit CBS-Alliance-Atlantis series CSI: Crime Scene Investigation. She joined the cast of that series from its inception, as Sara Sidle, a maverick investigator who specializes in materials and elements analysis. As the series opened, team leader Gil Grissom (William Petersen) called Sidle in from her post at the San Francisco coroner&amp;rsquo;s office to investigate the death of former CSI team member Holly Gribbs. After the unit solved that case, Grissom, impressed with her work, invited her to stay on board and solve additional cases. Series writers imparted an added dimension to Sidle&amp;rsquo;s character by revealing a backstory that involved the spousal abuse of her father, her mother&amp;rsquo;s decision to commit mariticide, and her own entry into foster care.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;~ Nathan Southern, All Movie Guide&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CBS Biography</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/biographies/cbs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/biographies/cbs/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Fox&amp;rsquo;s television credits include &amp;ldquo;ER,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;West Wing,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;Law and Order,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;Ellen&amp;rdquo; and, most recently, &amp;ldquo;Drop Dead Diva.&amp;rdquo; In addition to television, her film work includes &amp;ldquo;Memento,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;How to Make the Cruelest Month,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;The Kill-Off,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;Forever Fabulous&amp;rdquo; and Down with the Joneses.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A devoted wildlife advocate, Fox recently produced the documentary film &amp;ldquo;How I Became an Elephant.&amp;rdquo; The film is about one young girl&amp;rsquo;s mission to save the elephants, as she travels to south East Asia to work with her hero The Elephant Lady and shows how everyone can make a difference.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Having appeared in numerous stage productions, Fox continues to work tirelessly in conjunction with the theater company she co-founded, Honeypot Productions. Honeypot is an independent theater company in Los Angeles, which so far has mounted six original productions, of which she has starred in four, written three and directed one.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fox is a New York native currently living in Los Angeles. Her birth date is July 7.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gist TV Biography</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/biographies/gist-tv/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/biographies/gist-tv/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Birthplace: Melbourne Beach, Florida&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Date of Birth: 07/07/1968&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-gist:5ea8aa11e95392f6dddd794067641ba9&#34;&gt;The Gist&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sara Sidle on C.S.I.: Crime Scene Investigation Special Agent Gina Tuscano on The West Wing&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jorja Fox first began as a model. When she was sixteen, she had signed a modeling contract, and had moved to New York. Soon after, she was cast in her first film, The Kill Off.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A few small appearances here and there in films like The Jerky Boys led her to a full time position as Dr. Maggie Doyle, the highly competitive new doctor in the ER, and lesbian foil to Noah Wyle&amp;rsquo;s John Carter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With that security under her belt, she has worked on a few films here and there, and is now working double duty, working on both CSI, as Sara Sidle, and The West Wing, who&amp;rsquo;s smart talking Special Agent Gina Tuscano is no large step from Maggie Doyle.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;other-credits:5ea8aa11e95392f6dddd794067641ba9&#34;&gt;Other Credits&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;film:5ea8aa11e95392f6dddd794067641ba9&#34;&gt;Film&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The Hungry Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s Club: Delmar Youngblood - 1999&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;How to Make the Cruelest Month: Sarah Bryant - 1999&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Velocity Trap: Pallas - 1997&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Kill-Off: Myra Pavlov - 1989&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;television:5ea8aa11e95392f6dddd794067641ba9&#34;&gt;Television&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;CSI: Sara Sidle - 2000&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The West Wing: Special Agent Gina Tuscano - 1999-2000&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;ER: Dr. Maggie Doyle - 1996-1999&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hollywood.com Biography</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/biographies/hollywood.com/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/biographies/hollywood.com/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Adept at playing smart, strong women, this former teen model segued to acting with guest spots in after-school specials and evening dramas. A comely, gap-toothed brunette whose good looks can&amp;rsquo;t obscure her intelligence or hard-nosed attitude, Fox became a small-screen star with a trio of plum prime-time parts. In the mid-&amp;lsquo;90s she had a recurring role as a blunt doctor on ER who turned out to be a lesbian and — like Fox — a vegetarian. In a sly nod to her character&amp;rsquo;s sexual orientation, the actress had a cameo on the famous 1997 &amp;ldquo;coming out&amp;rdquo; episode of Ellen. In 2000 Fox appeared on a different NBC drama as a Secret Service agent on The West Wing, but later that year she jumped networks when she signed on to CBS&amp;rsquo; CSI as a dedicated investigator. Although the show turned her into a bold-faced name, behind-the-scenes bickering threatened to cut her run short: In 2004, she and costar George Eads were briefly fired during a contract dispute. Three years later during another salary standoff, Fox refused to show up to shoot the series&amp;rsquo; seventh season finale when she learned that her alter ego would be killed off. The episode was reshot with a more ambiguous ending.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IMDb Biography</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/biographies/imdb/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/biographies/imdb/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Jorja Fox has become a familiar face by playing major roles in three of the most successful television dramas in history: ER (1994), The West Wing (1999) and CSI: Crime Scene Investigation (2000).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a teenager, Fox had a career as a fashion model. She then turned to formal study of the acting craft at the Lee Strasberg Institute in New York, as well as under the tutelage of veteran actor William Hickey at HB Studios.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After appearing in several minor films and TV series, Fox got her big break in 1996 by landing a role in the immensely successful ER (1994) TV series. She appeared in 33 episodes as &amp;ldquo;Dr. Maggie Doyle&amp;rdquo; who became embroiled in a sexual harassment suit against a powerful hospital administrator. Fox then got a recurring role in the renowned The West Wing (1999) TV series where she portrayed a Secret Service agent who was in charge of protecting the President&amp;rsquo;s college-age daughter. She had a key role in that series&amp;rsquo; cliffhanger episode where the President&amp;rsquo;s entourage comes under gunfire by assassins.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fox appeared as part of the regular cast of the popular TV series CSI: Crime Scene Investigation (2000) where she portrayed one of the crime scene investigators as a regular until 2008. She was a guest star of the show in 2009, recurred in 2010, and returned as a regular from 2011 to the present. Fox shared in CSI&amp;rsquo;s 2005 Screen Actors Guild award for outstanding performance by an ensemble in a drama series.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In addition to her TV and movie roles, Fox is the co-founder of an experimental stage theater production company called &amp;ldquo;Honeypot Productions&amp;rdquo;. Fox is also a musician and songwriter. She wrote and performed the song &amp;ldquo;Lullabye&amp;rdquo; which was featured in the movie Traveling Companion (1998)), as well as co-producing a musical about Dusty Springfield in Los Angeles called &amp;ldquo;Stay Forever: The Life and Music of Dusty Springfield&amp;rdquo; in 2008. In 2010, she produced a feature documentary called &amp;ldquo;How I Became An Elephant.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;IMDb Mini Biography By: Roger Burns &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:rogerburns@att.net&#34;&gt;rogerburns@att.net&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TVGuide.com Biography</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/biographies/tvguide.com/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/biographies/tvguide.com/</guid>
      <description>&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Birth Name:&lt;/strong&gt; Jorja-An Fox&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Birth Place:&lt;/strong&gt; New York, NY&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Date of Birth / Zodiac Sign:&lt;/strong&gt; 07/07/1968, Cancer&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Profession:&lt;/strong&gt; Actor&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A former teen model who segued to acting with guest spots in after-school specials and evening dramas, Fox became a small-screen star with a trio of plum prime-time parts. In the mid-&amp;lsquo;90s she had a recurring role as a blunt doctor on &lt;em&gt;ER&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;who turned out to be a lesbian and â&amp;ndash; like Fox &amp;ndash; a vegetarian. In a sly nod to her character&amp;rsquo;s sexual orientation, the actress had a cameo on the famous 1997 &amp;ldquo;coming out&amp;rdquo; episode of &lt;em&gt;Ellen&lt;/em&gt;. In 2000 Fox appeared on a different NBC drama as a Secret Service agent on &lt;em&gt;The West Wing&lt;/em&gt;, but later that year she jumped networks when she signed on to CBS&amp;rsquo; *CSI**&amp;nbsp;*as a dedicated investigator. Although the show turned her into a bold-faced name, behind-the-scenes bickering threatened to cut her run short: In 2004, she and costar George Eads were briefly fired during a contract dispute. Three years later during another salary standoff, Fox refused to show up to shoot the series&amp;rsquo; seventh season finale when she learned that her alter ego would be killed off. The episode was reshot with a more ambiguous ending. However, following her initial departure, Fox returned to the series regularly as a guest-star. Off-screen, Fox is an animal activist, noted for her work with groups like PETA and supports the non-profit farm sanctuary Animal Acres.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;##Jorja Fox Fast Facts:##&lt;br /&gt;
* At age 5,&amp;nbsp;appeared as the rooster in school production of&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;Chicken Little&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;
* Worked as a candy striper as a teen.&lt;br /&gt;
* Appeared in the classic coming-out episode of &lt;em&gt;Ellen&lt;/em&gt; (&amp;ldquo;The Puppy Episode&amp;rdquo;) in 1997.&lt;br /&gt;
* Cofounded Honeypot Productions, an independent theater company in Los Angeles.&lt;br /&gt;
* Was fired from &lt;em&gt;CSI: Crime Scene Investigation&lt;/em&gt; and then rehired (along with costar George Eads) in 2004 following a reported contract dispute.&lt;br /&gt;
* Is an animal advocate and supports the non-profit farm sanctuary Animal Acres.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;##Jorja Fox Relationships:##&lt;br /&gt;
* Mark Fox - Father&lt;br /&gt;
* Marilyn Fox - Mother&lt;br /&gt;
* Jeff Fox - Brother&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;##Jorja Fox Awards:##&lt;br /&gt;
* 2004 Screen Actors Guild Awards: Outstanding Performance by an Ensemble in a Drama Series - Winner&lt;br /&gt;
* 2003 Screen Actors Guild Awards: Outstanding Performance by an Ensemble in a Drama Series - Nominee&lt;br /&gt;
* 2002 Screen Actors Guild Awards: Outstanding Performance by an Ensemble in a Drama Series - Nominee&lt;br /&gt;
* 2001 Screen Actors Guild Awards: Outstanding Performance by an Ensemble in a Drama Series - Nominee&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>