<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>2004 on Jorja Fox Library</title>
    <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/tags/2004/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 2004 on Jorja Fox Library</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 Dec 2004 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://jorjafox.net/library/tags/2004/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>The Age</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/the-age/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Dec 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/the-age/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Here are 10 good reasons why the babe factor plays a big part in solving crimes, writes David Campbell.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What is it about women and crime that kept blokes glued to their TV sets night after night watching the many American whodunits that dominated our screens (and our most-watched lists) during 2004?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A shapely lab coat looming over a blood-spattered corpse? A cotton bud in feminine fingers seeking a DNA sample from a tattooed tough? A large gun gripped by an attractive but steely-eyed blonde?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In truth, probably all of the above and much, much more. In our own spirit of scientific investigation, here, in reverse order, are the top 10 most-watchable crime-busting women from the past year.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[ &amp;hellip; ]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At No. 5 is the hauntingly wistful Jorja Fox as investigator Sara Sidle in &lt;em&gt;CSI&lt;/em&gt;. Nobody handles a forensic clue as deftly as Sara, nor does anyone manage that puzzled-but-hurt look quite as effectively. Poor Sara not only has to deal with baffling murders, she has to cope with the infuriatingly brusque non-attention of William Petersen as senior forensics officer Gil &amp;ldquo;Married to the Job&amp;rdquo; Grissom.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[ &amp;hellip; ]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So there they are: ratings for the top 10. Not that this represents my opinion, of course. I&amp;rsquo;ve compiled the list by listening to the comments of other blokes. You see, I watch these shows exclusively for the brilliance of the scripts and the quality of the acting.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Defamer</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/defamer-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Dec 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/defamer-3/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;My friend and I sat next to &lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; while dining at Eagle &amp;ldquo;Silverlake-in-Training&amp;rdquo; Rock vegetarian eatery Fatty&amp;rsquo;s at about 2pm on Sunday. (which makes sense since Jorja is a well-known vegetarian.) She was with a female, Punky Brewster looking non-famous friend. Jorja wasn&amp;rsquo;t wearing makeup, looking pretty, but very normal. She was dressed in a khaki sweater, black tshirt and jeans, Tall and very skinny in a non-anorexic, super metabolism way. She had a very lovely conversation with the owner, but looked very nervous and self-conscious, she clearly knew everyone in the restaurant knew who she was and was looking at her- i felt bad for her. Best of all, she ate a nice, big plate of real food- something hearty with eggs. Overall, she seemed very normal, friendly, and down to earth.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Huckleberry Fund Benefit</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2004/huckleberry-fund-benefit/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Dec 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2004/huckleberry-fund-benefit/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;rdquo;&amp;lsquo;Jorja Fox:&amp;ldquo;&amp;rsquo; Um, the Huckleberry Fund is an amazing organization, they help a lot of teenagers in the Los Angeles area. It&amp;rsquo;s a very, uh, it&amp;rsquo;s a group that gets overlooked a lot and obviously a group with a lot of special needs, very specific needs, um, taking care of medical as well as psychological, developmental stuff. Um, I&amp;rsquo;m lucky enough to have a photograph inside, it&amp;rsquo;s one of my favorite things to get to do, it&amp;rsquo;s my second time doing it. And they just give you a camera and they send you out and you can take pictures of whatever you want; mine are not that good, but uh, then you send it back to them and they develop it and uh, I think it&amp;rsquo;s going to be a night of amazing artwork, uh, not only by the kids, ah, that are represented by the Huckleberry Fund, but professional photographers and, you know, dorks like me that got lucky because we got a camera. &amp;ldquo;(laughs)&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Guide</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/tv-guide-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/tv-guide-4/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hey, &lt;em&gt;CSI&lt;/em&gt; fans! You die-hards may remember &lt;strong&gt;Sarah Buxton&lt;/strong&gt; from the &amp;ldquo;Eleven Angry Jurors&amp;rdquo; episode that aired last January. She played Lana, a Las Vegas stripper who served &lt;em&gt;her&lt;/em&gt; jury duty with a heapin&amp;rsquo; helping of sass on the side. In fact, Ms. Buxton&amp;rsquo;s resum&amp;amp;e reads like a laundry list of shady-lady roles &amp;#8212; go-go girls, hookers, home-wreckers and other miscellaneous temptresses &amp;#8212; in films, prime-time TV and daytime soaps like &lt;em&gt;Sunset Beach&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;Days of our Lives&lt;/em&gt;. Tonight she returns to &lt;em&gt;CSI&lt;/em&gt; (10 pm/ET on CBS) in a part that&amp;rsquo;s very risqu&amp;eacute;, even for her.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m a transsexual murder victim,&amp;rdquo; Buxton tells TV Guide Online with a naughty grin. &amp;ldquo;A &lt;em&gt;CSI&lt;/em&gt; director saw me in an L.A. play produced by [series regular] &lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; and called with lots of compliments. He asked Jorja if I&amp;rsquo;d be offended if I were asked to play this part. She told him no, since it&amp;rsquo;s an awesome role. And he wanted a real woman, since it&amp;rsquo;s important to the plot that the victim be believable as a girl from the beginning. So I guess I&amp;rsquo;m supposed to be a successful surgery case!&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An actress possessed of a more fragile ego &lt;em&gt;might&amp;rsquo;ve&lt;/em&gt; been irked. Not Buxton. &amp;ldquo;My voice is low and I have strong features,&amp;rdquo; she says. &amp;ldquo;It&amp;rsquo;s funny, because this summer I got very close to getting a role as a transsexual in a movie. I guess I&amp;rsquo;m different looking. I never wanted to play boring girlfriend roles anyway.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Indeed, Buxton &lt;em&gt;never&lt;/em&gt; bores us. This year, the expert vamp added some much needed comic relief to &lt;em&gt;Days&lt;/em&gt;&amp;#8216; ill-conceived serial-killer story line. &amp;ldquo;I was supposed to be there for four days and it ended up being three months,&amp;rdquo; says Buxton, who played a blackmailing prostitute called Crystal Chablis. &amp;ldquo;I couldn&amp;rsquo;t &lt;em&gt;believe&lt;/em&gt; a lot of the dirty things I said on daytime TV, which I personally would never say. I&amp;rsquo;d talk about making money on my back. Or I&amp;rsquo;d say, &amp;#8216;Mmm&amp;hellip; Tasty daddy,&amp;rsquo; about &lt;strong&gt;Drake Hogestyn&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;#8216;s character, John. I&amp;rsquo;d go on and on about how I wanted to take his tasty buns in the back of a limo. We laughed for weeks.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;By the way, Crystal&amp;rsquo;s currently MIA on &lt;em&gt;Days&lt;/em&gt;. Was she written out when fans weren&amp;rsquo;t looking? &amp;ldquo;They never told me goodbye,&amp;rdquo; Buxton says. &amp;ldquo;The last thing I did was say, &amp;#8216;I think I gotta get out of town. I&amp;rsquo;ll talk to you later.&amp;rsquo; Drake had beaten me up, tied me up, and thrown water on me. He was really mean to me! But this week&amp;rsquo;s &lt;em&gt;CSI&lt;/em&gt; really takes the cake when it comes to me not being done right by a man, let me tell you.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Extra TV</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2004/extra-tv/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2004/extra-tv/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Interviewer:&lt;/strong&gt; Let&amp;rsquo;s use the microphone. Now, what do you think keeps those thirty million people coming back each week?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; Um. I think it&amp;rsquo;s just way, way, way too many TV stations, and we&amp;rsquo;re on number two, so when you turn on the television, it&amp;rsquo;s fist number that comes up. It&amp;rsquo;s much simpler than surfing&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Interviewer:&lt;/strong&gt; I think there&amp;rsquo;s a little bit more to do than that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; Uh, I just- we&amp;rsquo;ve been so blessed, so lucky and I hope we keep doing it for a long time and don&amp;rsquo;t take any single day for granted.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Interviewer:&lt;/strong&gt; Are you squemish at all when you&amp;rsquo;re doing any of these scenes?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; Mmmhmm. Yeah, continuiously squeamish. Yeah.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Interviewer:&lt;/strong&gt; Really? Why is that?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; Well. The show&amp;rsquo;s kind of violent. It&amp;rsquo;s kind of dark, and horrible things happen to people and we recreate those scenes for the crime scenes. Then we go to the morgue and then we go to the lab and we chop up pieces of their liver or their heart.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Interviewer:&lt;/strong&gt; Are you looking at real life sort of &amp;hellip; crime scene situations, trying to figure them out? Now that you&amp;rsquo;ve been doing this for a long time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; No. No, not at all.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Interviewer:&lt;/strong&gt; You just let the- this is just work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; No. I watch Disney, I watch like, cartoons for kids. And light-hearted stuff like sitcoms.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Interviewer:&lt;/strong&gt; Just get yourself far, far away from this stuff.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; Yeah.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Interviewer:&lt;/strong&gt; We&amp;rsquo;re going to test your forensics&amp;rsquo; knowledge.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; Okay.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Interviewer:&lt;/strong&gt; What&amp;rsquo;s a luminol?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; I&amp;rsquo;ll put on my game face. It&amp;rsquo;s the purple stuff.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Interviewer:&lt;/strong&gt; That does what?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; That will tell if, ah, there&amp;rsquo;s blood on a- at the crime scene or not.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Interviewer:&lt;/strong&gt; Right on! Very good!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E! - Emmy Red Carpet</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2004/emmy-red-carpet/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Sep 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2004/emmy-red-carpet/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Star Jones:&lt;/strong&gt; In the mean time my girl is here.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; Hey. (hug)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Star Jones:&lt;/strong&gt; Hey Jorja, nice to see you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; How are you?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Star Jones:&lt;/strong&gt; So we are looking at one of the stars of one of the number one shows [[CSI]] &amp;hellip;they&amp;rsquo;re still watchin&amp;rsquo; Jorja.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; Ahh, thank you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Star Jones:&lt;/strong&gt; You&amp;rsquo;ve got to show yourself off here Jorja, because everybody&amp;rsquo;s looking for you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; I&amp;rsquo;ll try&amp;hellip;okay.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Star Jones:&lt;/strong&gt; Okay, got to tell you, great figure&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; Thanks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Star Jones:&lt;/strong&gt; I&amp;rsquo;m not going to pick on you and say if you ate a doughnut you&amp;rsquo;d look pregnant, but what did you eat today girl?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; (laughs) I had a half of a real Food Daily cheeseburger.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Star Jones:&lt;/strong&gt; You did!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; That&amp;rsquo;s all I had, yeah.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Star Jones:&lt;/strong&gt; Yeah, but you did have a little cheesburger. A little nourishment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; Yeah, vegetarian with the vege bacon and the vege cheese&amp;hellip;but it&amp;rsquo;s a cheeseburger.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Star Jones:&lt;/strong&gt; But it&amp;rsquo;s still a cheeseburger.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; Oh yeah.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Star Jones:&lt;/strong&gt; You didn&amp;rsquo;t do that stalk and cellery and lettuce thing?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; No, no, no, I gave up on all that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Star Jones:&lt;/strong&gt; You did?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; No, I can&amp;rsquo;t maintain all that. And I had a little bit of vodka and 7Up in the car. But don&amp;rsquo;t tell anyone, shh.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Star Jones:&lt;/strong&gt; That&amp;rsquo;s my girl, so you&amp;rsquo;re drinking vodka and 7Up in the car, shh, don&amp;rsquo;t tell anyone&amp;hellip; what are you listening to on the radio?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; Radio didn&amp;rsquo;t work, my goodness, so we listened to you know, sky, the sky sounds, that kind of thing. Sometimes I bring CDs, but I bring em&amp;rsquo;, then I forget em&amp;rsquo;. So I try to leave them at home and I should have today because the radio was broken.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Star Jones:&lt;/strong&gt; So all over limos in Los Angeles have like a stock of Jorja Fox CDs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; (laughs) Yeah.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Star Jones:&lt;/strong&gt; You won&amp;rsquo;t have any left. Are you excited about tonight?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; I am. I love this award show.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Star Jones:&lt;/strong&gt; It&amp;rsquo;s a lot of fun.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; I&amp;rsquo;m like a little kid. And it&amp;rsquo;s so nice you know, the movie people and the TV people are together&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Star Jones:&lt;/strong&gt; Absolutely&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; And it&amp;rsquo;s kind of a small space&amp;hellip; and it feels I know it&amp;rsquo;s weird to say but kind of family, like there&amp;rsquo;s a family feel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Star Jones:&lt;/strong&gt; You know why? Because it&amp;rsquo;s actors honouring other actors, and you all are a family.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; Yes, exactly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Star Jones:&lt;/strong&gt; And I just want to tell you&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; A happy family.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Star Jones:&lt;/strong&gt; A little dysfunctional, but a family none the less. Well, we wish you the best for CSI this year.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; Thank you. You are wonderful.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Star Jones:&lt;/strong&gt; Thank you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; I love seeing you here.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Star Jones:&lt;/strong&gt; Yes, keep watchin&amp;rsquo; baby, keep watchin&amp;rsquo;, we&amp;rsquo;ll see you next time.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MSNBC</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/msnbc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Sep 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/msnbc/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Both Jorja Fox and Drea de Matteo went shopping for their vintage&lt;br /&gt;
gowns at The Paper Bag Princess, with de Matteo picking a black chiffon&lt;br /&gt;
1930s gown with gold embroidery along the neckline and waist, and Fox&lt;br /&gt;
wearing a vintage Christian Dior pink slip gown with lingerie&lt;br /&gt;
details.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>People Magazine</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/people-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Sep 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/people-2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2 OF 6&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At least CSI star Jorja Fox got her lipstick right. Other than that, she looks better suited for a prom than the red carpet in this lace-trimmed pink dress and what seem to be faux pearls.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sign On San Diego</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/sign-on-san-diego/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Sep 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/sign-on-san-diego/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Earlier on the carpet, Jorja Fox of the Emmy-nominated &amp;ldquo;CSI: Crime&lt;br /&gt;
Scene Investigation&amp;rdquo; knew it would be hours before guests at the retro-&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;lsquo;60s official Governor&amp;rsquo;s Ball - where TV clips were being shown on 72&lt;br /&gt;
plasma screens - gorged on Steak Au Poivre with Rock Shrimp and&lt;br /&gt;
Television de Chocolat. A veggie, Fox had fortified herself with a soy&lt;br /&gt;
sausage omelet &amp;ldquo;because there&amp;rsquo;s booze offered every 3 feet in there and&lt;br /&gt;
you have to be careful.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Star Magazine</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/star-magazine/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Sep 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/star-magazine/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;For three years, CSI investigators Sara Sidle (played by Jorja Fox, 34) and Warrick Brown (Gary Dourdan, 37) have worked side by side, exchanging polite professional words. But at the People&amp;rsquo;s Choice Awards on Jan 11, the actors Fox and Dourdan snuck off repeatedly to hold hands and share smokes. The couple was spotted kissing by several backstage guests. &amp;#8216;They couldn&amp;rsquo;t keep their hands off each other,&amp;rsquo; a backstage photographer tell Star. Hmmm, looks suspicious. Dourdan&amp;rsquo;s publicist, Jerry Weinman, tells Star , &amp;#8216;They&amp;rsquo;re co-stars on TV&amp;rsquo;s number one show and sure, they&amp;rsquo;ve friends, but that&amp;rsquo;s all. That&amp;rsquo;s as far as their affection for each other goes.&amp;rsquo; Maybe..maybe not. Twice, an eyewitness tells Star, a handler at the event had to step in to tell the couple to stop touching each other. We&amp;rsquo;re not going to call this case closed, but as they say on CSI, &amp;#8216;The evidence never lies.&amp;rsquo;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Star Online</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/star-online/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Sep 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/star-online/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Glamour mixes with relaxed attitudes as stars enter the Shrine&lt;br /&gt;
Auditorium&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; star Jorja Fox gave a lot of thought to&lt;br /&gt;
preparing for the Emmy Awards&amp;rsquo; red carpet, but that did not save her&lt;br /&gt;
from some minor embarrassment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;I told my stylist I had to wear pink. I brought out 13 dresses,&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fox said in an interview Sunday just a few yards from the doors of the&lt;br /&gt;
Shrine Auditorium.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;It took me one-and-one-half hours to get ready and 15 minutes to&lt;br /&gt;
put on my dress,&amp;rdquo; she said.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then she opened her purse to show the products she brought to&lt;br /&gt;
continue to look glamorous on a windy and cooler-than-usual Emmy day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All that work, all that preparation, but not everything went&lt;br /&gt;
according to plan.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;What&amp;rsquo;s the most embarrassing thing that happened to me? In the last&lt;br /&gt;
hour?&amp;rdquo; she said.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fox said she went to an E! Channel interview and accidentally&lt;br /&gt;
interrupted the hosts trying to introduce her on live television.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fox, who almost left &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; over a contract dispute but came back&lt;br /&gt;
after temporarily being fired, said her character, Sara Sidle, will&lt;br /&gt;
continue to be in trouble. &amp;ldquo;Sara lives in a rabbit hole. It&amp;rsquo;s been like&lt;br /&gt;
a roller-coaster ride,&amp;rdquo; she said about the plot line.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Paper Bag Princess</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/the-paper-bag-princess/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Sep 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/the-paper-bag-princess/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;September 19, 2004 (Los Angeles)&lt;/strong&gt; In support of her Emmy-nominated series CSI: Crime Scene Investigation, this raven-haired beauty will hit the red carpet at tomorrow night&amp;rsquo;s Emmys ceremony in a glamorous pale pink vintage Christian Dior slip gown with ivory lace insets from The Paper Bag Princess. Jorja will accessorize her gorgeous gown with a vintage ivory floral beaded pouch bag with gold edge and handle, also from The Paper Bag Princess.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Northwest Herald</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/northwest-herald/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Aug 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/northwest-herald/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;CSI: Crime Scene Investigation&amp;rdquo; actress Jorja Fox is looking back on her and cast mate George Eads&amp;rsquo; temporary firing from the show as &amp;ldquo;a very bad dream that lingered. You think, &amp;#8216;This can&amp;rsquo;t really be happening,&amp;rsquo; but it is.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In her first interview since the highly publicized souring of the actors&amp;rsquo; contract renegotiations, Fox tells us she feels she and Eads have been unfairly slammed by some of the media  and that much of what has been reported about the dispute and its resolution has been inaccurate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Seven of the eight cast members had put in for a raise  probably all eight did, but I can only confirm seven,&amp;rdquo; she says. &amp;ldquo;When you are lucky enough to be on a show that&amp;rsquo;s a hit, you put in for a raise. That is commonly done &amp;hellip; There have been some very ugly contract renegotiations in Hollywood, but I didn&amp;rsquo;t think this was going to be one of those by any means. I&amp;rsquo;m not one to make demands and hold out. That&amp;rsquo;s not my style. I&amp;rsquo;m not a thug. It was kind of a bunch of strange events that lined up for this to happen.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fox reveals that &amp;ldquo;to CBS&amp;rsquo;s credit,&amp;rdquo; she was offered a raise, &amp;ldquo;but I decided not to take it for two reasons. One, it would have said this was about the money, and it wasn&amp;rsquo;t about the money. And two, George was out at that time, and we didn&amp;rsquo;t know what was going to happen, and to achieve or acquire something on the event of someone else&amp;rsquo;s firing just didn&amp;rsquo;t feel right to me.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The actress refrains from getting into specifics, and &amp;ldquo;I won&amp;rsquo;t talk about George.&amp;rdquo; She will say, &amp;ldquo;It&amp;rsquo;s definitely easier to be fired with a buddy, and it sounds terrible, but George is someone wonderful to be fired with.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They commiserated during their ouster and had a drink together once it was over. This week, she reports, six of the cast members are doing a scene together, and &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m sure the mood will be celebratory. We shut down for 10 days over this, and in that time, everyone in the cast and crew had a chance to think about how much we love doing this show. Coming back, it&amp;rsquo;s been kind of like a renewal of vows.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New York City</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/new-york-city-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Aug 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/new-york-city-2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;It&amp;rsquo;s like if you have a large rock fall on your head &amp;hellip; you absolutely don&amp;rsquo;t want another rock to fall on you!&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; actress Jorja Fox, talking tentatively for the first time about the shocking firing of her and co-star George Eads, and then the equally startling turnaround when CBS rehired them. &amp;ldquo;CSI,&amp;rdquo; a gritty, graphic forensic drama, is TV&amp;rsquo;s top-rated series and has spawned a successful spinoff, &amp;ldquo;CSI: Miami.&amp;rdquo; (Hollywood monolith Jerry Bruckheimer is the &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; producing power.) Fox and Eads have been with the show since it began. Money was at the heart of the matter, so the rumors went, when the actors supposedly didn&amp;rsquo;t show up for work. Eads, who starred in TNT&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Evel Knievel&amp;rdquo; last week, has insisted that he overslept. Fox, who says she is &amp;ldquo;still in shock&amp;rdquo; from the professional push- pull, says the issue was not cash-related:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;I can say that it absolutely wasn&amp;rsquo;t over money. But I can also say it is still something of a mystery to me. I mean, I don&amp;rsquo;t act for money. That&amp;rsquo;s not where I live, so to speak. I&amp;rsquo;ve done other things, had other jobs, where it was about money and putting a roof over my head and eating, but I don&amp;rsquo;t put a price on my acting. Although naturally I think everybody&amp;rsquo;s entitled to a raise when that time comes.&amp;rdquo; (Fans know Jorja from the film &amp;ldquo;Memento&amp;rdquo; and from her original exposure in &amp;ldquo;ER.&amp;rdquo;)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So why does she think she was fired? Fox, who emphasizes that she is &amp;ldquo;elated&amp;rdquo; to be back at work, replies carefully: &amp;ldquo;Well, it was over this letter that we were all asked to sign about reporting to work, and I&amp;rsquo;d really never seen such a letter in my life - my professional life - and I think they didn&amp;rsquo;t like my response &amp;hellip; I just don&amp;rsquo;t think the punishment fit the &amp;#8216;crime.&amp;rsquo; No threats were being made, nobody was asking for the sun, moon and stars &amp;hellip; and then, just as suddenly, CBS offered an olive branch. I really see this as a misunderstanding.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is clear the actress doesn&amp;rsquo;t want to get too specific (that first rock was a stunner) and her voice betrays considerable emotion and controlled indignation. It is humiliating to be fired, but she wants to put it behind her; there&amp;rsquo;ll be no prolonged autopsy on this event. She adds with rueful amusement, &amp;ldquo;I have no foresight. You know when I got &amp;#8216;CSI,&amp;rsquo; I thought, &amp;#8216;What a great show; nobody&amp;rsquo;ll watch this!&amp;lsquo;&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Still and all, we had to ask: Did she get a raise? &amp;ldquo;To CBS&amp;rsquo; credit, they did offer me more money. But I turned it down.&amp;rdquo; Why? &amp;ldquo;For one thing, George&amp;rsquo;s head was still on the block - it would have looked like I was dancing on his misfortune. And, again, that&amp;rsquo;s not what it was about.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On to happier subjects. Jorja&amp;rsquo;s theater company,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Honeypot Productions, has a well-reviewed musical running in L.A., &amp;ldquo;Dear Bernard.&amp;rdquo; She describes it with such enthusiasm, we suggest, &amp;ldquo;Why don&amp;rsquo;t you film it, put it on TV?&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;That&amp;rsquo;s an interesting idea,&amp;rdquo; she says.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Get CBS to do it. After all, if you didn&amp;rsquo;t get a raise, you should get something.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The actress laughs, &amp;ldquo;Oh, I don&amp;rsquo;t know about that. Remember, they offered the olive branch. Not the whole tree!&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AZ Central</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/az-central-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jul 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/az-central-2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt;, the &lt;em&gt;CSI: Crime Scene Investigation&lt;/em&gt; star who was fired for skipping work in a salary dispute, is returning to the hit CBS drama at her old $100,000-per-episode salary.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fox reached an agreement with the network and will be back on the set next week, the Associated Press reports.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Apparently, Fox did a better job cleaning CBS chief **Leslie Moonves&amp;rsquo; **floors with her toothbrush than did fellow *CSI *firee &lt;strong&gt;George Eads&lt;/strong&gt;. At last report, Eads, who&amp;rsquo;s spent much of the past week apologizing for &amp;ldquo;oversleeping&amp;rdquo; to anyone with a microphone, was still out of a job, although TV Guide Online reports that he probably will be rehired.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>