<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>2013 on JFO Library</title>
    <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/tags/2013/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 2013 on JFO Library</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2013 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://jorjafox.net/library/tags/2013/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>USA Today</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2013/usa-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2013/usa-today/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; actress Jorja Fox has made rescuing lions one of her life&amp;rsquo;s missions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;rdquo;&amp;lsquo;What:&amp;ldquo;&amp;rsquo; Animal Defenders International (ADI) ambassador&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;rdquo;&amp;lsquo;Why:&amp;ldquo;&amp;rsquo; &amp;#8216;I&amp;rsquo;ve been passionate about habitats, preservation and animals in captivity for a long time,&amp;rdquo; says Fox, who appears in and is an associate producer of the documentary Lion Ark. &amp;ldquo;We&amp;rsquo;re at a very critical time for this work to happen. We can do a lot better by these animals. We all know that.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;rdquo;&amp;lsquo;When:&amp;ldquo;&amp;rsquo; Lion Ark, which follows 25 lions rescued from illegal traveling circuses across Bolivia through their journey to a sanctuary in Colorado, is now at festival screenings ([&lt;a href=&#34;http://lionarkthemovie.com/screenings&#34;&gt;http://lionarkthemovie.com/screenings&lt;/a&gt; lionarkthemovie.com/screenings]).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Most of these lions had never put their paws to grass, yet alone had acres and acres to meander,&amp;rdquo; Fox says. &amp;ldquo;It&amp;rsquo;s a feel good movie; in many ways, sort of a mission impossible. I knew it was going to be an outstanding amazing thing for these animals. I underestimated what a great human story it was going to be. It really is true, a small group of people can come together and work diligently to make really big changes in something they are passionate about.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;rdquo;&amp;lsquo;Learn:&amp;ldquo;&amp;rsquo; [&lt;a href=&#34;http://ADIrescuediary.com&#34;&gt;http://ADIrescuediary.com&lt;/a&gt; ADIrescuediary.com]&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ecorazzi</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2013/ecorazzi/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2013/ecorazzi/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;rdquo;&amp;lsquo;Jorja Fox&amp;rdquo;&amp;rsquo; has a new best friend that she wasnt expecting to find.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The actress recently told People magazine that after losing her beloved dog, she didnt feel ready yet to welcome a new dog into her heart when she ended up rescuing a poodle mix named Bexar (the name is pronounced &amp;ldquo;bear&amp;rdquo;).&amp;ldquo;When we found each other, I had just lost my dog of 14 years. I actually spent the first months kind of pushing her away a bit and she did the same to me,&amp;rdquo; she said.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The two have become buddies, though. Fox added, &amp;ldquo;Then all of a sudden, it flipped, and now I&amp;rsquo;m completely in love with her. She&amp;rsquo;s the coolest, little scruffy dog I ever knew&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The star of CSI: Crime Scene Investigation&amp;rdquo;might be a full-time rescuer if not her for her acting job. She said, &amp;ldquo;If my life had gone in a different direction, this is something I mightve gone into. Animal welfare has given me an anchor in life.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Among other efforts, Fox has also advocated for a vegetarian diet, spoken out against circus cruelty, and been honored for her work helping to rescue 29 circus lions with Bob Barker and Animal Defenders International (ADI). Fox is one of ADIs ambassadors.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>People Pets</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2013/people-pets/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2013/people-pets/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Jorja Fox wasn&amp;rsquo;t quite ready to adopt a new dog. The &amp;ldquo;CSI: Crime Scene Investigation&amp;rdquo; star was still mourning the loss of her old pet, who died in January, when a scruffy little mutt came into her life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;When we found each other, I had just lost my dog of 14 years,&amp;rdquo; she reveals in an interview with Sweden with Love. Bexar (pronounded &amp;ldquo;bear&amp;rdquo;) had been found roaming the streets of San Antonio, Texas, but it wasn&amp;rsquo;t exactly love at first sight.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;I actually spent the first months kind of pushing her away a bit and she did the same to me  Then all of a sudden, it flipped, and now I&amp;rsquo;m completely in love with her,&amp;rdquo; Fox admits. &amp;ldquo;She&amp;rsquo;s the coolest, little scruffy dog I ever knew.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While Fox has fallen head over heels for the poodle mix, she&amp;rsquo;s also passionate about saving other animals in her role as ambassador for Animal Defenders International. The 45-year-old was involved rescuing 25 lions from circuses in Bolivia, and was in the airport hangar when the plane carrying the big cats touched down in Colorado, en route to their new home at the Wild Animal Sanctuary.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Their arrival  which is the subject of the documentary Lion Ark, premiering in N.Y.C. and L.A. on Nov. 15  was an emotional experience. &amp;ldquo;Lions were roaring from one section of the hangar to the other, trying to find their family members,&amp;rdquo; she says. &amp;ldquo;It&amp;rsquo;s a sound like nothing you&amp;rsquo;ve ever heard before  You can feel those roars in your muscles and bones.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fox, who celebrated the 300th episode of CSI at the end of October, is very passionate about animal rescue. &amp;ldquo;If my life had gone in a different direction, this is something I might&amp;rsquo;ve gone into,&amp;rdquo; she says. &amp;ldquo;Animal welfare has given me an anchor in life.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sweden With Love</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2013/sweden-with-love/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2013/sweden-with-love/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Actress** Jorja Fox** is standing in the middle of an airplane hangar in Boulder, Colorado, watching the doors of a Bolivian cargo jet open up. While the sun sets over the Rocky Mountains, individual crates housing twenty-five African lions are unloaded. Although from different prides, the lions share the same fate: rescued from circus abuse, they&amp;rsquo;re about to embark on a new life. All of a sudden, one lion after the other starts roaring, the sound bouncing off the walls in the giant hangar. A lion&amp;rsquo;s roar can travel up to five miles, and the roars turn into a symphony never before heard on the Colorado plains. &amp;ldquo;It&amp;rsquo;s a sound that completely penetrates you,&amp;rdquo; says Jorja. &amp;ldquo;You can feel those roars in your muscles and bones. If something like that had happened in the wild, where I was surrounded by twenty-five lions, I would&amp;rsquo;ve been petrified! But I wasn&amp;rsquo;t scared. It was one of the most amazing things I&amp;rsquo;ve ever felt.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Animal rescuer is a role that suits Jorja perfectly. A vegetarian since age 18, she became an ambassador for Animal Defenders International six years ago and has since saved both elephants and lions. The historic lion rescue, which is the subject of the documentary &lt;em&gt;Lion Ark&lt;/em&gt;, is the largest of its kind and was the result of ADI&amp;rsquo;s work helping ban the use of circus animals in Bolivia. &amp;ldquo;If you knew the abuse the animals suffer behind-the-scenes, you would never set your foot in a circus,&amp;rdquo; says Jorja. &amp;ldquo;There are far cooler things these animals can be doing.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At home in Los Angeles, the actress spends time with another four-legged creature, her rescue dog Bexar. And she gets a major kick out of her role as Sara Sidle on &lt;em&gt;CSI: Crime Scene Investigation&lt;/em&gt;, which recently celebrated its 300th episode. &amp;ldquo;The scripts still give me nightmares!&amp;rdquo; says Jorja, who also starred on &lt;em&gt;ER&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;The West Wing&lt;/em&gt;. &amp;ldquo;I only read them at night if I&amp;rsquo;m absolutely desperate. I rather get up first thing in the morning so my brain has all day to organize all those gory details and put them away somewhere before I go to bed.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jorja, who was photographed for &lt;em&gt;Sweden With Love&lt;/em&gt; by &lt;strong&gt;Elizabeth Messina&lt;/strong&gt;, has a quick, easy laugh that is utterly contagious. In an &lt;strong&gt;exclusive interview&lt;/strong&gt;, she talks surprisingly honestly — and hilariously — about being in her mid 40s. She also dishes on working with the &amp;ldquo;very distracting&amp;rdquo; &lt;strong&gt;George Clooney&lt;/strong&gt; for three years on &lt;em&gt;ER&lt;/em&gt;, how she keeps in shape and the secret passion she&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;not very good at&amp;rdquo; but still loves. Jorja&amp;rsquo;s kindness and gutsy spirit is refreshing, and her joy for life is contagious. Enjoy!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ulrica: It&amp;rsquo;s not often you find a woman — especially in Hollywood — as comfortable in her own skin as you are. You seem to have avoided all the trappings of turning 40.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; You know, I tried to lie about my age for years! I cheated myself down five years for the longest time. But then one day, the Internet just corrected it. Now, my age is everywhere and there&amp;rsquo;s no way to escape it. Everybody knows how old I am! I couldn&amp;rsquo;t hide it even if I wanted to.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ulrica: How do you deal with the pressure of staying eternally young? I think we all experience it on some level, even if we&amp;rsquo;re not in the public eye like you are.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; It really helps to have other women around you that are about the same age and who look and feel great about themselves. You know what&amp;rsquo;s cool? Elisabeth Shue and I are on the show together and we&amp;rsquo;re close in age. She&amp;rsquo;s gorgeous and down-to-earth and that&amp;rsquo;s really inspiring to me. It&amp;rsquo;s so fun, especially now being in my mid 40s, to have another woman around who is dealing with the same issues I am. I look at her and go, ‘Wow, she looks amazing!&amp;rsquo; I don&amp;rsquo;t think any of us ever thought we&amp;rsquo;d get old on &lt;em&gt;CSI&lt;/em&gt;, and no, we&amp;rsquo;re not getting old yet, but we&amp;rsquo;re aging very publicly and sometimes that can be hard. It&amp;rsquo;s a good problem to have, of course, but it&amp;rsquo;s nice to be able to share thoughts about wrinkles with other women who are the same age as you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ulrica: You know that phenomenon that happens when you live in L.A. and no one ever gets older? Do you ever feel that way?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; Yes! I have a grandmother here, so I see a whole bunch of senior citizens regularly. But I don&amp;rsquo;t really see people aging. There doesn&amp;rsquo;t seem to be anyone in between here. There are senior citizens and then there are all these other ageless people. I guess you&amp;rsquo;ve got to go somewhere else, you&amp;rsquo;ve got to disappear for a decade, and then come back and reintroduce yourself as a senior citizen with white hair [laugh].&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;**Ulrica: I find that, for each year that goes by, there&amp;rsquo;s also a greater sense of freedom because you stop caring about all the crap you used to care about.&lt;br /&gt;
**&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; You&amp;rsquo;re so right. I really don&amp;rsquo;t care about what people think about me and it&amp;rsquo;s such a relief. When I was in my 20s and 30s, I always thought about how I was perceived. Was I pretty enough? Was I cool enough? I just don&amp;rsquo;t have those anxieties anymore. I don&amp;rsquo;t worry about if I&amp;rsquo;m pretty enough or cool enough or fashionable enough. Those are the shallow ways we torture ourselves when we&amp;rsquo;re younger! That said, it&amp;rsquo;s still really important to me how people perceive me in terms of being a decent human being. But that stage when you&amp;rsquo;re constantly worrying about if you&amp;rsquo;re pretty enough or loud enough or quiet enough or &lt;em&gt;anything&lt;/em&gt; enough? I&amp;rsquo;m so glad I&amp;rsquo;m over that stage. There&amp;rsquo;s such freedom in not having to worry about those things.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ulrica: Okay, give me the dirt. You worked with George Clooney for three years on &lt;em&gt;ER&lt;/em&gt;. Is he really as cool as he seems?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; Yes, he&amp;rsquo;s really as cool as he seems. He really is. Even from thirty feet away, there&amp;rsquo;s that energy and charisma. You can&amp;rsquo;t quite escape it. It&amp;rsquo;s this amazingness and sexiness that radiate from wherever he is. It&amp;rsquo;s really &lt;em&gt;really&lt;/em&gt; distracting! I don&amp;rsquo;t think I ever got over it, even during the three years that I worked with him. On top of that, he&amp;rsquo;s so funny and disarming. During rehearsals, he would spend the entire time telling jokes and doing pranks. You never rehearsed until you were shooting with him. It would always throw me off my game. So yes, he&amp;rsquo;s a really great, talented and very distracting man!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;**Ulrica: &lt;em&gt;ER&lt;/em&gt; was a huge hit when you joined the cast, and that was a big turning point for you. So many actors on that show were catapulted into fame. Were you scared at all? **&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; I was completely terrified. I thought, &amp;ldquo;This is the moment when everyone in the world is going to realize I&amp;rsquo;m an impostor.&amp;rdquo; So many people were watching that show. There was this very real moment, the day before I was going to start on &lt;em&gt;ER&lt;/em&gt;, when I was sitting in my apartment in LA mapping out my escape to Mexico. I had it all planned out. I was going to drive to Mexico that night and be there before the morning. I would then call my manager and say I&amp;rsquo;d quit acting before any damage had been done. It was that moment of, &amp;ldquo;This is it. You either get out now or you move forward.&amp;rdquo; Fortunately, I decided to move forward. But every day I was there, I thought, &amp;ldquo;If they don&amp;rsquo;t fire me today, they&amp;rsquo;ll fire me tomorrow.&amp;rdquo; I still think that sometimes when I drive in to work on &lt;em&gt;CSI&lt;/em&gt;. It certainly keeps me on my toes. But I&amp;rsquo;ve been on a show now for 18 consecutive seasons now, so I&amp;rsquo;m going to have to go for 20!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;**Ulrica: As a child, I never felt comfortable visiting the zoo or going to the circus, and I refuse to take my own kids to a circus or a zoo now. So your work raising awareness about animals in circuses really speaks to me. **&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; So many of us, when we were kids and went to the circus or the zoo or the marine park for the first time, sensed there was something we didn&amp;rsquo;t like. Yes, it&amp;rsquo;s amazing to be able to see these animals, but the conditions they&amp;rsquo;re living in are not right. You take these huge land mammals like elephants, who easily walks 30 miles a day in the wild, and put them in tiny cages until they have to perform, sometimes several times a day, for years and years until they die. They&amp;rsquo;re abused, hit and scared into performing and they develop serious mental and physical illnesses. The bull hook, for example, is a standard instrument used for training elephants and it&amp;rsquo;s very violent. Watching &lt;em&gt;Lion Ark&lt;/em&gt;, it&amp;rsquo;s so easy to connect the dots.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ulrica: Why do you think there&amp;rsquo;s such a disconnect between our natural love for animals and the way they&amp;rsquo;re actually treated in our society?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; I think we&amp;rsquo;re taught from a very early age to have a certain mindset in relation to animals. They&amp;rsquo;re in our clothing, in our diets, in our makeup…they&amp;rsquo;re entertainment and they&amp;rsquo;re our pets. In some ways, you have to shut down to accept some of the roles animals play in modern society. You have to detach and disassociate yourself with the meat that&amp;rsquo;s in the grocery store, or the animals performing at the circus, or the leather shoes you&amp;rsquo;re wearing, in order to live life a certain way. You don&amp;rsquo;t have to think about your dinner choices at all, unless you really want to go out of your way to think about them. Society makes it easy for us to ignore these complex issues. But I think twenty years from now, with these environmental issues reaching such critical mass, there will be enormous progress in terms of the way we treat animals. I think people are very compassionate in general, and we all want to do the right thing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ulrica: So many people say, ‘Why do you care about animal rights when people are starving all over the world?&amp;rsquo;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; I&amp;rsquo;m extremely passionate about human rights, environmental rights &lt;em&gt;and&lt;/em&gt; animal welfare and it would be very hard for me to separate the three. They&amp;rsquo;re all interconnected and interrelated. If you look beneath the surface of an animal welfare issue, you&amp;rsquo;ll usually find an environmental issue and a human rights issue.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ulrica: You&amp;rsquo;ve been a vegetarian for 25 years. Why is that?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; I believe in non-violence, so it was a really easy thing for me to do. Living in New York and Los Angeles, there was no reason for me to eat meat for my survival. It&amp;rsquo;s worked out really great and I don&amp;rsquo;t miss meat at all. For me, it was never really for health reasons, but so many of the things we&amp;rsquo;re now learning about health and nutrition makes it a really exciting time to be a vegetarian or vegan. The cuisine is busting out! Some of the most exciting cuisine on the planet is happening in vegetarian or vegan cooking.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;**Ulrica: I became a vegan on a silly dare two years ago, just because I wanted to lose weight after I had my third child. I know my intentions were not the most honorable, but my body felt so different that I stuck with it. And I swear, in the process, my heart changed. In general, I just feel more compassion. **&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja&lt;/strong&gt;: That&amp;rsquo;s fascinating! I was 18 when I became a vegetarian, so I don&amp;rsquo;t remember some of the more subtle things, but it doesn&amp;rsquo;t shock me. You know, even if you don&amp;rsquo;t want to become a vegetarian or vegan, it&amp;rsquo;s a great thing to try out. Do meatless Mondays to start, and see how you feel. Even if you don&amp;rsquo;t care about animals or the environment, you&amp;rsquo;ll lose weight and you&amp;rsquo;ll feel better. And if you do care about animals and the environment…truthfully, the single greatest thing anyone could do for animals or the environment on a daily basis is to become a vegetarian or vegan.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ulrica: We need to talk about your dog Bexar, because she&amp;rsquo;s too adorable!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja&lt;/strong&gt;: She was found roaming the streets of San Antonio, Texas, so that&amp;rsquo;s why I named her Bexar. She&amp;rsquo;s a curly, floppy mutt that probably has some poodle in her. When we found each other, I had just lost my dog of fourteen years. My dog died in January, and when Bexar showed up in my life in May I wasn&amp;rsquo;t quite ready for another dog. I actually spent the first months kind of pushing her away a bit, and she did the same to me. I don&amp;rsquo;t think she wanted me, either! Then all of a sudden, it flipped. Now I&amp;rsquo;m completely in love with her. I adore her and she&amp;rsquo;s amazing. She&amp;rsquo;s the coolest, little scruffiest dog I ever knew.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ulrica: I know you love to surf. Is that how you keep fit?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; I never feel all that fit, but I love to work out because it calms my mind. I love to surf. I love to just be in the ocean and be a part of nature, and it keeps you really fit. Paddling out gives you a great arm and back workout. I also do yoga, and I take my dog [she has a rescue mutt, part poodle, that she found in Texas] on hikes. When I can&amp;rsquo;t go surfing, I work out with my trainer John Pierre at home. We have a routine I just started this summer that is tailored for me and keeps my body fit for surfing when I can&amp;rsquo;t get out in the water.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ulrica: Lastly, do you have a secret talent no one knows about?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; [laugh] Probably not! But I really love to garden. I won&amp;rsquo;t say I&amp;rsquo;m any good at it, but I love it so much. And I love to meander around my house. I&amp;rsquo;ve never had a designer or a decorator. I don&amp;rsquo;t have any talent for home decor, but it&amp;rsquo;s something that I secretly enjoy when I have the time. I like to find things that are vintage or reclaimed. I&amp;rsquo;ve had my house for almost ten years, and it&amp;rsquo;s still not done! But part of me doesn&amp;rsquo;t want it to be done, because I don&amp;rsquo;t want the project to be over. There are still rooms that need to be painted and pieces I have to find, like a new table for my breakfast nook. I&amp;rsquo;ve been looking for that table for two years! So even though it&amp;rsquo;s not something I&amp;rsquo;m talent at, it&amp;rsquo;s a secret passion.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jorja recently produced the award-winning documentary &lt;em&gt;How I Became An Elephant&lt;/em&gt;, about one young girl&amp;rsquo;s mission to travel to Asia to work with her hero, The Elephant Lady, and save elephants in captivity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ISSUES with Jane Velez-Mitchell</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2013/issues-with-jane-velez-mitchell/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2013/issues-with-jane-velez-mitchell/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jane Velez-Mitchell: CSI star Jorja Fox plays a determined crime scene investigator, who won&amp;rsquo;t let anything stand in her pursuit of the truth. When she&amp;rsquo;s off the set, she&amp;rsquo;s just as determined to free animals from captivity. I talked to Jorja about why she thinks Blackfish is a giant step for all animals in captivity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[Clip of CSI]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jane Velez-Mitchell: Jorja Fox, you play Sara Sidle on CSI and you do such a great job of investigating. In this movie, Blackfish, the director describes it as an investigation into what lies below the surface. Do you relate to that?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jorja Fox: Absolutely, and I&amp;rsquo;m so very thrilled that this documentary is out there and it&amp;rsquo;s going to be televised. I think that this is an issue that people are really going to respond to in a powerful, powerful way. And it&amp;rsquo;s a story whose time has come.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jane Velez-Mitchell: So when Sea World says &amp;ldquo;Hey, we&amp;rsquo;re the leaders in animal husbandry, we&amp;rsquo;re breeding these orcas in captivity.&amp;rdquo; is that a good thing or a bad thing in your opinion?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jorja Fox: It&amp;rsquo;s a bad thing, in my opinion. And it&amp;rsquo;s a pointless thing, in my opinion. It&amp;rsquo;s absolutely pointless. These animals live really long lives, sometimes, if they&amp;rsquo;re lucky, they live shorter lives. A life in captivity, for a wild marine mammal, is a life of suffering and misery and loneliness. It goes against every innate desire that they have.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[Clip of the movie]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jorja Fox: A good number of these captive orcas and killer whales were rounded up in a certain time in history. We have watched these pods in the wild for many years. We know where most of these orcas and killer whales, we know where their families are, we know where their pods are &amp;#8212;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jane Velez-Mitchell: So you endorse what Russell Simmons suggested? Change it radically, eliminate the performance of the orcas or shut down?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jorja Fox: I think the future that we&amp;rsquo;re looking at, if these animals can&amp;rsquo;t be released into the wild, then we can do much better by them. I&amp;rsquo;m talking about sanctuaries, I&amp;rsquo;m talking about ecological preserves, marine preserves, where these animals can live out their lives in somewhat more of a normal way. My first and foremost idea would be lets release as many of these animals as we can into the wild, and lets take the risk and see what happens.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(COMMERCIAL BREAK)&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TVGuide.com</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2013/tvguide-06/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2013/tvguide-06/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Wednesday&amp;rsquo;s episode of CSI marks the CBS procedural&amp;rsquo;s 300th episode, and no matter how you slice it, that&amp;rsquo;s a lot of murder.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Realizing the show would reach the milestone this season, executive producer Don McGill says they wanted this entire season in general, and the 300th episode in particular, to look back at the show&amp;rsquo;s history. &amp;ldquo;When Carol and I talked about the season, [we thought,] &amp;#8216;Back to the beginning,&amp;lsquo;&amp;rdquo; McGill says. &amp;ldquo;And looking at episode 300, literally we do go back to the beginning. We reference a case that was the one that got away for our CSIs.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The case hits particularly close to home for Sara (Jorja Fox). &amp;ldquo;It was her first high-profile case when she came to Las Vegas,&amp;rdquo; Fox tells us. &amp;ldquo;She&amp;rsquo;s getting a second chance at something. She&amp;rsquo;s been dealing with the family for all these years and not having the answers. There&amp;rsquo;s a weight and a sadness that she carries. But by the end, I think she absolutely gets some closure. And she feels fairly anchored, as much as Sara can.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The case involves a reclusive casino mogul (guest star Jason Priestley) who is suspected in a crime eerily similar to the case from 14 years ago. As the CSIs dig for clues, the show uses what McGill calls &amp;ldquo;faux-backs&amp;rdquo; to tie the two cases together. In addition to seeing Sara and Greg (Eric Szmanda) in circa 2000 looks, the episode also welcomes back original cast member Marg Helgenberger as Catherine Willows.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;We created these little vignettes,&amp;rdquo; McGill says. &amp;ldquo;It gave us a chance to have a window in the evolution of the characters. You could really see how far Sara has come, how far Greg has come, the influence of Catherine. It was a really fun opportunity to give a nod to how great the show is and how its longevity has really created this dynamic where we&amp;rsquo;ve seen the characters grow and evolve.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The episode will feature lots of Easter eggs, including 14 different references to the number 300. But Mendelsohn says the episode also pays appropriate homage to the show&amp;rsquo;s history. &amp;ldquo;Everybody&amp;rsquo;s been asking, &amp;#8216;What are your favorite episodes? What moments do you remember the best on set?&amp;lsquo;&amp;rdquo; she says. &amp;ldquo;And because we want to hark back to those iconic moments of the past, we flash back to some of the golden oldie cases. We took a poll among all the writers: What are your favorite cases? And those are the cases we flash back to during the episode.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In particular, the show pays homage to the show&amp;rsquo;s original protagonist and leader, William Petersen&amp;rsquo;s Gil Grissom. Although Grissom has only appeared a handful of times since the character was written out in Season 9, his spirit seems to always loom over the action. Mendelsohn gives Petersen credit for much of the show&amp;rsquo;s success.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Billy said, &amp;#8216;I do not want Gil Grissom to always be right.&amp;rsquo; That became our mantra,&amp;rdquo; Mendelsohn says. &amp;ldquo;It allowed us to create this incredible, iconic, forensic detective. Because of Billy&amp;rsquo;s instructions, he was both a student of the world and a teacher of the world. He has had such longevity and such a continuing presence on the show [because] Grissom taught all of our CSIs. And he was the teacher of all of us.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;[He took] us into a world that none of us had any exposure to and then to make science entertaining and exciting,&amp;rdquo; she continues. &amp;ldquo;Grissom held our hand and took us on that journey to the truth. So, we are reverential and referential to Grissom, but it&amp;rsquo;s because Gil Grissom started us all on the path to forensics. He was a new kind of detective. And in a world that was often gray, Grissom always led us to the truth.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And will that legacy lead to another 300 episodes? &amp;ldquo;Greg says something to Sara at the end of 300,&amp;rdquo; McGill says. &amp;ldquo;It&amp;rsquo;s something to the effect of, &amp;#8216;We&amp;rsquo;re only just getting started&amp;rsquo; I think Carol and I agree.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;CSI airs Wednesdays at 10/9c on CBS.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Talk (23 October 2013)</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2013/the-talk-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2013/the-talk-2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sara Gilbert:&lt;/strong&gt; I have to congratulate you guys on 300 episodes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[audience cheers]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; [pointing at Eric] He&amp;rsquo;s the only man in the pilot. Right here. All 300.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sara Gilbert:&lt;/strong&gt; You&amp;rsquo;ve been there since the first season, but I heard, Jorja, that you didn&amp;rsquo;t think the show was gonna take off.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; No, and I can say that we&amp;rsquo;re [Jorja and Eric] getting old. [laughter] I can&amp;rsquo;t speak for you guys [Elisabeth and Ted] at all. When I see a grey hair on his [Eric&amp;rsquo;s] head, I&amp;rsquo;m done. I&amp;rsquo;m out. That&amp;rsquo;s when it&amp;rsquo;s over. [group laughter] I though, &amp;ldquo;Okay it&amp;rsquo;s this show about death. It&amp;rsquo;s gonna be on a Friday night. Death in the Western Hemisphere culture, not so much.&amp;rdquo; I thought we were doomed. I thought we were gonna do six shows and we were canceled. I knew &lt;em&gt;I&lt;/em&gt; loved it! And I still love it. It&amp;rsquo;s weird&amp;hellip; we&amp;rsquo;re still here.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Aisha Tyler:&lt;/strong&gt; That&amp;rsquo;s awesome.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[audience applause]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[interview with Eric, Elisabeth, and Ted]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Julie Chen:&lt;/strong&gt; Now Jorja. The show is so serious, and you guys have such a great sense of humor, but it must get dark on the set at times because of the content. What do you do between takes to lighten the mood?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; Well, as a matter of fact, we have one of the great funny men of all time on the show now: Mr. Ted Danson. [audience laughter and cheers] And he &amp;#8212; he does some dancing. He was a competitive dancer, yeah, and many times, when it gets a little intense, you dance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ted Danson:&lt;/strong&gt; You know what it is? My hips are going. I fall. [audience laughter] I sway and fall and it looks like a dance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Julie Chen:&lt;/strong&gt; Are you gonna bust a move?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Aisha Tyler:&lt;/strong&gt; Yeah! We were hoping that &amp;#8212;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Julie Chen:&lt;/strong&gt; Come on, you&amp;rsquo;ve got to. One or two steps.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[audience cheers this idea on]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ted Danson:&lt;/strong&gt; I&amp;rsquo;ll dance, if Jorja &amp;#8212; cause she does these funny things where she takes her clothes off-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[The Talk ladies break into hysterics, Jorja laughs]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Julie Chen:&lt;/strong&gt; Fair is fair!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; Not in these heels, they&amp;rsquo;re not right for a dance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ted Danson:&lt;/strong&gt; No no! I will, but you&amp;rsquo;ve got to [laughter]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Julie Chen:&lt;/strong&gt; We want to keep it PG here! Maybe later Ted will bust a move. [&amp;hellip;]eros as an actor, and from the first day that we worked together, you kind of looked him in the eye and there was- as if we&amp;rsquo;d know each other ten years. He&amp;rsquo;s a master at intimacy. It&amp;rsquo;s not forced, it&amp;rsquo;s authentic, and it comes from, you know, like &amp;#8216;actor to actor.&amp;rsquo; I&amp;rsquo;ve said this before, but I swear he&amp;rsquo;s got wings on. Like under his jacket, there&amp;rsquo;s wings. He is an amazing guy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[group &amp;#8216;awwww&amp;rsquo; and applause]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Chen:&lt;/strong&gt; Now, in addition to your work on CSI, you work on other projects including &amp;#8212; there&amp;rsquo;s one that&amp;rsquo;s coming out later this year, and you&amp;rsquo;re really proud of it. It&amp;rsquo;s called &amp;ldquo;How I Became An Elephant.&amp;rdquo; Tell us about that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; Thank you for asking about that. It&amp;rsquo;s a documentary, feature documentary, that I produced a couple years ago. It&amp;rsquo;s really the story of a young girl, from southern California, who travels to Thailand to rescue an elephant. The heart of the story is that no matter how old you are or where you&amp;rsquo;re from or where your circumstances are, if you have a passion about something, you can make a difference. One person &lt;em&gt;can&lt;/em&gt; make a difference. The larger picture, of course, the umbrella is it&amp;rsquo;s a movie about wildlife habitats and environmentalism and preserving these wild places so that these creatures can continue to have a place to live.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[applause]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; Thank you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Chen:&lt;/strong&gt; Jorja Fox everyone, Jorja Fox. CSI: Crime Scene Investigation airs Wednesday at ten, right here on CBS. We&amp;rsquo;ll be back.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CBS CSI300 EPK</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2013/cbs-csi300-epk/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2013/cbs-csi300-epk/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jorja Fox: I was blown away by it, it was so different and I hadn&amp;rsquo;t seen anything ever like it. A show about death, on a Friday night? This is going to be canceled in six weeks, no one&amp;rsquo;s going to watch this! America&amp;rsquo;s not gonna watch this show! And boy was I &amp;hellip; that was extremely wrong about that! [breaks up laughing]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jorja Fox: It&amp;rsquo;s a great place to go back to. And also, under the umbrella of justice and truth and really trying to get to the heart of a very sad story is really awesomely compelling, I think, for us to get to tell.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jorja Fox: Being on a successful show is the cooling thing that could ever happen to a person. I wouldn&amp;rsquo;t trade it for anything. But I think &amp;hellip; I show up because I love being with the people that I get to work with every day.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TVGuide.com</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2013/tvguide-05/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2013/tvguide-05/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Over 14 seasons and 300 episodes, &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; has concocted some wild plots and brought in memorable guest stars to keep the body-bagging business fresh and fun. We asked the cast - including Marg Helgenberger, who reprises her role as Catherine Willows for Wednesday&amp;rsquo;s landmark 300th episode, which flashes back to a case the team failed to crack in 2000 - to reflect on the show&amp;rsquo;s best installments, selected by longtime executive producer Carol Mendelsohn.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;rdquo;&amp;lsquo;1. Blood Drops (Season 1, Episode 7)&amp;ldquo;&amp;rsquo; A 6-year-old Dakota Fanning plays the surviving daughter of a family that&amp;rsquo;s been butchered in their home. &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;ve had nightmares frm time to time about this one,&amp;rdquo; admits Jorja Fox (Sara). &amp;ldquo;Grissom [William Petersen] and Sara arrived so quickly after the murders that you could still feel the horrible events. I had one line - &amp;#8216;Her soul&amp;rsquo;s still in the room&amp;rsquo; - which has stayed with me as [emblematic] of the entire series.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;rdquo;&amp;lsquo;7. Law of Gravity (Season 7, Episode 15)&amp;ldquo;&amp;rsquo; A cop threatens to expose the dark past of fill-in boss Keppler (Liev Schreiber) if he doesn&amp;rsquo;t make the evidence in a case go away. &amp;ldquo;What a joy it was to have Liev with us for four episodes when Billy [Petersen] went to Chicago to do a play,&amp;rdquo; says Fox. &amp;ldquo;But we all knew it wasn&amp;rsquo;t going to end well for Keppler.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;rdquo;&amp;lsquo;10. CSI on Fire (Season 13, Episode 8)&amp;ldquo;&amp;rsquo; A mass grave in the desert is linked to an accused serial killer whom Finlay (Elisabeth Shue) pursued when she worked in Seattle. &amp;ldquo;Once in a while, the case is so close to your character that you get emotionally connected, which makes for deeper, richer scenes,&amp;rdquo; says Shue, who adds that she enjoyed making out with Finlay&amp;rsquo;s ex-husband (Cougar Town&amp;rsquo;s Brian Van Holt) at the end of the episode. According to Fox, &amp;ldquo;This storyline will come back later this season, when Fin will have to confront her past in Seattle so she can bravely help out Greg.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;CSI airs Wednesdays at 10/9c on CBS.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[Full disclosure: TVGuide.com is owned by CBS.]&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CableTV.com</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2013/cabletv-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2013/cabletv-2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Jorja Fox is best known for her role as Dr. Maggie Doyle in the television medical drama &lt;em&gt;ER&lt;/em&gt;. Since then, Fox has had many successful appearances in television shows including &lt;em&gt;The West Wing&lt;/em&gt; and most recently &lt;em&gt;CSI: Crime Scene Investigation&lt;/em&gt; playing Sara Sidle. Fox talks about her career, how &lt;em&gt;CSI&lt;/em&gt; changed her life, and what fans could expect this season.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Q: What does it feel like to reflect on your career and know that you have been on some of the biggest shows in history like &lt;em&gt;ER&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fox: Oh wow. Thank you. I think it was huge at the time for me. I started on ER in season three and they were the number one show in the country and those numbers were bigger then what you see now because there was less television to choose from. People had to actually turn on the TV at the right time a lot of the bigger shows people wanted to watch live so they could talk about them the next day. So I was terrified. I hadnt watched ER and it was my moms favorite show and a lot of my friends favorite shows and I was absolutely terrified when I got the job because I felt like everyone in America was going to know I was an impostor and that I wasnt a good actorits just crazy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Q: So after &lt;em&gt;ER&lt;/em&gt; you did a ton of television shows and then you land &lt;em&gt;CSI,&lt;/em&gt; which again is another huge show. Where was your mind set when you heard you got the role of Sara?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fox: That was also a big surprise. I really didnt think that &lt;em&gt;CSI&lt;/em&gt; was going to be successful. I fell in love with the story and the idea of it. Again, at the time it was really different and something that I hadnt really read about oftenbut I thought nobody was really going to watch a show about death on a Friday night that is just kind of not a really American culture thing to do and I was so wrong about that. I thought I would do &lt;em&gt;CSI&lt;/em&gt;, have some fun and be back on &lt;em&gt;The West Wing&lt;/em&gt; by Christmas. I thought the show was going to get canceled and here I am thirteen years later.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Q: How has Sara changed from Season one to Season thirteen?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fox: I think in someways she really hasnt changed that much [laughs]. When we met Sara in 2000 I think she was very much a product of her past and her history and the things she experienced as a young kid. You know, her mother killed her father and she was in foster care for a period of time. I think that she had this drive to be apart of CSI that stems from her experiences as a kid. I think when she left in season 7 and was gone most of season 8 she had a time to wrestle those demons and maybe not feel like she is controlled by her past anymore. She kind of cleared all of the ghosts out for herself. Here we are in season thirteen and I feel like we have a very mature character who is just as passionate about the cases and just as invested but is somehow free of her history and that is kind of how I have been playing the character.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Q: What can fans look forward to this season?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fox: I think so far we are in the middle of episode 7. I think we have an amazing season opening up and some great guest stars like oh you know what I dont know if I could say. We have some really interesting guest stars and a cooking show in episode four that is kind of based on these food contests on the food networks. There is funny stuff, there is haunting stuff  I think the writers this year again suggested to me, they like to pick a theme every season, and this one is definitely going to be about darkness and going darker and going deeper. We start the season with a funeral and its not really until we get to the end of the episode that we find out why we are all there and whose funeral it is, who has passed. Its a very compelling and suspenseful episode.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Honolulu Pulse</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2013/honolulu-pulse/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2013/honolulu-pulse/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The 33rd Hawaii International Film Festival started off with a buzz of energy on Thursday, Oct. 10.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A cheery crowd of filmmakers, actors, producers and staunch film fans mixed over stylish small bites, wine and cocktails at an opening night party at the Halekulani in Waikiki, as organizers flitted about and dignitaries, including Mayor Kirk Caldwell, greeted the fest.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The evening was especially fantastic for me, as I was able to sit down for an animated and uplifting talk with Jorja Fox, who plays Sara on &amp;ldquo;CSI,&amp;rdquo; one of contemporary televisions most popular and long-running series. The actor, who also appeared on &amp;ldquo;ER&amp;rdquo; and in a story arc on &amp;ldquo;The West Wing,&amp;rdquo; seems to have a knack for connecting with popular television dramas.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fox was in Hawaii to promote the documentary &amp;ldquo;Lion Ark,&amp;rdquo; along with producers/filmmakers/activists Tim Phillips and Jan Creamer, founders of Animal Defenders International.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The film depicts the rescue of 25 African lions from Bolivian circuses, in the wake of a 2010 law prohibiting the use of animals in traveling shows. Phillips and Creamer, whove made their first full-length film with &amp;ldquo;Lion Ark,&amp;rdquo; were right there every step of the way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The subject matter is dramatic and gripping  the quest brought the filmmakers into remote parts of Bolivia, and often circuses were not cooperative. In the films opening scenes, a circus operator, waving a knife, slashes their tires to try to prevent a rescue.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It also has a happy ending, as Fox and the filmmakers take pains to point out: All of the lions at risk were airlifted out of Bolivia, finding a home at a sprawling sanctuary in Colorado, where a giant (80-acre) protective enclosure was custom-built for the lions to help them adjust to the colder climate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;I like to think of it as an action-adventure-dramedy,&amp;rdquo; Fox said, partially joking. &amp;ldquo;There are some funny moments in it, but there is epic drama. To get to be a part of it was fantastic.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fox was there as the lions were being taken to shelter in Colorado, as is seen in the film.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;To be surrounded by 25 roaring lions  that real, raw power was an experience Ill never forget,&amp;rdquo; she said.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Creamer can speak passionately about the mistreatment imposed on animals in traveling circuses, while Phillips emphasizes their work is based on strictly factual findings  often uncovered by working surreptitiously to gather evidence on the scene, as the filmmakers did for years in Bolivia.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;FOX HAS worked with Phillips and Creamer for more than seven years, beginning with a collaboration on the short documentary film, &amp;ldquo;How I Became an Elephant.&amp;rdquo; Fox served as producer for that film, which exposes the treatment of elephants as &amp;ldquo;performers&amp;rdquo; in traveling shows and in movies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fox was involved with &amp;ldquo;Lion Ark&amp;rdquo; from the beginning, consulting with the filmmakers on the eye-witness approach and stepping in front of the camera during scenes films when the lions arrive in Colorado.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Shes also supporting the film by appearing at HIFF. Shell be at Dole Cannery on Saturday, Oct. 12, for the screening of &amp;ldquo;Lion Ark.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Ive been passionate about the environment, marine protection and wildlife, all my life,&amp;rdquo; Fox said, explaining why she got involved. Born in New York City, she lived in Melbourne, Florida with her family as a child. Now based in L.A., shes a surfer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;I was very familiar with Hawaii, but I wasnt that familiar with the festival until Jan and Tim got invited to come,&amp;rdquo; Fox confided.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As she spoke, a stylish woman with close-cropped hair leaned over our table to say, &amp;ldquo;Sorry to interrupt, but we love your show. I just had to come over and tell you that!&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;THE SHOW, of course, is &amp;ldquo;CSI,&amp;rdquo; which is about to reach a huge milestone: the airing of its 300th episode.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The episode has already been filmed, Fox said.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Its going to be amazing, thats all I can say,&amp;rdquo; she said. &amp;ldquo;We didnt really think it was that big a deal until we started shooting it, and then we started realizing that its pretty rare.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;With the new shows especially, so many of them are doing 13 episodes a season instead of 24  its going to take them 26 years to get to 300 episodes! I dont know that that many new shows are going to get there.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;We tried to enjoy every minute&amp;rdquo; of filming, she said. Special care was taken in writing the scenes, and some pieces of the episode pay tribute to the series long history, including &amp;ldquo;faux-back&amp;rdquo; segments that recreate characters storylines reaching back to the shows first year. Original cast member Marg Helgenberger (Catherine Willows) is also back for the 300th show.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I asked Fox how long the wild ride that has been &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; can last, and she responded that its up to viewers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;I hope my favorite episode is yet to come,&amp;rdquo; she said. &amp;ldquo;Its lasted far longer than I ever anticipated.  Now, I think Ill do it as long as the fans want us to do it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;I cant even imagine leaving at this point. It would seem foolish.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;IN THE MEANTIME, Fox is hoping for big audiences and international impact with &amp;ldquo;Lion Ark.&amp;rdquo; The film was just awarded the Audience Award at the San Diego Film Festival, where it sold out its screening. Screenings also sold out at Londons Raindance Film Festival, an offshoot of Robert Redfords Sundance Film Festival in Colorado.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Asked what she learned from working on &amp;ldquo;Lion Ark,&amp;rdquo; Fox said, &amp;ldquo;Anything is possible. If you put your heart and soul to it, you can move mountains.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Hawaiian Humane Society has teamed up with Animal Defenders International to promote &amp;ldquo;Lion Ark&amp;rdquo; at HIFF. For more on efforts to improve conditions for captive or domesticated animals here in Hawaii, go to hawaiianhumane.org.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mill Valley Film Festival Screening (05 October 2013)</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2013/mill-valley-film-festival-screening/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Oct 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2013/mill-valley-film-festival-screening/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;introduction:d8a5738ef7f3b53ed23480f0c7f01a6f&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Announcer:&lt;/strong&gt; Please, before we start anything, give a big hand to Pacific Sun, who is responsible for letting &lt;em&gt;Lion Ark&lt;/em&gt; be here today.  The film is co-presented by Animal Defenders International, which had, obviously you&amp;rsquo;ll see, an integral part in the creation of &lt;em&gt;Lion Ark&lt;/em&gt;. We&amp;rsquo;re very happy to have this film, it&amp;rsquo;s a powerful film, it&amp;rsquo;s an exciting film. It&amp;rsquo;s going to subvert a lot of your expectations about both seeing a documentary and about some of the assumptions we had growing up or seeing in our culture. I think it&amp;rsquo;s going to be a really successful event today. Please give a warm welcome to an ambassador for Animal Defenders International, and also the associate producer, Jorja Fox.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; Thank you. Thank you very much. Good afternoon everyone, &lt;em&gt;[Light laughter]&lt;/em&gt; and welcome to the North American premiere of &lt;em&gt;Lion Ark&lt;/em&gt;.  Very exciting day for us. On behalf of the filmmakers, Tim Phillips and Jan Creamer, we want to humbly thank the Mill Valley Film Festival for having us at this incredible event. And we also want to thank you very much for coming out to see the movie.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Being a part of &lt;em&gt;Lion Ark&lt;/em&gt; has been an epic adventure for me, and today is no exception. I&amp;rsquo;m thrilled to get to watch all of you watch the movie. It&amp;rsquo;s very fitting for &lt;em&gt;Lion Ark&lt;/em&gt; that we&amp;rsquo;re premiering here, as it&amp;rsquo;s the first place the first group of lions landed from Bolivia, back in the spring of 2010. Those four lions are living in the PAWS Sanctuary, near [Gulf(?)], California. Moving lions on airplanes is kind of a strange and rare thing. And the city of San Francisco, San Francisco International Airport and the surrounding areas were so very kind to us and welcomed us with a very serene calm and gracious resolve. We&amp;rsquo;re very grateful for that.  &lt;em&gt;Lion Ark&lt;/em&gt;&amp;#8216;s biggest stars, the main stars of the movie, lions, of course couldn&amp;rsquo;t be here today. They&amp;rsquo;re tired from their life in show business. But many of the key human players are here. They&amp;rsquo;ve traveled far and wide, from the United Kingdom to South America.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are having a Q&amp;amp;A immediately after the film, and I very much hope you&amp;rsquo;ll stick around for questions and comments, and to hear from this amazing and diverse group of people who are all experts in their fields. We&amp;rsquo;re also having a party tonight, a bit of a fundraiser for the next chapter of &lt;em&gt;Lion Ark&lt;/em&gt;. We cordially invite all of you to come. It&amp;rsquo;s going to be at Bungalow 44 at six o&amp;rsquo;clock. You can see anyone in the black &lt;em&gt;Lion Ark&lt;/em&gt; t-shirts with clipboards for tickets, and tickets will also be available at the door if we don&amp;rsquo;t sell out. Tickets are $70. As I mentioned, it&amp;rsquo;s a fundraiser. You&amp;rsquo;ll get drinks and appetizers, and a chance to mingle with the filmmakers and the rescue team. We hope to see all of you there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lastly, and I&amp;rsquo;ll be brief, I just want to talk about the film makers. Jane Creamer and Tim Phillips for a minute. Jan and Tim have been working absolutely tirelessly for over thirty years for the betterment of wild and domesticated animals alike, across the globe. They run an organization called Animal Defenders International. This wonderful film that you&amp;rsquo;re about to see highlights just one of their campaigns. Needless to say, they lead very exciting lives. From bustling cities to the most barren and remote landscapes, Jan and Tim have a knack for making friends and allies wherever they go. They&amp;rsquo;re bridge builders, of a sort. Metaphoric bridge building is a very rare skill, a very special skill. I think it&amp;rsquo;s a skill that&amp;rsquo;s sorely lacking in most fields in the landscape today. And I think that it is the Golden Key to finding solutions for our planets&amp;rsquo; issues.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Animal Defenders International works from private support. They depend on private support for the work that they do. If you feel inspired by this film, and I think you will, please offer up your own support, be it a donation, spreading the world, or volunteering, or all of the above. It&amp;rsquo;s ADI&amp;rsquo;s greatest hope &amp;#8212; sorry, forgot to change my page &lt;em&gt;[Jorja laughs at herself]&lt;/em&gt; &amp;#8212; It&amp;rsquo;s ADI&amp;rsquo;s greatest hope to give as many animals as possible, out in the world, a happy ending.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ladies and gentlemen, &lt;em&gt;Lion Ark&lt;/em&gt;. Thank you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#8212;-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;q-a:d8a5738ef7f3b53ed23480f0c7f01a6f&#34;&gt;Q&amp;amp;A&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[Asked how they got involved]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; I think I was lucky I grew up in a very small town in Florida. My grandmother was very influential in my life. She was a rabid environmentalist, and kind of a modern thinker on a lot of levels, and I took after her quite a bit. I think I also &amp;#8212; it was also the &amp;lsquo;80s, and it was music videos and it was new media and there were a couple kids in my school, eccentric kids in my school, who were vegetarians and would talk about that stuff. It kind of opened a door for me to learn as much as I could. I had a lot to do with books at that time too. I think it&amp;rsquo;s amazing, in the few short years since the &amp;lsquo;80s, how far some of these ideas have come. I really do think we&amp;rsquo;re reaching a tipping point with animals and entertainment and circuses and zoos. There&amp;rsquo;s better options. There&amp;rsquo;s PAWS and the Wild Animal Sanctuary and I think we&amp;rsquo;re starting to get those ideas, and I think we&amp;rsquo;re going to see some really positive changes over the next ten, fifteen, years. Maybe we&amp;rsquo;ll be thinking that&amp;rsquo;s really a thing of the past, it&amp;rsquo;s really not that cool to see an animal in a cage do a trick, like roll a ball or whatever. There&amp;rsquo;s far cool things they can do.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[How do they get all these animals in circuses?]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; You (Jan Creamer) kind of just said what I was going to say. Most of it, especially in the United States, all comes from breeding programs. The animals are here. It&amp;rsquo;s actually very difficult now to get them across International borders. People do it, sometimes for the right reasons, and sometimes not. I think there&amp;rsquo;s a whole bunch of animals up at PAWS that started out in somebody&amp;rsquo;s basement. They bought it on a black market, it was a pet for a time, and then it got too big, too strong, and they had to figure out what to do with it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#8212;-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Post Screening&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; You know, I love the film so much. And I&amp;rsquo;ve really only seen it finished twice, so today was my second time. I was moved a little more than I wanted to be, &amp;lsquo;cause I was in this public theater with a lot of people. I wanted to be so very cool and calm and collected. It was a thrill and a half. It was amazing. We&amp;rsquo;re so happy to be here at the Mill Valley Festival. We want to thank everybody or having us.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Interviewer:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;[unintelligible question]&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; Yeah, I think so. Not too many people left early, so that&amp;rsquo;s always a really good sign. I do, I kind of see the film as an action/adventure piece. It is a documentary, and it&amp;rsquo;s real events, but to me there&amp;rsquo;s a lot of hair-raising, edge-of-your-seats moments, and yes, I think the audience very much stayed with us for the film.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Interviewer:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;[unintelligible question]&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; Why did I have to make it? I think I was lucky to get to be a part of the film. The events, moving the lions from Bolivia to the United States a couple years ago, I got to be a part of that move, and at the time I remember somebody saying &amp;ldquo;Oh yeah, we&amp;rsquo;re documenting this.&amp;rdquo; and we all had mics on. I was just really thrilled to get to be a part of it. It was, I think, an epic accomplishment to move 28 lions 48,000 miles to a sanctuary. I really wasn&amp;rsquo;t sure that it could be done, that it could be pulled off. Certainly there would be some hitch somewhere along the way. You know, it&amp;rsquo;s funny. For a movie that&amp;rsquo;s so exciting, so much of the work that went into the actual move was so slow, and meticulous and methodical, including securing these laws on traveling circuses throughout the world. It&amp;rsquo;s very tedious work. It was a miracle that it all came together.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Interviewer:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;[unintelligible question]&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; It&amp;rsquo;s Northern California, I love this part of the country, I come here often. I think that Mill Valley is a very peaceful place, it&amp;rsquo;s a place that&amp;rsquo;s very connected with the nature surrounding it. There&amp;rsquo;s water everywhere, it&amp;rsquo;s in the foothills and the redwoods. There&amp;rsquo;s amazing surfing and sailing. So particularly, not only for this film, &lt;em&gt;Lion Ark&lt;/em&gt;, I think it&amp;rsquo;s a perfect match in terms of content in a place, but also for me as a person who&amp;rsquo;s a surfer and an outdoor person, it&amp;rsquo;s always good to be up here. I love the food here. I love the wine, I love the coffee. It&amp;rsquo;s a really great place to visit, and I&amp;rsquo;m sure a great place to live.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TVGuide.com</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2013/tvguide-04/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2013/tvguide-04/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;rdquo;&amp;lsquo;Is there any chance of Grissom popping up in &lt;em&gt;CSI&lt;/em&gt;&amp;#8216;s 300th episode? &amp;ldquo;Selena&amp;rdquo;&amp;ldquo;&amp;rsquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;rdquo;&amp;lsquo;ADAM:&amp;ldquo;&amp;rsquo; In the flesh? Nah. But the episode, which flashes back to a 14-year-old case, does feature a full-circle shout-out to the man who started it all. &amp;ldquo;[The writers] pay a very sound and beautiful homage to [Grissom],&amp;rdquo; Jorja Fox says. Speaking of Grissom, how is Sara handling the couple&amp;rsquo;s separation this season? &amp;ldquo;Sara is too young to sleep alone,&amp;rdquo; Fox says. &amp;ldquo;As painful as it is to not be with Grissom anymore, the idea of also being with the ghost of Grissom is really lonely and alienating.&amp;rdquo; Does that mean she&amp;rsquo;ll be sharing her bed with someone else? Not exactly. &amp;ldquo;Sara is always going to be in love with Grissom. She&amp;rsquo;s always going to pine for him and her heart is always, in a certain way, going to belong to him,&amp;rdquo; Fox says.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Guide Magazine</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2013/tvguide-03/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2013/tvguide-03/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;rdquo;&amp;lsquo;Marg Helgenberger and Jorja Fox answer burning questions about Sara&amp;rsquo;s return and the crime show&amp;rsquo;s killer new season&amp;rdquo;&amp;rsquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;T&lt;/strong&gt;he most baffling crime on &lt;em&gt;CSI&lt;/em&gt; last season wasn&amp;rsquo;t a stabbing or shooting. It was a missing persons case: The show&amp;rsquo;s lead investigator for its first nine seasons, William Petersen (Gil Grissom), left the series halfway through the year, sending &lt;em&gt;CSI&lt;/em&gt;&amp;#8216;s ratings slipping and causing concern for its cast and producers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;We look at last season in a way not dissimilar from the fans,&amp;rdquo; admits executive producer Carol Mendelsohn. &amp;ldquo;We may have shortchanged a number of our characters in being focused on the transition from Grissom&amp;rsquo;s team to Catherine&amp;rsquo;s. We;ll try to make up for that this season.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From the opening scene, it&amp;rsquo;s clear the mood is deadly on the graveyard shift. The team is &amp;ldquo;fractured,&amp;rdquo; says Mendelsohn. Enter Jorja Fox, who&amp;rsquo;s back, at least temporarily, to help Catherine (Marg Helgenberger) get the CSIs to play nice again. But where&amp;rsquo;s Grissom? &amp;ldquo;The audience will know in very short order the status of Grissom and Sara,&amp;rdquo; Mendelsohn promises. &amp;ldquo;I can say that between the time they left and now, there are no little Grissoms out there.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Meanwhile, both Nick Stokes (George Eads) and Ray Langston (Laurence Fishburne) get promoted and start a season-long hunt for a serial killer. &amp;ldquo;The crime scene for this killer &lt;em&gt;is&lt;/em&gt; a body,&amp;rdquo; says Mendelsohn.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The case may also be just the thing to bring the team together and feeling like a family again. &amp;ldquo;We were out of our rhythm a bit last year,&amp;rdquo; says Eads. &amp;ldquo;We needed to go back to the garage and find what inspired us, and there&amp;rsquo;s some good stuff with what&amp;rsquo;s happening on the show now.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That starts with the return of Fox, whose departure two seasons ago &amp;ldquo;felt like we lost our lead guitarist,&amp;rdquo; Eads adds. So, as &lt;em&gt;CSI&lt;/em&gt; tunes up for its 10th season, &lt;strong&gt;TV GUIDE MAGAZINE&lt;/strong&gt; sat down with Fox and Helgenberger to ask them questions send in by fans on [&lt;a href=&#34;http://tvguidemagazine.com&#34;&gt;http://tvguidemagazine.com&lt;/a&gt; tvguidemagazine.com], and found out how the team is getting its mojo back.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What would you like to see this year on &lt;em&gt;CSI&lt;/em&gt; that hasn&amp;rsquo;t already been done?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong style=&#34;color: #9000A1;&#34;&gt;Marg:&lt;/strong&gt; A musical episode! That&amp;rsquo;s something we&amp;rsquo;ve talked about since Season 2. The cast has, anyway. I don&amp;rsquo;t think the writers think it&amp;rsquo;s a great idea.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong style=&#34;color: #339999;&#34;&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; I&amp;rsquo;ve been advocating for the &lt;em&gt;CSI&lt;/em&gt; musical episode for a long time. And not because I have any talent musically, because I don&amp;rsquo;t. Everybody else does. Marg has a beautiful voice.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong style=&#34;color: #9000A1;&#34;&gt;Marg:&lt;/strong&gt; You do, too, have talent.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong style=&#34;color: #339999;&#34;&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; I can&amp;rsquo;t really sing. But I&amp;rsquo;d love a dance number.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja, why did you come back to &lt;em&gt;CSI&lt;/em&gt;?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong style=&#34;color: #339999;&#34;&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; I thought it would be a heck of a lot of fun. When I said my goodbyes, with cake in my mouth and flowers in my arms, the last thing I said to the producers was I&amp;rsquo;d love to visit. But this was very unexpected.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Is it possible Sara will return for good?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong style=&#34;color: #339999;&#34;&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; I&amp;rsquo;ll just say I&amp;rsquo;m very pleased with what they&amp;rsquo;ve come up with to bring Sara back. You do learn a little about what she&amp;rsquo;s been up to. I was pleasantly intrigued.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Marg, are you happy to have Jorja back on the set so you&amp;rsquo;re not the only woman?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong style=&#34;color: #339999;&#34;&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; I&amp;rsquo;m gonna cover my ears!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong style=&#34;color: #9000A1;&#34;&gt;Marg:&lt;/strong&gt; Well, obviously, Lauren Lee Smith [&lt;em&gt;who played Riley Adams&lt;/em&gt;] was with us last year, but there was a time before she joked us that I was the only woman, for the most part, other than Liz Vassey in the lab and Sheeri Rappaport. Not that I minded being around all these guys, &amp;lsquo;cause they&amp;rsquo;re all really great and cool and sexy and all that stuff. but there needed to be more of a presence of female power. So I was thrilled to have Jorja back. She&amp;rsquo;s just the coolest chick on the planet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Catherine and Sara have never really had a close friendship. Will they become closer?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong style=&#34;color: #9000A1;&#34;&gt;Marg:&lt;/strong&gt; I&amp;rsquo;ve always wanted them to have a closer relationship. I liked the characters&amp;rsquo; energies together. So it hasn&amp;rsquo;t been for a lack of me wanting and asking for it. I hope it happens. We do have a couple nice scenes in the first episode.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong style=&#34;color: #339999;&#34;&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; I know very little about where we&amp;rsquo;re going from here. Sara has pretty obvious authority issues, so when she&amp;rsquo;s locked horns with Catherine, it&amp;rsquo;s because Catherine&amp;rsquo;s in a position to tell Sara what to do. In her mind, Sara believes she doesn&amp;rsquo;t have a boss. She is her own boss. Most of their fights come out of that. They&amp;rsquo;re very different women but blend marvelously together.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Will we see more of Catherine as a strong supervisor this season?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong style=&#34;color: #9000A1;&#34;&gt;Marg:&lt;/strong&gt; Yes, you will. There is something that happens in the first episodes because someone leaks information to the press, [and the] hard-ass on the show, Ecklie [&lt;em&gt;Mark Vann&lt;/em&gt;], has to come down on someone, so it&amp;rsquo;s the leader. I think you&amp;rsquo;ll see Catherine on top of her game, confident.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong style=&#34;color: #339999;&#34;&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; Catherine&amp;rsquo;s had a leadership position on the show for some time. So it&amp;rsquo;ll seem sort of seamless and subtle. But for me, it&amp;rsquo;s exciting to see a woman in charge.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Will there be a Grissom and Sara wedding anytime soon?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong style=&#34;color: #339999;&#34;&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; I have no idea if there&amp;rsquo;ll be a wedding! Would I, as Jorja, like to see one? Sure. I think, even though it seems the antithesis of who Sara is, she&amp;rsquo;d like to see one too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What do you think happened between Grissom and Sara after the screen went black at the end of William Petersen&amp;rsquo;s final episode?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong style=&#34;color: #339999;&#34;&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; I think we left them happily ever after in a Costa Rican rain forest. I certainly would love to leave it at that. I liked that moment being suspended for a while. It was so slow in coming, season after season. It was something I was rooting for, and I was happy the story ended the way it did. So just let it hang there for a while.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Will we see Catherine find love in the future?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong style=&#34;color: #9000A1;&#34;&gt;Marg:&lt;/strong&gt; [&lt;em&gt;Laughs&lt;/em&gt;] I think it&amp;rsquo;s way overdue for Catherine to have a love interest! There was an ex, who was shot dead. I had a brief relationship with a guy who just wasn&amp;rsquo;t right for me. There was the whole Warrick [&lt;em&gt;Gary Dourdan&lt;/em&gt;] flirtation thing that we didn&amp;rsquo;t really follow through on. But I&amp;rsquo;d love to see Catherine&amp;rsquo;s vulnerable side.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong style=&#34;color: #339999;&#34;&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; And to see some sparks fly!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong style=&#34;color: #9000A1;&#34;&gt;Marg:&lt;/strong&gt; Catehrine needs somebody tall and dark. She&amp;rsquo;s always attracted to edgy-type guys, but at this point in her life and career, she knows that&amp;rsquo;s heading into dangerous water. I think she&amp;rsquo;s evolved a little bit. Not that she wants somebody who is milquetoasty.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong style=&#34;color: #339999;&#34;&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; [&lt;em&gt;Laughs&lt;/em&gt;] A foot doctor?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong style=&#34;color: #9000A1;&#34;&gt;Marg:&lt;/strong&gt; Sure. He probably gives great foot massages. Which would be quite sensual. [&lt;em&gt;Laughs&lt;/em&gt;] She does stand on her feet a lot.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Would Catherine ever kiss Sara?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong style=&#34;color: #339999;&#34;&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; We did today! At the TV Guide Magazine photo shoot. But on the show, probably not. Sara and Catherine love each other very much, but they probably wouldn&amp;rsquo;t kiss.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong style=&#34;color: #9000A1;&#34;&gt;Marg:&lt;/strong&gt; We have to keep some mystery.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Will we get to see Catherine&amp;rsquo;s daughter, Lindsey, and her mother this season?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong style=&#34;color: #9000A1;&#34;&gt;Marg:&lt;/strong&gt; I&amp;rsquo;ve always wanted to have my daughter be much more of a presence on the show, especially now that she&amp;rsquo;s a young woman. That allows for some great storytelling. I can only hope there will be more.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Will there be any more about Catherine&amp;rsquo;s father, Sam Braun, and his legacy?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong style=&#34;color: #9000A1;&#34;&gt;Marg:&lt;/strong&gt; That will definitely be there. Definitely that old-school Vegas stuff will be throughout the whole season.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What&amp;rsquo;s the funniest thing that ever happened on the set?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong style=&#34;color: #339999;&#34;&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; Back when we were doing the &amp;ldquo;Grave Danger&amp;rdquo; episode, and George [Eads] was in the box where he&amp;rsquo;s dying every minute he&amp;rsquo;s in there &amp;hellip; we get this tape in the mail from the Killer and it&amp;rsquo;s a Turtles song. The camera&amp;rsquo;s going around all of us, and we&amp;rsquo;re all there. We&amp;rsquo;re trying to analyze this tape, a critical moment in the story, and we all hear the music and start dancing to it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong style=&#34;color: #9000A1;&#34;&gt;Marg:&lt;/strong&gt; The musical episode!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong style=&#34;color: #339999;&#34;&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; Exactly!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Do you two hang out together off set?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong style=&#34;color: #9000A1;&#34;&gt;Marg:&lt;/strong&gt; I keep meaning to go down to watch her surf.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong style=&#34;color: #339999;&#34;&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; I just spent four days doing it. I&amp;rsquo;ve been surfing for about eight years.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong style=&#34;color: #9000A1;&#34;&gt;Marg:&lt;/strong&gt; I&amp;rsquo;ve been down to her place but haven&amp;rsquo;t seen her surf yet. I guess I might try doing it, too, but I&amp;rsquo;m not as brave as she is.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong style=&#34;color: #339999;&#34;&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; Oh, boy, that&amp;rsquo;s not true!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong style=&#34;color: #9000A1;&#34;&gt;Marg:&lt;/strong&gt; [&lt;em&gt;Laughs&lt;/em&gt;] The temperature of the water is what I&amp;rsquo;m most afraid of. If I was in Hawaii, I&amp;rsquo;d love to do it with you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong style=&#34;color: #339999;&#34;&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; Great! Let&amp;rsquo;s go to Hawaii and go surfing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Would either of you consider joining &lt;em&gt;Dancing With the Stars&lt;/em&gt; since you have the moves to blow the minds of America every week?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong style=&#34;color: #9000A1;&#34;&gt;Marg:&lt;/strong&gt; I could see where that would be a lot of fun, actually.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong style=&#34;color: #339999;&#34;&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; Would America be ready for dancing forensic investigators?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong style=&#34;color: #9000A1;&#34;&gt;Marg:&lt;/strong&gt; See? It all comes back to &lt;em&gt;CSI: The Musical&lt;/em&gt;. Every question comes back to that. If we keep putting it out there, it&amp;rsquo;ll happen.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CableTV.com</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2013/cabletv-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2013/cabletv-1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Monica Gleberman&lt;/strong&gt; .. and just ask you, how did you get involved in acting to begin with?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; Oh my goodness. I wanted to act since I was probably four or five years old. I think that the television that sat in the living room of my house was one of the bigger influences in my life. It was definitely a babysitter for me. You know, I grew up in a small town, so there weren&amp;rsquo;t many acting programs. And it was high school before I was able to be in a drama class. I think there were two things that happened. First of all I love it so much, and then second of all, people were really supportive of me, and doing acting. I think I had a lot of support doing it, and so there was no doubt in my mind. I went to New York and got lucky. I got in [something] very quickly because I ignored all these signs that said &amp;ldquo;Do Not Enter.&amp;rdquo; [laughter] I didn&amp;rsquo;t have an agency, you know &amp;#8216;Don&amp;rsquo;t go beyond this point.&amp;rsquo; And I sort of ignored all of those signs that told me not to go further and landed up in an agency, and I was able to have a conversation with my agency and I had an audition, and they started sending me out. It was so processed. But definitely I started my career in New York and was there for probably seven years before ending up in Los Angeles.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Monica&lt;/strong&gt; I have followed your career, and of course I did research before this. You have had some major television show lucky jobs. Some of the biggest shows known to man. So I want to ask you, of course you were on ER, you were on The West Wing. What was it like- I know when you&amp;rsquo;re on it, you might not think &amp;#8216;This is huge&amp;rsquo; and might not realize how big it is. But looking back, reflecting back on your appearances, what does that feel like? To look back and note that you were on these two shows that are probably going down in history as some of the best television?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja&lt;/strong&gt; Oh wow. Thank you. I think it was huge at the time for me. &lt;em&gt;ER&lt;/em&gt; in particular because I started on &lt;em&gt;ER&lt;/em&gt; in season three and they were the number one show in the country and those numbers were bigger then what you see now because there was less television to choose from. And less appointment television. I don&amp;rsquo;t know if you remember, but people had to actually turn on the TV at the right time. VCR&amp;rsquo;s existed but even then, people wanted to a lot of the bigger shows live so they could talk about them the next day. So I was terrified. Even though I hadnât watched ER, it was my momâs favorite show and a lot of my friends favorite shows and I was absolutely terrified when I got the job because I felt like in a week or two&amp;rsquo;s time, everyone in America was going to know I was an impostor. That I was just claiming to be an actor and I was terrible. So I came really close to just driving to Mexico the week before I started and forgetting the whole thing. But I&amp;rsquo;m glad I didn&amp;rsquo;t. I always felt it was a pretty incredible learning experience, to get to spend time with that caliber of people every day, writers and actors and BPs(?) and directors.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And absolutely the same goes for &lt;em&gt;West Wing&lt;/em&gt;. I think &lt;em&gt;West Wing&lt;/em&gt;&amp;hellip; I was a huge fan then, of Sorkin, and &lt;em&gt;ER&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;West Wing&lt;/em&gt; had a number of the same producers. I think the thing that surprised me the most for myself was I could get to be a part of telling a wonderful story like that. It was something that I hadn&amp;rsquo;t even dreamed of. I just felt like it was such an honor to get to try and tell that story. I really like looked after Martin Sheen&amp;rsquo;s daughter. I couldn&amp;rsquo;t believe it! I got to do something like that! I think that Sorkin, he said at the time on &lt;em&gt;West Wing&lt;/em&gt;, he&amp;rsquo;s alone, and there had been very few women Secret Service Agents at that time, that had actually been on screen. Even getting to be that, getting to be this female Secret Service Agent was kind of a lot of fun that people hadn&amp;rsquo;t gotten to do.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Monica&lt;/strong&gt; And I know, obviously, you&amp;rsquo;ve done a ton of movies and other TV shows, and then you land &lt;em&gt;CSI&lt;/em&gt;. Which, again, another- it&amp;rsquo;s like crazy, your career, because it&amp;rsquo;s another huge show! So I want to go back to Season one, and what that was like, finding out you&amp;rsquo;re going to be playing Sara, and where your mind was when you got that call.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja&lt;/strong&gt; Um. That was also a big surprise. I really didnât think that &lt;em&gt;CSI&lt;/em&gt; was going to be successful. I fell in love with the story and the idea of it. Again, at the time it was something that was pretty different and something that I hadnât really read about often. You know, &lt;em&gt;Quincy&lt;/em&gt; was sort of the thing that I could think of that sort of reminded me a little of &lt;em&gt;CSI&lt;/em&gt;. And I thought nobody was really going to watch a show about death on a Friday night, that is just kind of not a really American culture thing to do. I was so wrong about that. I really thought I would do &lt;em&gt;CSI&lt;/em&gt;, have some fun and be back on &lt;em&gt;The West Wing&lt;/em&gt; by Christmas. You know, that&amp;rsquo;s what I thought was going to happen! I thought the show was going to get canceled and here I am thirteen years later. And it was just this monster. Not &amp;#8212; I guess monster&amp;rsquo;s kind of &amp;#8212; this behemoth that none of us expected. I think that nobody could have imagined how big the ride was going to get.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And thank you for saying that! I&amp;rsquo;m actually starting my eighteenth consecutive season in a row on Prime Time television. It&amp;rsquo;s big for me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Monica&lt;/strong&gt; I know! It&amp;rsquo;s crazy!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja&lt;/strong&gt; So thanks for talking about that stuff.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Monica&lt;/strong&gt; I want to ask- so were you surprised &amp;#8212; before we get into Sara and where she&amp;rsquo;s gone over the course of- and now we&amp;rsquo;re in- there&amp;rsquo;s gonna be a fourteenth season. I want to ask you, I know that in 2007 you had announced that you were leaving the show. Were you surprised at how many fans freaked out and started sending in gifts and money and started a campaign to try to keep you on &lt;em&gt;CSI&lt;/em&gt;? Was that shocking to you at how many people cared about this character?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja&lt;/strong&gt; Absolutely. Yes. Absolutely. It was one of the most magnificent experiences. I had no idea there would be that kind of a response. Truthfully, that was my season twelve in a row, and I was tired. I was just thinking &amp;#8216;Oh my god, I just need to lie down for a minute.&amp;rsquo; I just needed to kind of sit down and reground. So I wanted to get off-screen before it started to show on screen, or before my coworkers started to notice. It was an amazing show of support, and I wished I could have changed my mind to show the fans the amount of gratitude I had for them suggesting that I stay. Honestly, if I wasn&amp;rsquo;t so exhausted, I absolutely would have. So yeah, it was an amazing feeling of surprise.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Monica&lt;/strong&gt; So now that you&amp;rsquo;re back, and you&amp;rsquo;ve been back for a while, everyone&amp;rsquo;s been super excited. I want to know from you how has Sara changed from season one, I know she&amp;rsquo;s had a lot of life changes with the proposal and getting married, but how has she changed from season one to season thirteen?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja&lt;/strong&gt; It&amp;rsquo;s funny. I think in some ways she really hasnât changed that much [laughs]. There&amp;rsquo;s been some &lt;em&gt;seemingly&lt;/em&gt; big changes. When we met Sara in 2000, if anything I think she was very much a product of her past and of her history and the things she experienced as a young kid. You know, her mother killed her father and she was in foster care for a period of time. I think that she had this drive to be a CSI that definitely stems from her experiences as a kid. I think when she left in season 7, and was gone most of season 8, she had a chance to really wrestle those demons and maybe not feel like she is controlled by her past anymore. She kind of cleared all of the ghosts out for herself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And yet, here we are in season thirteen and I feel like we have a very mature character, who is just as passionate about the cases and just as invested, but is somehow free of her history and that is kind of the way I&amp;rsquo;ve been playing the character for the last couple of season. And yet at the same time, now we are in season fourteen, I do feel that Sara- there is this compulsive drive, something very deep rooted. She can&amp;rsquo;t stop being a CSI, it&amp;rsquo;s what fuels her, maybe the duration of her life, she&amp;rsquo;s going to be there in the trenches, on the street, in the muck, in the darkness, trying to get justice for people. I&amp;rsquo;m looking at it again, myself, and like &amp;ldquo;huh!&amp;rdquo; I thought the compulsive side of her was finished, and now maybe it&amp;rsquo;s not, not at all. Maybe she&amp;rsquo;s just the same.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Monica&lt;/strong&gt; What can fans look forward to this season? What kind of cases? What are you guys going to get involved with, cause there&amp;rsquo;s always a craziness happening every episode. So what can fans expect this season for the upcoming episodes?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja&lt;/strong&gt; I think so far &amp;#8212; we are in the middle of episode 7 and I&amp;rsquo;ve seen the script for eight, and I think we have an amazing season opening up. Really exciting. We have some incredible guest stars including somebody likeâ¦ oh you know what I donât know if I could say cause I don&amp;rsquo;t know if I&amp;rsquo;m a spoiler alert. [laughs] We have some really interesting guest stars and a cooking show in episode four that is kind of based on these food contests on the food networks. There is funny stuff, there is haunting stuff â I think the writers this year again, they suggested to me, they like to pick a theme every season, and this one is definitely going to be about darkness and going darker and going deeper.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s going to be a darker season of &lt;em&gt;CSI&lt;/em&gt;, but within that also there&amp;rsquo;s going to be as much character stuff as there was last year. I think they&amp;rsquo;re continuing to write a lot of character stuff, which is great. Certainly we start the season with Morgan in jeopardy, the stakes are really high. We also start the season with a funeral and itâs not really until we get to the end of the show that you, the audience, will come to find out why we&amp;rsquo;re at the funeral and who has passed. Itâs a very compelling kind of suspenseful episode.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You know, yeah it gets crazier every year. I don&amp;rsquo;t know how the writers come up with stuff in season fourteen. The unfortunate thing is there&amp;rsquo;s no shortage of crazy crime in America to draw from. But the stakes continue to get higher, and I hope the fans will continue to enjoy that. I always am partial to the action/adventure show. And so in those episodes where we get a little kooky, hopefully the fans will still be able to roll with us.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Monica&lt;/strong&gt; I wanted to ask you, was it nice that all current cast members continued on for season fourteen?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja&lt;/strong&gt; Absolutely! Because we have had so many changes. You know, part of me, you were speaking about &lt;em&gt;ER&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;ER&lt;/em&gt; began to lose their core cast members in season three. So the fact that our show made it to season seven with the core cast intact, I think is a testament to the show and a compliment to how much we actually did get along and liked working together and did like the work itself. I think very few shows have gone seven seasons retaining their full original cast.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But yes, it&amp;rsquo;s been really nice to have a cast that&amp;rsquo;s been able to stay together for a couple of seasons. You can&amp;rsquo;t fake chemistry. You&amp;rsquo;ve sort of got to build it organically. The more you know each other, the more you work together, the deeper you can go. It&amp;rsquo;s given a chance for that. I think it&amp;rsquo;s been kind of a really great thing for the writers, because there were a lot of seasons where it was really hard for them to start breaking stories over the summer, because they weren&amp;rsquo;t completely sure who their cast was going to be. Knowing early enough that they were going to have everyone has allowed them to spread their wings more than they could for a bunch of season.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This team, this troupe of actors, you never think that &amp;#8216;Wow, three new actors in practically one season. This is definitely- this can&amp;rsquo;t go well. This is going to be difficult.&amp;rsquo; And to love these three actors as much as I do, as much as we all do, we&amp;rsquo;re having so much fun every day. I hope it shows on screen. As usual, I&amp;rsquo;m just grateful I get to come here and hang out, because it&amp;rsquo;s a really fun place to be.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Monica&lt;/strong&gt; Of course I have to ask too, season fourteen, will mark the 300th episode, which is like, nuts. So what is that? What have you guys, I think it&amp;rsquo;s like mid-season, right? The 300th?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja&lt;/strong&gt; The 300th? Episode five. We&amp;rsquo;re pretty soon, like pretty pretty soon. We&amp;rsquo;re going to do ten new shows in a row. I don&amp;rsquo;t think we&amp;rsquo;ve done that before. And so, yeah, I think five weeks after the premiere tomorrow, you&amp;rsquo;ll be able to see the 300th episode.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Monica&lt;/strong&gt; So what is that like? Being a part of &amp;hellip; I feel like a lot of this interview is about you being a part of these crazy, amazing, genius shows. And not only do you have this awesome career, but you&amp;rsquo;re a part of another benchmark, which is the 300th episode. So what is that like, being a part of?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja&lt;/strong&gt; It was such an honor for me. You know, it is a milestone. I didn&amp;rsquo;t think much about it going in, but then we all showed up for work the first day, and a couple people gave speeches, and I started to feel the gravity of it all. I think it&amp;rsquo;s been a great second chance for me. I missed the 200th episode, I wasn&amp;rsquo;t here. I was here for the 100th episode. And to get to be a part of the 300th episode meant a lot to me. More than I even imagined it would. I haven&amp;rsquo;t done 300 episodes yet, I&amp;rsquo;m behind several members of the cast because I did take that season off, and I don&amp;rsquo;t appear in every episode every year. I think with my combined with my &lt;em&gt;ER&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;West Wing&lt;/em&gt; I might be on episode 296 or something. I can share that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s funny, because &lt;em&gt;ER&lt;/em&gt; went 300 episodes, and Marg Helgenberger, George Eads and myself had all had parts on &lt;em&gt;ER&lt;/em&gt;, so with another show that the three of us can be happy for and be a part of this tiny piece of &lt;em&gt;ER&lt;/em&gt; history. Of course, the history that we have on &lt;em&gt;CSI&lt;/em&gt; is a lot deeper and bigger. It&amp;rsquo;s really cool. I don&amp;rsquo;t think it&amp;rsquo;s ever going to happen to me again, to be a part of something like this. I don&amp;rsquo;t know if it&amp;rsquo;s going to be possible for a lot of shows to get to do this. Most shows are doing 13 episodes a year instead of 24, which is what we started out with. It takes a long time doing 13 episodes a season to get to 300 episodes. I think this is kind of a marker we may not see that much of in the future. It meant a lot and I&amp;rsquo;m really proud of- for everyone. I&amp;rsquo;m really proud of everyone and just very excited to get to be a part of it. It&amp;rsquo;s cool.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Monica&lt;/strong&gt; I want to ask, and I know it could be a little spoiler, but in the 300th episode, I&amp;rsquo;ve heard rumors there might be some flash backs? Is that&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja&lt;/strong&gt; Ah yes. Flashbacks slash faux-backs. [laughs] That&amp;rsquo;s what we&amp;rsquo;re calling them. We did out best. It has been thirteen years. [laughs] Thirteen meaningful years. But it was truly fun and embarrassing and silly to try and do it- I hope we pulled it off. I hope the fans enjoy it. There&amp;rsquo;s- You know it&amp;rsquo;s not a huge chunk of the show, but three flashbacks. Four I think! We go back to 2000. There&amp;rsquo;s some funny clothes, and funny hairstyles. I threw in a wig. And it&amp;rsquo;s great. We do, we&amp;rsquo;re- the episode is really about a cold case from 2000, that has certainly haunted Sara for the last thirteen years. And I think it, within the show, Sara feels a certain exuberance at having a second chance at a case she thought had really slipped through her fingers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So not only did I get a second chance to be a part of something so exciting, but she&amp;rsquo;s getting a second chance to really try and find justice for somebody who&amp;rsquo;s living a nightmare several times.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Monica&lt;/strong&gt; Is there anything else you want to tell to the fans who are super excited &amp;#8212; they&amp;rsquo;re counting down the hours to the premiere. Is there anything you want to say to them? Anything about the season or just in general that you want them to know?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja&lt;/strong&gt; I think yes. I wanna say to all the fans of CSI, thank you so much! Thank you thank you thank you thank you for your support all these years. We are continually surprised and completely elated that we get ratings every years, that we continue to get to be on this show and do these things, that&amp;rsquo;s all because of you. Thank you for your loyalty and your willingness to go on some really crazy rides with us. I hope this year we don&amp;rsquo;t disappoint you and we&amp;rsquo;re really excited to show you what we have coming up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Monica&lt;/strong&gt; Okay! Great! Those were all my questions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja&lt;/strong&gt; Thank you so much, Monica, it was great speaking with you.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>