<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>2001 on Fans of Le Fox Library</title>
    <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/tags/2001/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 2001 on Fans of Le Fox Library</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2001 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://jorjafox.net/library/tags/2001/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Channels</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2001/channels/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2001/channels/</guid>
      <description>Fox heads the network war and forces CBS ratings to exploit all grounds. No stranger to television &amp;#8212; this brunette meets more than just the average eye.
Thursday TV is the talk of two networks: one that hopes it&amp;rsquo;s still on the way up, and one that&amp;rsquo;s trying to halt its slide down. For nearly two decades, NBC dominated Thursday nights with its &amp;ldquo;Must See TV&amp;rdquo; lineup &amp;#8212; until last year, when CBS&amp;rsquo; combination of &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Survivor&amp;rdquo; put the night in play.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FW</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2001/fw/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2001/fw/</guid>
      <description>Fresh for the fall and taking over living rooms across North America, FW brings you the rising stars from the hottest TV shows this season. Opinionated, multi-talented, stylish, indipendent and really easy on the eyes, these young stars show us what hitting the big time is all about.
&amp;ldquo;Personally I would define success as the amount of joy or passion you have for what you are doing. If people are doing what they love or if it means a lot to them, then that really is successful and really blessed and lucky.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Strong Magazine</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2001/strong-magazine/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2001/strong-magazine/</guid>
      <description>Actress Jorja Fox, star of CBS&amp;rsquo;s hit drama CSI, spends a lot of time in bed - but not necessarily for the reason you&amp;rsquo;re thinking. &amp;ldquo;Sleep is key,&amp;rdquo; she says. &amp;ldquo;I try to get a full eight hours a night. On the weekends, it might even be 10 or 11 hours.&amp;rdquo;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Us Weekly</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2001/us-weekly/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2001/us-weekly/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
If [William] Petersen (who is divorced and not dating anyone seriously) is &amp;ldquo;the dad&amp;rdquo; of the cast, according to [Marg] Helgenberger, then the rest of the family hierarchy is as follows: &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m the mom,&amp;rdquo; she says, &amp;ldquo;Jorja [Fox, who playes Grissom prot&amp;eacute;g&amp;eacute;e Sara Sidle] and George [Eads] are the little sister and brother.&amp;rdquo; And [Gary] Dourdan? &amp;ldquo;Gary is the really hot guy that makes our flesh tingle when he walks by,&amp;rdquo; she says, laughing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shape Magazine</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2001/shape-magazine/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2001/shape-magazine/</guid>
      <description>Jorja Fox admits she has trouble seeing herself as the beautiful woman she is today. &amp;ldquo;Up until the age of 17, I was an overweight kid,&amp;rdquo; she says. &amp;ldquo;So I still see my body that way sometimes. It stays with you.&amp;rdquo; Lately though, Fox has been feeling more comfortable in her own skin, having landed a coveted role as crime scene investigator Sara Sidle on last season&amp;rsquo;s top-rated freshman drama, CSI.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Time Out New York</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2001/time-out-new-york/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2001/time-out-new-york/</guid>
      <description>CSI&amp;rsquo;s Jorja Fox is out for truth, justice and a steady job
This week, Jorja Fox returns for a second season of the CBS drama CSI: Crime Scene Investigation as determined detective Sara Sidle. This is big news- her previous characters have had a habit of disappearing from top-rated shows.
Five years ago, on ER, Fox played Maggie Doyle, the lesbian pediatrician who pissed off nurses and colleagues, then wandered off the series when the writers couldn&amp;rsquo;t find anything more for her to do.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Houston Chronicle</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2001/houston-chronicle/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Sep 2001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2001/houston-chronicle/</guid>
      <description>Jorja Fox speaks for many of us trying to work while also worrying about current events.
&amp;ldquo;I go from moments where you don&amp;rsquo;t want to come to work, to being very focused and concentrating, knowing there is something I&amp;rsquo;ve got to do, to other moments when I can&amp;rsquo;t seem to get it together,&amp;rdquo; said Fox, who plays Sara Sidle on CBS&amp;rsquo; hot sophomore drama CSI: Crime Scene Investigation.
In the wake of the Sept.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Guide Canada</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2001/tv-guide-canada/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Sep 2001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2001/tv-guide-canada/</guid>
      <description>She&amp;rsquo;s been on three hit TV series in as many years - ER, The West Wing and CSI - so you can&amp;rsquo;t say Jorja Fox doesn&amp;rsquo;t know how to pick choice roles. But while the natures of her shows have been diverse, the characters she&amp;rsquo;s played have all had at least one thing in common: they are strong, independent women. On ER, Fox played cranky medical intern Maggie Doyle, on The West Wing she played the recurring role of Secret Service agent Gina Toscano.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Find Law</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2001/find-law/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Aug 2001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2001/find-law/</guid>
      <description>HOLLYWOOD (Variety) - It was difficult to conduct interviews with director Allison Anders and stars Kim Dickens and Gabriel Mann Thursday during Showtime&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Things Behind the Sun&amp;rdquo; premiere after-party at the Paramount Theater.
Tearful guests could not stop coming up to these three, professing love and gratitude; one fan literally bowed to kiss Dickens&amp;rsquo; foot.
This is the intense reaction a film about a 12-year-old&amp;rsquo;s gang rape will provoke in people.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hollywood.com 24</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2001/hollywood.com-24/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Aug 2001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2001/hollywood.com-24/</guid>
      <description>Actress Jorja Fox has been everywhere on the tube-from a three-season stint on ER to a guest role on The West Wing-but she&amp;rsquo;s found a home on CBS&amp;rsquo; critically acclaimed series C.S.I., playing forensics expert Sara Sidle.
Fox, 33, spoke with Hollywood.com over the phone from her L.A. home to discuss her role on C.S.I., the upcoming Emmys ceremony, the success of ER and the joys of nudity.
Jorja, you&amp;rsquo;re a busy girl these days.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jezebel Magazine</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2001/jezebel-magazine/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Aug 2001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2001/jezebel-magazine/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Note: Jorja Fox&amp;rsquo;s answers were hand written, and spelling errors were not corrected.&amp;rdquo;
With a name like Georgia Fox&amp;hellip;er&amp;hellip;Jorja Fox, have you ever visted Altanta. If so, what did you like most about our city?
I have family in Atlanta and I&amp;rsquo;ve been there many times. I have fantasies of living there, having a big old covered porch, and a little theater. I love the Reverand, Doctor King museum!
What do you think of Southern men?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Animal Planet Radio</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2001/animal-planet-radio/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jul 2001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2001/animal-planet-radio/</guid>
      <description>Introduction [&amp;hellip;] TV star Jorja Fox of &amp;ldquo;Crime Scene Investigation: CSI&amp;rdquo; talked about how she plays with her pooch while she has time between scenes. She also talked about her roles on &amp;ldquo;The West Wing&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;E/R.&amp;rdquo; Jorja says her dream job would be appearing on TV on Animal Planet. Were the bosses listening that day?
Animal Planet Radio - (10 min) Steve Dale We&amp;rsquo;ll be right back with Jorja Fox on Animal Planet Radio!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>In Style</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2001/in-style/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jul 2001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2001/in-style/</guid>
      <description>What is the strangest thing in your fridge?
Jorja Fox
Actress, CSI
&amp;ldquo;I have a cat ball in a plastic container with catnip and dog vitamins that look like sausages.&amp;rdquo;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Entertainment Weekly</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2001/entertainment-weekly/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jul 2001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2001/entertainment-weekly/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
One minute a poker-faced sleuth can be found intoning &amp;ldquo;We chase the lie till it leads to the truth&amp;rdquo;; the next they&amp;rsquo;ll be gesturing to an anatomical sketch, cracking &amp;ldquo;This is the vagina, and it does tell a monologue.&amp;rdquo;
[&amp;hellip;]
Cold ones too, most likely, considering he and the rest of the crew are spending this nippy March night outdoors-lensing the opener to an upcoming episode in which a couple is found stabbed to death outside a restaurant.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>News Limited</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2001/news-limited/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jul 2001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2001/news-limited/</guid>
      <description>It started with Quincy M E. but now a new tea of dedicated experts are solving crimes using forensic science. SHARON RAINSBURY visited the set of Nine&amp;rsquo;s CSI and spoke to series&amp;rsquo; stars william Petersen and Jorja Fox. IT is 8.30am on Monday morning, but the Las Vegas criminalistics bureau is already a hive of activity. Uniformed police officers come and go through the front door as two cars pull up outside the grey building.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CSI Season 1 DVD extras</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2001/csi-dvd-extras/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jul 2001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2001/csi-dvd-extras/</guid>
      <description>Jorja Fox Ah, my character&amp;rsquo;s name is Sara Sidle, and she&amp;rsquo;s come in from San Francisco, ah, the character of Grissom has called her up and said there&amp;rsquo;s, you know, there&amp;rsquo;s a major problem happening down in Vegas, would you come down and help out for a while. So that&amp;rsquo;s what I&amp;rsquo;ve done, I&amp;rsquo;ve sort of just come off an airplane and like everybody else I haven&amp;rsquo;t slept in like two days, came right in.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Late Late Show</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2001/the-late-late-show/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jun 2001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2001/the-late-late-show/</guid>
      <description>The Late Late Show with Craig Kilborn is a TV Talk show/variety show, hosted by Craig Kilborn. Jorja Fox was the second guest, and introduced as a &amp;ldquo;beautiful actress &amp;hellip; helming the hit TV series CSI&amp;rdquo;.
Craig Kilborn: Welcome back, our next guest is a beautiful actress who has helped make CBS series &amp;ldquo;CSI.&amp;rdquo; the highest rated new drama on television. Please welcome Jorja Fox. &amp;ldquo;(cheers and applause)&amp;rdquo;
Jorja: I&amp;rsquo;m doing great.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New York Post</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2001/new-york-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Jun 2001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2001/new-york-post/</guid>
      <description>I never got off the bus
Who are your heroes?
I actually have a lot. Reverend Dr. Martin Luther King, Jr., John Lennon, Oprah Winfrey, Geronimo, Harvey Milk, Maya Angelou, Einstein. All share courage, independent thinking, immense creativity and a passion/compulsion for freedom and equality for all people. Geronimo, the only non-pacifist in the group, never gave up, faced unbeatable odds and persevered with ingenious strategy.
Is there a book or movie that has changed your life?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>USA Today Weekend</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2001/usa-today-weekend-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jun 2001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2001/usa-today-weekend-1/</guid>
      <description>Issue date = June 17, 2001
Online extra: Q&amp;amp;A with actress Jorja Fox of &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo;
Jorja Fox, &amp;ldquo;CSI: Crime Scene Investigation&amp;rdquo; forensics investigator Sara Sidle, has a knack for landing in the hot show of the moment. Her face is familiar to viewers of both &amp;ldquo;ER&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;The West Wing&amp;rdquo;, on which she had recurring parts as a doctor and secret service agent respectively. Patty Rhule caught up with her on the final week of filming &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo;, the CBS hit with a remarkable debut season.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>USA Today Weekend</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2001/usa-today-weekend-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jun 2001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2001/usa-today-weekend-2/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m one of the many fans of CBS&amp;rsquo; hit crime drama, &amp;ldquo;CSI: Crime Scene Investigation&amp;rdquo;. Tell me about Jorja Fox, one of the forensic investigators.
Roseanne Turner, Denver, Ind.
She has a talent for being in the show of the moment: Fox, 32, was in ER early on, The West Wing last year and now CSI, plus the acclaimed indie movie &amp;ldquo;Memento&amp;rdquo;. The New York native is unmarried but &amp;ldquo;involved, and not allowed to talk about it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KTLA Local News</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2001/ktla-local-news/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 May 2001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2001/ktla-local-news/</guid>
      <description>Jorja Fox currently stars on the highest ranked drama of the new TV season, CSI: Crime Scene Investigation on CBS. She plays a member of the autopsy team who heads-up the gritty drama series. &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; airs on CBS&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Filmhead.com</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2001/filmhead-com/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 May 2001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2001/filmhead-com/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
Jorja Fox as Leonard&amp;rsquo;s wife has just a few moments to make the audience love her, and she succeeds.
[&amp;hellip;]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AandE</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2001/aande/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Apr 2001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2001/aande/</guid>
      <description>I know you&amp;rsquo;re a huge CSI fan.
I love CSI. Jorja Fox rules!
I&amp;rsquo;m glad to hear that. I enjoy the show, but I think it&amp;rsquo;s a &amp;ldquo;good enough&amp;rdquo; show. Because, to me, it&amp;rsquo;s finally the cop show that nerds have been waiting for.
I don&amp;rsquo;t agree with that. I think it&amp;rsquo;s much more complex than that. I think Billy Petersen&amp;rsquo;s character is a great character. We&amp;rsquo;ve never had a character like that before on TV-a guy who is actually really a teacher, and is withdrawn in a way most guys on these shows aren&amp;rsquo;t.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stepping Out</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2001/stepping-out/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Apr 2001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2001/stepping-out/</guid>
      <description>No stranger to television, Fox also starred on NBC&amp;rsquo;s top-rated series &amp;ldquo;ER&amp;rdquo; as resident intern Dr. Maggie Doyle prior to her segue as Secret Service Agent Gina Toscano on Aaron Sokin&amp;rsquo;s Emmy Award-winning drama, &amp;ldquo;The West Wing.&amp;rdquo; Additional credits include guest turns on &amp;ldquo;Law and Order&amp;rdquo; and the historic coming out episode of &amp;ldquo;Ellen.&amp;rdquo;
Fox has also managed to carve out some impressive film credits that includes this year&amp;rsquo;s Sundance Film Festival dramatic competitor &amp;ldquo;Memento.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UNICRU</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2001/unicru/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Apr 2001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2001/unicru/</guid>
      <description>Before she landed the role of scientist Sara Sidle on C.S.I., actress Jorja Fox&amp;rsquo;s life was literally going to the dogs.
What was your first job?
I worked at a kennel in New York City called the Montrose Pet Hotel. That was when I was 16, so I have no idea if it&amp;rsquo;s still there or not.
What did you have to do?
I would feed the dogs, and I&amp;rsquo;d take them from their little hotels to these indoor dog runs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Early Show</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2001/the-early-show/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2001/the-early-show/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Early Show&amp;rdquo; is a CBS morning show. On Thursday, April 26th, they aired a &amp;#8216;behind the scenes&amp;rsquo; sequence on CSI. Gary Dourdan, George Eads and Jorja Fox gave tours.
CSI is filmed in Santa Clarita, California, and Jorja Fox showed off Grissom&amp;rsquo;s Office, where they keep bugs, and other fun toys.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yahoo Chat</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2001/yahoo-chat/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Apr 2001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2001/yahoo-chat/</guid>
      <description>This chat log was cut short by technical difficulties (dialup connection crashed). Despite promises to provide the full log, Yahoo! never did.
&amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; star Jorja Fox It&amp;rsquo;s got to be a fabulous Spring for actress Jorja Fox. She&amp;rsquo;s in the coolest TV show of the season &amp;#8212; CSI: Crime Scene Investigation &amp;#8212; and one of the most talked about movies of the year &amp;#8212; Memento. But you know, the last few years couldn&amp;rsquo;t have sucked&amp;hellip; In the 99-00 season, she portrayed Secret Service Special Agent Gina Toscano on The West Wing, protecting President Bartlet&amp;rsquo;s youngest daughter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MetroActive</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2001/metroactive/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Apr 2001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2001/metroactive/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
Jorja Fox (who can&amp;rsquo;t keep her mouth shut on TV&amp;rsquo;s CSI.) has the dialogue-free part of Shelby&amp;rsquo;s murdered wife. It seems like the wife ought to be the most important role. It seems also that this role was cast haphazardly, but maybe the problem is that Nolan didn&amp;rsquo;t create a more poignant sense of lost marital love.
When it goes Rashamonic and metaphysical at the disappointing end of the story, Memento gropes for a broader significance it doesn&amp;rsquo;t earn.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Venice Magazine</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2001/venice-magazine/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Apr 2001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2001/venice-magazine/</guid>
      <description>There&amp;rsquo;s a line in Memento, written and directed by Christopher Nolan, where Guy Pearce (L.A. Confidential), as tormented lead character Leonard Shelby, is asked, &amp;ldquo;What&amp;rsquo;s the last thing you remember?&amp;rdquo; He says, &amp;ldquo;My wife.&amp;rdquo; But the sum of what he can piece together from his injury-induced chronic loss of short-term memory is &amp;ldquo;the feel of a person.&amp;rdquo; Jorja Fox, who suffers a Psycho-like death and haunts the film as Shelby&amp;rsquo;s memory of his murdered wife, does exactly that on the screen: creates the feel of a person.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zap2It</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2001/zap2it/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Mar 2001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2001/zap2it/</guid>
      <description>Jorja Fox has appeared in a number of prominent television shows, including E.R., C.S.I. and West Wing. In Memento, she shows up as the victimized wife of Leonard Shelby - only seen in flashback sequences. For her, the experience of filming the film was almost like a dream because she only had to be on-set for a few days. &amp;ldquo;I filmed, I think, three days out of 29. So I had a very short, easy time,&amp;rdquo; she said.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Slush</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2001/slush/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Mar 2001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2001/slush/</guid>
      <description>Attendees at the premiere party for MEMENTO, the tale of murder, mayhem and a man with memory loss, might have thought they&amp;rsquo;d fallen into a swell, well-stocked celebrity fishbowl at LAS PALMAS. There were the stars of the film, GUY PEARCE, JOE PANTOLIANO and JORJA FOX, getting down to the wee hours with actors BARBARA HERSHEY, Oscar nominee MARCIA GAY HARDEN, SELMA BLAIR, JENNIFER BLANC, AMANDA DETMER, ELISA DONOVAN, THOMAS JANE (who, before the film, was spotted daringly chowing down on a plate of nachos topped with a nuclear-looking gooey cheese product), D.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hollywood At Large</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2001/hollywood-at-large/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2001/hollywood-at-large/</guid>
      <description>In 2001, Court TV had a new show, Hollywood at Large, in which they look into various TV shows and how they portray the criminal justice system. CSI was featured in the pilot, on Feb 23, 2001.
Jorja Fox had a brief interview on the show (the CSI scene lasted for about five minutes). In her interview she stated that she has liked forensic TV shows (like &amp;lsquo;The New Detectives&amp;rsquo;) since before she started working on CSI, and that she still gets grossed out the easiest.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Star Magazine</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2001/star-magazine/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2001/star-magazine/</guid>
      <description>JORJA FOX, C.S.I.&amp;rsquo;s high-tech, no-nonsense investigator, Sara Sidel, once sand and played drums and guitar as a member of Honey Pot &amp;#8212; an all girl band lead by lesbian singer Heather Grody.
Jorja also protrayed gay internist Dr. Maggie Doyle on ER, and a gay woman on the famous &amp;#8216;coming out&amp;rsquo; episode of Ellen.
But the unattached actress played it straight when she stared as Secret Service agent Gina Toscano on The West Wing &amp;#8212; and almost became an accident victim.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BartCop</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2001/bartcop/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2001/bartcop/</guid>
      <description>First time I remember seeing her was as a doctor or ER. Then she moved to the hottest new show of last year, West Wing, where she played the lady Secret Service agent who was guarding the president&amp;rsquo;s daughter. Then she moved to this year&amp;rsquo;s hottest new show, C.S.I., where she plays a criminologist. She must think this whole Hollywood thing is pretty damn easy.
I&amp;rsquo;ll bet Tally Briggs would kill to have Jorja&amp;rsquo;s luck&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sun TV</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2001/sun-tv/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2001/sun-tv/</guid>
      <description>Jorja Fox probably prefers not to describe her talents as &amp;ldquo;acting chops.&amp;rdquo; The dedicated vegetarian told The Sun&amp;rsquo;s Claire Bickley she even finds playing one of CSI&amp;rsquo;s forensic investigators a little too realistic.
THE SUN: Does the show&amp;rsquo;s grisly subject matter ever make you sick?
FOX: I think I&amp;rsquo;ve toughened up. My skin is a little bit tougher than when I started. That was my only concern when I started the show.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Plugged In</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2001/plugged-in/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2001/plugged-in/</guid>
      <description>The increasing presence of motion picture producers and directors in television is turning prime time into an unwatchable mess of PG-13 and even R-style mini-movies. Prominent names such as Joel Silver (The Matrix, Lethal Weapon) and Kevin Williamson (Scream) have already brought their big-screen values to small-screen series. Now add Jerry Bruckheimer (Coyote Ugly, The Rock) to the list. He serves as executive producer for CBS&amp;rsquo; grim CSI: Crime Scene Investigation, the highest-rated new drama of the season and the only new show nominated for a Golden Globe &amp;ldquo;Best Series&amp;rdquo; Award.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Canoe Jam! Showbiz</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2001/canoe-jam/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2001/canoe-jam/</guid>
      <description>Jorja Fox is on some kind of new career trajectory.
The actress moved from E.R., TV&amp;rsquo;s most popular series, to The West Wing, TV&amp;rsquo;s most critically acclaimed. She departed West Wing for C.S.I., the show that has turned out to be this season&amp;rsquo;s highest-rated new drama.
Is it even possible to improve on good fortune like that?
How about CBS moving CSI next week from Friday nights to Thursdays, where it will follow Survivor: The Australian Outback, almost guaranteeing it a spot in TV&amp;rsquo;s Top 10.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gist</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2001/gist/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2001/gist/</guid>
      <description>ER fans know Jorja Fox as Dr. Maggie Doyle. West Wingers may remember her as Secret Service agent Gina Toscano, who saved the life of the president (Martin Sheen) last season. Currently, she&amp;rsquo;s co-starring in CBS&amp;rsquo;s surprise hit series CSI: Crime Scene Investigation. But even though she&amp;rsquo;s appeared on three of the hottest shows on television, Jorja Fox is not exactly a household name.
&amp;ldquo;I do like to keep a lower profile,&amp;rdquo; says Fox, 31, who plays forensic investigator Sara Sidel on CSI.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Minneapolis Star Tribune</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2001/minneapolis-star-tribune/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2001/minneapolis-star-tribune/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
Jorja Fox, who plays gung-ho investigator Sara Sidel, said writers are thinking about doing more to develop the characters, but she suspects that will happen slowly, over &amp;ldquo;a long haul.&amp;rdquo; In the meantime, &amp;ldquo;I love being mysterious,&amp;rdquo; she said.
The approach makes for some wonderful scenes. At the end of &amp;ldquo;If These Walls Could Talk,&amp;rdquo; Grissom is leaving the office after finishing the long, gruesome case. On the way out, he grabs an apple from the break room and notices a half-finished crossword puzzle on the table.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Inside Media at The Paley Center</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2001/inside-media-at-the-paley-center/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2001/inside-media-at-the-paley-center/</guid>
      <description>Actor/executive producer William Petersen (Gil Grissom) and executive producer Carol Mendelsohn point out the reasons they brought Jorja Fox (Sara Sidle) onto the show.
Why Jorja Fox? William Petersen: It was very interesting. Here was this young girl who was basically a rookie. And she comes out and we basically ignore her through out the night because we were too busy doing our stuff. And to have her get shot at the end of a pilot was somewhat profound.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LA Weekly</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2001/la-weekly/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2001/la-weekly/</guid>
      <description>Though its title might suggest a playhouse built of grease-stained pizza boxes and soiled tube socks, in actuality there isn&amp;rsquo;t a stained or soiled thing going on in director Gregory Ruzzin&amp;rsquo;s light, well-intentioned and too-tepid-to-be-trite new feature. A bunch of healthy-looking, Anytown, USA-dwelling white people, whose tiny, tinny lives remain in the general orbit of a divorced mom named Delmar (played by ER&amp;rsquo;s Jorja Fox, who resembles a more robust Julianne Moore), occasionally convene over fabulous home-cooked meals to furrow their brows about nothing in particular.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Memento Premiere</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2001/memento-premiere/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2001/memento-premiere/</guid>
      <description>Jorja Fox was interviewed at the premiere of &amp;ldquo;Memento&amp;rdquo;
Interviewer: I saw the movie and it was fabulous-
Jorja Fox: Thank you.
Interviewer: -um, and it looked real scary to lay in that bag.
Jorja Fox: It was really scary, actually, &amp;ldquo;(laughs)&amp;rdquo; and, and the tile was very very cold, and there was water being spritzed on me occasionally, so I had a very&amp;hellip; I think I uh, I think I dozed off for a little while.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>News Articles (2001)</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2001/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2001/</guid>
      <description>Date Source    January 01 LA Weekly   January 19 Minneapolis Star Tribune   January 24 Canoe Jam! Showbiz   January 24 Gist   February 01 Plugged In   February 02 Sun TV   February 06 BartCop   February 13 Star Magazine   March 23 Slush   March 24 Zap2It   April 01 Venice Magazine   April 05 MetroActive   April 27 UNICRU   April 29 Stepping Out   April 30 AandE   May 08 Filmhead.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>