<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Producer Movies on JFO Library</title>
    <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/tags/producer-movies/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Producer Movies on JFO Library</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="http://jorjafox.net/library/tags/producer-movies/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Extinction Soup</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/producer/extinction-soup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/producer/extinction-soup/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Extinction Soup&amp;rdquo; follows documentary filmmaker Philip Waller on his quest for adventure as he sets out to tell the story of his larger-than-life friend and extreme sports legend, Jimmy Hall. The film quickly takes a surprise turn when Waller finds himself consumed with exposing to the world an environmental catastrophe in the making - the extinction of the oceans&amp;rsquo; shark population through the mass slaughter of these magnificent animals for their fins. Waller documents the efforts of conservationist Stefanie Brendl as she fights to educate lawmakers and help pass ground-breaking legislation that will curb the consumption of shark fin soup, considered a delicacy in many Eastern cultures, and the impetus behind 70 million sharks being killed per year.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How I Became an Elephant</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/producer/how-became-elephant/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/producer/how-became-elephant/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;How I Became An Elephant is more than just a film. It&amp;rsquo;s one girl&amp;rsquo;s story&amp;hellip; which led to a movement, which led to a continuing plan, to save a species.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lion Ark</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/producer/lion-ark/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/producer/lion-ark/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;More action adventure than traditional documentary, Lion Ark follows the world’s most ambitious and daring animal rescue, with a narrative compiled from film, interviews, conversations and reactions as events unfolded. How attitudes to animals were changed in Bolivia, illegal circuses pursued and closed, and 25 lions airlifted to freedom.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>