<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Health on Fans of Le Fox Library</title>
    <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/tags/health/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Health on Fans of Le Fox Library</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://jorjafox.net/library/tags/health/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Gal to Gal Virtual Walk</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/gal-to-gal/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/gal-to-gal/</guid>
      <description>Gal to Gal Virtual Walk was a 31-city virtual walk across the United States to benefit breast cancer courtesy of a computer, an avatar and a $3 donation. Jorja Fox was one of the initial 1500 walkers in 2007.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Macy&#39;s Passport Fund</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/macys-passport-fund/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/macys-passport-fund/</guid>
      <description>Macy’s Passport Fund supports agencies providing HIV/AIDS programming in certain counties with an operating Macy’s store location.
One of the nation&amp;rsquo;s longest-running HIV/AIDS fundraisers, The Macy&amp;rsquo;s and American Express HIV/AIDS Fundraiser (often referred to as Passport) has brought the excitement of live theatre and the best of Macy&amp;rsquo;s fall collections for men, women and children to audiences while raising over $10 million for HIV/AIDS agencies.
Jorja attended the fundraiser in 2002.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Susan G. Komen for the Cure</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/susan-g-komen/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/susan-g-komen/</guid>
      <description>Susan G. Komen fought breast cancer with her heart, body and soul. Throughout her diagnosis, treatments, and endless days in the hospital, she spent her time thinking of ways to make life better for other women battling breast cancer instead of worrying about her own situation. That concern for others continued even as Susan neared the end of her fight. Moved by Susan&amp;rsquo;s compassion for others and committed to making a difference, Nancy G.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What a Pair! (2006)</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/what-a-pair/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/what-a-pair/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The whole is more than the sum of its parts.&amp;rdquo; - Aristotle
 What A Pair! is a non-profit 501c3 that was created when a personal tragedy motivated three Hollywood producers to do something to give back. Co-founders Jo Levi DiSante, Jody Price, and Ruth Stalford believe that by partnering the right people with the right organizations, allowing folks to share their talent and expertise, we can make the world a better place and enrich lives.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>