<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>1999 on JFO Library</title>
    <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/tags/1999/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 1999 on JFO Library</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 Nov 1999 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://jorjafox.net/library/tags/1999/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Austin Chronicle Movies</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/1999/austin-chronicle-movies/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 1999 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/1999/austin-chronicle-movies/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Director: Gregory Ruzzin&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Starring: Suzanne Mara, Bill Nunn, David Shackelford, Paul Provenza, Peter Murnik, Katherine Kendall, Jorja Fox&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(PG-13, 93 min.)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Commercially speaking, this ingratiating low-budget romantic comedy seems bound for one of two starkly opposed fates: Death on arrival or modest word-of-mouth success among fans who root for the underdog in all areas of life. (These willful contrarians are easily identified by their tendency to drink Mr. Pibb, use Atari computers, and communicate by CB radio.) Lacking any brand-name stars and based on an obscure self-published novel by Lynn Scott Thomas, its pedigree couldn&amp;rsquo;t be more nondescript. Still, Ruzzin&amp;rsquo;s film obviously had something going for it to merit national theatrical release. That something would appear to be its almost fascistically positive worldview, in which no misfortune or human conflict presents more than token resistance to the jackbooted rule of sweetness and light. Extra points were probably earned by its modish cooking-as-life-metaphor theme and cast full of young actors whose resemblance to more famous stars lends them instant appeal. Unfortunately, The Hungry Bachelors Club&amp;rsquo;s prospects for repeating the success of analogous movies like Like Water for Chocolate and Soul Food are severely limited by screenwriter Fred Dresch&amp;rsquo;s unfocused, hard-to-follow script. Even for those of us raised in the post-Altman era of mandatory multiple plotlines, there&amp;rsquo;s way too much information to comfortably digest. Stressed-out single mom Delmar (E.R. semi-regular Fox) dreams of starting her own restaurant. Lacking the cash, she cuts a $50,000 surrogate motherhood deal with a rich lawyer who&amp;rsquo;s also the boss of yuppie geek Stanley (Provenza), who&amp;rsquo;s stringing along her best friend Hortense (Mara) with vague hints of marriage. The frustrated Hortense, meanwhile, is consoling herself in the arms of sexy deadbeat novelist Marlon (Shackelford), best bud of Delmar&amp;rsquo;s New Agey auto mechanic bro Jethro (Murnik), who&amp;rsquo;s befriended both worldly-wise, gourmet-cooking ex-convict Moses (Nunn), and reforming cokehead Missy (Kendall), who &amp;hellip; well, you get the idea.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The result of Dresch&amp;rsquo;s efforts to resolve all these plot threads within what Ruzzin clearly views as a character-driven story is a disorienting narrative slalom course racing from one emotion-drenched, morally improving set-piece to another &amp;#8212; with no real sense of what actual events or thought processes are provoking these emotions. There&amp;rsquo;s a similar odd tension among the writerly influences of Thomas and Dresch, resulting in a funky stylistic ragout of Joshua Brand (Northern Exposure), Amy Tan, and Callie Khouri. On the upside, The Hungry Bachelors Club boasts ensemble acting that rivals many of its obvious models. Fox, a pretty serviceable Geena Davis facsimile, does an impressive job of reconciling the tough, tender, humorous and sensual aspects of Delmar&amp;rsquo;s character. The underused Nunn, convincingly aged 25 years beyond his role as Radio Raheem in Do the Right Thing, is equally good as her business partner/soulmate. Still, in the end, this is one of those too-common movies whose luster owes mainly to the reflected glory of its models. Eat, if you&amp;rsquo;re so inclined, but don&amp;rsquo;t be surprised if you&amp;rsquo;re hungry again an hour later.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chicago Sun-Times</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/1999/chicago-sun-times/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 1999 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/1999/chicago-sun-times/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Mama&amp;rsquo;s Boys LLC presents a film directed by Gregory Ruzzin. Written by Fred Dresch and Ron Ratliff. Running time: 93 minutes. Rated PG-13 (for language). Opening today at Deerbrook, Lincoln Mall, Randhurst and Yorktown.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are so many things wrong with &amp;ldquo;The Hungry Bachelors Club&amp;rdquo; that it&amp;rsquo;s easy to overlook some of the actors&amp;rsquo; fine work. It&amp;rsquo;s unfortunate that they&amp;rsquo;re stuck portraying one-dimensional characters who make the &amp;ldquo;Melrose Place&amp;rdquo; crew appear deep.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Delmar Youngblood (Jorja Fox) is a gourmet chef who toils away as an insurance adjuster. She lives with her mother, young son and best friend Hortense (Suzanne Mara), and dreams of the day when she&amp;rsquo;ll have enough money to open her own restaurant.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Opportunity knocks when Hortense&amp;rsquo;s boyfriend Stanley (Paul Provenza) brokers a deal for Delmar to be a surrogate mother for his boss. If she agrees, she&amp;rsquo;ll receive $25,000, and he&amp;rsquo;ll be promoted to partner.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After considering Stanley&amp;rsquo;s promise to marry Hortense when he makes partner and - more importantly - her own desire to quit her job and start up her own business, Delmar says yes.&lt;br /&gt;
The only one who opposes her decision is her studly brother Jethro (Peter Murnik), who teaches anthropology by day and restores Cadillacs at night.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The entire premise of the movie is ridiculous. And because you don&amp;rsquo;t feel a connection to any of the characters, you really don&amp;rsquo;t care whether Delmar gets to open her restaurant, much less whether she&amp;rsquo;ll keep the baby.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jethro&amp;rsquo;s best friend Marlon (David Shackelford) is supposed to be a goofy, lovable character. But after the camera shows him staggering around drunk, revealing rear cleavage three times too many, you&amp;rsquo;ve already written him off as an idiot.&lt;br /&gt;
Couple that with trite stereotypes of a domineering Middle Eastern ex-husband and a chirpy Chinese gynecologist, and you&amp;rsquo;ve got really bad comedy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The movie&amp;rsquo;s saving grace is the presence of Bill Nunn, who lends a quiet dignity to his role of Moses - an ex-con who falls in love with Delmar. It&amp;rsquo;s unfortunate that director Gregory Ruzzin didn&amp;rsquo;t set the romance up better.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jae-Ha Kim previews film and entertainment highlights every Friday on Channel 32&amp;rsquo;s noon.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Entertainment Today</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/1999/entertainment-today-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 1999 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/1999/entertainment-today-2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Offscreen bonds help the ensemble cast of The Hungry Bachelors Club bring a relaxed emotional honesty to their roles.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you glimpsed the title The Hungry Bachelors Club on, say, a movie theater marquee, this romantic comedy might bring to mind a gaggle of frat boys chasing girls and chugging beer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;I was afraid of that,&amp;rdquo; admitted director Gregory Ruzzin in an interview a week before his film&amp;rsquo;s opening.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But as Ruzzin and Club&amp;rsquo;s ensemble cast can tell you, once you get beneath the misleading title you&amp;rsquo;ll find a hometown story - about family, acceptance and new beginnings. It is a world where mistakes are forgiven, racial lines are never drawn, friends are dependable and dreams are always within reach.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And the food is always delicious.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If all that seems a little too ideal, Ruzzin doesn&amp;rsquo;t mind the criticism. &amp;ldquo;My work has always been about making [the] world a better place by telling stories,&amp;rdquo; Ruzzin said. &amp;ldquo;Hopefully it rubs off on someone who sits through the movie, even if just a little bit.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The title The Hungry Bachelors Club refers to Delmar Youngblood&amp;rsquo;s (Jorja Fox) dream of opening a restaurant. For years, Delmar&amp;rsquo;s home literally transforms into a hungry bachelors club, where her Cadillac-collecting brother Jethro (Peter Murnik), romantically insecure roommate Hortense (Suzanne Mara) and piano-playing mother Hannibal (Candice Azzara) are the regulars, constantly welcoming both friends and strangers to the feast.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Naturally, Delmar wants to extend her culinary talents and feel-good atmosphere to even more people. However, her Hungry Bachelors Club can&amp;rsquo;t open without adequate funds. An opportunity presents itself when Delmar gets offered $50,000 to be a surrogate mother.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Meanwhile, there&amp;rsquo;s plenty happening elsewhere. Hortense struggles to please her ambitious lawyer boyfriend, Stanley, while slacker writer Marlon (David Shackelford) pines for her. Jethro befriends drug addict Missy (Katherine Kendall) and ex-con Moses (Bill Nunn), who are focused on enriching the world around them after having been given a second chance. And Delmar, with more circumstances than one woman could seemingly handle, falls in love with Moses while feeding everyone well. The food and cooking are an extension of love, according to Ruzzin, who has thrown quite a few dinner parties himself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;I grew up in an Italian family,&amp;rdquo; Ruzzin said. &amp;ldquo;I would go home and I wouldn&amp;rsquo;t leave the kitchen for a week&amp;hellip;. So it was not unnatural for me to do this film. I&amp;rsquo;m famous for little dinner parties on Sunday nights as an excuse to see my friends. You express love for people in your life by feeding them and caring for them.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Working in such familiar territory, Ruzzin didn&amp;rsquo;t quite need influence from other food-themed films like Soul Food and Like Water for Chocolate. The most difficult aspect of the film for the Detroit native and Santa Monica-based director would be crafting its close-knit relationships - and within a small town, to top it off. But Ruzzin got that prepackaged as well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;By uncanny coincidence, the three lead actresses and old friends - Fox, Mara and Kendall - all found themselves flying to Denver to shoot the film. &amp;ldquo;I got offered the role very suddenly,&amp;rdquo; said Fox, who plays Delmar. &amp;ldquo;In two days, we were on a plane to Colorado. I knew Katherine got offered the role within an hour, and at that point it didn&amp;rsquo;t matter what it was about, but I was going to be making a movie with good friends. It would have to be hard-core porn [for me] not to do it.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;It was the best gift,&amp;rdquo; Mara added. &amp;ldquo;On most drunken Saturday nights, the three of us would think how great it would be if we all did a film together.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Though the thought of simply working together would be enough for the actresses - who saw more of each other at casting calls than movie sets - playing good friends and acting out scenes that reflected their own lives were a doubly rewarding experience. Such a scene had Hortense, who diets profusely to please her boyfriend, confess that she wished to be beautiful and thin like Missy, played by Katherine Kendall.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Katherine and I met when we were 17, and we lived together on East 16th Street in New York. I&amp;rsquo;ve always hated her and was jealous of her for being so thin,&amp;rdquo; Mara said. &amp;ldquo;When we had to do the scene, I said to Gregory, &amp;#8216;Let&amp;rsquo;s not even rehearse, let&amp;rsquo;s just do it,&amp;rsquo; and it came off perfectly on the first take.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That may partially explain how natural and low-key this film feels when done by three friends who used to act in plays together, moved to Hollywood from the East Coast together and founded their own Los Angeles theater company, Honeypot Productions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But even their close-knit friendship needed a little push at times in order for it to translate fully on the screen. So Ruzzin was far from a casual observer, sitting back in his director&amp;rsquo;s chair and watching the movie come together by itself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;From the top down, the film feels very natural,&amp;rdquo; Mara said. &amp;ldquo;In one scene between Delmar and Hortense, it just wasn&amp;rsquo;t working, so Gregory (Ruzzin) let us take 45 minutes out of production so we could work on making the story move along. He is an actor&amp;rsquo;s director.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;According to Ruzzin, it is all a symbiotic relationship. &amp;ldquo;When I signed on to do the film, the principal casting had been completed, and I was handed these fantastic actors,&amp;rdquo; Ruzzin said. &amp;ldquo;To have these actresses already know each other and have all the things friends have before they play these parts, it reads much better than what we [would have been] able to create otherwise.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But Ruzzin also had a clear picture in mind of what The Hungry Bachelors Club should be. With several complex storylines, including an interracial romance between Delmar and Moses, surrogate motherhood and the ubiquitous fear of commitment, it&amp;rsquo;s hard to pin down what the film is essentially about; Ruzzin pre-apologizes for getting carried away&amp;hellip; showing that he&amp;rsquo;s obviously done his homework.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;The film shows people caring enough to get involved,&amp;rdquo; Ruzzin said. &amp;ldquo;Our community nowadays becomes more isolated, more mechanized, [so] that you can shop online and you don&amp;rsquo;t even need to leave your house for anything. Another example is a level of tolerance; we&amp;rsquo;re very intolerant of others&amp;rsquo; peculiarities. We made sure the fact that Moses is a black man is a non-issue. That&amp;rsquo;s a better message than calling attention to it or we&amp;rsquo;d still be living in the past. He&amp;rsquo;s also an ex-con and most people wouldn&amp;rsquo;t give him the time of day, but in the film, people recognize his innate quality.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Known for roles in films such as Do the Right Thing, Money Train and The Last Seduction, veteran character actor Nunn signed on because of a friendship with co-screenwriter Fred Dresch, who adapted Lynn Scott Meyers&amp;rsquo; novel with Ron Ratliff. Playing a &amp;ldquo;regular guy&amp;rdquo; who happens to be both a talented cook and an ex-con was somewhat of a departure. Taking on a role that wasn&amp;rsquo;t carved from movie stereotypes like a cop or a lawyer, Nunn used his own life experiences and outlook to play a man who slowly discovers that many people out there are willing to help you forge a new beginning.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;ve actually had that experience,&amp;rdquo; Nunn said. &amp;ldquo;When family members visit and stay too long, they contribute by pulling their own weight, and Moses pulls it from day one. He&amp;rsquo;s not a burden or a deadweight. The people I helped out thought I was doing them a favor, but they were doing me the favor. I wanted my character to enrich the other people&amp;rsquo;s lives.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fox and Mara experienced the same phenomenon with their characters, drawing from their own lives the salient and subtle features that help flesh out an extremely level-headed woman in Delmar and a self-depriving woman in Hortense - not to mention the journey each character experiences within the film.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Hortense already has an idea of what she wants her life to be,&amp;rdquo; Mara said. &amp;ldquo;She wants two kids and she&amp;rsquo;s so insecure with herself. There&amp;rsquo;s a nice arc in the film of her coming of age and becoming a wild woman, where she&amp;rsquo;s tearing into the chicken, letting it touch her lips.&amp;rdquo; (Throughout the rest of the film, Hortense doesn&amp;rsquo;t eat anything.)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Delmar&amp;rsquo;s trying to hold everything together, and she&amp;rsquo;s just very cool,&amp;rdquo; Fox said. &amp;ldquo;She knows she&amp;rsquo;s gotta feed her son and fix the plumbing. She focuses on things that could happen instead of daydreaming. I like to think of myself as someone who gets things done.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With characters that seem to exist on a parallel plane with the actors themselves, perhaps Ruzzin&amp;rsquo;s vision isn&amp;rsquo;t too far off from the real world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Perhaps.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;The community in the film is something I&amp;rsquo;ve tried to create in my own life,&amp;rdquo; Ruzzin said, again speaking of his dinner parties. &amp;ldquo;The group is just open to who comes in and out, and inviting [new] people in isn&amp;rsquo;t a big issue. There&amp;rsquo;s more than just a societal level, but a culturally diverse one. I live in a white enclave on the Westside and everything is so segregated. Los Angeles is so segregated, it makes me feel uncomfortable because the variety of cultures is what makes life great.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Entertainment Today</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/1999/entertainment-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 1999 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/1999/entertainment-today/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Don&amp;rsquo;t let the slightly misogynistic title fool you. This food-themed film, focusing on thirtysomethings at the helm of change, can be compared to &lt;em&gt;Soul Food&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;Eat Drink Man Woman&lt;/em&gt; with a dash of &lt;em&gt;Like Water for Chocolate&lt;/em&gt;. Single mother Delmar Youngblood (Jorja Fox) dreams of opening a restaurant called The Hungry Bachelors Club, so named for the weekly bachelor-littered dinner parties she throws. Without enough money, however, Delmar agrees to &amp;ldquo;loan an egg and rent a womb&amp;rdquo; to a couple willing to pay $50,000. Meanwhile, her best friend Hortense (Suzanne Mara) is dieting profusely for her lawyer boyfriend - who is supposed to propose - while a writer forcefully pines for her. Delmar&amp;rsquo;s brother Jethro (Peter Murnik) brings drug abuser Missy (Katherine Kendall) and ex-con Moses (Bill Nunn) into the circle of friends and family; they in turn discover new beginnings with the Youngbloods. You can call it a gumbo of stories - from hot topic issues of interracial relationships and surrogate motherhood to the more ubiquitous fear of commitment and second chances. Absolutely nothing is heavy-handed in this film, almost to a fault, but Greg Ruzzin manages to keep this close-knit community feeling real. The actors also pull off quite a feat, collectively keeping the story funny, involving and dramatic, in a quiet and almost private way, like they&amp;rsquo;re hiding a constantly running stream of consciousness behind their seemingly mundane actions.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Variety</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/1999/variety/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 1999 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/1999/variety/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A Mama&amp;rsquo;s Boys Prods. release of a Taggart Transcontinental and Managed Passion Films presentation of a Mama&amp;rsquo;s Boys production. Produced by Dan Gifford, Amy Sommer Gifford. Executive producer, Kimberly Becker. Co-producer, Robert Lynn New.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Directed by Gregory Ruzzin. Screenplay, Fred Dresch, Ron Ratliff, based on the novel by Lynn Scott Myers. Camera (FotoKem color), Robert Smith; supervising editors, Stephen Myers, Andrew Frank; music, Larry Brown; music supervisor, Spencer Proffer; production designer, Timothy Duffy; costumes, Katie Saunders; sound (Dolby), David Schaaf; supervising sound editor, Tim Kimmel; line producer, Jim Glander; assistant director, Jonathan Southard; casting, Peggy Larson. Reviewed at the Avco Cinema, L.A., Nov. 13, 1999. MPAA Rating: PG-13. Running time: 93 MIN.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;PRE&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
     Hannibal Youngblood     Candice Azzara&lt;br /&gt;
     Harold Spinner          Michael Des Barres&lt;br /&gt;
     Delmar Youngblood       Jorja Fox&lt;br /&gt;
     Missy Bainbridge        Katherine Kendall&lt;br /&gt;
     Hortense                Suzanne Mara&lt;br /&gt;
     Jethro Youngblood       Peter Murnik&lt;br /&gt;
     Moses Grady             Bill Nunn&lt;br /&gt;
     Stanley Diggers         Paul Provenza&lt;br /&gt;
     Marlon                  David Shackelford&lt;br /&gt;
     Mr. Ringold             W. Morgan Sheppard&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/PRE&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Hungry Bachelors Club&amp;rdquo; is a low-cal affair in which none of the ingredients are properly measured and the final dish is nothing to give thanks for. Self-styled romantic comedy offers few if any laughs, with only a happy (albeit ridiculous) ending making pica &amp;ldquo;comedy&amp;rdquo; in literary sense of the word. Ultra-soft approach to a quasi-Altmanesque tale featuring numerous characters in a Southern city severely throttles any B.O. potential for the project, which understandably lured no distribs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Although based on a novel, script by Fred Dresch and Ron Ratliff could still use a compass. Story focus constantly changes amid a crowded roster of characters, and lumpy, bland passages of conversation give way near the end to an absurdly compacted series of unlikely plot twists. Setup, however, suggests a classic comedy situation, as divorcee Delmar (Jorja Fox) and roommate Hortense (Suzanne Mara) stage one of their regular dinner parties for friends and family. Hortense is impatiently waiting for b.f. and rising lawyer Stanley (Paul Provenza) to pop the question, but, instead, Stanley pops one to Delmar: Would she be surrogate mom for his boss and his barren wife?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She agrees, thinking that fee for her labors will help her open her dream restaurant, the Hungry Bachelors Club. Meanwhile, we&amp;rsquo;re awkwardly introduced to quiet, sweet excon Moses (Bill Nunn), who&amp;rsquo;s sleeping in a derelict Cadillac being sought out by Delmar&amp;rsquo;s bro Jethro (Peter Murnik) and pal Marlon (David Shackelford).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Typical of story&amp;rsquo;s arch notions is character of Jethro, who explains to new buddy Moses that he teaches Mesoamerican anthropology at the local college and restores old Cads with Marlon in his spare time. This character detail comes in oh-so-handy when, back at the party, a guest dies and Jethro and the guys perform a Mayan funerary ritual on the dead woman with her daughter, Missy (Katherine Kendall) arriving in tears.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Before pic&amp;rsquo;s 93 minutes are up, wads of distracting, tragic backstory are unleashed about Missy, Moses and Jethro, with characters instantly bonding in ways that defy life and good dramatics. Even Delmar and Moses&amp;rsquo; eventual link-up comes too easily, and the restaurant opening and Delmar&amp;rsquo;s pregnancy go without the least bit of struggle.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With their pic dramatically walking in its sleep, filmmakers attempt an 11th-hour resuscitation by injecting a nonsensical flurry of plot conflicts in final minutes, including the birth of Delmar&amp;rsquo;s baby, which all are shocked to see is mixed race, meaning that Moses is the father &amp;#8212; which is logically and chronologically impossible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stronger thesps may have punched up flat material, but the actors here are undone by the flabby script. It should be Fox&amp;rsquo;s movie, and though she&amp;rsquo;s robbed of much screen time, ex-&amp;ldquo;ER&amp;rdquo; thesp doesn&amp;rsquo;t generate much rooting interest in an indifferent perf. The usually strong Nunn wastes his time in a part that goes nowhere. Only Kendall generates some true moments of passing emotion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pic would have benefited from greater specificity, starting with identifying the particular Southern city where it&amp;rsquo;s set. Several mediocre Spencer Proffer tunes are sung onscreen, all off-key and shoddily dubbed. Tech credits are just above TV caliber.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;COPYRIGHT 1999 Cahners Publishing Company&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;COPYRIGHT 2000 Gale Group&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Austin Chronicle Screens</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/1999/austin-chronicle-screens/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Oct 1999 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/1999/austin-chronicle-screens/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;D: Werner Molinsky; with Jean Smart, Robert Wagner, Emily Procter, Justin William Root, Jorja Fox, Mink Stole.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mix the tackiness of The Valley of the Dolls and the campiness of The Adventures of Priscilla: Queen of the Desert, and you get a sense of what Tiara Tango is all about. Jean Smart (Designing Women) stars as Lorelei, the former &amp;ldquo;Miss Texas Gal 1968,&amp;rdquo; who still manages beauty pageants and has now pinned her hopes on her beauty-contestant daughter. Good dialogue and performances pepper the story, but these are too often marred by a murky storyline and unmotivated actions. Word is that the print that showed at the festival is a work-in-progress, so we can hope that some of these plot hindrances will be rectified in the final edit. Robert Wagner is hilarious in a small role as Lorelei&amp;rsquo;s live-in boyfriend. He also stars in the short film by Jason Sklaver preceding the feature, &amp;ldquo;The Kidnapping,&amp;rdquo; a sardonic comedy about modern art.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tuned In</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/1999/tuned-in/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jul 1999 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/1999/tuned-in/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;PASADENA, CALIF. &amp;#8212; TV critics can be an unforgiving lot, but UPN&amp;rsquo;s fall schedule makes compassion tough to muster.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In an effort to draw more viewers &amp;#8212; particularly young, male viewers &amp;#8212; the struggling network has scheduled two hours of WWF wrestling Thursday night. Critics are bound to sneer, but it&amp;rsquo;s an easy move that&amp;rsquo;s likely to boost the network&amp;rsquo;s ratings.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[ &amp;hellip; ]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;UPN entertainment president Tom Nunan said the Fontana/Levinson show, once titled &amp;ldquo;Flesh and Blood,&amp;rdquo; was filmed only as a presentation. It&amp;rsquo;s being reworked as &amp;ldquo;The Beat,&amp;rdquo; keeping some of the same characters and jettisoning others (including original star Jorja Fox, who plays Maggie Doyle on &amp;ldquo;ER&amp;rdquo;).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fontana and Levinson will be directly involved in &amp;ldquo;The Beat.&amp;rdquo; Fontana wrote the pilot, which Levinson will direct next month in Manhattan.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[ &amp;hellip; ]&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MetroMix</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/1999/metromix/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 May 1999 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/1999/metromix/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Gregory Ruzzin&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;The Hungry Bachelors Club,&amp;rdquo; produced by the team that gave us the award-winning documentary &amp;ldquo;Waco: The Rules Of Engagement,&amp;rdquo; is in many ways a trifle, a low-key romantic comedy about a close-knit group of friendly oddballs who occasionally gather for discussion, companionship and home-cooked meals. Where it rises above the ordinary is in its attempt to address issues of personal consequence &amp;#8212; like infidelity, interracial romance and surrogate motherhood &amp;#8212; even as it maintains its tenuous comic roots.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Unfortunately, those concerns are not always dealt with successfully, due in part to some sluggish writing and the inconsistencies of the main players. Strong characters include Delmar (Jorja Fox), the single mom/earth mother of the group, who dreams of opening her own restaurant someday, and Moses (Bill Nunn), a soft-spoken ex-con whose love of cooking is equal to his passion for old cars. As the circle widens, however, the members become sketchier, including Marlon (David Shackelford), a drunken wannabe novelist who has the extreme hots for Delmar&amp;rsquo;s frustrated roommate, Hortense (Suzanne Mara), whose own biological clock is ticking as she waits for her lawyer boyfriend to pop the question.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Chances are that &amp;ldquo;The Hungry Bachelors Club&amp;rdquo; will drift through theaters for a couple of weeks before showing up on video shelves this winter, but those who are partial to a soothing cinematic Sunday meal of, say, roast chicken and potatoes instead of something more daring may find this gentle tale of love delayed and dreams deferred to be surprisingly satisfying. MPAA rating: PG-13.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bergen Records</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/1999/bergen-records/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Feb 1999 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/1999/bergen-records/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Special from The Philadelphia Inquirer&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After hospitals (&amp;ldquo;St. Elsewhere&amp;rdquo;), cops (&amp;ldquo;Homicide&amp;rdquo;), and prison (&amp;ldquo;Oz&amp;rdquo;), what&amp;rsquo;s left for madly prolific producer Tom Fontana?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why, all three, of course.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;UPN&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;The True Story&amp;rdquo; (working title) stars Jorja Fox (intern Maggie Doyle on &amp;ldquo;ER&amp;rdquo;) as &amp;#8212; get this &amp;#8212; a medical intern whose father is in prison for killing her mother.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And, oh yes, intern Meghan has a brother who&amp;rsquo;s a cop.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;In one regard, this is a cavalcade of the work of Tom Fontana,&amp;rdquo; says the producer, who&amp;rsquo;s creating the new show with his longtime partner in crime, Barry Levinson. &amp;ldquo;If we included &amp;#8216;Tattingers,&amp;rsquo; we could throw in a restaurant.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Appearances to the contrary, &amp;ldquo;Story,&amp;rdquo; to launch in the fall, is less about doctors, cops, and prisoners than it is about Fontana&amp;rsquo;s vision of the American family.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;ve never wanted to do a family show because I always found them kind of sentimental and easy,&amp;rdquo; says Fontana, 47. &amp;ldquo;I want to do a show about a functional family that survives an enormous tragedy.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Story&amp;rdquo; is based on a real incident involving a couple Fontana knew: A man murdered his wife, then jumped off the roof of their apartment building. When their young son returned home from school, he saw his father&amp;rsquo;s body on the sidewalk, then ran upstairs to discover his mother&amp;rsquo;s.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;I think all of us, as children, experience some kind of trauma that informs us for the rest of our lives and shapes us as adults,&amp;rdquo; Fontana says. &amp;ldquo;I wanted to take that to an extreme.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In &amp;ldquo;Story,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;here are two children who were very young when the tragedy happened. I&amp;rsquo;ve written so much about the immediacy of violence. But I thought, &amp;#8216;What is the aftermath 25 years later?&amp;lsquo;&amp;rdquo; He made the woman a doctor and the man a cop so &amp;#8216;they both become different kinds of helpers.&amp;lsquo;&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;UPN has ordered a pilot and six scripts of &amp;ldquo;Story.&amp;rdquo; Once the project gets the green light, production on 13 episodes will begin in July.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;By that point, the third season of &amp;ldquo;Oz&amp;rdquo; will be in the can, Fontana says, which means he&amp;rsquo;ll only have to focus on one other ongoing series &amp;#8212; &amp;ldquo;Homicide.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Den</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/1999/the-den/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Feb 1999 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/1999/the-den/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Jorja who? No one really knows who the hell she is, but she&amp;rsquo;s pretty hot, she&amp;rsquo;s on ER, and that&amp;rsquo;s good enough for UPN.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jorja Fox, who plays intern Maggie Doyle on &lt;em&gt;ER&lt;/em&gt;, is apparently doing her best David Caruso impersonation by leaving a hit show to take the lead role on the new UPN sure-fire bomb &lt;em&gt;The True Story.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The show, from the creators of &lt;em&gt;Homicide,&lt;/em&gt; Tom Fontana and Barry Levinson, will be ready for UPN&amp;rsquo;s fall schedule provided the two&amp;rsquo;s escape from Betty Ford goes off without a hitch.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;UPN originally ordered six episodes of the series for fall, but now it is just funding a pilot and six scripts because they are a bunch of sissies or are still digging themselves from the financial trench compliments of &lt;em&gt;The Secret Diary of Desmond Pfieffer.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fox will play Meghan, a medical intern, whose father is in prison for killing her mother. Meghan will also have a cop brother who will most likely be a tough non-practicing Catholic type, who &amp;ldquo;doesn&amp;rsquo;t take no shit from nobody.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Aside from &lt;em&gt;ER,&lt;/em&gt; Fox&amp;rsquo;s soon-to-be-over career has included appearances on the &amp;ldquo;coming-out&amp;rdquo; episode of &lt;em&gt;Ellen,&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;Law &amp;amp; Order.&lt;/em&gt; She recently completed the indie film &lt;em&gt;Tiara Tango&lt;/em&gt; with Jean Smart. Also, Fox has had roles in the films &lt;em&gt;Jerky Boys&lt;/em&gt; and the unforgettable &lt;em&gt;Feminist Warriors.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fox&amp;rsquo;s last line on &lt;em&gt;ER&lt;/em&gt; will reportedly be, &amp;ldquo;File that yourself, bastard.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Gist</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/1999/the-gist/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Feb 1999 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/1999/the-gist/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Jorja Fox, who plays intern Maggie Doyle on &lt;em&gt;ER&lt;/em&gt;, is going to keep her job even as she moves to a hospital on the UPN network. She will still be a medical intern on &lt;em&gt;The True Story&lt;/em&gt;, a drama series being considered by UPN for its fall lineup. However, Fox will be the star instead of an &lt;em&gt;ER&lt;/em&gt; bit player; her character&amp;rsquo;s father is in jail for killing her mother.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If that series doesn&amp;rsquo;t sound unusual enough, consider two other programs UPN may greenlight: &lt;em&gt;Student Affairs&lt;/em&gt;, a spoof of daytime soaps set in college, and &lt;em&gt;Secret Agent Man&lt;/em&gt;, which is loosely based on the &amp;lsquo;60 series &lt;em&gt;The Man from U.N.C.L.E.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ultimate TV</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/1999/ultimate-tv/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Feb 1999 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/1999/ultimate-tv/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;ER&amp;rdquo; costar Jorja Fox has been cast as a lead on the new Tom Fontana/Barry Levinson series for UPN, according to Daily Variety. In &amp;ldquo;The True Story,&amp;rdquo; Fox is slated to play a medical intern &amp;#8212; basically the same role she currently has on TV&amp;rsquo;s hottest drama.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;UPN&lt;/strong&gt; is funding a pilot and six scripts of &amp;ldquo;True Story,&amp;rdquo; but will decide after the pilot is completed whether or not to commit to 13 episodes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Before &amp;ldquo;ER,&amp;rdquo; Fox played Sarah Bryant in the 1998 television special &amp;ldquo;How to Make the Cruelest Month.&amp;rdquo; She has also starred in &amp;ldquo;Jerky Boys,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;Tiara Tango&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Feminist Warriors.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apollo Guide</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/1999/apollo-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 1999 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/1999/apollo-guide/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;You are two hours from collision with an asteroid, and pirates have disabled your spaceship, seeking the forty billion dollars in cash thatï¿½s stuffed in your hold. This is Velocity Trap. It&amp;rsquo;s pretty standard mid-range action science fiction fare that benefits a lot from recent improvements in special effects technology.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When watching this film, you must first ask yourself what are you looking for and how are you judging it? If your primary interest in watching films is great acting and a stellar plot, you really ought not to look here first. This one is more about action and special effects than anything else &amp;#8212; and it succeeds fairly well on those counts. The plot is predictable and has holes you could drive any one of the film&amp;rsquo;s starships through. Still, the setting is not too implausible and is at least internally self-consistent. It is also a cut above many other science fiction films because the writers, producers and director appear to be at least aware of the genre in print. I can&amp;rsquo;t count the number of films that claim to be new and original yet are simply inferior rehashes of themes that were first treated in books as far back as the nineteen thirties. Another weakness many science fiction films share is a complete ignorance of basic physics. For anyone in space there is one simple and obvious way to put out a fire. This film uses it. It is refreshing to see a science fiction film without the complete and arrogant ignorance that afflicts so many filmmakers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Olivier Gruner is an acceptable lead &amp;#8212; I enjoyed the scenes of his interstellar cop Ray Stokes doing ballet in a starship while wearing his long johns for the sheer incongruity. Jorjan Fox also does a good job as Pallas, drawing us into her character from her earliest scenes. It&amp;rsquo;s not a complex character &amp;#8212; few here are &amp;#8212; but she makes us share the other characters&amp;rsquo; understanding of her. The other characters are little more than plot devices. They do what they need to do in order to move the story along but they don&amp;rsquo;t enhance the film to any degree. Bruce Weitz&amp;rsquo;s spaceship captain is a perfect example of this. His character comes across as a captain, starship, curmudgeonly, model 502B: nothing more or less.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In short, Velocity Trap&amp;rsquo;s strengths are primarily in its credible science fiction than in its value as a film. This is not to say that it is a perfect example of science fiction &amp;#8212; far from it. But this is a science fiction film that gets enough of the science fiction setting right that a sci-fi fan can watch it without feeling insulted. If you are looking for a basic action flick in an outer space setting you can always give this one a try. The plot may be predictable and full of holes but it does drive the story along.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Box Off</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/1999/box-off/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 1999 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/1999/box-off/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Starring Jorja Fox, Bill Nunn and Suzanne Mara. Directed by Gregory Ruzzin. Written by Fred Dresch and Ron Ratliff. Produced by Dan Gifford and Amy Sommer. A Mama&amp;rsquo;s Boys release. Romantic comedy. Rated PG-13 for some mature thematic elements. Running time: 91 min.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Intended as a succulent dish spiced with equal parts quirkiness and homeyness, &amp;ldquo;The Hungry Bachelors Club&amp;rdquo; starts out appetizing enough, but ends as a bland mishmash of conflicting ingredients.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Central to this goulash is Delmar Youngblood (Jorja Fox, best known for her recurring role on television&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;ER&amp;rdquo;), unhappy in her pressure-cooker job as an insurance adjuster. She is a young single mother raising a son while dreaming of using her culinary skills to open a restaurant with her best friend, the romantically conflicted Hortense (Suzanne Mara). Hovering in the girls&amp;rsquo; orbit are Delmar&amp;rsquo;s anthropologist brother, Jethro, obsessed with vintage Cadillacs; his buddy, good old boy Marlon, who only has eyes for Hortense; and Delmar&amp;rsquo;s mother Hannibal, whose kookiness extends to a series of colorful turbans and a mysteriously wealthy gentleman caller. These supposed misfits are joined by Moses (Bill Nunn in the most well-rounded performance in the film), who is discovered by Jethro and Marlon one night in a car graveyard.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Adapted from a novel by Lynn Scott Myers, the script by Fred Dresch and Ron Ratliff unevenly works in devices unusually focused on motherhood: Delmar&amp;rsquo;s leap at surrogate motherhood, a mother-fixated Southerner, a drug-addled woman whose mother dies unexpectedly at one of Delmar&amp;rsquo;s dinner parties and other foolishness such as a disturbingly stereotyped Arab as Delmar&amp;rsquo;s ex and a silly exercise in Mayan funeral rites.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Of the many problems with &amp;ldquo;Hungry Bachelors Club,&amp;rdquo; primary is the stunted development of almost all of the characters (who are not nearly as unique or unusual as intended) and the numerous plot threads that dribble off into nothing of consequence. Clearly hoping to recreate the food-as-social-bonder spirit so delectably done in &amp;ldquo;Fried Green Tomatoes&amp;rdquo; a few years back, &amp;ldquo;Hungry Bachelors Club&amp;rdquo; (the inevitable and inexplicable name of Delmar&amp;rsquo;s restaurant, as everyone is romantically paired up by that stage) leaves one starved for something more substantial.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Checkout</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/1999/checkout/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 1999 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/1999/checkout/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Gregory Ruzzin directs this romantic comedy about 30-somethings looking for love. Divorcee Delmar and her roommate Hortense prepare for one of their usual dinner parties for their sundry friends and associates. Hortense is anxiously waiting for her boyfriend Stanley (Paul Provenza) to propose, but instead he proposes an unusual request to Delmar: Would she being to bear a child for his boss and barren wife? Delmar agrees. Meanwhile, shy Moses (Bill Nunn) who lives in an old Cadillac, is being sought after by Delmar&amp;rsquo;s brother Jethro and his buddy Marlon. Melodramatic twists and turns ensue before the ultimately upbeat ending.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Five Stars (out of ten)&lt;br /&gt;
:- 1999&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>