<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Dvd on Fans of Le Fox Library</title>
    <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/tags/dvd/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Dvd on Fans of Le Fox Library</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Jul 2007 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://jorjafox.net/library/tags/dvd/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>CSI season 7 DVD extras</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2007/csi-season-7-dvd-extras/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jul 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2007/csi-season-7-dvd-extras/</guid>
      <description>Jorja Fox &amp;ldquo;(on Billy Petersen leaving the show for four weeks in November of 2006)&amp;rdquo; I wasn&amp;rsquo;t disappointed at all, I think, you know, obviously as I met Billy he had come almost directly out of this excitement of theater he was doing in Chicago and he&amp;rsquo;s very famous for that theater that he&amp;rsquo;s done. I think that it&amp;rsquo;s been the heart of his work over the time of his career, he&amp;rsquo;s done some films that are ground-breaking and memorable and everybody, those, that&amp;rsquo;s probably the way that the most people know Billy Petersen, but I think that people who know Billy Petersen &amp;ldquo;know&amp;rdquo; that his heart and his soul has always been in the theater, so, and it&amp;rsquo;s almost as if in a sense odd that it took him six years to find his way into one, you know, and I think that it&amp;rsquo;s a testament to the show, how much &amp;ldquo;CSI:&amp;rdquo; has all this passion that he hasn&amp;rsquo;t felt like he could go do a play at the same time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CSI Season 5 DVD extras</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2005/csi-season-5-dvd-extras/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2005/csi-season-5-dvd-extras/</guid>
      <description>Jorja Fox All bets are off, and on at the same time. Anything can happen to anybody, there&amp;rsquo;s lines that have been drawn, and uh, it does make it really fascinating.
[&amp;hellip;]
Jorja Fox It, we&amp;rsquo;re split almost down the middle, 50 percent of the people who watch &amp;ldquo;CSI:&amp;rdquo; want more character stuff, and 50 percent of the people who watch the show don&amp;rsquo;t want that much of it, they really like the stories and the science.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CSI Season 3 DVD extras</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2003/csi_season_3_dvd_extras_2003/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2003/csi_season_3_dvd_extras_2003/</guid>
      <description>Crash and Burn Jorja Fox You know, Sara Sidle had a very dark year in season 3; she had a tough one, she really had a tough one. It really started, uh, I would say, in January, about midway through the season. Ah, the first thing that happens is, is, a very good friend of hers betrays her very personally. And the next time we see Sara, her boyfriend, it turns out, has a girlfriend and he also betrays her.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CSI season 2 DVD extras</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2002/csi-season-2-dvd-extras/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2002/csi-season-2-dvd-extras/</guid>
      <description>Jorja Fox &amp;ldquo;(shot of the characters viewing a &amp;lsquo;corpse&amp;rsquo;; Jorja walks away holding her stomach)&amp;rdquo; Uh. It&amp;rsquo;s too early. &amp;ldquo;(to &amp;lsquo;corpse&amp;rsquo;)&amp;rdquo; I mean, I&amp;rsquo;m sure you&amp;rsquo;re a really nice guy&amp;hellip;
[&amp;hellip;]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CSI Season 1 DVD extras</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2001/csi-dvd-extras/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jul 2001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2001/csi-dvd-extras/</guid>
      <description>Jorja Fox Ah, my character&amp;rsquo;s name is Sara Sidle, and she&amp;rsquo;s come in from San Francisco, ah, the character of Grissom has called her up and said there&amp;rsquo;s, you know, there&amp;rsquo;s a major problem happening down in Vegas, would you come down and help out for a while. So that&amp;rsquo;s what I&amp;rsquo;ve done, I&amp;rsquo;ve sort of just come off an airplane and like everybody else I haven&amp;rsquo;t slept in like two days, came right in.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>