<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Talk Shows on JFO Library</title>
    <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/tags/talk-shows/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Talk Shows on JFO Library</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2013 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://jorjafox.net/library/tags/talk-shows/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>CableTV.com</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2013/cabletv-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2013/cabletv-1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Monica Gleberman&lt;/strong&gt; .. and just ask you, how did you get involved in acting to begin with?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; Oh my goodness. I wanted to act since I was probably four or five years old. I think that the television that sat in the living room of my house was one of the bigger influences in my life. It was definitely a babysitter for me. You know, I grew up in a small town, so there weren&amp;rsquo;t many acting programs. And it was high school before I was able to be in a drama class. I think there were two things that happened. First of all I love it so much, and then second of all, people were really supportive of me, and doing acting. I think I had a lot of support doing it, and so there was no doubt in my mind. I went to New York and got lucky. I got in [something] very quickly because I ignored all these signs that said &amp;ldquo;Do Not Enter.&amp;rdquo; [laughter] I didn&amp;rsquo;t have an agency, you know &amp;#8216;Don&amp;rsquo;t go beyond this point.&amp;rsquo; And I sort of ignored all of those signs that told me not to go further and landed up in an agency, and I was able to have a conversation with my agency and I had an audition, and they started sending me out. It was so processed. But definitely I started my career in New York and was there for probably seven years before ending up in Los Angeles.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Monica&lt;/strong&gt; I have followed your career, and of course I did research before this. You have had some major television show lucky jobs. Some of the biggest shows known to man. So I want to ask you, of course you were on ER, you were on The West Wing. What was it like- I know when you&amp;rsquo;re on it, you might not think &amp;#8216;This is huge&amp;rsquo; and might not realize how big it is. But looking back, reflecting back on your appearances, what does that feel like? To look back and note that you were on these two shows that are probably going down in history as some of the best television?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja&lt;/strong&gt; Oh wow. Thank you. I think it was huge at the time for me. &lt;em&gt;ER&lt;/em&gt; in particular because I started on &lt;em&gt;ER&lt;/em&gt; in season three and they were the number one show in the country and those numbers were bigger then what you see now because there was less television to choose from. And less appointment television. I don&amp;rsquo;t know if you remember, but people had to actually turn on the TV at the right time. VCR&amp;rsquo;s existed but even then, people wanted to a lot of the bigger shows live so they could talk about them the next day. So I was terrified. Even though I hadnât watched ER, it was my momâs favorite show and a lot of my friends favorite shows and I was absolutely terrified when I got the job because I felt like in a week or two&amp;rsquo;s time, everyone in America was going to know I was an impostor. That I was just claiming to be an actor and I was terrible. So I came really close to just driving to Mexico the week before I started and forgetting the whole thing. But I&amp;rsquo;m glad I didn&amp;rsquo;t. I always felt it was a pretty incredible learning experience, to get to spend time with that caliber of people every day, writers and actors and BPs(?) and directors.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And absolutely the same goes for &lt;em&gt;West Wing&lt;/em&gt;. I think &lt;em&gt;West Wing&lt;/em&gt;&amp;hellip; I was a huge fan then, of Sorkin, and &lt;em&gt;ER&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;West Wing&lt;/em&gt; had a number of the same producers. I think the thing that surprised me the most for myself was I could get to be a part of telling a wonderful story like that. It was something that I hadn&amp;rsquo;t even dreamed of. I just felt like it was such an honor to get to try and tell that story. I really like looked after Martin Sheen&amp;rsquo;s daughter. I couldn&amp;rsquo;t believe it! I got to do something like that! I think that Sorkin, he said at the time on &lt;em&gt;West Wing&lt;/em&gt;, he&amp;rsquo;s alone, and there had been very few women Secret Service Agents at that time, that had actually been on screen. Even getting to be that, getting to be this female Secret Service Agent was kind of a lot of fun that people hadn&amp;rsquo;t gotten to do.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Monica&lt;/strong&gt; And I know, obviously, you&amp;rsquo;ve done a ton of movies and other TV shows, and then you land &lt;em&gt;CSI&lt;/em&gt;. Which, again, another- it&amp;rsquo;s like crazy, your career, because it&amp;rsquo;s another huge show! So I want to go back to Season one, and what that was like, finding out you&amp;rsquo;re going to be playing Sara, and where your mind was when you got that call.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja&lt;/strong&gt; Um. That was also a big surprise. I really didnât think that &lt;em&gt;CSI&lt;/em&gt; was going to be successful. I fell in love with the story and the idea of it. Again, at the time it was something that was pretty different and something that I hadnât really read about often. You know, &lt;em&gt;Quincy&lt;/em&gt; was sort of the thing that I could think of that sort of reminded me a little of &lt;em&gt;CSI&lt;/em&gt;. And I thought nobody was really going to watch a show about death on a Friday night, that is just kind of not a really American culture thing to do. I was so wrong about that. I really thought I would do &lt;em&gt;CSI&lt;/em&gt;, have some fun and be back on &lt;em&gt;The West Wing&lt;/em&gt; by Christmas. You know, that&amp;rsquo;s what I thought was going to happen! I thought the show was going to get canceled and here I am thirteen years later. And it was just this monster. Not &amp;#8212; I guess monster&amp;rsquo;s kind of &amp;#8212; this behemoth that none of us expected. I think that nobody could have imagined how big the ride was going to get.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And thank you for saying that! I&amp;rsquo;m actually starting my eighteenth consecutive season in a row on Prime Time television. It&amp;rsquo;s big for me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Monica&lt;/strong&gt; I know! It&amp;rsquo;s crazy!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja&lt;/strong&gt; So thanks for talking about that stuff.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Monica&lt;/strong&gt; I want to ask- so were you surprised &amp;#8212; before we get into Sara and where she&amp;rsquo;s gone over the course of- and now we&amp;rsquo;re in- there&amp;rsquo;s gonna be a fourteenth season. I want to ask you, I know that in 2007 you had announced that you were leaving the show. Were you surprised at how many fans freaked out and started sending in gifts and money and started a campaign to try to keep you on &lt;em&gt;CSI&lt;/em&gt;? Was that shocking to you at how many people cared about this character?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja&lt;/strong&gt; Absolutely. Yes. Absolutely. It was one of the most magnificent experiences. I had no idea there would be that kind of a response. Truthfully, that was my season twelve in a row, and I was tired. I was just thinking &amp;#8216;Oh my god, I just need to lie down for a minute.&amp;rsquo; I just needed to kind of sit down and reground. So I wanted to get off-screen before it started to show on screen, or before my coworkers started to notice. It was an amazing show of support, and I wished I could have changed my mind to show the fans the amount of gratitude I had for them suggesting that I stay. Honestly, if I wasn&amp;rsquo;t so exhausted, I absolutely would have. So yeah, it was an amazing feeling of surprise.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Monica&lt;/strong&gt; So now that you&amp;rsquo;re back, and you&amp;rsquo;ve been back for a while, everyone&amp;rsquo;s been super excited. I want to know from you how has Sara changed from season one, I know she&amp;rsquo;s had a lot of life changes with the proposal and getting married, but how has she changed from season one to season thirteen?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja&lt;/strong&gt; It&amp;rsquo;s funny. I think in some ways she really hasnât changed that much [laughs]. There&amp;rsquo;s been some &lt;em&gt;seemingly&lt;/em&gt; big changes. When we met Sara in 2000, if anything I think she was very much a product of her past and of her history and the things she experienced as a young kid. You know, her mother killed her father and she was in foster care for a period of time. I think that she had this drive to be a CSI that definitely stems from her experiences as a kid. I think when she left in season 7, and was gone most of season 8, she had a chance to really wrestle those demons and maybe not feel like she is controlled by her past anymore. She kind of cleared all of the ghosts out for herself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And yet, here we are in season thirteen and I feel like we have a very mature character, who is just as passionate about the cases and just as invested, but is somehow free of her history and that is kind of the way I&amp;rsquo;ve been playing the character for the last couple of season. And yet at the same time, now we are in season fourteen, I do feel that Sara- there is this compulsive drive, something very deep rooted. She can&amp;rsquo;t stop being a CSI, it&amp;rsquo;s what fuels her, maybe the duration of her life, she&amp;rsquo;s going to be there in the trenches, on the street, in the muck, in the darkness, trying to get justice for people. I&amp;rsquo;m looking at it again, myself, and like &amp;ldquo;huh!&amp;rdquo; I thought the compulsive side of her was finished, and now maybe it&amp;rsquo;s not, not at all. Maybe she&amp;rsquo;s just the same.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Monica&lt;/strong&gt; What can fans look forward to this season? What kind of cases? What are you guys going to get involved with, cause there&amp;rsquo;s always a craziness happening every episode. So what can fans expect this season for the upcoming episodes?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja&lt;/strong&gt; I think so far &amp;#8212; we are in the middle of episode 7 and I&amp;rsquo;ve seen the script for eight, and I think we have an amazing season opening up. Really exciting. We have some incredible guest stars including somebody likeâ¦ oh you know what I donât know if I could say cause I don&amp;rsquo;t know if I&amp;rsquo;m a spoiler alert. [laughs] We have some really interesting guest stars and a cooking show in episode four that is kind of based on these food contests on the food networks. There is funny stuff, there is haunting stuff â I think the writers this year again, they suggested to me, they like to pick a theme every season, and this one is definitely going to be about darkness and going darker and going deeper.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s going to be a darker season of &lt;em&gt;CSI&lt;/em&gt;, but within that also there&amp;rsquo;s going to be as much character stuff as there was last year. I think they&amp;rsquo;re continuing to write a lot of character stuff, which is great. Certainly we start the season with Morgan in jeopardy, the stakes are really high. We also start the season with a funeral and itâs not really until we get to the end of the show that you, the audience, will come to find out why we&amp;rsquo;re at the funeral and who has passed. Itâs a very compelling kind of suspenseful episode.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You know, yeah it gets crazier every year. I don&amp;rsquo;t know how the writers come up with stuff in season fourteen. The unfortunate thing is there&amp;rsquo;s no shortage of crazy crime in America to draw from. But the stakes continue to get higher, and I hope the fans will continue to enjoy that. I always am partial to the action/adventure show. And so in those episodes where we get a little kooky, hopefully the fans will still be able to roll with us.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Monica&lt;/strong&gt; I wanted to ask you, was it nice that all current cast members continued on for season fourteen?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja&lt;/strong&gt; Absolutely! Because we have had so many changes. You know, part of me, you were speaking about &lt;em&gt;ER&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;ER&lt;/em&gt; began to lose their core cast members in season three. So the fact that our show made it to season seven with the core cast intact, I think is a testament to the show and a compliment to how much we actually did get along and liked working together and did like the work itself. I think very few shows have gone seven seasons retaining their full original cast.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But yes, it&amp;rsquo;s been really nice to have a cast that&amp;rsquo;s been able to stay together for a couple of seasons. You can&amp;rsquo;t fake chemistry. You&amp;rsquo;ve sort of got to build it organically. The more you know each other, the more you work together, the deeper you can go. It&amp;rsquo;s given a chance for that. I think it&amp;rsquo;s been kind of a really great thing for the writers, because there were a lot of seasons where it was really hard for them to start breaking stories over the summer, because they weren&amp;rsquo;t completely sure who their cast was going to be. Knowing early enough that they were going to have everyone has allowed them to spread their wings more than they could for a bunch of season.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This team, this troupe of actors, you never think that &amp;#8216;Wow, three new actors in practically one season. This is definitely- this can&amp;rsquo;t go well. This is going to be difficult.&amp;rsquo; And to love these three actors as much as I do, as much as we all do, we&amp;rsquo;re having so much fun every day. I hope it shows on screen. As usual, I&amp;rsquo;m just grateful I get to come here and hang out, because it&amp;rsquo;s a really fun place to be.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Monica&lt;/strong&gt; Of course I have to ask too, season fourteen, will mark the 300th episode, which is like, nuts. So what is that? What have you guys, I think it&amp;rsquo;s like mid-season, right? The 300th?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja&lt;/strong&gt; The 300th? Episode five. We&amp;rsquo;re pretty soon, like pretty pretty soon. We&amp;rsquo;re going to do ten new shows in a row. I don&amp;rsquo;t think we&amp;rsquo;ve done that before. And so, yeah, I think five weeks after the premiere tomorrow, you&amp;rsquo;ll be able to see the 300th episode.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Monica&lt;/strong&gt; So what is that like? Being a part of &amp;hellip; I feel like a lot of this interview is about you being a part of these crazy, amazing, genius shows. And not only do you have this awesome career, but you&amp;rsquo;re a part of another benchmark, which is the 300th episode. So what is that like, being a part of?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja&lt;/strong&gt; It was such an honor for me. You know, it is a milestone. I didn&amp;rsquo;t think much about it going in, but then we all showed up for work the first day, and a couple people gave speeches, and I started to feel the gravity of it all. I think it&amp;rsquo;s been a great second chance for me. I missed the 200th episode, I wasn&amp;rsquo;t here. I was here for the 100th episode. And to get to be a part of the 300th episode meant a lot to me. More than I even imagined it would. I haven&amp;rsquo;t done 300 episodes yet, I&amp;rsquo;m behind several members of the cast because I did take that season off, and I don&amp;rsquo;t appear in every episode every year. I think with my combined with my &lt;em&gt;ER&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;West Wing&lt;/em&gt; I might be on episode 296 or something. I can share that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s funny, because &lt;em&gt;ER&lt;/em&gt; went 300 episodes, and Marg Helgenberger, George Eads and myself had all had parts on &lt;em&gt;ER&lt;/em&gt;, so with another show that the three of us can be happy for and be a part of this tiny piece of &lt;em&gt;ER&lt;/em&gt; history. Of course, the history that we have on &lt;em&gt;CSI&lt;/em&gt; is a lot deeper and bigger. It&amp;rsquo;s really cool. I don&amp;rsquo;t think it&amp;rsquo;s ever going to happen to me again, to be a part of something like this. I don&amp;rsquo;t know if it&amp;rsquo;s going to be possible for a lot of shows to get to do this. Most shows are doing 13 episodes a year instead of 24, which is what we started out with. It takes a long time doing 13 episodes a season to get to 300 episodes. I think this is kind of a marker we may not see that much of in the future. It meant a lot and I&amp;rsquo;m really proud of- for everyone. I&amp;rsquo;m really proud of everyone and just very excited to get to be a part of it. It&amp;rsquo;s cool.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Monica&lt;/strong&gt; I want to ask, and I know it could be a little spoiler, but in the 300th episode, I&amp;rsquo;ve heard rumors there might be some flash backs? Is that&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja&lt;/strong&gt; Ah yes. Flashbacks slash faux-backs. [laughs] That&amp;rsquo;s what we&amp;rsquo;re calling them. We did out best. It has been thirteen years. [laughs] Thirteen meaningful years. But it was truly fun and embarrassing and silly to try and do it- I hope we pulled it off. I hope the fans enjoy it. There&amp;rsquo;s- You know it&amp;rsquo;s not a huge chunk of the show, but three flashbacks. Four I think! We go back to 2000. There&amp;rsquo;s some funny clothes, and funny hairstyles. I threw in a wig. And it&amp;rsquo;s great. We do, we&amp;rsquo;re- the episode is really about a cold case from 2000, that has certainly haunted Sara for the last thirteen years. And I think it, within the show, Sara feels a certain exuberance at having a second chance at a case she thought had really slipped through her fingers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So not only did I get a second chance to be a part of something so exciting, but she&amp;rsquo;s getting a second chance to really try and find justice for somebody who&amp;rsquo;s living a nightmare several times.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Monica&lt;/strong&gt; Is there anything else you want to tell to the fans who are super excited &amp;#8212; they&amp;rsquo;re counting down the hours to the premiere. Is there anything you want to say to them? Anything about the season or just in general that you want them to know?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja&lt;/strong&gt; I think yes. I wanna say to all the fans of CSI, thank you so much! Thank you thank you thank you thank you for your support all these years. We are continually surprised and completely elated that we get ratings every years, that we continue to get to be on this show and do these things, that&amp;rsquo;s all because of you. Thank you for your loyalty and your willingness to go on some really crazy rides with us. I hope this year we don&amp;rsquo;t disappoint you and we&amp;rsquo;re really excited to show you what we have coming up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Monica&lt;/strong&gt; Okay! Great! Those were all my questions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja&lt;/strong&gt; Thank you so much, Monica, it was great speaking with you.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ET Online</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2011/et-online/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2011/et-online/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I like to think that I know Marg very well. And she&amp;rsquo;s one of the toughest, most stoic people &amp;lsquo; forget about woman or ladies &amp;lsquo; I mean one of the most stoic people I&amp;rsquo;ve ever met. And these moments where she&amp;rsquo;s kind of overcome are once in a blue moon. Probably the last time I ever saw that happen her dog died, probably six years ago. She&amp;rsquo;s got nerves of steel. So yeah, it&amp;rsquo;s really overwhelming. I lovingly call this job the &amp;lsquo;Hotel California&amp;rsquo;. There&amp;rsquo;s a line in the song that says that &amp;lsquo;You can check out anytime you like but you can never leave.&amp;lsquo; I&amp;rsquo;ve made that joke to her several times in the last couple of weeks. I&amp;rsquo;m like, &amp;lsquo;You&amp;rsquo;ll be back, don&amp;rsquo;t worry. You&amp;rsquo;re always a part of the team. You&amp;rsquo;re always part of the family.&amp;lsquo; And I think that, I mean, I believe in my heart I think it makes it easier to say goodbye to her right now because I believe in my heart she will be back at some point, some time. Obviously that will be Marg&amp;rsquo;s decision and that will be the writers&amp;rsquo; decision. And, you know, fate will prevail.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Issues with Jane Velez-Mitchell</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2011/issues-with-jane-velez-mitchell-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2011/issues-with-jane-velez-mitchell-2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;(BEGIN VIDEO CLIP)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;UNIDENTIFIED MALE: How do you train or break an elephant? That word, &amp;ldquo;break&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;UNIDENTIFIED FEMALE: Elephants are extremely social and they need the environment, they need movement, they need exercise.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;UNIDENTIFIED FEMALE: Abused, 24 hours until the baby totally lost their mind. Many baby died.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then the baby elephant fear the man. The man can control and the boy make baby elephant obey.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(END VIDEO CLIP)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;VELEZ-MITCHELL: We&amp;rsquo;re talking about another kind of crime right now. We&amp;rsquo;ve got a famous CSI investigator on this case looking into disturbing horrific animal abuse. You recognize her &amp;#8212; from CSI? That&amp;rsquo;s right. The CSI investigator, known to the rest of the world as Jorja Fox and she is fighting for elephants.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When people use elephants as entertainment, most don&amp;rsquo;t think, oh, they see these beautiful animals going here, there or everywhere. They don&amp;rsquo;t realize how these animals were captured; how they were taken from the wild. Elephants tortured and abused to perform for humans. Elephants tortured and abused to perform for humans.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But one 14-year-old girl figured it out. She made the connection. And now she is making a movie, &amp;ldquo;How I Became an Elephant&amp;rdquo; and it&amp;rsquo;s changing hearts and saving lives, one person and one elephant at a time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Joining me now to talk about her passion for this heroic effort, actress Jorja Fox, star of CSI; you know her from this show. Check it out.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(BEGIN VIDEO CLIP)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;UNIDENTIFIED MALE: You showed your hand today to a master manipulator, your words.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;JORJA FOX, ACTRESS, ANIMAL ACTIVIST: She has a right to know. She did this, five years ago, three weeks ago, and she&amp;rsquo;s going to do it again.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(END VIDEO CLIP)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;VELEZ-MITCHELL: What do you want to say for the elephants and the movie you&amp;rsquo;re making to save the elephants?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;FOX: Well, what I would like to say is I would like to see sort after of a transformation or an evolution in the way that a lot of people view elephants in the way elephants are treated, particularly in captivity, in the entertainment industry, in circuses and zoos. The movie that we made is called, &amp;ldquo;How I became an Elephant&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And truly about a 14-year-old girl who travels to Thailand to learn about elephants. She meets probably the person of elephant information across the globe. The name is Lek Chailert and she has an elephant sanctuary there in Thailand. A lot of people don&amp;rsquo;t realize that there&amp;rsquo;s really only been one way to train elephants from hundreds of thousands of years. It goes back. It is an Asian technique. To this day in 2011, we are using the same technique.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;VELEZ-MITCHELL: Is it cruel?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;FOX: It is beyond cruel. It&amp;rsquo;s beyond. It is completely barbaric and horrific. If you see an elephant in captivity, including a zoo, even if they&amp;rsquo;re not doing a trick, they have probably been trained with these techniques.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;VELEZ-MITCHELL: Well, Juliette saves an elephant in this documentary. Her bravery is important because these horrific animals, well, they are innocent. Nobody can speak for them except human beings who care.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Check this out. It is called &amp;ldquo;The Crash Box&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(BEGIN VIDEO CLIP)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;UNIDENTIFIED FEMALE: They were tied, maybe everything; tied the ear, the tail, the leg, and at the time maybe lost freedom. Moaning, screaming all night.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(END VIDEO CLIP)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;VELEZ-MITCHELL: Where to help &amp;#8212; all right, if you want to help, what do you do, Jorja?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;FOX: You go to howibecameanelephant.com. You stop going to circuses and zoos. Sanctuaries are great. We have elephants in captivity that we&amp;rsquo;re going to need to house. Go to a sanctuary and see them there. Don&amp;rsquo;t support those kinds of industries. If you are in Thailand be very, very careful; there&amp;rsquo;s over 300 trekking organizations in Thailand. Go to the right one.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;VELEZ-MITCHELL: All right. We&amp;rsquo;re going to leave it there. Love you Jorja.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(COMMERCIAL BREAK)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;VELEZ-MITCHELL: And you, of course, know Jorja Fox from &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo;. And there you are, Jorja Fox working on CSI as an investigator. You&amp;rsquo;ve actually used some of the skills that you learned on the show to help you investigate the plight for elephants.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;FOX: Yes. Indeed. Research is really the key. In that clip I&amp;rsquo;m getting hammered by my new boss actually for being a renegade, which is not the first of probably the last time that will happen to me personally and on the show.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(CROSSTALK)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;VELEZ-MITCHELL: You&amp;rsquo;re an animal lover.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;FOX: I am.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;VELEZ-MITCHELL: Things are changing in the world, aren&amp;rsquo;t they, for animals?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;FOX: Well, yes. And I&amp;rsquo;m an environmentalist and a conservationist. And we&amp;rsquo;re really at a critical, critical point. I mean if you look at the (INAUDIBLE) list of endangered animals, if we keep going the way we&amp;rsquo;re going in another 50 years we really critically won&amp;rsquo;t have a lot of the animals that we, as humans, need to survive on the planet. It&amp;rsquo;s not fun and games anymore.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;VELEZ-MITCHELL: I don&amp;rsquo;t have any kids, you don&amp;rsquo;t have any kids, but people who have kids want to have animals for them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;FOX: Yes. I would like us to be able to stay on this planet. I don&amp;rsquo;t want to move it Mars. I would like to stay here and I&amp;rsquo;d like &amp;#8212;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(CROSSTALK)&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Talk</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2011/the-talk/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2011/the-talk/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Julie Chen: Welcome back to &amp;ldquo;The Talk&amp;rdquo;. Our first guest is best known for her role as Sara Sidle on the hit CBS drama &amp;ldquo;CSI: Crime Scene Investigation&amp;rdquo;. Take a look.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;rdquo;(clip from CSI)&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Julie: Please welcome Jorja Fox.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jorja Fox: (walks in, waves to audience) Oh wow! (hugs hosts, sits down on the couch with Julie Chen, Sharon Osbourne and Sara Gilbert) I am so honored to be here, thanks for having me&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Julie: Oh, we&amp;rsquo;re honored to have you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jorja: &amp;hellip;I really am.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sara Gilbert: So are you a good tipper?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jorja: Oh my goodness. You know, I think that we all would like to think that we&amp;rsquo;re really good tippers (laughs) you know? I did work in the service industry for quite a while in New York, before I was (airquotes) &amp;#8216;acting full time&amp;rsquo;, and so yeah, I do try to tip generously, even if the service is horrible. (laughs)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sara: And get attention for it, like Leah [Remini]?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jorja: (nods) Yep. (laughs) That&amp;rsquo;s possible, yeah.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Julie: What&amp;rsquo;s generously? Because like I&amp;rsquo;m straight-forward 20% cause it&amp;rsquo;s a little more than 15 and the math is easy, but I find that-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jorja: The math is easy. (gestures at Julie)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Julie: -the math is easy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jorja: That&amp;rsquo;s an important-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Julie: -but if I&amp;rsquo;m with someone who like, I see is looking at, you know, when you&amp;rsquo;re doing the math, they&amp;rsquo;re just looking, I ntip up because I want them to think I&amp;rsquo;m more generous than I am.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jorja: (laughs) No.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Julie: -I&amp;rsquo;m like, &amp;#8216;yeah, throw on another ten bucks&amp;rsquo;. Isn&amp;rsquo;t that terrible? So what do you do? Do you do, what, the 20%?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jorja: Yeah, usually a &lt;em&gt;minimum&lt;/em&gt; of 20. Even if it&amp;rsquo;s a big group, you know, with 18 [percent] included.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sharon Osbourne: So many of us, especially in the industry that we&amp;rsquo;re in now, we all started serving.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jorja: (nods) Mm-hm.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sharon: I mean, I did. And didn&amp;rsquo;t do very well at it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jorja: Me either. (laughs at herself)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sharon: But I always feel, I always feel bad because people think it&amp;rsquo;s just an easy job, and it isn&amp;rsquo;t. It&amp;rsquo;s a very difficult job to do it well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jorja: Absolutely.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sharon: It&amp;rsquo;s tough to be able to serve well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jorja: (gestures) And I think in Los Angeles, honestly, sometimes the service &lt;em&gt;isn&amp;rsquo;t&lt;/em&gt; so great, because people really are, their passion is something else.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sharon: Yeah.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jorja: And they&amp;rsquo;re working to be a writer (ticks things off on her fingers), to be an actor,-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sharon: Yeah.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jorja: -to be a musician. So often yeah, you&amp;rsquo;re, you, you don&amp;rsquo;t necessarily have the best service you&amp;rsquo;ve ever had in your whole life, but at the same time, I like supporting the arts-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sharon: Me too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jorja: -so I tip. (laughs)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Julie: You, um, so you worked in the service industry, but were you a child actor, because you are such a wonderful actress.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jorja: (smiles) Oh, that&amp;rsquo;s so nice of you. Um, thank you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(audience applause)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Julie: What were you like as a child?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jorja: Um, the time. I &lt;em&gt;knew&lt;/em&gt; I wanted to be an actor when I was five, and I, I grew up in a very very small coastal town in Florida, so, and, and every once in a while I think to myself, &amp;#8216;well, I&amp;rsquo;m living my life based (gestures with her hands) on a decision I made when I was five&amp;rsquo; which is all so (gestures again) kind of interesting, I mean I-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sara: Me too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jorja: -Yeah, yeah.-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sara. It&amp;rsquo;s weird.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jorja: Like, &amp;#8216;oh, okay, should I rethink that&amp;rsquo; but, you know, &amp;lsquo;cause acting&amp;rsquo;s not really a grown-up job, I think, I play make-believe for a living, &lt;em&gt;but&lt;/em&gt;, it&amp;rsquo;s so rewarding still, I, I kinda decided y&amp;rsquo;know as long as this is fun for me, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna keep doing it. But, I was a chubby kid, um, my mom was a parent of the Depression, and to her, a, a great way to love her kids was to feed her kids, so I ate five times a day. And this was, uh, like late 70&amp;rsquo;s, early 80&amp;rsquo;s so I don&amp;rsquo;t know if you remember, they, there was a really popular t-shirt called &amp;#8216;Foxy Lady&amp;rsquo; that everybody was wearing, you know the one, everybody wore one-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Julie: Kind of.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jorja: Yeah. And my mom bought one for every day of the week, &amp;lsquo;cause she thought this was amazing, &amp;lsquo;cause my last name was Fox, and I was sent off to school in these &amp;#8216;Foxy Lady&amp;rsquo; t-shirts-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(laughter from audience)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sara, Julie: Ohhhh&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jorja: I learned some humility real, really young.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sara: But then it all turned around, right, because you became a model&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jorja: Weird.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sara: Right.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sharon: No, not with those legs it ain&amp;rsquo;t, missy. Those&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jorja: Thank you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sara: No, it&amp;rsquo;s not weird now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jorja: I went to&amp;hellip; we had built a mall in this small town, probably, you know, a couple of years, you know, I was about 14 when this mall showed up. So I&amp;rsquo;m about fifteen and a half, and my mother told me I was hanging with the wrong circle of friends, I can&amp;rsquo;t, I&amp;rsquo;m not to hang out with them any more, they were older than me, and they had cars, and we would go places that were a little further than my mother wanted me to go. So I arranged to meet these friends at the mall to say goodbye, to have a very dramatic goodbye with them, and I had been crying all morning, and, there was a modeling contest at the mall. It was the last thing that I wanted to do, but of course my friends were very fashion-forward and really cool, they&amp;rsquo;re like, &amp;#8216;well let&amp;rsquo;s, you know, I know we&amp;rsquo;re saying goodbye to you, but let&amp;rsquo;s just join the modeling contest&amp;rsquo;, and oddly, weirdly, strangely, I won. And again, you know, growing up in Florida in a small town, sort of the idea - you, you described this earlier (looking at Sharon) - what was beautiful in Florida was blonde, tanned,-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sharon: Mm-hmm.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jorja: -you know I was &lt;em&gt;none&lt;/em&gt; of those things, I mean, um, obviously I&amp;rsquo;m very fair-skinned, I&amp;rsquo;m &lt;em&gt;taller&lt;/em&gt; than most of the men even in Los Angeles, forget about the women-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(audience laughs)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sharon: Most of the men I date, anyway.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jorja: Some of them, yes. And, yeah, so winning this contest was the, the greatest fluke that ever happened to me, and my face was in the *paper&lt;/e,&gt;, and the kids at school were like (covers her mouth briefly) &amp;#8216;okay, chubby, Foxy Lady girl won the modeling contest?&amp;lsquo;. Like-&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sharon: Never.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jorja: Oh yeah.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Julie: We&amp;rsquo;ll have more with Jorja Fox when we come right back.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[commercial break]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Julie: Oh, we&amp;rsquo;re on &lt;em&gt;this&lt;/em&gt; camera - sorry. Maybe I should do television sometime. Hah hah. Welcome back to &amp;ldquo;The Talk&amp;rdquo;, we&amp;rsquo;re having a conversation with Jorja Fox. Hello, hello, hello.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jorja: Hello, hello.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sharon: I wanted to ask you about the work that you do with Bob Barker because you do a lot of work for animal advo-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jorja: Ahhh.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sara: Advocacy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sharon: Thank you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jorja: That&amp;rsquo;s a tough one, right?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sharon: I can&amp;rsquo;t get it, I can never get it out.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jorja: Um, I had the honor and pleasure of working with Bob this spring-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sharon: He is amazing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jorja: He is. He is a force to be reckoned with. And he funded the transport of 25 lions from Bolivia, ex-circus lions, to a wildlife sanctuary north of Denver, Colorado. This has never been done before, 25 lions have never gotten on a plane and, and been taken somewhere else-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sharon: Wow.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jorja: -in connection with an organization called ADI. And basically, Bolivia outlawed their travelling circuses, which is a thing that&amp;rsquo;s sort of happening all over the world, and they didn&amp;rsquo;t have the infrastructure afterwards to, to provide sort of decent, compassionate homes for these animals. So the wildlife animal sanctuary in Colorado took all 25 of them, and now they have &lt;em&gt;80 acres&lt;/em&gt; to share-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(audience cheers, applauds)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sharon: That must give you tremendous satisfaction.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jorja: You know, on a personal level it really does, and then, you know, it stems, like I&amp;rsquo;m an environmentalist, I care about the planet, and, and these &lt;em&gt;great&lt;/em&gt; land mammals that we have are, are falling off the planet at a very fast, fast pace, and&amp;hellip; so for me my commitment is habitat for them, to keep the wild places wild, and the animals that are in captivity that we &lt;em&gt;already&lt;/em&gt; have, let&amp;rsquo;s take good care of them, I think they deserve it. So&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Julie: What I, actually, but what I also hear about you is that you love to play games. (Jorja smiles) So we have a little game for you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jorja: Uh-oh.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Julie: You have to get up and switch seats with me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jorja: All right.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Julie: Okay.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(they switch seats)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jorja: Very exciting.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Julie: This is a little game that we call &amp;#8216;Jorja On My Mind&amp;rsquo;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(audience applause)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Julie: (hands Jorja a red headband)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jorja: Any game that involves a headband, something I&amp;rsquo;m excited about.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Julie: Put the headband on with the velcro facing out and here&amp;rsquo;s how it works.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jorja: (puts on the headband, straightens her hair)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Julie: I have a stack of cards-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jorja: I do uh, all [Jimmy] Fallon or Bjork style?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sara: Yeah, yeah.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jorja: Cool. (makes a funny face)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sara: Wait, pull the hair down a little&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jorja: Pull it down a little? (adjusts her hair)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sara: The hair, there we go.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(Jorja and Sara laugh)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Julie: This stack of cards is a picture of a celebrity. We&amp;rsquo;re going to give you clues as to who you&amp;rsquo;re wearing on your forehead, and-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jorja: Uh-huh.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Julie: -and like you, Jorja Fox, they too have the name of an animal in their name, but it might be the first name. Okay, it doesn&amp;rsquo;t have to be the last name.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jorja: Okay.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Julie: But it could be, either-or.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jorja: Can I get hints from the audience?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Julie: No.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(audience &amp;#8216;awwws&amp;rsquo;, Jorja looks around)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sharon: No.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Julie: No, you only get hints, we&amp;rsquo;re going to take turns giving you hints,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jorja: Okay.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Julie: If you don&amp;rsquo;t want one, you can pass and we&amp;rsquo;ll go on to the next one.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jorja: Okay.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Julie: Okay, and if you get five right in 45 seconds, everyone in the audience goes home with a &amp;ldquo;Talk&amp;rdquo; t-shirt (holds up the t-shirt).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(audience applause)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Julie: 45 seconds on the clock, please!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jorja: No pressure there&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Julie: The most famous golfer in the world, cheated on his wife.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jorja: Tiger Woods.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Julie: Allegedly!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Julie: Go, Sharon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sharon: Singer, songwriter, beautiful, blonde&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jorja: Male, female?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sharon: Gorgeous blonde lady!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jorja: Okay.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sharon: Gorgeous!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sara: If it makes you happy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jorja: Sheryl Crow!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Julie: Sara, go!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sara: Okay, he&amp;rsquo;s a singer married to Heidi Klum, it&amp;rsquo;s on a rose, an animal&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jorja: Oh, Seal!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Julie: Okay, the most famous Tibetan monk.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jorja: Dalai Lama.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(audience starts counting down the clock)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sharon: You&amp;rsquo;re good at this! She thinks she&amp;rsquo;s Angelina Jolie.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sara: Married to Brian Austin Greene.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(clock counts down to zero)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sara: She once transformed into each other- (buzzer sounds)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jorja: (makes a face) Augh!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Julie: She has the same last name as you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jorja: Megan Fox.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Julie: You know what, everyone goes home with a t-shirt! (Julie and Jorja hug; Jorja bangs into Julie&amp;rsquo;s chin) Jorja Fox!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Julie: You can see &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; every Thursday night at 9 o&amp;rsquo;clock right here on CBS. We&amp;rsquo;ll be right back.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(as the camera cuts away, Julie points to her chin)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jorja: I&amp;rsquo;m so sorry about that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Issues with Jane Velez-Mitchell</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2011/issues-with-jane-velez-mitchell-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2011/issues-with-jane-velez-mitchell-1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;(BEGIN VIDEO CLIP)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;TIM PHILLIPS, ANIMAL DEFENDERS INTERNATIONAL: These lions have lived their life in a tiny, rusting, disgusting cage on the back of a lorry. Tomorrow they&amp;rsquo;re going to feel the wind blow in their face. They&amp;rsquo;re going to feel grass beneath their feet. They&amp;rsquo;re going to roam into the bushes. They&amp;rsquo;re going to do whatever they want. They&amp;rsquo;re going to be as lions, possibly for the first real time in their lives.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(END VIDEO CLIP)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;VELEZ-MITCHELL: Tonight, an unprecedented flight to freedom for 25 magnificent animals. Bravo. Abused lions rescued from hideous conditions in Bolivia are now living out their lives in an amazing Colorado sanctuary. Last week&amp;rsquo;s operation was the largest ever rescue of its kind. It could not have been done without the help of two amazing animal-loving celebrity who join me right here on ISSUES tonight. I&amp;rsquo;m talking about my dear friends and my heroes, Bob Barker and Jorja Fox.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now, when Jorja is not busy solving murders on CSI &amp;#8212; come on, how many episodes have you seen her on, right? This time she is investigating real life crimes against animals.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And of course, Bob Barker is a legend from &amp;ldquo;The Price is Right&amp;rdquo; fame. You know, he is my hero because he helped pay for this massive rescue mission. I think he gave something like $200,000. He is an amazing, amazing hero for the animals and he&amp;rsquo;s long time vegetarian and just an activist all the way around for these animals.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Listen to this.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(BEGIN VIDEO CLIP)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;BOB BARKER, ANIMAL ACTIVITIES: Help control the pet population, have your pet spayed or neutered.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(END VIDEO CLIP)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;VELEZ-MITCHELL: Yes. Have your pet spayed and neutered. That&amp;rsquo;s his famous line.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Straight out to my dear friends: Jorja Fox and Bob Barker; Jorja, going to start with you. First of all, bravo to all of you, to both of you and the organizations involved for getting these animals out.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tell us about the conditions that these poor, poor lions have endured for their entire lives. What did you get them out of, Jorja?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;JORJA FOX, ANIMAL ACTIVIST: Jane, thank you so much for having us. Again it&amp;rsquo;s a pleasure to be with you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To give you a few examples we had eight lions, a pride of lions, a whole family living together. This is adult lions, living on the back of a truck, the size of two double beds. That&amp;rsquo;s one example of the conditions of these animals.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another lion had been in a very small zoo cage for 11 years; hadn&amp;rsquo;t seen another lion in all of that time. Two other lions had never seen another lion before; they were kept in small cages in circuses all by themselves.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;VELEZ-MITCHELL: Some of these lions, literally as you just heard, never set foot outside a small, filthy cage. Now, take a look at these conditions. No surprise that many were malnourished, stressed and traumatized. But within days of being rescued they were healthier, they were less aggressive, they had shiny coats even. Listen to this.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bob Barker, again, you gave $200,000 to help make this happen. You are my hero. What runs through you emotionally when you see these animals taken from this hellish situation and put in this fabulous sanctuary where they literally have a 15,000 square foot biosphere to live out their lives as if in nature? Bob.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All right. Jorja, went to take that one?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;FOX: Yes, I just wanted you to know that the biosphere is actually temporary. It is 15,000 square it, it has heat, it&amp;rsquo;s got grass inside, it has toys. This is merely a space for the lions to acclimate to the Denver climate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a couple months they will have 80 full acres to share there. The animal sanctuary, a wild animal sanctuary north of Denver has two other lion prides. And it was a surprise to me to find out that lions actually are genetically wired for winter as they traversed Africa they spent a lot of time in the mountains in northern Africa, it gets very cold. So this will be a great place for them. But because they&amp;rsquo;re just out of Bolivia they&amp;rsquo;re going to stay a little warmer until the weather warms up a bit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;VELEZ-MITCHELL: well, I want to go to my big issue. I got to say, zoos are basically prisons. Ok. That is my opinion. It is easy to criticize other nations where zoos are terrible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But let&amp;rsquo;s talk about the United States. We have countless animals, like Billy the elephant, he is the subject of a huge battle. He is stuck in concrete enclosure at the L.A. Zoo with no companion. See the way they&amp;rsquo;re rocking like that. That is a sign of distress.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These animals are not meant to live this way, Bob Barker. What would you say to anybody who goes to a zoo?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;BARKER: Well, let me say first, that I have heard nothing that has been said thus far. So, I don&amp;rsquo;t know what you have asked me. I understand you&amp;rsquo;ve been talking.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;VELEZ-MITCHELL:L Tell me about the zoos, Bob, come on. Tell us about the zoos and why you are against them?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;BARKER: I am against zoos. I consider them prisons for animals. And the Los Angeles Zoo has kept that poor Billy out there for years, alone with &amp;#8212;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;VELEZ-MITCHELL: More after the break. More Bob.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(COMMERCIAL BREAK)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(BEGIN VIDEO CLIP)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;UNIDENTIFIED FEMALE: We certainly couldn&amp;rsquo;t have done it without your help, Mr. Barker.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;BARKER: Line number one, come on down.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(END VIDEO CLIP)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;VELEZ-MITCHELL: Yes. This is an amazing story, the largest airlift of lions ever, thanks to Bob Barker, of &amp;ldquo;Price is Right&amp;rdquo; fame; a second chance at life for 25 beautiful lions. They spent their entire lives in filthy cages as part of really deplorable Bolivian circuses and we&amp;rsquo;re going to show you that video as we talk.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bob Barker, the Bolivians aren&amp;rsquo;t really the bad guys here because they&amp;rsquo;re actually way ahead of us. They&amp;rsquo;ve actually passed a law that the United States needs to pass. Tell us about it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;BARKER: Well, the ADI people went undercover and they collected such horrendous tape on the treatment of animals in Bolivia that the government actually passed this legislation that banned circuses that used any animals, even domestic animals. They are banned in Bolivia.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And after that legislation was passed, with other wildlife organizations, ADI went out and gathered up lions and other animals of all kinds and the lions, they brought to the United States, 25 beautiful lions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;VELEZ-MITCHELL: Jorja why don&amp;rsquo;t we do this in the United States? We just showed you video of Billy, the elephant at the L.A. Zoo. We could put him up again. You could tell he is in distress, he&amp;rsquo;s rocking back and forth. There&amp;rsquo;s been, I don&amp;rsquo;t know how many legal battles over this elephant. They want to keep that elephant.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There&amp;rsquo;s a sanctuary that&amp;rsquo;s dying to take him. There he is. Look, when they rock back and forth like that, that shows that they are not happy, they are in distress, this poor guy on concrete.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now, Bolivia is ahead of the United States. Why the heck, when we have the video here, this animal is not happy, we cannot get this animal freed to go to a sanctuary?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;JORJA: Well, Jane, I want to say, you know Billy is an amazing example of just how horrible zoos can be for animals. He is not the exception, you know. Billy&amp;rsquo;s story is a very, very common story. He happens to be one of the more famous elephants out there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think it is coming to the United States. I think that the more people find out what&amp;rsquo;s going on and also examples, it is a true testament to the Bolivian people what they were able to accomplish very quickly. And when you hear a success story like that and you see that it can actually be done, and you see these lions moving to a sanctuary, it brings it all into the realm of the possible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think in the United States, we are going to see a movement like this becoming more and more powerful over the next couple of years. It&amp;rsquo;s a long time coming. And I believe in the goodness of people. This lion expedition was really for the lions and about the lions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But at the end of the day, it was a true testament to the human spirit and what people can accomplish when they work together to make something great happen; so many people stepped forward.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(CROSSTALK)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;VELEZ-MITCHELL: Absolutely. Yes. And I want to thank some of the organizations. You can help the lions as well by supporting the amazing groups that were involved and made this happen, check out Animal Defenders International, you can go to AD-International.org. You can also visit wildanimalsanctuary.org and make a donation and get involved.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Listen, Bob Barker, I am going to give you the last word. You are just a hero. What would you say to Americans about zoos?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;BARKER: Well, I think that the progressive, well-informed zoos are already closing their elephant exhibits. I would like to see them close all of the big animal exhibits. I think that the sooner that there are &amp;#8212;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;VELEZ-MITCHELL: We are out of time. I love both of you. Thank you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(COMMERCIAL BREAK)&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pets In The City</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2011/pets-in-the-city/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2011/pets-in-the-city/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;**Pets In The City: **For many of us, the circus brings back fond memories of lions, tigers, and other large, beautiful creatures performing incredible acts of courage and agility usually with their tamers and trainers on board. But in recent years, the ability of some circuses to properly care for these large beasts has been under scrutiny. This scrutiny has not been limited to the United States. Joining us today is Jorja Fox, who plays the popular character Sara Sidle on the mega hit *CSI *Las Vegas, to talk about her personal work on behalf of some very special and now globe-trotting lions that she and other notable stars have helped move from Bolivia to the U.S. through their support of Animal Defenders International and their work on Operation: Lion Arc. Thanks so much for joining us today, Jorja.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; Oh Diane, thank you so much for having me, I&amp;rsquo;m really excited about this project.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PITC:&lt;/strong&gt; So give us a little bit of background; tell us what life is like as you know it from your involvement in this project- what life is like for a typical circus lion in Bolivia.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;JF:&lt;/strong&gt; Uh&amp;hellip; well, goodness, and that&amp;rsquo;s a huge question, the organization ADI- Animal Defenders International- started an investigation, it was sort of a two-year undercover investigation, to the treatment and soft of the everyday life of circus animals throughout South America. And they found some really, really tough findings, you know, the animals are obviously kept in very small spaces, some of them are often malnourished, they were on the road all the time, the temperatures, as we know, can either be extremely hot, or extremely cold.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Their researches- it&amp;rsquo;s pretty well-documented on their website- [inaudible] presented these findings to a bulk of counties in South America and they invited and soft of asked these nations if they could do better, and what could they do, and um, in a beautiful stroke of sort of, genius, a lot of the nations in South America responded lovingly and decided to ban circuses. So, this country that we&amp;rsquo;re dealing with right now, Bolivia, has put in a full ban in set, uh, it was actually passed by their Congress- it&amp;rsquo;s billed 40-40- and um, made traveling circuses and all circuses with large land mammals illegal. Uh, there&amp;rsquo;s-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PITC:&lt;/strong&gt; Wow.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;JF:&lt;/strong&gt; -three other countries right now in South America with bans that are pending, uh, including Peru, Brazil and Ecuador. Uh, Costa Rica banned a long time ago, I think, probably three or four years ago, uh, which really was phenomenal, because it was sort of ridged between Mexico and South America, and when Costa Rica decided to outlaw traveling circuses, they sort of put in effect- it became very difficult for these traveling circuses to get from one country to another, you know, Costa Rica, Panama, Guatemala sort of being the gateway of nations. It wasn&amp;rsquo;t an easy feat, and ADI, when they were able to successfully put these bans in effect, sort of made a pledge to the country Bolivia that they would help them with any circus animal that was left over from the ban. Obviously these animals are very difficult and expensive to care for, they have huge needs, they need a lot of land and space, and um, they told Bolivia, &amp;ldquo;Don&amp;rsquo;t hesitate&amp;rdquo;, you know, &amp;ldquo;if there&amp;rsquo;s an animal, we will be responsible for them for the duration of that animal&amp;rsquo;s life.&amp;rdquo; And out of that has come Operation: Lion Arc; ADI successfully moved four lions in May of 2010 out of Bolivia to the PAWS sanctuary in Northern California.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think it was one of the first times that something like that had been done and the problem was that, um, Bolivia unfortunately, right now, doesn&amp;rsquo;t really have the type of sanctuaries to care for these animals if they&amp;rsquo;re not privately owned through circuses. Hence the giant air-lift, and it seems sort of like an extreme measure to take to, the different life sanctuary, and also because a lot of the laws are so different throughout a lot of those countries, um, there&amp;rsquo;s a fear of leaving some of these animals behind, in essence, they could get sold off, and, and could end up almost anywhere, to a nation which hasn&amp;rsquo;t banned circuses yet, and uh, the hope was really to provide- if the ban was going to take effect, you know, the dream was to improve the circumstances for these animals, not to sort of leave them in a limbo or a purgatory.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So they have gone about the country of Bolivia with the permission and the great help of the nation of Bolivia, uh including the president and mayor and governor of Santa Cruz [California], and have collected in- I think they were able to go to seven circuses in seven days, and collect a bulk of the lions and with the one final lion that they did pick up on February 4th, there&amp;rsquo;s a total of twenty-five [lions], three of them are cubs, and one of them is a quite aged, half-blind lion named Kimba, who was given, uh, you know, just a brief window into [inaudible] in a cage in Bolivia, for the last eight years without ever leaving that cage&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PITC:&lt;/strong&gt; Wow.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;JF:&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;hellip;and they had to sledge-hammer him out, they literally had to break walls down in the zoo just to get the lions out of the zoo to get him transported. You know, after he retired from some circuses, he&amp;rsquo;d been living in the zoo for eight years, so- and that went well, that went great. And they&amp;rsquo;ve been getting him healthy enough to travel and they will be air-lifting him on February 15 to the wild animal sanctuary just outside of Denver, Colorado. They&amp;rsquo;re the largest and oldest non-profit wild-life sanctuary in the United States and, um, that&amp;rsquo;s sort of just the just of it. Any circus animal- at least, I can speak for in the United States, and having done, you know, a lot of educating myself about South America- it&amp;rsquo;s really one of the most unnatural things that we could ask of these animals. Um, nothing about the circus is in any way humane or natural for animals, particularly large land mammals like lions, bears, elephants, uh, even animals like zebras or llamas, it goes against the very grate of their nature, and I think that we&amp;rsquo;re in the kind of history that&amp;rsquo;s pretty exciting because I think a lot of people are recognizing that, and evolving beyond it, you know, there&amp;rsquo;s other ways- you know, we&amp;rsquo;re stuck with these animals now that can&amp;rsquo;t be released back into the wild because they&amp;rsquo;re not able to do so, and so what is the best possible thing that we can do for them?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The wild-life animal sanctuary in Denver, Colorado allows visitors which is one of the ways that they&amp;rsquo;re able to keep the sanctuary going, and I offer that to people who really want to see these animals, who want to, you know, educate their kids about these animals; don&amp;rsquo;t go to the circus, don&amp;rsquo;t go the zoo. Find a sanctuary in your area, there&amp;rsquo;s a decent amount of them, and take your kids there. I live in California, you know, go whale watching, don&amp;rsquo;t go to Sea World.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PITC:&lt;/strong&gt; Now, you raised a number of really interesting hot topics here. Now, one thing I kind of zeroed in on is when you say having to deal with different countries, I would imagine that gets very, very delicate, &lt;em&gt;(laughs)&lt;/em&gt; you know, when you have people from the United States going in and saying &amp;ldquo;Hey, you&amp;rsquo;re doing something wrong, we&amp;rsquo;re gonna take these lions, you know, from you&amp;rdquo;, I mean, how important was it to have the local authorities behind your efforts in that?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;JF:&lt;/strong&gt; I don&amp;rsquo;t think it can be done *without *the local authorities and without the popular support of the region. ADI sort of started their circus campaign- you know, they&amp;rsquo;re originally out of London, their headquarters is is Los Angeles now but they still have a very active office in London- and they began their campaign in Europe and they were able to implement several bans in Europe first, you know, and London has got a ban pending, and I think with the success of that they were able to branch out into other areas. I think they were connected in South America, I think that they saw that there was a dire, dire, dire need in South America, and that was one of the reasons they chose to go there next.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They&amp;rsquo;re laughing their American Circus Campaign relatively soon and I think we should&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PITC:&lt;/strong&gt; Oh really?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;JF:&lt;/strong&gt; Yeah, I think we should expect that within the year, as well. And because the U.S. is such a juggernaut of different laws and different recommendations and different statistics, I think that, uh, ADI has wanted to make sure that they&amp;rsquo;re very well prepared before they launch and part of the air-lift I think, hopefully, will let people know that ADI is out there and will sort of bring ADI home to the United States and, and that&amp;rsquo;ll create at least a platform for them to slowly begin their launch.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PITC:&lt;/strong&gt; I do have to ask you this: now, a lot of us who are &amp;ldquo;of a certain age&amp;rdquo;, shall we say &lt;em&gt;(Jorja laughs)&lt;/em&gt; have these fond memories of going to the circus, and I mean, it wasn&amp;rsquo;t a big deal, you know, that was actually one of the big things we were looking for, you know, the lions jumping through the fire, jumping through the hoops. You know, how do you fundamentally change somebody&amp;rsquo;s, I guess, childhood memories of that? You know, is there a challenge to shifting from saying &amp;ldquo;What you were watching was horrible and awful, but we want you to watch this instead?&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;**JF: **Yeah. Well, and I wouldn&amp;rsquo;t want to try and reframe people&amp;rsquo;s memories, you know, certainly if they have good memories, that&amp;rsquo;s a great first connection, you know, because if they have a great memory of animals in a circus then probably they connected at some point that there was a, a love and admiration for these animals. So, I&amp;rsquo;ve been lucky enough- and I&amp;rsquo;m not all that young myself- but I&amp;rsquo;ve been lucky enough to you know, kind of grow up with first &lt;em&gt;National Geographic&lt;/em&gt; and now *Animal Planet *and you know, IMAX theaters, and I think that there&amp;rsquo;s so many other great ways, including some of these Disney feature films that have been out, that have kind of came out of &lt;em&gt;Planet Earth&lt;/em&gt;, there&amp;rsquo;s just so many better ways to do it now, and um, you know that the legacy of importing wild animals all over the world has been a really tragic and sad one across the globe, you know, and has led in many respects to a lot of a lot of these [animal] populations being on the brink of extinction.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now we have a whole other crisis because even if we can care for a lot of these animals, we don&amp;rsquo;t have all that many places to put them where we can really call it a sanctuary, you know, whether it&amp;rsquo;s in Africa or Europe, the United States, space is limited, it&amp;rsquo;s very expensive, and, you know, along with global warming and so many of these other issues that are pressing on us, is how do we keep habitats and environments that&amp;rsquo;s sustainable for these animals and for the next two hundred, three hundred, four hundred years for our kids and their kids? And really, in my opinion, it&amp;rsquo;s sort of a balance of the planet, I mean all of these animals in the wild have very important jobs that they do, and have kept the balance of the Earth in a beautiful- I would say a very beautiful state, and I don&amp;rsquo;t think you have to be a rocket scientist to look around and see things, you know, everything from like, fishing populations disappearing, you know, at the base of it, we&amp;rsquo;re going to have to feed ourselves and hopefully live on the planet and have enough oxygen and enough trees so we can all flourish and with that, you know, without the wild-life population, I don&amp;rsquo;t think really think that&amp;rsquo;s entirely possible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PITC:&lt;/strong&gt; When you say, you know, that all of us can flourish, the lion laying down with the lamb, and us, you know, taking care of everybody as well, what occurs to me is when you do go into countries like Bolivia and you know, like certain farmers in Africa who, you know, have their crops trampled by elephants, I&amp;rsquo;m wondering, is there a very delicate balance where you can say, &amp;ldquo;Look, we care about you humans as well, and here&amp;rsquo;s an alternative that you can do to make a living as, you know, opposed to infringing upon the wild animals, you know, is that part of it as well?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;JF: Absolutely, like how can you make this sustainable for everybody? And I mean, my environmentalism and my animal advocacy comes directly out of love for people, you know, and I don&amp;rsquo;t really want to move to Mars, you know, I mean, I guess &lt;em&gt;(host laughs)&lt;/em&gt; that can always be a last resort, but-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PITC:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;(laughing)&lt;/em&gt; CSI Mars!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;JF: -you know- Yeah! &lt;em&gt;(laughs)&lt;/em&gt; I can &lt;em&gt;only&lt;/em&gt; imagine. So of course, you know, and that&amp;rsquo;s one of the bigger issues with a lot of these wild animals, is habitat encroachment, you know, and that is because the populations of people are expanding in ways that we didn&amp;rsquo;t predict thirty and forty and fifty years ago, or maybe that we just didn&amp;rsquo;t make space for, and that&amp;rsquo;s where a lot of these clashes are coming from in terms of wild habitats. You know, there&amp;rsquo;s cultural things, you know like in the U.S., I think 80% of wild [animal] trafficking ends up in the United States of China. The U.S. really loves wild animals as pets and entertainment. China loves them as pets and entertainment, they also use them for medicinal purposes and they really eat exotic animals in a way that we don&amp;rsquo;t.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So we all have our cultural sensitivities and things that we can perhaps be working on, you know, for me it starts right here in Los Angeles and California and it is, you know, it&amp;rsquo;s a very tense balance and you have to show a lot of respect for people, and hopefully at the same time we can all work together to make things better for all of us, instead of, you know, at the exclusion of, you know, farmers in let&amp;rsquo;s say the Serengeti or, you know, a lot of animals that will be gone in twenty to twenty-five years, I mean, if you get on the [inaudible] website, I mean it&amp;rsquo;s terrifying, sort of that look at what could happen. I mean now, it was a hundred years from now, then it was sixty years from now, you know now it&amp;rsquo;s twenty years from now so I really invite anybody who cares about these issues, pick your specialty and get involved, because this is something that&amp;rsquo;s gonna happen while most of us are on the planet, we&amp;rsquo;re going to see this happen. And I do think it will lead also to the fall of the human race; I don&amp;rsquo;t think that it will be exclusive to the fall of the animal kingdom.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And why is it over so many years it seems like there&amp;rsquo;s been some sort of battle- you know, maybe back when we were cave people, you know, man needed to exert his authority over the planet- at this point, we&amp;rsquo;ve won, I mean we won fair and square, we really-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PITC:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;(laughs)&lt;/em&gt; I think that&amp;rsquo;s-that&amp;rsquo;s being generous that we-that we won!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;JF:&lt;/strong&gt; We won that battle, and it&amp;rsquo;s now my generation&amp;rsquo;s time to sort of put a balance back into things. There&amp;rsquo;s a lot of ways to do that, I mean there&amp;rsquo;s a lot of people out there working very diligently on these projects. ADI is one of them, and you know, these animals are coming, primarily with the tremendous benevolence of Bob Barker, who over the last twenty years has just done some phenomenal things for animals, but because ADI has pledged to support these animals for the rest of their natural lives, they are actively seeking support and donations from people who are interested in adopting a lion or seeing these animals through. It&amp;rsquo;s a pretty remarkable undertaking, it&amp;rsquo;s the biggest seizure and rescue operation of lions ever and, um, you can go to- let me get this- savethelionsappeal.com or adiusa.org if you&amp;rsquo;d like to support this endeavor.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PITC:&lt;/strong&gt; I&amp;rsquo;ve seen that, you know a lot of us have trouble, you know, fitting our overhead luggage on the plane and I&amp;rsquo;m thinking My God, you know, how do you move a lion, you know-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;JF:&lt;/strong&gt; Yeah.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PITC:&lt;/strong&gt; *(laughs) *-on the plane from Bolivia?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;JF:&lt;/strong&gt; Twenty-five-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PITC:&lt;/strong&gt; I mean, as Jorja says, you really have to- just the logistics of moving twenty-five lions-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;**JF: **Mm-hmm.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PITC:&lt;/strong&gt; -is quite amazing. So we&amp;rsquo;re going to take a brief break, and when we&amp;rsquo;re gonna come back, and yes everyone, I am gonna ask Jorja about CSI so don&amp;rsquo;t hang me, I will be right back. &lt;em&gt;(Jorja and the host laugh)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;After the break&amp;hellip;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PITC:&lt;/strong&gt; And we&amp;rsquo;re back. And as you can see, Jorja Fox, in addition to being apparently a world investigator &lt;em&gt;(Jorja laughs)&lt;/em&gt; in getting these beautiful, exotic animals back here, as we all know, she is one of our favorites on &lt;em&gt;CSI&lt;/em&gt; Las Vegas. That&amp;rsquo;s the only CSI for a lot of us out there AHEM, but anyway* (laughs)*&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;JF:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;(laughs)&lt;/em&gt; Thank you!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PITC:&lt;/strong&gt; Jorja plays Sara Sidle who is an amazing- the evolution of that character has been amazing to watch, Jorja. What is this, the eleventh season?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;JF:&lt;/strong&gt; Yes! Season eleven! Who coulda thought?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PITC:&lt;/strong&gt; And you were gone for, what, about two years, and people went bananas!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;JF:&lt;/strong&gt; Ohhh, well thank you. Yeah, I took a sabbatical, it was, you know, interestingly enough I ended up doing at least a couple of episodes every season so far, but there was a year there, I took sort of a year off where I- I found myself tired and I decided that I wanted to get off TV before people noticed or before, perhaps, my coworkers started to notice. &lt;em&gt;CSI&lt;/em&gt; was kind enough to let me go so, and then um, you know, the year passed, and I was ready to work. I did a lot of traveling, I worked on some of my own projects, little things that I&amp;rsquo;ve been wanting to do, and things that you know, you kind of want to do &amp;lsquo;em when you&amp;rsquo;re young enough that you&amp;rsquo;ll still &amp;lsquo;em, and, and then I started looking for work and I think I&amp;rsquo;d been looking for work for about three weeks when &lt;em&gt;CSI&lt;/em&gt; called me and said &amp;ldquo;Hey, I hear you&amp;rsquo;re looking for work, would you like to come back?&amp;rdquo; and I couldn&amp;rsquo;t think of a single reason under the sun to say no and it&amp;rsquo;s been really fun, I guess I&amp;rsquo;ve been back, you know, two seasons already, almost.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PITC:&lt;/strong&gt; Hold on a second, let me back-track up this. Okay, they had to call you and say &amp;ldquo;Hey I hear you&amp;rsquo;re looking for work?&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;JF:&lt;/strong&gt; Well, you know, they had given me this amazing, beautiful, dramatic goodbye with cake and flowers and (host laughs) a party and you know, I remember saying to Carol Mendehlson, who&amp;rsquo;s our-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PITC:&lt;/strong&gt; -but they send you to South America, right? Didn&amp;rsquo;t they send you to South America?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;JF:&lt;/strong&gt; They did!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PITC:&lt;/strong&gt; Interestingly enough?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;**JF: **They did. Sara got to go to Costa Rica, she got on the Sea Shepherd off the Galapagos, she did all kinds of exciting things, and the last thing that I said to our show runner Carol Mendehlson was, you know, &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;ll miss you, thank you so much, I&amp;rsquo;m leaving, but I&amp;rsquo;d love to visit sometime.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;**PITC: **Mm-hmm.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;JF:&lt;/strong&gt; So that sort of- that, you know, one thing led to another and I had first came back, um, when William Petersen was ready to take &lt;em&gt;his&lt;/em&gt; sabbatical, they invited me back for a couple of shows, to sort of help him get off the show, and that&amp;rsquo;s where we were left, you know, sort of suspended, you know, and it was one of these great- in my opinion, it was one of these great Hollywood endings with two characters that were going to live happily ever after, exploring the world together, there was a part of me that thought, you know, we should just let that sit, you know, the book is closed, you know, the chapter at the end says &amp;ldquo;The End&amp;rdquo; and it&amp;rsquo;s over, and so, there was that, where I thought maybe the best thing for those characters was to just sort of stay there, and then there was this call from &lt;em&gt;CSI&lt;/em&gt; saying &amp;ldquo;Well why don&amp;rsquo;t you just come visit for a little while?&amp;rdquo; and I was thrilled, I never expected that to happen, you know, TV shows move on, you know, when people leave the show for whatever reason, they tend to move on, and so it was very flattering and ended up being great for me, and um, now we&amp;rsquo;re sort of in a balance where I get to do a lot of episodes and, and if there&amp;rsquo;s something else I want to do, like go to Denver in February and greet these lions for a few days, they are often able to tell me to go do it, so it&amp;rsquo;s a great, great job.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PITC:&lt;/strong&gt; You and Grissom, and as you were saying, that&amp;rsquo;s your wonderful co-star William Petersen, you guys, for a lot of people, have an ideal marriage. *(Jorja cracks up) &lt;em&gt;You know, it&amp;rsquo;s like, you love each other, you Skype in once in a while, &amp;ldquo;Hey, how you doing?&amp;rdquo;, and whatever&lt;/em&gt; (laughs)*&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;**JF: **Yeah!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PITC:&lt;/strong&gt; And I mean, and you, forget it, you teased everybody [in] the last episode [The Two Mrs. Grissoms] that he was on there and you guys were talking&amp;hellip; does that mean that Gil might be coming back?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;JF:&lt;/strong&gt; Well thanks for watching, first of all, and-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PITC:&lt;/strong&gt; Oh, of course!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;JF:&lt;/strong&gt; -and that was, yeah, a really great scene for me, you know, I had done one episode where I was on the Sea Shepherd and I Skyped Grissom, and I essentially break up with him, you know, and say you know, I&amp;rsquo;m not going to wait for you anymore, and you know, I love you and you&amp;rsquo;re free, go live your life, and sort of for that to come full circle and where I&amp;rsquo;m sitting at &lt;em&gt;CSI&lt;/em&gt; and he&amp;rsquo;s in Peru, you know, working on these ruins, well, it was a great moment, and he was kind enough to come- I don&amp;rsquo;t think it means anything necessarily for the future of Grissom and Sara on CSI, that would definitely be a question for Billy [Petersen], but I was really grateful that he showed up, and you know, at least in this make-believe world, you know, Sara and Grissom are still very much in love and happily married and, and you know, they were always two very, very independent souls who kind of always went where their heart led them and, and so I think that is a great thing about their relationship that they can be together and they&amp;rsquo;re both people who have both wanted to do some really exotic, crazy things and that they have the space in their relationship to allow each other to do that is really cool for me. I really like them as a couple, too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PITC:&lt;/strong&gt; And I mean it really seems they&amp;rsquo;ve both evolved as characters, I mean, you&amp;rsquo;ve really seen them both come out of their shells and I mean every so often you hear a revelation that&amp;rsquo;s like &amp;ldquo;Wow, you know, maybe that&amp;rsquo;s what forms a personality&amp;rdquo; but I gotta tell you, one thing I really love about Sara is, you know, you see that there&amp;rsquo;s a lot more to her than meets the eye, over the past ten years, I mean, she seems very shy and reserved, but I mean, highly intelligent, but very shy and reserved, and then, you know, every so often you like a pearl like you know, you find out she was in foster care, and then you find out that you know, she&amp;rsquo;s had other stuff, and I mean it just seems like really inspiring to a lot of women, I think, that showing a strong woman who&amp;rsquo;s overcome some hardships and has now carved out a successful career for herself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;JF:&lt;/strong&gt; Thank you, and yeah, I certainly think- and that was very polite of you, I mean, I might describe her as a little socially inept, or *(host laughs) *a little [inaudible]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PITC:&lt;/strong&gt; She&amp;rsquo;s a nerd! She&amp;rsquo;s a lab nerd!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;**JF: **&lt;em&gt;(laughs)&lt;/em&gt; But yeah, you know, it&amp;rsquo;s a testament to our writers, I think, for sure the moral of the story is that your stuff or your junk or your trauma, you know, doesn&amp;rsquo;t have to define you for your entire life, you know, and I think that&amp;rsquo;s a really awesome message, that you can make apple sauce out of apples, you know, that you can, you can persevere, and um, and you know, her and Grissom are very unique, I mean he was kind of eccentric himself when it came to such personal skills, and-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;**PITC: **Yeah!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;JF:&lt;/strong&gt; And it took them a &lt;em&gt;really long time&lt;/em&gt;&amp;#8212; I think that they &amp;#8212; that there was a connection between them and a chemistry but it took them both a really long time to both decide that they could actually spend their lives with another person. I think they both kind of thought of themselves as loners, and that maybe, that kind of a relationship wouldn&amp;rsquo;t necessarily be something they&amp;rsquo;d experience, and they were able to make it work, you know, that&amp;rsquo;s a great message too, you know, you may feel sometimes like you have trouble connecting with people, but there &lt;em&gt;is&lt;/em&gt; somebody, somewhere, out there, you know, that might make life more fun, you know, if you share it with them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PITC:&lt;/strong&gt; Even in a forensics lab!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;**JF: **Yeah! *(host laughs) *Even, even in our darkest hours, you know.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PITC:&lt;/strong&gt; You know, it also seems like you&amp;rsquo;ve been able to weave some aspects of your personality into Sara, I mean, she&amp;rsquo;s a vegetarian, right, she&amp;rsquo;s very-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;JF:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;(laughs)&lt;/em&gt; Yeah!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PITC:&lt;/strong&gt; She&amp;rsquo;s very involved with animal rights, you don&amp;rsquo;t wanna- I mean, I&amp;rsquo;ve seen a few episodes like that you don&amp;rsquo;t want to work with meat and stuff, and is this something you requested or the writers kinda did?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;JF:&lt;/strong&gt; We did an episode- it might have even been season one, I think- we did an episode, you know, it&amp;rsquo;s not uncommon in forensics for scientists to use pigs in experiments, primarily because their skin is so similar to humans. So there was an episode where Grissom had gotten himself a pig from the butcher shop and was trying to recreate how long someone might have been dead by watching the pig for several days. And the way he ascertained this was through, you know, what elements, what sort of bugs would visit the body, what time, and he was successful, he was able to recreate how long this poor woman had been dead in a forest, and through that episode, you know, what happened when I got the script, because Sara&amp;rsquo;s supposed to sit with Grissom over this whole thing, I called one of the writers and I said, &amp;ldquo;You&amp;rsquo;re not gonna use a real pig, right? Like, we&amp;rsquo;re not, please, PLEASE don&amp;rsquo;t use a real pig&amp;rdquo; and at that point, Josh Berman, who was one of the writers on the show, said &amp;ldquo;Why, are you a vegetarian?&amp;rdquo; and I said, &amp;ldquo;Well yes I am.&amp;rdquo; and he said, &amp;ldquo;Wow, so is my mom!&amp;rdquo; so he said &amp;ldquo;Well, let&amp;rsquo;s make Sara a vegetarian, wouldn&amp;rsquo;t that be cool?&amp;rdquo; and I said yeah it&amp;rsquo;d be great, so it was actually a writer&amp;rsquo;s idea, and uh, we used that episode as sort of a stepping off point for Sara that after having sat with that poor dead pig for three days that she made a personal change in her life that she wasn&amp;rsquo;t gonna eat eat anymore, and she wasn&amp;rsquo;t gonna use animals as experiments.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And we don&amp;rsquo;t use, you know, obviously, all the dead things on &lt;em&gt;CSI&lt;/em&gt; are either real, breathing live people or prosthetic, you know, brought-to-you-by the wonders of special effects, and, uh, special effects make-up people, you know, we used a fake pig, uh, and we&amp;rsquo;ve reused him two or three times in the show, he&amp;rsquo;s actually &lt;em&gt;(laughs)&lt;/em&gt; he&amp;rsquo;s ended up being worth his cost.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PITC:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;(laughs)&lt;/em&gt; He brings home the bacon, so we say!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;JF:&lt;/strong&gt; Yeah! Yeah, and I don&amp;rsquo;t condone using animals for experiments, personally, but.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;**PITC: **I have to tell you, I have a friend who works in a forensic lab here in New York, and they say, you know what, wow, I wish that we had some of those things that-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;**JF: **Yeah!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PITC:&lt;/strong&gt;* (laughs)* I mean it&amp;rsquo;s- the graphics, and this and that, I mean you guys, although, then again, there were many forensic scientists you&amp;rsquo;ve given birth to through this show.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;JF:&lt;/strong&gt; Ohhhh, well thank you, that would be nice. Yeah, there was a time about three or four years ago, that we had the best-funded forensics lab in the country. *(host laughs) *And it was sitting on a film stage in LA. Almost all of our equipment is real, and it&amp;rsquo;s- you know, some of it is donated, some of it&amp;rsquo;s purchased for the show, and so, you know, I don&amp;rsquo;t know if that&amp;rsquo;s as true today, but there was something really sad about that at the time, that Hollywood, you know, has the backing behind it to make that happen, there&amp;rsquo;s- I think that the forensics world is doing better than it did before the &lt;em&gt;CSI&lt;/em&gt; shows, you know, there&amp;rsquo;s some backlash to that too, in a sense that, you know, people, particularly, they want answers much quicker, you know, they &lt;em&gt;(laughs)&lt;/em&gt; they say, &amp;ldquo;Well yeah, but on &lt;em&gt;CSI&lt;/em&gt; they can find out the results in, you know, five minutes&amp;rdquo; and you have to wait a few weeks, and I think it&amp;rsquo;s been helpful in court because as forensic evidence is presented, jurors have a better, sort of- it&amp;rsquo;s been more acceptable to them, so forensics is not something they&amp;rsquo;re hearing for the first time when they go into a courtroom.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And thank goodness for it, you know, that&amp;rsquo;s something that&amp;rsquo;s really come out of, again, really, the last thirty years of science, you know, has made amazing strides, there, you know, there&amp;rsquo;s a cold case just solved on the news last night of a woman who had killed her kid, I feel like it was-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;**PITC: **That&amp;rsquo;s right, I remember seeing that. And the brother recently just came forward and said- my mother- yeah, yeah. That was sad. No, I-I-I-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;**JF: **-put the pieces together.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PTIC:&lt;/strong&gt; Now on the flip side of that, what I&amp;rsquo;ve heard, like once in a while a criticism is sort of like &amp;ldquo;Yeah, but you&amp;rsquo;re showing criminals exactly what they have to do not to get caught.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;JF:&lt;/strong&gt; Yes! Yeah.* (host laughs) &lt;em&gt;I think that&amp;rsquo;s true, and I also think that there&amp;rsquo;s very, very, very few ways to get away with a crime these days, you know, that window- and criminals will always&lt;/em&gt; try &lt;em&gt;to think of ways to outsmart, you know, law enforcement- but in the age that we&amp;rsquo;re living in right now, it&amp;rsquo;s pretty amazing at just how little you can actually get away with, you know. And I think the show also shows&lt;/em&gt; that* &lt;em&gt;(laughs)&lt;/em&gt; Like, oh well, we&amp;rsquo;re probably gonna arrest you. Very few of &lt;em&gt;(laughs)&lt;/em&gt; our criminals actually get off; it happens! I was outsmarted by a twelve-year-old, twice, the same genius twelve-year-old. Uh, you gotta watch those kids, because I think they&amp;rsquo;re the most ahead of the technology, you know, of anybody.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;**PITC: **Oh yeah, let me tell you. You know, my niece, she&amp;rsquo;s seven years old, she has an iPad, I&amp;rsquo;m like, you gotta be kidding me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;JF:&lt;/strong&gt; *Woooow. *&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;**PITC: **Yeah, yeah, yup, it&amp;rsquo;s amazing. So listen, I really appreciate you spending time with us, I would be remiss with our pets in this city at Life Radio listeners to not let them know that in addition to all this great stuff about you, you are also a native New Yorker.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;JF:&lt;/strong&gt; I am indeed, yes, and I miss it dearly! There&amp;rsquo;ve been several times I&amp;rsquo;ve thought to myself, &amp;ldquo;Why couldn&amp;rsquo;t I get on that *CSI *&lt;em&gt;New York&lt;/em&gt;?&amp;rdquo; &lt;em&gt;(laughs)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;*&lt;em&gt;PITC:&lt;/em&gt; ***&lt;em&gt;(laughs)&lt;/em&gt; They don&amp;rsquo;t- they don&amp;rsquo;t film that in New York, right? I mean everybody&amp;rsquo;s-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;JF:&lt;/strong&gt; No, they do the same thing we do, and the same thing that Miami does when they go, you know, four times a year or so and they shoot exteriors, so we-we go to Vegas about four times a year, and that would probably be uh, two more times a year that I&amp;rsquo;d get to be in the city that I&amp;rsquo;m in right now, if I&amp;rsquo;m lucky I get there once or twice a year, and you know, I love it. I was born in New York City-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PITC:&lt;/strong&gt; Oh! Okay.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;JF:&lt;/strong&gt; And my family relocated to a very, very, very, very small town in Florida when I was three.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PITC:&lt;/strong&gt; Oh, okay.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;**JF: **So I was primarily young in Florida, I had moved back to New York at the age of sixteen, I finished high school there, and uh, my family would go back and forth a lot. My mom was- had only lived in Montreal, and New York, sort of bigger cities, all her life, and had a dream of taking the kids and moving them down to a very small beach town, which is what she did- she would do, but she would also get homesick, often, for New York, so we would just pack it up, she&amp;rsquo;d take me out of school and we&amp;rsquo;d go up to New York for a week and a half or so and then come back.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;**PITC: **Okay, great.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;JF:&lt;/strong&gt; Yeah, no, I&amp;rsquo;m a native New Yorker, and uh, my dog, unfortunately, just passed away last week at fourteen.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PITC:&lt;/strong&gt; Oh, my goodness.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;**JF: **She was also a native New Yorker, and my cats were also native New Yorkers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PITC:&lt;/strong&gt; I&amp;rsquo;m so sorry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;JF:&lt;/strong&gt; Oh, thank you, yeah, it&amp;rsquo;s been a rough week, but she had a really peaceful goodbye.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;**PITC: **Oh my goodness. And what- how do you mean they were native New Yorkers, did you adopt them from here?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;JF:&lt;/strong&gt; Yeah, they were all rescues out of New York, yeah. And then I moved to Los Angeles, I guess about&amp;hellip; fourteen years ago now? So they all made the move with me, and adapted, you know, seamlessly, of course, so the weather out here, they loved the idea of having a yard and all that kind of stuff that I didn&amp;rsquo;t have in New York, so. But my dog- you know, I was living in LA when my dog came- it was sort of a weird rescue, a friend of a friend that had a dog that needed a home, and sort of one of those stories, and the original owner was an actor, so he threw out some auditions, he brought the dog, who was ten months old, and for about the first, I&amp;rsquo;d say, eight or nine months of her living in Los Angeles, all she wanted to do was walk up and down concrete streets [inaudible]. &lt;em&gt;(host laughs)&lt;/em&gt; I couldn&amp;rsquo;t get her to go hiking, she was- she just didn&amp;rsquo;t get it, and then as she got a little older she was like, &amp;ldquo;Oh, I guess this hiking thing&amp;rsquo;s OK&amp;rdquo;, you know.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;**PITC: **Wow, that&amp;rsquo;s-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;JF:&lt;/strong&gt; I have had in these last fifteen years or so, two cats; one came out of a shelter in New York City, one came out of a shelter in Brooklyn, and then a Boxer- I was already living in LA- that came out of New York City out to LA to be with me, and yeah, so all three of my pets are from New York, and were all rescues.&lt;br /&gt;
**&lt;br /&gt;
PITC:** Wow. And I know you said that you had lost, um, two of them recently.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;JF:&lt;/strong&gt; I lost my dog Ali last Sunday, uh, January 30th-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;**PITC: **Awww, I&amp;rsquo;m sorry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;JF:&lt;/strong&gt; She was fourteen years and four months young. Um, for a Boxer, that&amp;rsquo;s a really, really, really long, great life, yeah. She&amp;hellip; she was sort of on borrowed time for a few years already, and uh, yeah, I&amp;rsquo;ll miss her horribly. So I&amp;rsquo;m recovering from that, I&amp;rsquo;m sure-I&amp;rsquo;m sure there will be another dog in my future, but I&amp;rsquo;m going to take a little and just celebrate her first.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;**PITC: **Never gets easier, it never gets easier.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;JF:&lt;/strong&gt; No, no, it doesn&amp;rsquo;t, and uh, that&amp;rsquo;s their big joke on us, is that their lifespans are so much shorter than ours, I think* (laughs)* I was thinking, well, maybe I&amp;rsquo;ll get a turtle, you know, or a parrot &lt;em&gt;(host laughs)&lt;/em&gt; Takes them a long time! And, uh, but again, I actually don&amp;rsquo;t advocate exotic pets as pets for anybody, but you know, I think about it; it&amp;rsquo;d be nice to have an animal that, you know, would be with me hopefully as long as I have left.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;**PITC: **Well, you know, you kinda have by proxy twenty-five lions in Colorado so there you go.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;JF:&lt;/strong&gt; *(both laugh) &lt;em&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s gonna be exciting! I hope everybody will tune into the ADI website; they do a great job of presenting video diaries, you can sort of check updates almost daily, and sort of join along in this adventure and this journey, and um, Jan Creamer&amp;rsquo;s been in Bolivia for a couple of months already, preparing everything. Tim Phillips, who&amp;rsquo;s based out of London is now there too, the next time I&amp;rsquo;ll see them will be at the Denver airport. We imagine February 16, probably sometime around in the day, and, uh, it is a huge undertaking as you mentioned, getting&lt;/em&gt; four* lions to California was a massive ordeal and the plane had to reload in Panama, so you&amp;rsquo;re really bringing in three countries. You had Bolivia, you had the country of Panama and the country of the United States, that were all able to coordinate this together, they landed at San Francisco International in San Francisco. Couldn&amp;rsquo;t have been more amazing, uh, it was an odd request, and not something they get everyday &lt;em&gt;(host laughs)&lt;/em&gt; and, uh-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PITC:&lt;/strong&gt; I would imagine!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;JF:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;(laughs)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PITC:&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;ldquo;Excuse me, customs! Uh, what do you have to declare?&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;Oh sorry, five lions.&amp;rdquo; &lt;em&gt;(laughs)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;**JF: **Yeah, and you know, there&amp;rsquo;s pretty strict, you know, wild-life importation laws in the United States and that&amp;rsquo;s a GOOD thing. But, when you&amp;rsquo;re actually trying to do something like this, it can be a very complicated procedure, the paperwork alone, the different languages that people speak, as I said, um, it&amp;rsquo;s quite an ordeal, and one of the coolest things about these twenty five lions is that a couple of them are-had been living in prides already, under these circus conditions, so they&amp;rsquo;ll be together. As soon as the first lion moved, we were moving three brothers and a sister, and they&amp;rsquo;ve been together their whole lives, and the transition was actually very smooth, and we believe [it&amp;rsquo;s because] we didn&amp;rsquo;t separate them for the entire journey. And so these guys will all go together and the few that didn&amp;rsquo;t know each other have had a chance to get to know each other, in the last couple of months in the temporary compound, which we&amp;rsquo;re very grateful to Mayor Hernandez in Santa Cruz for providing the space for; a large, temporary compound for twenty-five lions! &lt;em&gt;(laughs)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PITC:&lt;/strong&gt; Uh, yeah! &lt;em&gt;(laughs)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;JF:&lt;/strong&gt; That came from Bolivia, and they&amp;rsquo;ll be bidding them farewell, so, um, it&amp;rsquo;s gonna be amazing, I mean the wild animal sanctuary in Colorado is a remarkable place, uh, they have three hundred acres and these animals, you know, most of them have never stepped on grass, they&amp;rsquo;ve never had a pond or a lake to swim around in, their lives will be *drastically *different in a couple of weeks for the better.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PITC:&lt;/strong&gt; Jorja, can you tell us one more time how our listeners can help, you know, basically really make this a great happy ending and a great new home for the lions?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;JF&lt;/strong&gt;: Yes, please! If you&amp;rsquo;re inspired or moved, you can go directly to the savethelionsappeal.com or adiusa.org- there will be a link to their site- ADI, also, I believe will be hosting video diaries if you want to find out more or learn more about these lions. They are endangered and they&amp;rsquo;re incredibly majestic animals, and I think that we need them, and they deserve a nice place to live.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;**PITC: **And so we&amp;rsquo;ll be in touch with you hopefully, you know, in a week or two, and see what&amp;rsquo;s going on?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;JF:&lt;/strong&gt; Oh, I&amp;rsquo;d love that!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;**PITC: **Okay!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;JF:&lt;/strong&gt; Yeah, follow up, that&amp;rsquo;d be great!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;**PITC: **Fantastic! Jorja, we really appreciate you visiting with us today, thank you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;**JF: **Oh Diane, thank you so much!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PITC:&lt;/strong&gt; That was very cool. I really hope that you guys got some good dish from &lt;em&gt;CSI&lt;/em&gt; Las Vegas from, of course, the wonderful Jorja Fox who plays Sara Sidle, and we&amp;rsquo;re gonna check in with her again and see how the lions are doing. We will put all the information she had spoken about how you can help the lions settle in at their new home, up on our Pets In The City On PetLife Radio website, so check that out after you listen.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Insider</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2010/the-insider/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2010/the-insider/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Watch Now: Trouble on the &amp;lsquo;CSI&amp;rsquo; Set&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;George Eads:&lt;/strong&gt; For the last couple years I was a big fan of the &amp;ldquo;Hoarders&amp;rdquo; documentary program. And so I was telling everybody-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; I think many of us are. George turned me on to it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GE:&lt;/strong&gt; I was telling you the other night!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;JF:&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;ldquo;I was watching this show the other night and you gotta check it out!&amp;rdquo; And I went and checked it out, and now it&amp;rsquo;s on my TiVo. So this is definitely a story George has wanted to tell for a while. It was in the making, it was gonna happen, and now it&amp;rsquo;s happening. It is really exciting when that &amp;hellip; happens.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GE:&lt;/strong&gt; One of the things that we &lt;em&gt;don&amp;rsquo;t&lt;/em&gt; have to deal with when we go to crime scenes is the odor. So we got lucky when it comes to that, because it&amp;rsquo;s &amp;lsquo;Movie Trash.&amp;rsquo; It&amp;rsquo;s still pretty disgusting under there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;JF:&lt;/strong&gt; It&amp;rsquo;s unbelievable, and you&amp;rsquo;ve got three and a half straight days in there. So yes, again, thank god it&amp;rsquo;s a set, but its extremely tight quarters. It&amp;rsquo;s very intimate. You get the crew in there setting lights, and move through it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GE:&lt;/strong&gt; Yeah but we talked about how there&amp;rsquo;s nobody we&amp;rsquo;d rather be with if we were stuck in a stinky set in tight quarters. You know?&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Issues with Jane Velez-Mitchell</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2010/issues-with-jane-velez-mitchell/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jun 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2010/issues-with-jane-velez-mitchell/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;JANE VELEZ-MITCHELL: In tonight&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Spotlight&amp;rdquo;, a fabulous mercy mission for four rescued circus lions. These magnificent animals were freed from their pitiful, abusive existence in a Bolivian circus last month. Bolivia recently did what every country should do &amp;#8212; banned the use of animals in circuses. These majestic animals will live out their lives at the amazing Paws Sanctuary in northern California.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our guest tonight, CSI star, Jorja Fox, who was right there for their dramatic arrival.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(BEGIN VIDEO CLIP)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;JORJA FOX, ANIMAL RIGHTS ACTIVIST: Lion number one &amp;#8212; come on down.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;TIM PHILLIPS, ANIMAL DEFENDERS INTERNATIONAL: These lions have lived their life in a tiny, rusting, disgusting cage on the back of a lorry. Tomorrow they&amp;rsquo;re going to feel the wind blow in their face. They&amp;rsquo;re going to feel grass beneath their feet. They&amp;rsquo;re going to be as lions, possibly for the first real time in their lives.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(END VIDEO CLIP)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;VELEZ-MITCHELL: I am so thrilled to welcome actress Jorja Fox, ambassador for Animal Defenders International. Jorja, great to see you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tell us how you felt inside watching these majestic animals take their very first steps into freedom.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;FOX: Well, Jane, thanks for having me. It was sheer magic. It was such a beautiful moment. You know, these kind of thing don&amp;rsquo;t happen very often. I wish that I can say that they did. But to see animals that have been in cages their entire lives, large, endangered, land mammals, take to grass is a spectacular thing to see.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;VELEZ-MITCHELL: Now, while in the circus, two of the rescued lions had their fang cut out so the trainers could handle them. Another had her claws ripped out one by one without any anesthesia. You know it&amp;rsquo;s time for this kind of institutionalized animal torture to stop.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Check this out.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(BEGIN VIDEO CLIP)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;PHILLIPS: There&amp;rsquo;s a welfare problem at the moment, but that&amp;rsquo;s in the circuses. If we shut them we can give these animals a great life. So the world is watching.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(END VIDEO CLIP)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;VELEZ-MITCHELL: Jorja, what do people need to know about the scores of animals who are still suffering in the captivity of zoos and circuses around the world?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;FOX: Well, I think there&amp;rsquo;s several thing that people should know. Number one, most of these animals are on the endangered species list or on the vulnerable list. We have so few resources left on this planet. And I really think it&amp;rsquo;s our responsibility to care for the one that we have.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The unfortunate truth about zoos and circuses is that they&amp;rsquo;re cruel, they&amp;rsquo;re arcane, they are not suitable places for animals, especially large wild animals. I think we&amp;rsquo;ve evolved beyond them. I think there&amp;rsquo;s a lot of people out there who realize in the same way that we&amp;rsquo;ve evolved beyond asbestos and lead paint that we&amp;rsquo;re now at a place in our evolution where we can say, you know what, this is not a compassionate thing, this is not a smart thing. It&amp;rsquo;s a waste of resources and it&amp;rsquo;s a waste of these animals&amp;rsquo; lives.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;VELEZ-MITCHELL: Now, when you saw the animals go from their cages and actually step on grass for the very first time, what do you think they were thinking? What kind of a transformation did they experience?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;FOX: Well, these are animals that really had spent most of their lives in small pens on the back of a truck. Even though they were exhausted &amp;#8212; it was a 14-hour journey &amp;#8212; they weren&amp;rsquo;t fed during the journey. They did have access to water.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When they finally reached the sanctuary in a very rural, remote area in California, they leapt. They leapt like you would see small puppies leaping outside in the park somewhere.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;VELEZ-MITCHELL: I am so happy and thank you so much. And the animals thank you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yey, Jorja Fox of CSI. And we love these lions. If you love them &amp;#8212; hey, don&amp;rsquo;t go to the circus.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Kevin and Bean Show</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2009/the-kevin-and-bean-show/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2009/the-kevin-and-bean-show/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Host:&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;hellip; It&amp;rsquo;s 9:15.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Host:&lt;/strong&gt; And what a treat for us. &lt;em&gt;CSI&lt;/em&gt; returns tonight at 9 on CBS. Ladies and gentlemen, Jorja Fox right now on the Kevin and Bean show.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; Aw, thank you!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Host:&lt;/strong&gt; More importantly, Sara Sidle returns tonight. That&amp;rsquo;s what I care about.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Host 2:&lt;/strong&gt; Yes! Yes yes yes.!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; Thank you so much!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Host:&lt;/strong&gt; What your character has been put through in the course of this series, Jorja-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; My goodness gracious! Right?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Host:&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;ndash; is been ridiculous!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; Yeah, I would have to agree. But happily so. It&amp;rsquo;s been so much fun to do all that stuff.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Host:&lt;/strong&gt; Great stuff to play, I&amp;rsquo;m sure.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; There was one episode alone where I felt like the writers were trying to kill me. Just about every way that you could try to kill somebody on this show.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Host:&lt;/strong&gt; They crushed you with a car, I remember that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; Yeah! There was under the car, there was getting thrown out of the car, there was a fistfight, there was walking through the desert. You know, pretty much, yeah! The whole episode.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Host:&lt;/strong&gt; And then they sent you off to Costa Rica. And now you&amp;rsquo;re back.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; Yeah, that&amp;rsquo;s where we&amp;rsquo;ve last seen Sara. That was a big moment, cause there Billy and I were, under the sort of like, the Costa Rican canopy, and it was-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Host:&lt;/strong&gt; By Billy you mean William Petersen?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; William Petersen, of course, yes. He plays Grissom.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Host 2:&lt;/strong&gt; I&amp;rsquo;m gonna start calling him Billy! I like that!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; Only it may be a little overly familiar! But I thought &amp;ldquo;Well, this might be it!&amp;rdquo; You know, &amp;ldquo;This might be the end of Sara&amp;rsquo;s chapter, it might be the last time I&amp;rsquo;m here.&amp;rdquo; So I was very surprised to get a call this summer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Host:&lt;/strong&gt; And that time, you came back cause Warrick got shot. Right? That was the circumstance?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; Yeah, well that was, you know, that&amp;rsquo;s still something that&amp;rsquo;s sort of a touchy subject. I wish that Warrick was alive out there, somewhere. But. Warrick was murdered, before the last scene where Billy goes to Costa Rica. So the last time we see &amp;ndash;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Host 2:&lt;/strong&gt; Oh! that&amp;rsquo;s right that&amp;rsquo;s right!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;ndash; William Petersen and Sara Sidle, is in a Costa Rican rainforest.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Host 2:&lt;/strong&gt; My timeline was off.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Host:&lt;/strong&gt; Well, you know, Jorja, time travel is very big on TV these days. Isn&amp;rsquo;t it possible that you guys could go back to just before he was shot and stop it? Save him? Put him back on the show?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; I- You know, I&amp;rsquo;ve been pitching a prequel for years! It gets harder and harder. We&amp;rsquo;re starting our tenth season, so to try and do a prequel means people have to de-age us by a decade. And that&amp;rsquo;s pretty challenging at this point.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Host 2:&lt;/strong&gt; Piece of cake! Piece of cake.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; Maybe the animated prequel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Host 2:&lt;/strong&gt; Exactly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Host:&lt;/strong&gt; Before we get caught up and talk about what happens tonight, and the return of season 10, thereâs no way anyone, in the beginning, thought that &lt;em&gt;CSI&lt;/em&gt; would turn into one of the biggest hits in the history of television. When you guys started, I mean, this was something new on network television. Your show came out, doing stuff different. But nobody expected the juggernaut that it became, right?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; I thought a show about death, on a Friday night, was gonna be a gigantic clunker. Really, terrible, horrible, clunker. But the story was so intriguing to me, I sort of fell under a trance from the moment I read the script. I was like &amp;ldquo;Alright, well I have to do this!&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Host 2:&lt;/strong&gt; I think, people take it for granted now, but at the time we had never seen anything like it before on television.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; Thank you. Well, there was Quincy! That goes back a ways&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Host 2:&lt;/strong&gt; [&lt;em&gt;Laughs&lt;/em&gt;] This is far stretch from Quincy. Forensics have come a long way since Quincy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; [&lt;em&gt;Laughs&lt;/em&gt;] Yes. And they&amp;rsquo;re still coming a long way which, I think, is an advantage that we have. New technology is coming out every month, and we can use it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Host:&lt;/strong&gt; I remember in the early episodes, where they would follow the path of a bullet into the body, and show you all the damage it does. And your head would explode! You&amp;rsquo;d never seen anything like it, even in a movie, let alone on television! And then, you thought initially, week to week, solving cases, we&amp;rsquo;ve seen this done on tons of procedural cop shows, and that kind of stuff.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; Yeah, it&amp;rsquo;s one of the standard. The old standards.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Host:&lt;/strong&gt; But the character development in &lt;em&gt;CSI&lt;/em&gt; is what I feel really set it apart. How we got so attached to your characters and followed them through all these different permutations over the years.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; Like an old suit, from the 70s, slowly but surely-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Host:&lt;/strong&gt; But you find twenty bucks pockets! Now you must have, in the course of research or just interaction with experts that come by to advice on the show, you must have dealt with a lot of real life C.S.I. people over the years. Who are the people that go into this field, that love this kind of work? What drives them?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; It&amp;rsquo;s a very diverse group. I think that there&amp;rsquo;s a couple things they have to have. They have to have almost like an OCD type of focus, and a patience and a persistence. And I think they&amp;rsquo;ve got to be very, very, committed to crime fighting. And we still, every day, we have a tech advisor on our set, every day, still trying to help us look as realistic as possible. There&amp;rsquo;s real crime scene investigators in the writers room almost every day. We have personal relationships with a lot of those guys, both from &amp;ndash; The cool thing about our show because we shoot in LA but we take place in Vegas is that we can &amp;ndash; if it&amp;rsquo;s real in either one of those cities, we can put it on air. So we have people from both cities giving us stories and advice.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Host:&lt;/strong&gt; Oh I see! Are there are lot of women that go into the field? And are there &lt;em&gt;more&lt;/em&gt; women going into the field now because of you? And because of Catherine&amp;rsquo;s character?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; Well that&amp;rsquo;s very kind of you. They tell us that that&amp;rsquo;s true. That yes, there are a lot of women going into the field. One of our first advisors, Liz Devine, was in Los Angeles, a very early sort of woman in the field, and she was blonde and well endowed in all the right places. Sort of faced that textbook stuff you hear about when women enter fields that they&amp;rsquo;re not traditionally in. More and more so, I think women, if I&amp;rsquo;m going to get stereotypical, I think women are really, really geared towards the field because of that patience and that persistence.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Host:&lt;/strong&gt; But they&amp;rsquo;re not really smart enough though, right?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; They&amp;rsquo;re very good at detail oriented work, where you&amp;rsquo;re on hour eleven and you&amp;rsquo;re still holding your focus.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Host:&lt;/strong&gt; Really it&amp;rsquo;s just puzzle solving more than anything else.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; Yeah, great big puzzle.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Host:&lt;/strong&gt; Let me ask you one more question before the break. Jorja Fox is here and will tell you all about the premiere of season ten of &lt;em&gt;CSI&lt;/em&gt;. But here&amp;rsquo;s the question I have to ask, is it true that because of the success of &lt;em&gt;CSI&lt;/em&gt;, it is harder now to impress a jury? Or harder to &amp;ndash; in many cases a jury will think that they real life is like the television show, and it makes it harder for prosecutors sometimes, when they don&amp;rsquo;t have the slam dunk, scientific evidence that you often come up with on your show. Have you heard that?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; What we hear, actually, is the opposite. We hear it&amp;rsquo;s a lot harder for cops. For instance, I get my car broken into, and a police officer arrives, and I want the crime solved in, like, 48-hours, and I want him to pull out his DNA kit, fingerprinting and stuff. I think, originally, in courtrooms, it made it a little easier, because these guys were pitching this kind of science, for a while, but juries weren&amp;rsquo;t quite grasping it. Now they have a really good understanding of what all of it means.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Host:&lt;/strong&gt; Ballistics, GSR, latent GSR! GSR all over his hands!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Host:&lt;/strong&gt; Laypeople &amp;ndash; We amateurs know so much more about police work and science of the C.S.I. than we ever would have thought possible, because you found a way to make it entertaining.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; Thank you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Host:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;CSI&lt;/em&gt; returns tonight at 9. A quick break! More with Jorja Fox, if she doesn&amp;rsquo;t give us all the Swine Flu, when we return, right after this on the Kevin and Bean Show!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Host:&lt;/strong&gt; Jorja Fox is in our studio. The return of &lt;em&gt;CSI&lt;/em&gt;, season 10, tonight at 9 on CBS. Now because you&amp;rsquo;re the big dog on the television schedule, every year the other networks try to figure out &amp;ldquo;How are we going to take &lt;em&gt;CSI&lt;/em&gt; down.&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;What are we going to do this year to take &lt;em&gt;CSI&lt;/em&gt; down?&amp;rdquo; You have been up against every show in the history of television.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; True! Yeah, and we&amp;rsquo;re up against a pretty good one right now, who&amp;rsquo;s name I can&amp;rsquo;t mention on the air. But you guys have been promoting it several times this morning.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lisa (co-host):&lt;/strong&gt; Oops!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Host:&lt;/strong&gt; We&amp;rsquo;re not responsible for commercials.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; Yeah, little medical drama.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Host:&lt;/strong&gt; Don&amp;rsquo;t hold it against us! &amp;ndash; OH! That one! Oh that show SUCKS! It&amp;rsquo;s all &lt;em&gt;CSI&lt;/em&gt;! It&amp;rsquo;s way &lt;em&gt;CSI&lt;/em&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; Aww! Thank you!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Host:&lt;/strong&gt; You&amp;rsquo;re either gay or Lisa if you&amp;rsquo;re gonna watch that show.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lisa:&lt;/strong&gt; It&amp;rsquo;s just a chick show, yeah.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Host:&lt;/strong&gt; So Sara returns tonight. Do we find out the state of her relationship with Grissom, while they&amp;rsquo;ve been away? Do we look into that at all this evening?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; In about 12 short hours, in Los Angeles, you will. I think you&amp;rsquo;ll get at least a sort of an establishing amount of information that I was very pleased with.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Host:&lt;/strong&gt; We&amp;rsquo;ve all been curious what&amp;rsquo;s been going on after that kiss in Costa Rica.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; I think we were in Costa Rica for a nice long time. That&amp;rsquo;s all I can say at the moment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lisa:&lt;/strong&gt; Got a lot accomplished, did you?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Host:&lt;/strong&gt; How used to seeing Sara can we get, as fans of the show? You gonna be around for a while, or is this another hit and run? You gonna tease us and run off again? Another foreign country you gonna run off to?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; I know, right? I keep having these really big, dramatic, goodbyes, and then &amp;ndash; It&amp;rsquo;s like &amp;ldquo;Oh, gosh! It&amp;rsquo;s her again!&amp;rdquo; I think you can&amp;rsquo;t pull that off that much before &amp;ndash; I mean people are already rolling their eyes at me. They&amp;rsquo;ve done that for years. That will continue, I think, if I keep saying &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m back! Goodbye!&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;Hey, I&amp;rsquo;m back! Goodbye!&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Host:&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;ldquo;But this time I mean it!&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;ldquo;Send me flowers!&amp;rdquo; No, I&amp;rsquo;m visiting, and I&amp;rsquo;m thrilled to do so. As I said, I wasn&amp;rsquo;t expecting it at all, especially after the Costa Rican episode. SO we&amp;rsquo;ll see! We&amp;rsquo;re taking it one day at a time. It&amp;rsquo;s so much fun, it&amp;rsquo;s like going home in some respects. In some respects it&amp;rsquo;s like having a brand new job and being somewhere for the first time. I have so much love and devotion in my heart for everybody there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Host:&lt;/strong&gt; How&amp;rsquo;s Laurence Flishburn- Fishburne to work with.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; Laurence Flishburn?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&lt;em&gt;Everyone laughs&lt;/em&gt;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Host:&lt;/strong&gt; Laurence Flishburn.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; Notable actor?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Host:&lt;/strong&gt; Yeah. I&amp;rsquo;ve started drinking already. Laurence Fishburne, one of my favorite actors, and he&amp;rsquo;s so good on the show.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; He is! He&amp;rsquo;s spectacular.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Host:&lt;/strong&gt; How exciting is it to work with that stature when you come back to a project like &lt;em&gt;CSI&lt;/em&gt;?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; Very humbly. You know, Liev Schrieber guest stared a couple seasons ago too, and he and Fishburne would be two of my all time favorite actors. It&amp;rsquo;s just kind of weird that all of the sudden they&amp;rsquo;re sort of like at your house. You know? Like they knock on the door and you&amp;rsquo;re like &amp;lsquo;Hey, come on in! Would you like a cup of coffee?&amp;rsquo; or something. He&amp;rsquo;s amazing. He&amp;rsquo;s as kind and benevolent and generous and sweet and funny as you could ever imagine that he might be.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Host:&lt;/strong&gt; There&amp;rsquo;s where you&amp;rsquo;ve got smart guys and gals running the show. Because when you lose your star, when you lose Mr. Grissom&amp;rsquo;s character, when you lose that you need a guy with &amp;ndash; not only a great actor, but with gravitas. Who can come in and pick up the slack. And he has that. He&amp;rsquo;s one of those guys, you can&amp;rsquo;t take your eyes off the screen.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; Mesmerizing. And he&amp;rsquo;s sicker than I am and he&amp;rsquo;s in New York doing the press, so you&amp;rsquo;ve gotta give him credit for that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Host:&lt;/strong&gt; He&amp;rsquo;s spreading the virus on that coast.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; We all have the &lt;em&gt;CSI&lt;/em&gt; bug, it&amp;rsquo;s very contagious.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Host:&lt;/strong&gt; What did you do, when you left the show, about the show? Did you continue to watch it as a fan, or did you not want to see your boyfriend move on with another woman?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; Yeah! That was scary! And that happened a little bit. Sort of. They left that very ambiguous, thank God. I watched for a while and then I realized, &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m on sabbatical. I&amp;rsquo;m taking a year off.&amp;rdquo; And then I kind of turned off my TV. So for the most part there was very little that I watched, including &lt;em&gt;CSI&lt;/em&gt;, in that year. I did a bunch of traveling.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Host:&lt;/strong&gt; Wow! That&amp;rsquo;s a surprise.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; I thought, if I&amp;rsquo;m really gonna take a year off, as long as my heads in the game, if I&amp;rsquo;m watching TV every night. But, when they called this summer, I had them TIVO&amp;rsquo;d, most of them, and I did sit down at watch a lot of them. I still have a couple left to watch. I&amp;rsquo;ve worked my way up to the season finale of last year, it&amp;rsquo;s the one episode I haven&amp;rsquo;t see yet. Which is weird, because we&amp;rsquo;re premiering tonight, so I&amp;rsquo;ve probably have to go home and watch it today! I have to watch it this afternoon! And I thought last season was amazing, I thought they did a really great job. It&amp;rsquo;s really difficult to lose three characters in the space of a year or so. The writers are brilliant. I thought they handled very well, and I thought that &amp;ndash; there hasn&amp;rsquo;t been a ton of subtext on &lt;em&gt;CSI&lt;/em&gt; the last year. Everybody&amp;rsquo;s been grieving the loss of old people, and also hopeful of new folks coming in. I think that played on screen a lot.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Host:&lt;/strong&gt; And plus, you just want to see McDreamy happy. Right?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lisa:&lt;/strong&gt; Not the same show.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; I&amp;rsquo;m sorry, who are you? What radio show is this? Where am I?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lisa:&lt;/strong&gt; Big boy!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Host:&lt;/strong&gt; Here&amp;rsquo;s a tweet question for you, Jorja. Eric wants to know if it&amp;rsquo;s sometimes hard to act with all the special effects that they use on the show?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; Eric. To be honest with you, I rarely see the special effects. We&amp;rsquo;re generally in a stage, we&amp;rsquo;re in a room. We see more &amp;ndash; we see the stunts and the car wrecks and things like that. But a lot of the &lt;em&gt;CSI&lt;/em&gt; stuff that they do comes in post-production, which is one of the reasons I actually really watch the show! Because so much of it happens in post. The music gets laid in post. We&amp;rsquo;re really proud of our music, we&amp;rsquo;ve had a lot of really amazing bands come through. And I like to watch everybody else&amp;rsquo;s work and see what they did.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Host:&lt;/strong&gt; Tonight at nine on CBS. For folks who are gonna try &lt;em&gt;CSI&lt;/em&gt; for the first time, or haven&amp;rsquo;t been paying as close attention as they should, what is the 30-second setup that you give people that are prepared to sit down and watch &lt;em&gt;CSI&lt;/em&gt;?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; Uh &amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Host:&lt;/strong&gt; Ten years of work!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Host:&lt;/strong&gt; That&amp;rsquo;s not saying recap every plot point!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; I gotta pitch it? I can say this. When I read the script this summer, I think, whenever you&amp;rsquo;ve been on as long as we have &amp;ndash; and we&amp;rsquo;re ooooolllld now, I feel like we&amp;rsquo;ve got canes and walkers and all kinds of stuff &amp;hellip; Geritol. I read the script, I was excited I was coming back, and I was like, &amp;ldquo;You know, this show&amp;rsquo;s probably peaked. I&amp;rsquo;m sure it&amp;rsquo;s gonna be a great script.&amp;rdquo; I thought it&amp;rsquo;s probably &amp;hellip; The best is in the past. And when I read the first page of the first scene, I was strapped into a seatbelt and I thought to myself &amp;ldquo;Game. On.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Host:&lt;/strong&gt; Wow! That sounds great.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lisa:&lt;/strong&gt; I&amp;rsquo;m excited!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Host:&lt;/strong&gt; And I hope that Sara and Catherine will finally act on their long standing attraction to one another.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; That&amp;rsquo;s been coming up a lot, actually!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Host:&lt;/strong&gt; I think it&amp;rsquo;s about time for that wrinkle to be &amp;hellip; on &lt;em&gt;CSI&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; Someone should get something on &lt;em&gt;CSI&lt;/em&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Host:&lt;/strong&gt; Exactly!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Host:&lt;/strong&gt; Well, sweeps have got to be right around the corner. Let&amp;rsquo;s not be crazy here.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Host:&lt;/strong&gt; Well, Jorja, so nice to finally meet you. We&amp;rsquo;ll happily take the Swine Flu from you-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; Oh, great!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Host:&lt;/strong&gt; -just because you happen to be here today.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; Thank you so much for having me, I&amp;rsquo;m a huge fan. You guys have been so nice to me for such a long time, and it&amp;rsquo;s really an honor to be here.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Host:&lt;/strong&gt; Thank you, Jorja. &lt;em&gt;CSI&lt;/em&gt; tonight at 9 on CBS!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Today Show</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2009/the-today-show/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2009/the-today-show/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; It was breathtaking, it was magic. There was so much going on on &amp;ldquo;ER&amp;rdquo; that I certainly had never seen on television before. I don&amp;rsquo;t think you&amp;rsquo;ve seen a lot of it in feature films. The use of steady-cams &amp;hellip; you could do almost an entire act of the show in one sweeping, sort of solid, motion. It was a dance.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Access Hollywood</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2008/access-hollywood/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2008/access-hollywood/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Interviewer:&lt;/strong&gt; What are some tips you have to going green?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; Going green? Oh, wow, I love it. Well, you know, start with the simple stuff. There&amp;rsquo;s some very simple things you can do. Recycling, obviously, I think we&amp;rsquo;re all doing that in California. I&amp;rsquo;m amazed. I go visit some of my family members across the country, and they don&amp;rsquo;t have recycling centers yet. And most of them are doing it themselves anyway. I am a big believer in reusing, you know what I mean. Everything down to like shopping for clothes and stuff, everything you want is probably already out there already anyway. Go to a secondhand store or a thrift shop, and rather than buy something new, buy something that&amp;rsquo;s already still cool.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ian Harvie Show</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2008/ian-harvie-show/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jan 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2008/ian-harvie-show/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; Ten and a half years of deaths -&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ian Harvie:&lt;/strong&gt; Yes&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; - violence -&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ian Harvie:&lt;/strong&gt; What is it with you -&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; I just had it of dead bodies -&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ian Harvie:&lt;/strong&gt; Yeah, seriously!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; I mean I&amp;rsquo;ve just had it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ian Harvie:&lt;/strong&gt; Seriously, what is it with you and these roles, like these really hard, like, and the dialog is like really hard too! And like &amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; Yeah!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ian Harvie:&lt;/strong&gt; And like &amp;ldquo;ER&amp;rdquo; and like, seriously, like, all these-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;laughing&lt;/em&gt; It was the dialog! It was so hard! I couldn&amp;rsquo;t do it anymore.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ian Harvie:&lt;/strong&gt; No, I know, I-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; No, I&amp;rsquo;ve been very lucky. I&amp;rsquo;ve gotten to play some very, very smart women. Which is a stretch for me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ian Harvie:&lt;/strong&gt; Which is fantastic.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; And, yeah, and I mean - Sara Sidle studied nuclear physics and fusion at Harvard and Berkley. And that was really excited, I was really proud of that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ian Harvie:&lt;/strong&gt; I was really intimidated having you on the show because of all that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; Really? It&amp;rsquo;s not me, though!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ian Harvie:&lt;/strong&gt; Do you remember any of your lines from that? Cause it&amp;rsquo;s always really hot. The stuff that you say is totally-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;Embarrassed&lt;/em&gt; Thanks, aw, thank you. Phenoethylene terephtalete.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ian Harvie:&lt;/strong&gt; Yeah, what the hell is that?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;laughing&lt;/em&gt; Yeah.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ian Harvie:&lt;/strong&gt; I&amp;rsquo;m going to make myself wait till later -&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; Mass Spectrometer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ian Harvie:&lt;/strong&gt; - wait till later, yeah.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;laughing&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ian Harvie:&lt;/strong&gt; Do you have any idea what that means?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; Phenoethylene terephtalete? Not anymore. No. That&amp;rsquo;s the problem. Like the short term memory. You learn it for the day and then you have no idea what you said the day before.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ian Harvie:&lt;/strong&gt; Do they tell you what it is you&amp;rsquo;re saying, or&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; At the time, yes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ian Harvie:&lt;/strong&gt; So &amp;ldquo;This is what it means.&amp;rsquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; Yeah, and that one was so hard I had to practice it for about four days. Cause you want it to, try and sort of roll off the tongue, so I&amp;rsquo;ll never forget the word, and I have &amp;ldquo;no&amp;rdquo; idea what it means.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ian Harvie:&lt;/strong&gt; Okay. What was the storyline? Why did you leave? You were IL, you were in love with somebody, or you-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; I did. I had a smokin&amp;rsquo; hot boyfriend on the show, and we got engaged. And then I dumped him, I gave him a Dear John letter and I just took off in the middle of the night. And essentially, for the character, it was she had this stressful experience, the serial killer took her out to the desert and almost killed her and &amp;hellip; She&amp;rsquo;d had it, really, with the death.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ian Harvie:&lt;/strong&gt; Does that stuff ever feel real to you?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; Well, it&amp;rsquo;s, you know, we try to make it as fun as we can. The unfortunate thing is that many of our stories are based on real &amp;hellip; stories. So, when you get the script and it&amp;rsquo;s somebody&amp;rsquo;s life, yeah, I think it affects you a little more. You know it&amp;rsquo;s make believe that you&amp;rsquo;re shooting it, but it really happened to someone.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ian Harvie:&lt;/strong&gt; But - And you were on &amp;ldquo;ER&amp;rdquo; and it&amp;rsquo;s the same kind of lingo. As far as-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; Depressing. Totally depressing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ian Harvie:&lt;/strong&gt; Yeah.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;laughing&lt;/em&gt; At least sometimes they lived! Every once in a while on &amp;ldquo;ER&amp;rdquo; you&amp;rsquo;d cure them. Which is good for them. But it was really high stakes, high stress.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ian Harvie:&lt;/strong&gt; I can&amp;rsquo;t remember how long you were on that for.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; Three years. Yeah, I had a little run and then it was &amp;ldquo;West Wing&amp;rdquo; in there, and then &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; for the last seven and a half years.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ian Harvie:&lt;/strong&gt; That&amp;rsquo;s right, &amp;ldquo;West Wing&amp;rdquo;. Another easy one, another easy show.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; Yeah. Another violent. &lt;em&gt;laughing&lt;/em&gt; My role anyway. The show wasn&amp;rsquo;t violent, my role was. I was a part of this plot, this racist plot to assassinate the president. And so my role was really violent. &lt;em&gt;laughing&lt;/em&gt; My part of the show.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ian Harvie:&lt;/strong&gt; So, and &amp;ldquo;Memento&amp;rdquo;, you were in &amp;ldquo;Memento&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; Violent, pretty gross.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ian Harvie:&lt;/strong&gt; Yeah.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; Pretty gross shit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ian Harvie:&lt;/strong&gt; Who&amp;rsquo;s your fucking agent!? I mean, it&amp;rsquo;s like &amp;ldquo;I think this would be really good for you.&amp;rsquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;laughing&lt;/em&gt; Yeah. Well it&amp;rsquo;s been amazing. I feel so blessed. I think I&amp;rsquo;m one of the luckiest people in the world, really. And it&amp;rsquo;s not that I&amp;rsquo;ll never do violent stuff again, I&amp;rsquo;m sure I will. Violence is great drama. Just for a minute, I just kind of needed to get off. You know? Just take a little break.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ian Harvie:&lt;/strong&gt; Right. Now-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; I&amp;rsquo;m taking sailing lessons.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ian Harvie:&lt;/strong&gt; Are you really?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; Yeah, I&amp;rsquo;m learning how to play the drums. Finally.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ian Harvie:&lt;/strong&gt; Awesome!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; Years later. That whole rumor that I play drums is not true.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ian Harvie:&lt;/strong&gt; The rumor that you play guitar is true, though.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; That one is true. Yeah, badly. &lt;em&gt;laughing&lt;/em&gt; Yeah, a couple people [in the audience] have seen me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ian Harvie:&lt;/strong&gt; Why do you say badly?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; Bad guitar? I just really, I never really, I don&amp;rsquo;t really have any musical talent. I&amp;rsquo;m persistent and &lt;em&gt;laughing&lt;/em&gt; I practice a lot, but I have no ear. At all.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ian Harvie:&lt;/strong&gt; Where are you playing the drums? Where can we see you rock it out?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; Nowhere yet, thank god.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ian Harvie:&lt;/strong&gt; Any bands? Any garage bands?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; No. I&amp;rsquo;m just taking classes. So right now it&amp;rsquo;s percussion classes. I bring my African drum and we go and we kind of do stuff. And then, hopefully, that class is about eight weeks, and then I&amp;rsquo;ll move to the kit class. Hopefully.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ian Harvie:&lt;/strong&gt; The what- Oh the kit!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; The drum kit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ian Harvie:&lt;/strong&gt; The kit. That&amp;rsquo;s what it is, right.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; Kind of musician talk.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ian Harvie:&lt;/strong&gt; The lingo. &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m gonna move to the drum kit.&amp;rdquo; Yeah, that&amp;rsquo;s awesome.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; Wish me luck!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ian Harvie:&lt;/strong&gt; What was it - you said? Sailing! Where at? Where are you sailing at?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; There&amp;rsquo;s sailing classes you can take down at Marina Del Rey.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ian Harvie:&lt;/strong&gt; Are they teaching you in like those little Sunfish boats? With the one little sail and the scoop out -&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; Yeah and you have to wear those plastic floatie things. On your arms. It&amp;rsquo;s in the bathtub, actually, at the YWCA.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ian Harvie:&lt;/strong&gt; What are those things called? Wings. They&amp;rsquo;re called wings. No, seriously, are they in that kind of little boat, or-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; It&amp;rsquo;s a decent sized boat, you know what I mean. Like they&amp;rsquo;ll take - I don&amp;rsquo;t know how many people they have - the class. Our class has like 12 people in it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ian Harvie:&lt;/strong&gt; Okay, so you&amp;rsquo;re all on the boat.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; Yeah, most of the time. I mean there&amp;rsquo;s parts there where you have to learn - you learn the lingo. You know and like nautical. Words like that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ian Harvie:&lt;/strong&gt; Right. Tacking. Tack. Tacking. Which means fucking duck. It means f-ing duck. That&amp;rsquo;s really all you need to know on that one, right?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;laughter&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#8212;-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; I was born in New York City and then they moved to Florida. My mom had the dream, she wanted to live in the small beach town. She had that dream her whole life. And three years after I was born, they made it happen. So they moved down -&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ian Harvie:&lt;/strong&gt; Oh cool.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; Yeah. They moved down there. And I moved back when I was 16.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ian Harvie:&lt;/strong&gt; You when to high school there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; I finished high school in New York.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ian Harvie:&lt;/strong&gt; Yeah.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; I actually did finish.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ian Harvie:&lt;/strong&gt; What was your first acting &amp;#8212; You did finish?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; It was a close one.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ian Harvie:&lt;/strong&gt; You did?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; Yeah. I have even a real diploma. It&amp;rsquo;s not even a GED. I almost had a GED and then I-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ian Harvie:&lt;/strong&gt; And you didn&amp;rsquo;t get it off the Internet cause they didn&amp;rsquo;t have the Internet back then.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; Yeah, no. Nothing. There was nothing, no gadgets at all.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ian Harvie:&lt;/strong&gt; The interwebs. What was your first acting thing? What is high school or something after?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; High school was first. Actually, I wanted to be an actor since I was very little, and my mom found &amp;ldquo;one&amp;rdquo; acting class, you know, in like an hour of where we grew up. I was five years old, and I was really excited. And the deal with the acting class is that in order to take it, you also have to take the modeling classes. And I didn&amp;rsquo;t really - I wasn&amp;rsquo;t really interested in modeling at all, but I really wanted to act. So I took the classes for a while, and, um, I got a job. The first job I got, we were going to do a play at the mall, &amp;ldquo;Chicken Little.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ian Harvie:&lt;/strong&gt; Uh huh.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; In Florida. And I practiced really hard and I got the role of the Rooster.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ian Harvie:&lt;/strong&gt; Oh, awesome.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; And, uh, &lt;em&gt;laughing&lt;/em&gt; I was awesome until I did my first thing as the Rooster, and everybody laughed really, really, really, really, really hard.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ian Harvie:&lt;/strong&gt; Do you remember the line? Do you remember any lines?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; It was like a &lt;em&gt;crows like a rooster&lt;/em&gt;. Something like that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Audience cracks up &amp;hellip; Ian cracks up .. Jorja cracks up&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; And I quit! I was so mortified, really. Everyone was laughing at me. &lt;em&gt;looks at the audience, mock accusing them of the same.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ian Harvie:&lt;/strong&gt; That&amp;rsquo;s awful.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; I didn&amp;rsquo;t act again until high school. There was finally a drama department in high school. And oddly enough, I moved to new York for my modeling career. But it was only because that was my ticket out of Florida. Like that was the way I could go to New York. So once again I had to model to try to be an actor.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ian Harvie:&lt;/strong&gt; Did you do some of that?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; A little bit. Yeah. It was great, actually, at that age. Cause you know, 17, 18. I got to travel a lot, I lived in Europe. I was a &amp;ldquo;terrible&amp;rdquo; model. I mean, I never really enjoyed it, I wasn&amp;rsquo;t good at it. But I made some money, and I was able to take acting classes for a couple years.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ian Harvie:&lt;/strong&gt; And do what you wanted.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; Drink cappuccino.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ian Harvie:&lt;/strong&gt; Yeah. Be very romantic.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; We were all 19. Yeah, smoking, the cappuccino, talking about Mamet and stuff. It was really cool.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ian Harvie:&lt;/strong&gt; Where were you?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; Uh, mostly Italy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ian Harvie:&lt;/strong&gt; Cool.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; Brooding, it was a brooding time of my life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ian Harvie:&lt;/strong&gt; What are your -&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; Not much has changed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ian Harvie:&lt;/strong&gt; You had your journal open.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; Oh yeah. I still have my journal. I&amp;rsquo;ve got it with me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ian Harvie:&lt;/strong&gt; What&amp;rsquo;s your passion right now? What do you-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; You know what I &lt;strong&gt;fuckin&lt;/strong&gt; really hate?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ian Harvie:&lt;/strong&gt; What? Bring it, sister! Wha&amp;rsquo;d&amp;rsquo;ya got?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; I fuckin&amp;rsquo; hate the people in the &amp;ldquo;left&amp;rdquo; lane of the freeway so fucking much that won&amp;rsquo;t move over! Like when you&amp;rsquo;re trying to pass them. I really think there should be a law and people should get tickets for that shit. It&amp;rsquo;s just - It&amp;rsquo;s rude, it&amp;rsquo;s selfish. I mean- okay, maybe you mean something a little different.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ian Harvie:&lt;/strong&gt; No, no that was perfect. Are you thinking about a 501&amp;copy;(3)? Sort of a non-profit route?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; Yeah, you know I would love to - yeah for that? Yeah. I&amp;rsquo;m accepting donations!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ian Harvie:&lt;/strong&gt; Now, actually, are you a vegetarian?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; I am a vegetarian.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ian Harvie:&lt;/strong&gt; You are?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; Yeah. The environment&amp;rsquo;s a really big-big thing for me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ian Harvie:&lt;/strong&gt; So, if you were going to, like, swing me over the fence to be a vegetarian, what would you tell me? Like what - three things -&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; I, uh, try not to proselytize.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ian Harvie:&lt;/strong&gt; Okay.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; But&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ian Harvie:&lt;/strong&gt; Like three things that I would need to know.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; Okay. Well, cows &amp;hellip; produce more methane from farting than any substance on the planet. So a big part of global warming is actually cows in fields &amp;ndash; it&amp;rsquo;s true! &amp;ndash; sending up a lot of really noxious fumes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ian Harvie:&lt;/strong&gt; And because of our demand for meat.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; Yeah, they&amp;rsquo;re everywhere. And it&amp;rsquo;s also a huge reason for deforestation and a big reason for - you know like the spinach thing last year. Where a lot of people ate organic spinach and they got really sick, was because cow was getting into crops. You know that stuff goes down rivers and streams and it pollutes waterways. I&amp;rsquo;ve always been kinda of like &amp;#8212; we all do what we can do.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ian Harvie:&lt;/strong&gt; I think one of the things that&amp;rsquo;s hardest is the cooking part of it. Like I&amp;rsquo;m so ingrained: I have meat, I have starch. How do you change that thinking? It&amp;rsquo;s so hard.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; It&amp;rsquo;s not easy. I&amp;rsquo;m French-Irish and all we ate was meat and potatoes. So it&amp;rsquo;s really all we ate. When I became a vegetarian - I&amp;rsquo;ve been a vegetarian for like 20 years, and the first two years all I did was eat cheese and eggs cause I really didn&amp;rsquo;t know what else to eat. I was extremely confused. For like every meal.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ian Harvie:&lt;/strong&gt; So, like, eggs are cool with you?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; You know, I don&amp;rsquo;t eat that much, but I eat them. It&amp;rsquo;s a very personal choice. But, yeah, the cooking thing is hard. I think that in, like, LA or New York &amp;#8212; If I was in the Arctic Tundra and it was like me an a seal? And I was really hungry? Maybe, you know, I would make the choice to survive. But if I&amp;rsquo;m living in LA? I mean, there&amp;rsquo;s right next door there&amp;rsquo;s Damiano&amp;rsquo;s. You can get, like, a slice of soy cheese pizza with veggie &amp;ldquo;pepperoni&amp;rsquo;. It&amp;rsquo;s easy. It&amp;rsquo;s pretty easy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ian Harvie:&lt;/strong&gt; That&amp;rsquo;s good pizza over there. You have something going on that you&amp;rsquo;re -&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; I do.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ian Harvie:&lt;/strong&gt; That you&amp;rsquo;re excited about. Tell me about it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; I&amp;rsquo;m really excited about it. Kirsten Holly Smith, who&amp;rsquo;s a really old friend of mine, is here tonight and we&amp;rsquo;re doing a play. I&amp;rsquo;m producing, she is staring in it. Uh. A show about Dusty Springfield. It&amp;rsquo;s a music. &lt;em&gt;crowd cheers&lt;/em&gt; Yeah! And the story is way overdue to be told. She had an amazing, incredible life. Pretty much a 30 year career span, over in Europe and the United States. And we&amp;rsquo;re doing this show, it opens February 7th, in Los Angeles, at the Gay and Lesbian Center, the Tomlin and Wagner Theater. Kirsten&amp;rsquo;s myspace page or my website will have it posted in a week or two.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ian Harvie:&lt;/strong&gt; Your website is?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.jorjafox.org&#34;&gt;Jorjafox.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ian Harvie:&lt;/strong&gt; Okay, .org.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; Mmm hmm. And that&amp;rsquo;s filled with political ramblings of all kinds. It&amp;rsquo;s my myspace page.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ian Harvie:&lt;/strong&gt; And give us a couple sentences background about her life. About Dusty&amp;rsquo;s life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; Well, Dusty&amp;rsquo;s pretty &amp;ndash; She really came on the music scene in the early &amp;lsquo;60s. She was one of the very first women that produced her own music and her own sound. She was one of the very first performers to stand up against Apartheid. In honor of Martin Luther King Day, today, thank you very much for that. She was also one of the first artists to come out as bisexual and lesbian. Like way before David Bowie and all those guys. So she&amp;rsquo;s a very brave lady. She dealt with substance abuse and breast cancer. We&amp;rsquo;re going to tell some of that in the story, it&amp;rsquo;s almost &amp;ndash; it&amp;rsquo;s kind of too rich a life to tell it all in 90 minutes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ian Harvie:&lt;/strong&gt; Right.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; We&amp;rsquo;ll also perform, I think, 10? Dusty Springfield songs. Or 11. And the band&amp;rsquo;s amazing, the story&amp;rsquo;s amazing, Kirsten&amp;rsquo;s amazing. You&amp;rsquo;ll get to see her in a second.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ian Harvie:&lt;/strong&gt; Alright. Fantastic. There is one question that I&amp;rsquo;m sure is on everybody&amp;rsquo;s mind here. That everybody&amp;rsquo;s probably wanted to ask you, and I don&amp;rsquo;t know if anybody&amp;rsquo;s ever asked you this before.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; Really?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ian Harvie:&lt;/strong&gt; And I know it&amp;rsquo;s kinda one of those things that maybe, you know, that in this sort of atmosphere I could probably ask it, and it would be okay. I guess I just want to ask, what was it like to film that After School Special back in 93?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ian Harvie:&lt;/strong&gt; Was it 93? I&amp;rsquo;m sorry, what year was that?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; Gaaaaahd. You know- I can&amp;rsquo;t believe you asked me that. No comment. I don&amp;rsquo;t talk about that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ian Harvie:&lt;/strong&gt; Fair enough, fair enough.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; Cool. Alright, cool.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ian Harvie:&lt;/strong&gt; Fair enough. Jorja Fox, everybody! Thank you so much.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ET</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2007/et/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Oct 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2007/et/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Announcer:&lt;/strong&gt; And sad news for &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; fans as a star says goodbye.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; That&amp;rsquo;s the end of me for a while&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Announcer:&lt;/strong&gt; At the Frederick&amp;rsquo;s of Hollywood Fashion show last night Jorja Fox told &amp;ldquo;ET&amp;rdquo; the real reason she&amp;rsquo;s leaving CBS&amp;rsquo;s crime solving show&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; I just need to take a little break, and do some evaluating. Hopefully I will return.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Early Show</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2007/the-early-show-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 May 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2007/the-early-show-2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt;: I&amp;rsquo;m not a big fan of Sara being in, in peril. I think that when you play a character as long as I have, what, it&amp;rsquo;s going on 36 years? No, 7 years, you become very, very, very, very, very close to that character in ways that, uh, are difficult to describe. So intrinsically as an artist, y&amp;rsquo;know, my desire is to protect that character and keep that character safe. Why me? No, I don&amp;rsquo;t want to be the victim of this jerkoff, this, this terrible serial killer. And then the part of me that&amp;rsquo;s the actor was kinda thrilled that, um, I had something really meaty to do in the last episode of the season.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; Yeah, like I leave him alone for 5 minutes and he tells everybody that we&amp;rsquo;re having this fabulous little secret love affair. Assuming that, y&amp;rsquo;know, Sara makes it out okay, I mean, who knows what&amp;rsquo;s gonna happen&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Early Show</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2007/the-early-show/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 May 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2007/the-early-show/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Chen&amp;rsquo;s &amp;lsquo;CSI&amp;rsquo; Investigation&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Julie Chen gets an exclusive behind-the-scenes look at the hit crime drama &amp;ldquo;CSI.&amp;rdquo; She speaks with actors Marg Helgenberger, William Petersen, Paul Guilfoyle and Jorja Fox.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Julie Chen:&lt;/strong&gt; This season, CSI has given us everything from Grissom and Sara big romance to the so-called &amp;lsquo;Miniature killer&amp;rsquo; who left scale model miniature of crime scenes. Cast members told me those models were as fascinating for them as they were for viewers. [&amp;hellip;] This season we were also drawn in by the complicated secret romance between Grissom and Sara. Which gets more tangled in tonights episode. Actress Melinda Clark returns tonight as the mysterious Lady Heather. She flirts with danger, almost getting strangled to death playing out a Western town fantasy. She flirts with Grissom, too, as far back as their first meeting, six years ago. [&amp;hellip;] We got to see the jealous side of Sara.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;laughter&lt;/em&gt; Just for a second, though. Maybe one of my favorite scenes of the whole season is the scene that Marg and I have in the saloon.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>