<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Television on Fans of Le Fox Library</title>
    <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/tags/television/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Television on Fans of Le Fox Library</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 16 Aug 2009 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://jorjafox.net/library/tags/television/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Drop Dead Diva</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/actor/drop-dead-diva/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Aug 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/actor/drop-dead-diva/</guid>
      <description>The series revolves around vapid aspiring model, Deborah &amp;ldquo;Deb&amp;rdquo; Dobkins, who is killed in a car crash on the way to an audition for The Price Is Right. As her soul enters the gates of Heaven, she finds herself being judged by a gatekeeper named Fred. As a result of her shallowness, Fred declares her a &amp;ldquo;zero-zero,&amp;rdquo; since she has performed zero good deeds and zero bad deeds during her time on Earth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Early Show</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2005/the-early-show-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2005/the-early-show-2/</guid>
      <description>Julie Chen: After six seasons and a pair of spin-offs, &amp;ldquo;CSI:&amp;rdquo; remains a true original. It&amp;rsquo;s still a ratings powerhouse too with nearly 30 million viewers tuning in every week. I sat down with some of the show&amp;rsquo;s stars inside the CSI autopsy room to dissect the secret of their success.
[&amp;hellip;]
Julie Chen: &amp;ldquo;(voiceover)&amp;rdquo; In tonight&amp;rsquo;s episode, the sexual tension also continues between Sara and Grissom.
Julie Chen: In season six you still kinda have a crush on Grissom, right?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Early Show</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2005/the-early-show/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2005/the-early-show/</guid>
      <description>Julie Chen: If you can&amp;rsquo;t get enough of TV&amp;rsquo;s hottest drama, CSI:, then you&amp;rsquo;re in luck. Every Friday, we&amp;rsquo;re going to take you behind the scenes to show you how they make it happen. In last night&amp;rsquo;s episode, called &amp;ldquo;Secrets and Flies&amp;rdquo;, star Jorja Fox came face to face with an actor&amp;rsquo;s big challenge: working with a baby. Or did she?
Jorja Fox: The camera comes in, you find a woman who&amp;rsquo;s obviously deceased, you don&amp;rsquo;t know what&amp;rsquo;s happened, there&amp;rsquo;s a pool of blood, and the only other sound in the house is of a baby crying.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Land&#39;s Top Ten Sexiest Men</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2005/tv-land-s-top-ten-sexiest-men/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2005/tv-land-s-top-ten-sexiest-men/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;TV Land&amp;rsquo;s Top Ten&amp;rdquo; is a show about the top ten .
Jorja Fox was on the June 15, 2005 episode for &amp;lsquo;Sexiest Men&amp;rsquo;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My First Place: Celebrity Style</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2005/my-first-place-celebrity-style/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2005/my-first-place-celebrity-style/</guid>
      <description>HGTV, in a interesting move, released excerpts from it&amp;rsquo;s new show &amp;ldquo;&amp;lsquo;My First Place: Celebrity Style&amp;rdquo;&amp;rsquo; online.
Jorja Fox was filmed for an upcoming episode and her quote on the main page is as follows:
 I was a bad teenager. I had to get out of there. My family was very old-fashioned and I knew quite young that I needed to get my own place. I was 16. I moved in with my friends.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CSI: Crime Scene Investigation</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/actor/csi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/actor/csi/</guid>
      <description>Premise The show follows the cases of the Crime Scene Investigation division of the Clark County (Nevada) Sheriff&amp;rsquo;s Department, usually referred to by officers as the &amp;ldquo;Las Vegas Crime Lab.&amp;rdquo; The division solves crimes almost entirely through the means of forensics evidence, which may or may not come to the conclusion of a murder or accidental death. Keeping in theme with the setting, investigations often lead to taboo subjects, such as sexual deviations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Courthouse</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/actor/courthouse/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/actor/courthouse/</guid>
      <description>Jorja Fox&amp;rsquo;s appearance in this is unverified. If you have information than can confirm, please contact us, and be sure to cite your source.
Character Jorja Fox played &amp;ldquo;Maureen Dawes&amp;rdquo; in the pilot episode.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dodges City</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/actor/dodges-city/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/actor/dodges-city/</guid>
      <description>Jorja Fox&amp;rsquo;s appearance in this is unverified. If you have information than can confirm, please contact us, and be sure to cite your source.
Produced by Paramount, Eric Szmanda (who played Greg Sanders on CSI) starred as Johnny Dodge, a fearless, thrill seeking private investigator with a taste for fast cars and faster women.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ER</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/actor/er/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/actor/er/</guid>
      <description>Character Dr. Maggie Doyle arrived from a hospital that had been closed. A wonderful dichotomy, Doyle was a gun-toting, lesbian vegetarian. She was good friends with John Carter, and had enough attitude for everyone.
Doyle slogged through a fairly nasty piece of litigation, when surgeon Dr. Robert &amp;lsquo;Rocket&amp;rsquo; Romano blasted her on her evaluation when she threatened to tell about his harassment of her. While Doyle filed the report, the plot fell by the wayside, and Romano became the Chief of Emergency Medicine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ellen</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/actor/ellen/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/actor/ellen/</guid>
      <description>Episode: &amp;ldquo;The Puppy Episode (2)&amp;rdquo;  Aired 30 April 1997 Season 4, Episode 23  Ellen senses a kindred spirit when she meets a gay woman, who enlightens her to her own sexual identity. Confused by this startling self-discovery, Ellen seeks the guidance of a therapist and braces herself for yet another moment of truth-telling her friends about this personal revelation.
Character On the now infamous &amp;lsquo;Coming Out&amp;rsquo; episode of Ellen, Jorja Fox played the uncredited, unnamed, lesbian in the coffee house who walks up to Ellen, sits down next to her, smiles, and proceeds to hit on Ellen&amp;rsquo;s best friend (and good looking friend), Paige.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Filmography</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/filmography/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/filmography/</guid>
      <description>A filmography is, in essence, the resume of a performer, listing all their cinematic achievements. This filmography has been broken down by section, to aid in sorting her work.
Jorja is credited as Jorja Fox unless otherwise noted.
Actor    Title   Date(s)   CSI: Immortality (TV Movie) Sara Sidle  2015   CSI: Crime Scene Investigation (TV Series) Sara Sidle – 2000-07 (main cast)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Law &amp; Order</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/actor/law-order/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/actor/law-order/</guid>
      <description>Episode: &amp;ldquo;Securitate&amp;rdquo;  Aired 5 May 1993 Season 3, Episode 20  When a Romanian immigrant kills, his lawyer announces he will plead his client &amp;ldquo;not guilty due to cultural insanity&amp;rdquo; claiming the man had been conditioned to violence in his homeland.
Character Paula Engren and a friend are on their way to a club when they&amp;rsquo;re witness to a man being dragged behind a car. They call the cops, but remember no useful information.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>List of CSI: Crime Scene Investigation episodes</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/actor/csi-episodes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/actor/csi-episodes/</guid>
      <description>The following is a list of episodes from the CBS television series, &amp;ldquo;CSI: Crime Scene Investigation&amp;rdquo; in which Jorja Fox appeared or was credited. Episodes are rated based on quality and volume of Jorja&amp;rsquo;s scenes. Episodes in which she is listed in the credits but does not appear are rated with zero stars.
Season One   # Title Airdate Rating  1 &#34;Pilot&#34; Oct 6, 2000   Grissom investigates a suicide that presents little evidence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>List of ER episodes</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/actor/er-episodes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/actor/er-episodes/</guid>
      <description>The following is a list of episodes from the CBS television series, &amp;ldquo;ER&amp;rdquo; in which Jorja Fox appeared or was credited. Episodes are rated based on quality and volume of Jorja&amp;rsquo;s scenes. Episodes in which she is listed in the credits but does not appear are rated with zero stars.
Jorja appeared as a regular guest in seasons three, four and five. In season 15, the final season of ER, her character&amp;rsquo;s nameplate can be seen in two episodes, on the wall of doctors who have left the ER.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>List of Missing Persons episodes</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/actor/missing-persons-episodes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/actor/missing-persons-episodes/</guid>
      <description>The following is a list of episodes from the CBS television series, &amp;ldquo;Missing Persons&amp;rdquo; in which Jorja Fox appeared or was credited. Episodes are rated based on quality and volume of Jorja&amp;rsquo;s scenes. Episodes in which she is listed in the credits but does not appear are rated with zero stars.
Season 1   # Title Airdate Rating  1x01 &#34;Pilot&#34; Aug 30, 1993   1x02 &#34;Cabe?... What kind of name is that?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>List of The West Wing episodes</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/actor/west-wing-episodes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/actor/west-wing-episodes/</guid>
      <description>The following is a list of episodes from the CBS television series, &amp;ldquo;The West Wing&amp;rdquo; in which Jorja Fox appeared or was credited. Episodes are rated based on quality and volume of Jorja&amp;rsquo;s scenes. Episodes in which she is listed in the credits but does not appear are rated with zero stars.
Season One   # Title Airdate Rating  16 (225915) &#34;20 Hours in LA&#34; Feb 23, 2000   Not Available  17 (225916) &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Missing Persons</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/actor/missing-persons/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/actor/missing-persons/</guid>
      <description>The show aired from August 1993 through February 1994 on ABC at 8 p.m., apart from the feature-length pilot episode, which was broadcast as the Monday Night Movie from 9 p.m.-11 p.m. ET.
Episodes usually began with some sort of humorous exchange between the team as they all crowded round the coffee machine, eating doughnuts. Ray would then come out from his office and hand out the cases for the day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nineteen</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/actor/nineteen/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/actor/nineteen/</guid>
      <description>Nineteen filmed a pilot episode, produced by CBS, and was an angst ridden comedy about a couple getting married at 19. Noah Lee Margetts played Michael Spattavechia to Jorja Fox&amp;rsquo;s Ruth Manicotti, with Meredith Scott Lynn playing Ruth&amp;rsquo;s best friend.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Partners</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/actor/partners/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/actor/partners/</guid>
      <description>Jorja Fox&amp;rsquo;s appearance in this is unverified. If you have information than can confirm, please contact us, and be sure to cite your source.
Jorja Fox played &amp;ldquo;Alex&amp;rdquo; in episode 3 &amp;ldquo;My Sister, My Enemy&amp;rdquo;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Summer Stories: The Mall</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/actor/the-mall/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/actor/the-mall/</guid>
      <description>Experience summer at the mall with Sarah, Spinner, Marla, Diane (Jorja Fox), Teresa, Kwan, and their friends.
Episodes  Aired Summer 1993  As these brand-new high school graduates prepare to head in new directions, poised between the past and the future, they learn a few of each other&amp;rsquo;s secrets&amp;hellip;and a lot more about themselves. Some of the stories in the first program, First Impressions, continue in the second program, Second Chances, as well as in the third program, Temptations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The True Story</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/actor/true-story/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/actor/true-story/</guid>
      <description>The True Story was to be produced by Tom Fontana and shown on UPN for the 1999&amp;frasl;2000 season. However for reasons unknown, it was reworked into a show named The Beat became about young, male, cops, one of whom was the son of a man who&amp;rsquo;d killed his wife 25 years ago. The Beat aired only 6 episodes and was marked as being one of the more foul-mouthed shows on the air.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The West Wing</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/actor/west-wing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/actor/west-wing/</guid>
      <description>Character Jorja Fox played Gina Toscano, the Secret Service agent assigned to protect the President&amp;rsquo;s youngest daughter, Zoey.
Special Agent Gina Toscano was a Secret Service agent assigned to protect the President&amp;rsquo;s daughter (Zoey), while Zoey was in college.
Gina attended University of Virginia (studying Criminology), and was in the Army ROTC (2nd Lt. in MP). She was the first agent to sign up for the detail or protecting Zoey and trained for 18 months before earning the assignment.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>