<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>2012 on Fans of Le Fox Library</title>
    <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/tags/2012/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 2012 on Fans of Le Fox Library</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Dec 2012 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://jorjafox.net/library/tags/2012/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Heeb Magazine</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2012/heeb-magazine/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Dec 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2012/heeb-magazine/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
How long have you been working on this show
About 7 years ago, I started to listen heavily to her music, watching videos and reading anything I could get my hands on. I wrote monologues in her voice and sang her songs at an open mic night at The Gardenia Club in West Hollywood. I won a screenwriting grant at University of Southern California and used that to get some musical charts in order and prototype a show.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Fanatic</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2012/tv-fanatic/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Dec 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2012/tv-fanatic/</guid>
      <description>Santa visited &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; fans early this year, as we received the unexpected gift of a Sara-centered episode on &amp;ldquo;Risky Business Class.&amp;rdquo; It was based on a former colleague of Sara&amp;rsquo;s, Doug Wilson from the NTSB, asking for the help from the crime lab.
First, I&amp;rdquo;m thrilled that we got an episode that focused on this team member, specifically her marriage to Grissom. Many fans have wondered why there isn&amp;rsquo;t more mention of Grissom or why Sara doesn&amp;rsquo;t seem to acknowledge that she&amp;rdquo;s even hitched.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TVEquals</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2012/tvequals/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Dec 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2012/tvequals/</guid>
      <description>Now that all of my fellow GSR fans have breathed a collective sigh of relief, although it might be a bit premature, I can honestly say that &amp;lsquo;Risky Business Class,&amp;rsquo; this week&amp;rdquo;s episode of CSI, will only ever be memorable as the episode that clearly exposed the rift in Grissom and Sara&amp;rdquo;s marriage.
There have been signs that the long distance arrangement is wearing on her all season, but it usually takes something big to make us wake up and realize there&amp;rdquo;s a problem in our lives, and for Sara it took the appearance of Doug Wilson, an NSTB investigator and former fling from San Francisco, who arrived in Vegas to investigate the crash of a small charter plane just off the Strip.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CSI Files</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2012/csi-files-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Dec 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2012/csi-files-01/</guid>
      <description>There&amp;rsquo;s a fine line to ride when doing interviews with folks from the CSI: Crime Scene Investigation franchise. Obviously, I am a huge fan of the shows (otherwise I would not be here), so there’s always a bit of excitement and nostalgia when doing promotional material. But there’s always a reminder in the back of my head that CSI Files is a very professional outlet, and I have to be somewhat on guard as to how ‘geeky’ I get.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Televizier</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2012/televizier/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2012/televizier/</guid>
      <description>[Translated from Dutch by Google &amp;amp; Corrected by Volunteers.]
&amp;rdquo;&amp;lsquo;In the new season of CSI, Russel has to save his granddaughter. Sara finds an important lead. If he hadn&amp;rdquo;t had herâ¦&amp;rdquo;&amp;rsquo;
A corrupt officer of the LAPD appears to be working closely with the kidnappers. He leads CSI-investigator Finn (Elisabeth Shue) to where D.B. Russell&amp;rdquo;s (Ted Danson) granddaughter Katie is being held. The girl is allowed to call her grandfather to show she is still alive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CSI Files</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2012/csi-files-09/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2012/csi-files-09/</guid>
      <description>CSI: Crime Scene Investigation is preparing for some heavy character development in the second stretch of Season Thirteen.
Sources close to the show tell CSI Files exclusively that Sara Sidle (Jorja Fox), Nick Stokes (George Eads), and Morgan Brody (Elisabeth Harnois) will be dealing with some significant character development during the remainder of this season, and also potentially set the stage for a visit from returning characters.&amp;lsquo;We want to more completely address the issue of Sara and Grissom; the challenge of that for her, certainly,&amp;rsquo; one source tells CSI Files.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CSI Files</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2012/csi-files-03/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2012/csi-files-03/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
CSI Files: Who of the original team is most affected by this episode?
Mularz: I&amp;rdquo;d say Nick and Sara. Nick and Sara, I feel like, take it the hardest. Brass has a really nice moment where he talks about how he actually hasn&amp;rdquo;t been to the cemetery since Warrick&amp;rdquo;s funeral, but he has his own ways of remembering him. Brass likes to think about how much energy Warrick had. He says a little piece about Fight Nights, those are the nights that he thinks of Warrick.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ming Lo (25 October 2012)</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2012/ming-lo/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Oct 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2012/ming-lo/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
From time to time, the music we play and with all the noise, we&amp;rdquo;d have to take a break from shooting. For example, they played Queen&amp;rdquo;s &amp;lsquo;We will rock you&amp;rsquo;, and the crowd got into it, dancing and waving their hands. Meanwhile, the crew and cast would walk around and record video of everyone. On another one of these breaks, Jorja Fox did an impressive little dance in a little hidden space behind video village.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Examiner.com</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2012/examiner-com/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Oct 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2012/examiner-com/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;CSI,&amp;rdquo; which airs on CBS 2 in Queens, may be dealing with a possible act of terrorism in an upcoming episode. What happened? On Saturday,Â SpoilerTVÂ shared the following synopsis for episode 10, &amp;ldquo;Risky Business Class.&amp;rdquo;
 &amp;ldquo;When a small executive jet crash lands a mile off the Strip, the CSIs wonder if it was intended as an act of terror, and to solve the case, Sara teams up with a former colleague from San Francisco with whom she still has sparks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CSI Files (17 October 2012)</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2012/csi-files-04/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2012/csi-files-04/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
&amp;rdquo;&amp;lsquo;CSI Files:&amp;ldquo;&amp;rsquo; Sara [&amp;ldquo;&amp;lsquo;Jorja Fox&amp;rdquo;&amp;rsquo;] brings up her relationship with Grissom [&amp;ldquo;&amp;lsquo;William Petersen&amp;rdquo;&amp;rsquo;] this week. What&amp;rdquo;s the status with those two? Is he living in Vegas or is he still abroad?
&amp;rdquo;&amp;lsquo;Pokaski:&amp;ldquo;&amp;rsquo; He&amp;rdquo;s still abroad. This year, without giving too much away, we&amp;rdquo;re going to start dealing with the fact that long-distance relationships are hard. I don&amp;rdquo;t know if you&amp;rdquo;ve ever been in a long-distance relationship, but my wife and I were apart for a while and there&amp;rdquo;s a lot of message leaving.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ScreenPicks</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2012/screenpicks/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Oct 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2012/screenpicks/</guid>
      <description>Written in conjunction with PopCulturePassionistas.com.
Jorja Fox, best know for her roles on CSI: Crime Scene Investigation along with The West Wing and ER, is also an avid environmentalist and conservationist. She is being honored this weekend with the Animal Champion Award for her work with Animal Defenders International. ADI has worked tirelessly to rescue and protect the abused and neglected animals across the globe.
The event this weekend, called the Lion Ark Night will focus on the rescue mission performed last year where ADI uncovered and put an end to cruelty to circus animals in Bolivia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CSI Files</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2012/csi-files-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Oct 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2012/csi-files-02/</guid>
      <description>Anyone who knows Jorja Fox&amp;nbsp;understands just how special of a woman she is. The Sara Sidle actress is not only amazingly humble, talented, and yes, beautiful, but she&amp;rdquo;s also incredibly&amp;nbsp;brilliant, kind, and well spoken, which makes anyone in her presence feel special. After playing this one character for over twelve seasons, she knows the ins and outs of her character to a T, and is always eager to add new layers and nuances to her performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CSI Files</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2012/csi-files-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Sep 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2012/csi-files-10/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
CSI Files: It brought back memories from Season Four, when Sara started popping cough drops to mask her issues with alcohol and ultimately facing a DUI. If anyone is going to stop [Nick] from loosing focus, it&amp;rdquo;s her; and she did. Will they talk about this issue in subsequent episodes?
Barbour: Yes. There was purpose to the fact that they&amp;rdquo;re in different places in their lives and yet it was very poignant for Sara and Nick to get into it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>USA Today</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2012/usa-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Sep 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2012/usa-today/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
***CSI: Crime Scene Investigation
***CBS, Wednesdays, 10 ET/PT
Premiere: Sept. 26
Where we left them: Under attack from the former undersheriff of Las Vegas, the murderous Jeffrey McKeen (Conor O&amp;rsquo;Farrell) &amp;#8212; who runs an underworld empire of drugs and corrupt cops from his prison cell &amp;#8212; the CSI team was on the ropes, with Undersheriff Ecklie (Marc Vann) gunned down on the street, investigator Nick Stokes (George Eads) handing in his resignation in frustration, and supervisor D.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FormulaTV</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2012/formulatv/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Sep 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2012/formulatv/</guid>
      <description>Translated from Spanish.
CSI: Las Vegas returns to Telecinco and does so with what is already its eleventh season.
Chain broadcast every Thursday from 22:00 two new episodes of the long-running fiction starring Marg Helgenberger, Laurence Fishburne, George Eads, Eric Szmanda and Robert David Hall, Jorja Fox. Recently, Jorja spoke about the premiere of new episodes and one of the major complaints: the lack of Gil Grissom. William Petersen will briefly return to the show via Skype and talk to his wife and mother.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Xfinity TV Blog</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2012/xfinity-tv-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2012/xfinity-tv-blog/</guid>
      <description>&amp;lsquo;CSI: Crime Scene Investigation&amp;rdquo;s&amp;rsquo; season finale proved that even though the procedural drama has been on the air for 12 seasons, it&amp;rdquo;s still got what it takes to surprise viewers. The kidnapping of D.B. Russell&amp;rdquo;s (&amp;ldquo;&amp;lsquo;Ted Danson&amp;rdquo;&amp;rsquo;) granddaughter Kaitlyn (&amp;ldquo;&amp;lsquo;Mia Hayes&amp;rdquo;&amp;rsquo;) and the resignation of Nick Stokes (&amp;ldquo;&amp;lsquo;George Eads&amp;rdquo;&amp;rsquo;) set such dramatic â and unforeseen â events in motion that the audience will be compelled to tune in for 13th season premiere to get answers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hudson Valley Good Stuff</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2012/hudson-valley-good-stuff/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Sep 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2012/hudson-valley-good-stuff/</guid>
      <description>It was a pleasure sitting down with Jorja Fox on a park bench on a quiet Wall Street in Kingston on Labor Day to interview her about the new documentary she produced called &amp;ldquo;How I Became an Elephant.&amp;rdquo; The documentary was one of the films screened in the first Kingston NY Film Festival.
Jorja Fox is a vegetarian so I wanted to know where she dined. Which Hudson Valley restaurants offer good vegetarian cuisine?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CSI Files</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2012/csi-files-05/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2012/csi-files-05/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
&amp;rdquo;&amp;lsquo;CSI Files:&amp;ldquo;&amp;rsquo; There&amp;rdquo;s also an unwavering amount of requests from the fans for an appearance by &amp;ldquo;&amp;lsquo;William Petersen&amp;rdquo;&amp;rsquo;. An attempt was made last season but some personal matters conflicted with filming, and now he has a potential new series on pay-cable. Has progress been made to lure him back for an episode or two?
&amp;rdquo;&amp;lsquo;McGill:&amp;ldquo;&amp;rsquo; The door is always open. As you&amp;rdquo;ve pointed out, we talked to Billy in the past about storylines that would bring Grissom back to CSI.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Viva Magazine</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2012/viva-magazine/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 May 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2012/viva-magazine/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
&amp;rdquo;&amp;lsquo;Did You Knowâ¦&amp;rdquo;&amp;rsquo; &amp;lsquo;CSI: Miami&amp;rsquo; is getting the boot from the Fall season line-up, but Jorja Fox of &amp;lsquo;CSI&amp;rsquo; will be back in September. [&amp;hellip;]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Hollywood Reporter</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2012/the-hollywood-reporter/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 May 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2012/the-hollywood-reporter/</guid>
      <description>The original cast member has signed a new pact with CBS Television Studios to return to the long-running procedural for its upcoming 13th season.
CSI: Crime Scene Investigation&amp;#8216;s **Jorja Fox **is remaining on the case.
The actress has signed a new one-year deal with CBS Television Studios to remain on the long-running procedural, *The Hollywood Reporter *has learned exclusively.
Fox plays forensic scientist Sara Sidle on the CBS drama, a role she first stepped into in the second episode of the Anthony Zuiker procedural in 2000.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Comcast TV Blog</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2012/comcast-tv-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 May 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2012/comcast-tv-blog/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
What should fans look forward to next season? And if you haven&amp;rdquo;t gotten that far yetâ¦what would your dream season be?
We start with our &amp;lsquo;Cape Fear&amp;rsquo;-style premiere, putting Russell and the team on the line. A villain from the past, former Under Sheriff Jeff McKeen (Conor O&amp;rdquo;Farrell), who took the life of CSI Warrick Brown (Gary Dourdan), is now out to get all of our CSIs. Also in the works is a mass killing at a favorite haunt of the lab rats.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EW</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2012/ew-03/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 May 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2012/ew-03/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
In general,Â *CSI*Â has become a richer series. It&amp;rdquo;s minimized the crazy-Vegas murder scenarios that were beginning to undermine minimal believability, and I&amp;rdquo;d say that even if you wish that, say, Jorja Fox&amp;rdquo;s Sara had more of a role in the show these days, that reflects the way things happen in any given workplace â some veterans tend to recede into the background, content to do their jobs well, while new faces (Shue&amp;rdquo;s Finn, in this case) come on like gangbusters, eager (or neurotic, or insecure, or all of the above) to prove themselves.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ecorazzi</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2012/ecorazzi/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Apr 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2012/ecorazzi/</guid>
      <description>CSI&amp;rdquo;s &amp;ldquo;&amp;lsquo;Jorja Fox&amp;rdquo;&amp;rsquo; is taking on circus animal abusers in a new PSA for Animal Defenders International (ADI). The PSA is only 90 seconds long but the impact of the video is strong. The scenes flip from free roaming wild elephants in Africa to a traveling circus elephant named Krissy that is chained, beaten, and broken for the entertainment of humans.
Fox appears in the PSA holding a bullhook with a very solemn expression on her face.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Houston Chronicle</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2012/houston-chronicle/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Apr 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2012/houston-chronicle/</guid>
      <description>CSI actress Jorja Fox released a new video message about circus animal abuse today on behalf of Animal Defenders International (ADI)
Los Angeles, CA (PRWEB) April 19, 2012
Actress Jorja Fox (who plays CSI&amp;rdquo;s Sarah Sidle) released a new video message about circus animal abuse today, on behalf of Animal Defenders International (ADI). Fox is seen holding a bullhook, a weapon used to control elephants saying, &amp;lsquo;This is a bullhook it&amp;rdquo;s heavy, it&amp;rdquo;s sharp, and it hurts,&amp;rsquo; she continues, &amp;lsquo;This is the weapon of choice for elephant circus performers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CSI Files</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2012/csi-files-08/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Mar 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2012/csi-files-08/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
CSI Files: George Eads spoke with me about how he&amp;rdquo;d like to see a bit of a relationship between Nick and Finn.
Shue: Nice, I like that! That would be fun; I think that would be great. They probably don&amp;rdquo;t like the characters on CSI to get too intimateâ¦ I don&amp;rdquo;t know why, but I don&amp;rdquo;t think they&amp;rdquo;ve ever&amp;ndash;except for Jorja [Fox, Sara Sidle] and Billy Petersen&amp;rdquo;s [Gil Grissom] character.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CSI Files</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2012/csi-files-06/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Mar 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2012/csi-files-06/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
CSI Files: There&amp;rdquo;s word that Gil Grissom will somehow factor into the episode. Will there be an appearance by William Petersen before the end of the season?
Pokaski: I can&amp;rdquo;t speak to the end of the season (or I might not make it past it myself), but part of Wednesday night&amp;rdquo;s story is dedicated to understanding Married life between Sara [Sidle, Jorja Fox] and Grissom. How it works, and why it works.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CSI Files</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2012/csi-files-07/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2012/csi-files-07/</guid>
      <description>Tonight, &amp;ldquo;&amp;lsquo;Marg Helgenberger&amp;rdquo;s&amp;rdquo;&amp;rsquo; run as sexy, smart, and sassy crime scene investigator Catherine Willows will reach its conclusion. A twelve year tenure with more than 250 episodes under her belt, the actress has decided to pursue other opportunities and is bound for more success, whether it be a Broadway show or returning to film. Though her departure will surely bring tears to the show&amp;rdquo;s audience, the cast and crew of CSI: Crime Scene Investigation are looking on the bright side, reflecting back at their time on the show with the universally adored actress.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Entertainment Weekly</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2012/ew-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2012/ew-02/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
Jorja Fox had written this card for me with a polar bear on it â a photograph of a polar bear. What she said in the card was so beautiful about how I&amp;rdquo;m an endangered species and blah, blah, blah. It was just so moving. So I just feel so blessed to have had this experience all these years.
[&amp;hellip;]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Guide</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2012/tv-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2012/tv-guide/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
TV Guide Magazine: So was your last day like a celebration or a wake?
Helgenberger: [Laughs] To be honest, I didn&amp;rsquo;t sleep well those first couple days afterward. It was a tearful exit from the set, then I went out with a few close friends like Eric [Szmanda], [Robert] David [Hall] and Jorja [Fox]. It&amp;rsquo;s never a good idea to start drinking tequila at 10:30 at night, but it was a perfect way to end things.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Marg Helgenberger&#39;s Star on Hollywood Boulevard</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2012/marg-helgenberger-star-on-hollywood-boulevard/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2012/marg-helgenberger-star-on-hollywood-boulevard/</guid>
      <description>Jorja Fox: Hello! Hi, I&amp;rsquo;m the one who&amp;rsquo;s going to have to read everything, as Marg knows.
Marg Helgenberger: It&amp;rsquo;s what you do.
Jorja Fox: Yeah. I&amp;rsquo;m so happy for you. I had the very good fortune of meeting Marg Helgenberger in July of 2000, just as we were embarking on what would prove to be one of the signature adventures of our lives. Over the course of these last twelve years, we&amp;rsquo;ve shared some of the best and most exciting times a person can have.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Entertainment Weekly</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2012/ew-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2012/ew-01/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
On Dec. 7, the 53-year-old actress became the third original star (behind Gary Dourdan and William Petersen) to depart the long-running crime drama. All of her current costars &amp;#8212; Ted Danson (D.B. Russel), George Eads (Nick Stokes), Jorja Fox (Sara Sidle), and Paul Guilfoyle (Capt. Jim Brass) among them &amp;#8212; were there to appear in Helgenberger&amp;rsquo;s final scene and to bid farewell to the unofficial den mom of the franchise.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>News Articles (2012)</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2012/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2012/</guid>
      <description>Date Source    January 06 Entertainment Weekly   January 24 TV Guide   January 25 CSI Files   January 25 Entertainment Weekly   March 20 CSI Files   March 26 CSI Files   April 20 Ecorazzi   April 20 Houston Chronicle   May 09 Comcast TV Blog   May 09 EW   May 11 The Hollywood Reporter   May 28 Viva Magazine   July 18 CSI Files   September 05 Hudson Valley Good Stuff   September 11 Xfinity TV Blog   September 13 FormulaTV   September 14 USA Today   September 26 CSI Files   October 10 CSI Files   October 13 ScreenPicks   October 17 CSI Files (17 October 2012)   October 20 Examiner.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>