<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>2010 on Jorja Fox Library</title>
    <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/tags/2010/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 2010 on Jorja Fox Library</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 Dec 2010 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://jorjafox.net/library/tags/2010/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Humane Society</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2010/humane-society/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Dec 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2010/humane-society/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ten celebrities share their 2011 wishes for animals&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We asked some favorite celebrities to share their resolutions for animals in 2011:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;JORJA FOX:&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;ldquo;My resolution is to support he HSUS&amp;rsquo;s effort to end dogfighting, and all they&amp;rsquo;re doing to help at-risk communities.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Jorja Fox, star of the hit TV series CSI, has been a long-time supporter of The HSUS and our End Dogfighting campaign.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Entertainment Weekly</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2010/ew-03/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2010/ew-03/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;lsquo;CSI&amp;rsquo; EXEC PRODCERS DROP TEASERS, TALK JORJA FOX&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And I&amp;rsquo;ve saved the best for last. Jorja Fox fans have emailed me in a fury about rumors that the lovely forensic scientist would only be on 11 episodes. But the CSI honchos were happy to report that while they&amp;rsquo;re still discussing exactly how many episodes she will appear in, fans can &amp;hellip;look for more than 11.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zap2it</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2010/zap2it/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2010/zap2it/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;If Marlee Matlin has her way, there will be more &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; dramas than just the three &amp;#8212; the original, &amp;ldquo;CSI: Crime Scene Investigation,&amp;rdquo; and its spin-offs, (&amp;ldquo;CSI: Miami&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;CSI: NY&amp;rdquo;) that CBS has on the air now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Matlin guest-stars in an episode of the original &amp;ldquo;CSI,&amp;rdquo; tentatively scheduled to air Thursday, Feb. 3. In &amp;ldquo;The Two Mrs. Grissoms,&amp;rdquo; which has been in production this past week, Matlin plays Julia Holden, a professor at a college for the deaf, whose mentor is fellow professor Betty Grissom (Phyllis Frelich), mother of former head CSI Gil Grissom (William Petersen).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This causes tension with Grissom&amp;rsquo;s current wife, CSI Sara Sidle (Jorja Fox), who simultaneously must deal with her mother-in-law and with Julia, who&amp;rsquo;s also Grissom&amp;rsquo;s ex-girlfriend. It doesn&amp;rsquo;t help that both Julia and Mrs. Grissom are deaf and can speak to each other in American Sign Language, which Sara is struggling to learn.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As to whether Mrs. Grissom might have preferred Julia to Sara as a daughter-in-law, Matlin speaks in sign language through an interpreter, telling Zap2it, &amp;ldquo;She adores me better, I know that. I just had to say that.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DTVUSAForum.com</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2010/dtvusaforum-com/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Dec 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2010/dtvusaforum-com/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The February 3rd episode of &amp;ldquo;CSI: Crime Scene Investigation&amp;rdquo; will have a pair of Grissoms facing off, but unfortunately, neither of them will be Gil Grissom, the role vacated a couple of years ago by William Petersen. Rather, it will be Grissom&amp;rsquo;s wife Sara (Jorja Fox) and his mother, who isn&amp;rsquo;t Fox had left the hit crime series the year before Petersen, but she returned for his final scene on the show, the couple closing things out with a big kiss. Last season, Fox returned to the show for a handful of appearances. Her character sported a wedding ring and was occasionally referred to by her married name of Grissom.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the current season, the CBS show hasn&amp;rsquo;t made many Grissom references even though Fox has returned as a regular, appearing in a majority, but not all, of the episodes. That&amp;rsquo;s why this news is rather exciting.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Playing the role of Gil&amp;rsquo;s mom is Phyllis Frelich, the deaf actress who achieved acclaim with her performance in Children of a Lesser God on Broadway. The role was taken over by Marlee Matlin when made into a film. Interestingly, Matlin is also going to appear in this TV episode as Mrs. Grissom&amp;rsquo;s preferred daughter-in-law.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There is a murder to be solved so it won&amp;rsquo;t be all soap opera, and who knows, maybe Petersen can be talked into a brief cameo. Viewers can always dream.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Entertainment Week</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2010/ew-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2010/ew-02/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Get ready for the mother of all &lt;em&gt;CSI&lt;/em&gt; episodes, because we&amp;rsquo;re about to meet Gil Grissom&amp;rsquo;s long lost mother! EW has learned exclusively that Tony award-winning actress Phyllis Frelich will play the role of Mrs. Grissom &amp;ndash; and go head-to-head with the new Mrs. Grissom &amp;ndash; in an episode tentatively scheduled to air Feb. 3.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here are the details: A murder occurs at a school for the deaf where Grissom&amp;rsquo;s mom is a professor. Sara (Jorja Fox) goes to investigate but ends up facing an unexpected challenge &amp;ndash; a surprising lack of affection from her mother-in-law. Apparently, Grissom&amp;rsquo;s mom never felt that Sara was the one for her beloved Gil so the two women have a few fences to mend. The episode also stars Oscar winner Marlee Matlin as a school colleague who not only serves as Mrs. Grissom&amp;rsquo;s protege but used to date Gil. Guess who momma Grissom prefers?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sadly, William Petersen won&amp;rsquo;t appear in the episode. (Fans are supposed to think that Gil is contantly on the move so he and Sara maintain a long-distance relationship.) But the story is a continuation of an arc that started way back in season one&amp;rsquo;s memorable &amp;hellip;Sound of Silence&amp;rdquo; episode, in which we first learn that our hero can sign because he grew up with a deaf mother.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Frelich, who is deaf, won a Tony Award for her work in the 1980 Broadway production of Children of a Lesser God &amp;ndash; the play that inspired the movie of the same name that starred Matlin, who won an Oscar for her role. Frelich has also appeared in numerous TV shows, including &lt;em&gt;ER&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;Diagnosis: Murder&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;L.A. Law&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E! Online - Watch With Kristin</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2010/e-online/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2010/e-online/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ainav in Israel: I found a piece of information on the web that episode 11.13 of &lt;em&gt;CSI&lt;/em&gt; is called &amp;ldquo;The Two Mrs. Grissoms&amp;rdquo;! Now I don&amp;rsquo;t really care much for &lt;em&gt;CSI&lt;/em&gt; anymore, but if that&amp;rsquo;s true then I care a whole lot!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s true! The Mrs. Grissoms in question are Sarah Sidle (the current Mrs. Grissom)&amp;hellip;and Grissom&amp;rsquo;s mom! Producers are casting now for the older Mrs. Grissom, who is described as a &amp;ldquo;strong, confident, intelligent and influential woman has never allowed her lack of hearing to keep her from doing anything she wanted, and has no trouble making her feelings known to one and all.&amp;rdquo; She&amp;rsquo;s a former librarian, who, while being deaf, is fluent in American Sign Language as well as being a capable English speaker. Any ideas for casting other than maybe &lt;strong&gt;Marlee Matlin&lt;/strong&gt; in old-lady makeup?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Fanatic</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2010/tv-fanatic/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Oct 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2010/tv-fanatic/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Following an early season&amp;rsquo;s worth recent rocky episodes, &amp;ldquo;House of Hoarders&amp;rdquo; was a pleasant surprise.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After weeks of sharks in pools, vampires taking on werewolves, and a gimpy serial killers wearing pleather suits, I was almost certain the show&amp;rsquo;s handling of this psychological ailment of the moment would be serve as nothing but shock value.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But the writers took time to address the issue as a mystery and a very real problem.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Of course, there were plenty of shocking, and pretty gross moments throughout the hour.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The house itself was depicted as an unpleasant, debilitating environment, but every reveal and disgusting detail was played toward the episode&amp;rsquo;s mystery. &lt;em&gt;Was the hoarder really a killer? Was the mental disorder being played to hide a more sinister intent?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There were also some great character interactions, especially between Sara and Nick, as they viewed the case in different ways.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sara had sympathy for Mrs. Santiago, which clashed with Nick&amp;rsquo;s view that this woman&amp;rsquo;s condition was little more than a disguise for psychopathic tendencies. Their views on the matter remained divided even as the bodies found in the house began to mount up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Such care seemed to be put into the building of the mystery surrounding the house and the family that lived there, with interesting red herrings tossed out to distract, and such lovely emotional resonance in the performances of Jorja Fox, and guest stars Bertila Damas (Mrs. Santiago) and Ramon De Ocampo (Julian Santiago), but all that work was sort of steam-rolled in a conclusion that wrapped up too quickly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The final reveal of the actual killer felt like a brick wall, lacking the surprise I believe the writers intended.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Overall this was a nice change from previous episodes. There seems to be hope that CSI will get back on track, leaving the improbable and impossible plotlines behind for what has always made it a wonderful show with great mysteries, a little bit of gore, and great performances that invoke an emotional connection to the characters.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>411 Mania</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2010/411-mania/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2010/411-mania/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;- &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; premiere thoughts:&lt;/strong&gt; Man, where to freaking begin? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Okay, first the good stuff. Larry Fishburne enters his third season on the show with some goddamn attitude, something his Dr. Raymond Langston character has been missing since he started in 2008, and it&amp;rsquo;s been great. Langston, still hurt from the prison attack that ended last season, walks around with a cane and a sneer, like he&amp;rsquo;s telling the world &amp;ldquo;I am through with you all fucking with me!,&amp;rdquo; which is just awesome. He&amp;rsquo;s also much more confident at the crime scenes, and while he&amp;rsquo;s still not Gil Grissom, he&amp;rsquo;s become his own thing and that&amp;rsquo;s just great. That vampire episode was brilliant, one of the best I&amp;rsquo;ve seen with Langston so far. Hopefully there are more of those kinds of episodes coming this season. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Marg Helgenberger seems to be trying very hard &lt;em&gt;not&lt;/em&gt; to check out as this is her last season, which is a good thing. I imagine that she&amp;rsquo;s going to become the focus of the show towards the end of the season so she can get the big send off. I do wonder, though, who is going to take her place on the show when she leaves. Will Jorja Fox&amp;rsquo;s Sara take the lead female spot, or will the show create a new character, sort of like how &amp;ldquo;CSI: New York&amp;rdquo; did with Sela Ward? I&amp;rsquo;m not sure what I&amp;rsquo;d rather see. Will CBS allow Jerry Bruckheimer to hire another &amp;ldquo;name&amp;rdquo; actor? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Insider</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2010/the-insider/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2010/the-insider/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Watch Now: Trouble on the &amp;lsquo;CSI&amp;rsquo; Set&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;George Eads:&lt;/strong&gt; For the last couple years I was a big fan of the &amp;ldquo;Hoarders&amp;rdquo; documentary program. And so I was telling everybody-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; I think many of us are. George turned me on to it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GE:&lt;/strong&gt; I was telling you the other night!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;JF:&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;ldquo;I was watching this show the other night and you gotta check it out!&amp;rdquo; And I went and checked it out, and now it&amp;rsquo;s on my TiVo. So this is definitely a story George has wanted to tell for a while. It was in the making, it was gonna happen, and now it&amp;rsquo;s happening. It is really exciting when that &amp;hellip; happens.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GE:&lt;/strong&gt; One of the things that we &lt;em&gt;don&amp;rsquo;t&lt;/em&gt; have to deal with when we go to crime scenes is the odor. So we got lucky when it comes to that, because it&amp;rsquo;s &amp;lsquo;Movie Trash.&amp;rsquo; It&amp;rsquo;s still pretty disgusting under there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;JF:&lt;/strong&gt; It&amp;rsquo;s unbelievable, and you&amp;rsquo;ve got three and a half straight days in there. So yes, again, thank god it&amp;rsquo;s a set, but its extremely tight quarters. It&amp;rsquo;s very intimate. You get the crew in there setting lights, and move through it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GE:&lt;/strong&gt; Yeah but we talked about how there&amp;rsquo;s nobody we&amp;rsquo;d rather be with if we were stuck in a stinky set in tight quarters. You know?&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Squad</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2010/tv-squad/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2010/tv-squad/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s the most important holiday EVER today. No, not my birthday, it&amp;rsquo;s World Vegetarian Day!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As one of the token vegetarians around the TV Squad offices, I know all about the hardships of choosing to remain meat-free. But hey, I&amp;rsquo;m not alone. I&amp;rsquo;ve got millions of other vegetarian and vegan brethren &amp;#8212; even fictional ones!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In honor of this joyous holiday, I&amp;rsquo;m grilling up some tofu and paying respect to some of TV&amp;rsquo;s best vegetarians. There aren&amp;rsquo;t many TV characters who are vegetarians, and there&amp;rsquo;s a surprising lack of male vegetarians, but it is easy to play favorites.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;bull; Sara Sidle, &amp;#8216;CSI&amp;rsquo;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sara, like actress Jorja Fox, is a vegetarian. She became one after spending a night with a dead pig and Grissom. In the 2002 episode &amp;#8216;Burden of Proof,&amp;rsquo; Sara gets sassy with Grissom about her vegetarianism. &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m a vegetarian, everyone here knows I&amp;rsquo;m a vegetarian,&amp;rdquo; she said. &amp;ldquo;I haven&amp;rsquo;t eaten meat since we stayed up that night with that dead pig. It pains me to see ground beef. Forget about cleaning it up.&amp;rdquo; Bonus, Fox&amp;rsquo;s &amp;#8216;ER&amp;rsquo; character, Dr. Maggie Doyle, was also a vegetarian.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jorja All Around</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2010/jorja-all-around/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2010/jorja-all-around/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;JAA:&lt;/strong&gt; How long have you been working as a stunt-woman?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CM:&lt;/strong&gt; I&amp;rsquo;ve been a working stunt-woman for about 10 years but got in the business over 15 years ago. Working is the key word!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;**JAA: **What was the most terrifying or difficult stunt you&amp;rsquo;ve ever had to perform?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;**CM: **Hmmmmm I always get asked this question and really it&amp;rsquo;s not ever terrifying as it is an incredible [adrenaline] rush &amp;hellip;. Difficult? Well sometimes [it] all can be difficult as you want to make sure you give the coordinator what they want and [also give it] 100%&amp;hellip; I must say &amp;hellip; this will sound funny, BUT on an episode of &lt;em&gt;CSI&lt;/em&gt;&amp;hellip; I think a few seasons back I was playing a passenger on a community bus and I was sitting in the very back while they were shooting. We drove up and down and around North Hollywood for several hours and I got REALLY bad motion sickness! Now the motion sickness, yes, was the problem BUT not letting the crew and stunt coordinator know how bad it really was [because] I was a stunt-woman &amp;hellip; [I] had to be tough and getting motion sickness on a bus was not so tough! I really wanted to throw up but truly held it in [until] we finally got off and was able to get some soda water! THAT was the most terrifying/difficult job so far&amp;hellip; not letting anyone know how bad it was! HA HA.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;JAA:&lt;/strong&gt; We&amp;rsquo;ve seen you before on* CSI* in the episode &lt;em&gt;The Gone Dead Train&lt;/em&gt; in season nine. You got in a pretty nasty bite on Catherine &lt;strong&gt;(Marg Helgenberger)&lt;/strong&gt;! Was it fun to tangle with Marg?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;**CM: **She was so amazing and sweet! She was tough and a real trooper when I had to throw her around and attack her!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;**JAA: **You&amp;rsquo;ve now gone at both of &lt;em&gt;CSI&lt;/em&gt;&amp;#8216;s leading ladies! Who else would you like to take a swing at?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CM:&lt;/strong&gt; I [would] rather they swing at me! And anyone who wants to!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;**JAA: **As far as stunts go, was setting up your scene with Marg Helgenberger in season nine relatively simple? Did you give Marg any sort of direction from your background of fighting expertise?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;**CM: **That&amp;rsquo;s all done with the Stunt Coordinator! I just make sure she [is] comfortable with the action I&amp;rsquo;m told to do.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;JAA:&lt;/strong&gt; We saw you take a pretty hard punch from Sara Sidle **(Jorja Fox) **in the &lt;em&gt;CSI&lt;/em&gt; season eleven premiere! How much preparation went into setting up the scene?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;**CM: **Again that&amp;rsquo;s all set up by the Stunt Coordinator. Doing that shot with Jorja Fox took a few rehearsals but she was such a professional and a quick learner [that] it didn&amp;rsquo;t take much time at all. She was having a blast!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;JAA:&lt;/strong&gt; What was it like to work with Jorja Fox? Did you both have fun going at each other?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;**CM: **I must say [*CSI *is] one of the best sets to work on. EVERYONE is very friendly and fun! Jorja Fox was very friendly and so fun&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;she&amp;rsquo;s a sweetie!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;**JAA: **Any fun experiences while working on the &lt;em&gt;CSI&lt;/em&gt; set?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;**CM: **This will sound stupid&amp;hellip;BUT really every experience I have on &lt;em&gt;CSI&lt;/em&gt; is fun!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;JAA:&lt;/strong&gt; You have an extensive background working as a stunt-woman on various television and film sets. What is it like to see yourself in these roles?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CM:&lt;/strong&gt; Hate it!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;JAA:&lt;/strong&gt; Will we see more of you this season?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CM:&lt;/strong&gt; [In] episode 3 I&amp;rsquo;m doubling the legendary &amp;ldquo;ANN MARGRET&amp;rdquo; [and] got to do some fun stunts and meet her! She is awesome and that&amp;rsquo;s when I feel fortunate with the job I [have]! I think the episode is called &amp;ldquo;SQWEEGEL&amp;rdquo; [or] something like that. I&amp;rsquo;m sure you&amp;rsquo;ll find it!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>People Pets</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2010/people-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2010/people-1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Actress Jorja Fox may play a forensic scientist on CSI, but her real-life role is playing the part of mom to her 13-year-old boxer, Ali. &amp;ldquo;She was a rescue, and a friend of mine was desperately trying to find her a home,&amp;rdquo; Fox told PEOPLEPets.com last week at the Taste of Beverly Hills. After taking her in, &amp;ldquo;I had her only two or three weeks when I realized, &amp;#8216;This is probably the best decision I ever made.&amp;rsquo; &amp;ldquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fox boasts that on Oct. 10 (10/10/10), Ali will be celebrating her fourteenth birthday, which is &amp;ldquo;pretty old for a boxer.&amp;rdquo; With age, she has developed &amp;ldquo;a little arthritis [and is] a little hard of hearing,&amp;rdquo; adds Fox, &amp;ldquo;but she&amp;rsquo;s a great girl and I&amp;rsquo;m really thrilled to still have her around.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Although Ali is almost 100 in doggie years, age is just a number for the active pup! &amp;ldquo;I still take her to the beach [and] run her around. She likes that,&amp;rdquo; says Fox. &amp;ldquo;She still loves to go on car rides and smell the city.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TeLe Star</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2010/tl-star-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Aug 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2010/tl-star-1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;This article has been translated from it&amp;rsquo;s original French by Angela of &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.melinda-clarke.org/&#34;&gt;Melinda-Clarke.org&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;*&lt;strong&gt;CSI*&amp;#8216;s Jorja Fox says she wasn&amp;rsquo;t sure to re-sign&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Asked by the weekly French magazine Tele Star, Jorja Fox talked about the season 11 of &lt;em&gt;CSI&lt;/em&gt;. She re-signed for 11 episodes and will see in early 2011 if she wants to do more. Making only a few episodes works for her.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She wasn&amp;rsquo;t sure about returning to the show. Since 12 years now she has been working on television series, including &lt;em&gt;ER&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;CSI&lt;/em&gt;, and she started to lose energy. She was afraid that people see it on screen.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She decided to return this season because she felt like the whole cast and the writers were really behind the show. As for CBS refusing to give the actors a pay raise, she replies that not only the actors are concerned about it but also the crew. &lt;em&gt;&amp;ldquo;All the Americans are touched by the financial crisis so we must tighten our belts too.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TeLe Star</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2010/tl-star-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Aug 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2010/tl-star-2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;This article has been translated from it&amp;rsquo;s original French.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Jorja Fox, 42, will return for the eleventh season as Sara Sidle. While CSI is ailing the United States, the actress puts things in the clear. Exclusively.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;**Tele Star: After a thriller about your presence, then you will play in the season 11 Experts &amp;hellip; **&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; Yes, I&amp;rsquo;m returning for eleven episodes. I&amp;rsquo;ll decide January if I want to continue. Turn a few episodes for me. That leaves me free time for other activities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;**Why has it taken so long? **&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;J.F.:&lt;/strong&gt; To be honest, I hesitated to re-sign. Between ER and CSI, I&amp;rsquo;ve been on TV series for twelve years. I started to feel my energy wane and I fear that this is way to the screen.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;**What made you finally decide? **&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;J.F.:&lt;/strong&gt; When I decided to continue, it was because I felt the whole team, from actors to writers, were in tune.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;**Marg Helgenberger (Catherine Willows in the series) has it, decided to leave. You understand her choice? **&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;J.F.:&lt;/strong&gt; But nothing says she won&amp;rsquo;t change her mind. (She smiles.) I know her well and I think she may reverse her decision.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Is it true that George Eads (aka Nick) has also been close to leaving &amp;hellip;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;J.F.:&lt;/strong&gt; It was close, yes. He signed his contract only two days before the beginning of shooting. We felt a certain tension on the set.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;**These hesitations and these departures, are they linked with the salary increase of employees involved? **&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;J.F.:&lt;/strong&gt; I don&amp;rsquo;t think so. Moreover, it is not just actors, but also the writers and technicians. All Americans are concerned by the crisis. So we understand that we should also tighten our belts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;**People say the show is out of steam in the U.S., actors are leaving &amp;hellip; How do you revive the series? **&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;JF:&lt;/strong&gt; I do not think we need to make too many changes. And in the long run, the CSI series are the most watched in the world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;**However, the writers have announced changes &amp;hellip; **&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;J.F.:&lt;/strong&gt; True. This will be an important year for the character of Marg! And there are great chances that we might see Grissom.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Female solidarity ineffective&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
After William Petersen (Grissom) and Marg Helgenberger (Catherine Willows), it is time for the character of Wendy Simms (one of the heroines often confined to the laboratory) to disappear from the series. Liz Vassey has indeed been thanked by the production. It&amp;rsquo;s a great dissapointment to Jorja Fox: &amp;ldquo;I am very disappointed. Liz, Marg and I were the only heroines. We wanted to look for more women, it&amp;rsquo;s sad.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sveket mot minkarna</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2010/sveket-mot-minkarna/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Aug 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2010/sveket-mot-minkarna/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Den amerikanska skådespelerskan Jorja Fox, känd från bland annat CSI där hon spelar kriminalteknikern Sara Sidle som löser mystiska brott, ger sig nu in i debatten om svenska minkfarmer. Hon gör vad hon kan för att stoppa de lagbrott som pågått sedan 1988 genom att skriva ett öppet brev till stadsminister Fredrik Reinfeldt, där hon vädjar om att minkfarmerna ska förbjudas.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;** OPEN LETTER TO THE PRIME MINISTER OF SWEDEN - AUGUST 17, 2010**&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;*His Excellency Fredrik Reinfeldt&lt;br /&gt;
Prime Minister of Sweden&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dear Mr. Prime Minister,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am writing on behalf of my friends at the Animal Rights Alliance to ask that you please make a strong statement against cruelty to animals by banning fur farms in Sweden. Please take a moment to view footage from the Animal Rights Alliance&amp;rsquo;s recent undercover investigation of 18 Swedish fur farms. After watching the footage, I hope you will agree that the way animals suffer and die in this industry violates Sweden&amp;rsquo;s Animal Welfare Act, which clearly states that animals bred for fur production should be kept in such a way that promotes their health and allows them to engage in natural behavior.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Minks are semi-aquatic, solitary animals who may occupy up to 2,500 acres of wetland habitat in the wild. On fur farms, minks are crammed into wire cages and are never allowed to feel the earth under their feet or dive into a cool stream. As seen in the Animal Rights Alliance&amp;rsquo;s undercover video, the crowding and confinement on fur farms prevents minks from taking more than a few steps in any direction, and they often go insane and resort to self-mutilation and cannibalism.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As you know, fox farming has already been phased out in Sweden because of strict regulations. Won&amp;rsquo;t you please consider joining a host of other countries&amp;ndash;including Austria, Croatia, and the U.K.&amp;ndash;in banning fur farming altogether? I can be reached via Djurrättsalliansen at 0046 76 230 12 00.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank you for your time and consideration.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sincerely,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>