<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Advocacy on Fans of Le Fox Library</title>
    <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Advocacy on Fans of Le Fox Library</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2004 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>I Have a Dream Foundation</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/i-have-a-dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/i-have-a-dream/</guid>
      <description>The &amp;ldquo;I Have a Dream&amp;rdquo; Program helps children from low-income areas reach their education and career goals by providing a long-term program of mentoring, tutoring, and enrichment with an assured opportunity for higher education.
Jorja Fox attended their 6th annual brunch on 18 January 2004.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>&#39;Artists &amp; Athletes Alliance</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/artists-athletes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/artists-athletes/</guid>
      <description>The &amp;lsquo;Artists and Athletes Alliance&amp;rsquo; assists artists and athletes in navigating the halls of government, as well as helping them better understand the political process. By providing top-line educational information to artists and athletes through one-on-one meetings, private briefings, roundtable discussions, forums and other related events on the specific public policies and political issues of interest to them, the Alliance hopes to engage in productive dialogue with lawmakers, policymakers and opinion-leaders so the voices of the artistic and athletic community can be heard on the many important issues facing our nation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>&#39;Until the Violence Stops: Los Angeles</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/until-violence-stops/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/until-violence-stops/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Until the Violence Stops: Los Angeles&amp;rdquo; (aka UTVS:LA) is the LA organization who organizes and promotes V-Day. A coalition of activists, artists, entertainers, educators, civic leaders and concerned citizens who reside in Los Angeles County, UTVS:LA wants to see Los Angeles become the safest city on earth for women and girls.
 V-Day is a global movement to stop violence against women and girls. V-Day is a catalyst that promotes creative events to increase awareness, raise money and revitalize the spirit of existing anti-violence organizations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advocacy</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/main/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/main/</guid>
      <description>Advocacy is an umbrella term for organized activism related to a particular set of issues. Advocacy is expected to be non-deceptive and in good faith, though it is sometimes tainted by use of propaganda. It is almost always organized into or by an advocacy group or special interests. In other instances, an individual may act as a lobbyist, on their own account, or on behalf of a corporation or industry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Andean Bear Conservation Project</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/andean-bear/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/andean-bear/</guid>
      <description>The Andean Bear Foundation is a 501&amp;copy;(3) registered non-profit in the USA, and funds the Andean Bear Project&amp;rsquo;s research, conservation, rescue, rehabilitation and release of Andean bears in Ecuador.
Jorja Fox narrated a documentary about the bears.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Animal Acres</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/animal-acres/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/animal-acres/</guid>
      <description>Animal Acres is a farmed animal sanctuary and compassionate living center located just 45 minutes from Los Angeles. Animal Acres works to promote compassionate living through its farmed animal rescue and refuge efforts, public education and outreach, and advocacy projects to prevent cruelty to farmed animals.
Jorja Fox has attended many events for Animal Acres. She is also a supporter of &amp;ldquo;ACI: Animal Cruelty Investigations&amp;rdquo;, a sub-site of Animal Acres.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Animal Defenders International</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/adi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/adi/</guid>
      <description>Animal Defenders International (ADI) is an animal welfare organization, dedicated to international campaigning group that lobbies on issues such as animals in circuses; worldwide traffic in endangered species; vegetarian/vegan diet; factory farming; and pollution. ADI involves itself in international animal rescues as well as educational work on animal welfare, conservation and the environment.
Animals in entertainment Jorja Fox joined ADI when they went to Austin, Texas to look into the issue of circus animal cruelty in Austin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CBS Cares</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/cbs-cares/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/cbs-cares/</guid>
      <description>While on CSI: Crime Scene Investigation, Jorja Fox and many of her cast members filmed Public Service Announcements for CBS.
Peace (2002)  These days, good communication takes more than phones or computers. It means getting along with people from every race or foreign culture. CBS Cares.
 Mentoring (2005)  A little time with a caring adult makes a huge difference in a child&amp;rsquo;s life &amp;ndash; and you&amp;rsquo;ll be amazed at what a huge difference it makes in your life as well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Californians for Humane Farms</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/ca-for-humane-farms/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/ca-for-humane-farms/</guid>
      <description>Californians for Humane Farms is sponsored by the Humane Society of the United States, Farm Sanctuary and other animal protection groups, family farmers, veterinarians, and public health professionals, who have joined together in an effort to launch a statewide initiative for the November 2008 ballot &amp;ndash; one that will improve the lives of millions of farm animals in California.
Jorja Fox (among other celebrities) endorses the campaign.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Charity Folks</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/charity-folks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/charity-folks/</guid>
      <description>Charity Folks is the leading online charity auction venue. Inspired by the belief that there&amp;rsquo;s nothing more important than the work nonprofits are doing to improve people&amp;rsquo;s lives, they strive to provide innovative ePhilanthropy solutions that help raise the money &amp;amp; awareness needed for nonprofits to accomplish their mission.
In the American Red Cross Disaster Relief Auction for Hurricane Katrina, Jorja Fox donated four items to raise money.
*Signed Head Shot from CSI star Jorja Fox with a special message</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Climate Star</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/climate-star/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/climate-star/</guid>
      <description>The following is a text only reprint of an ad done by Jorja Fox for Climate Star.
Intro The hottest stars in the entertainment universe are concerned about something serious that&amp;rsquo;s happening to our planet &amp;ndash; global warming. The following is from the advert Jorja Fox was in.
Ad  Stranded.
No, it&amp;rsquo;s not a new reality show.
It&amp;rsquo;s what thousands of species now face thanks to global warming. Habitats are changing along with the climate, and many species will disappear from their present homes while others may disappear altogether.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Clothes Off Our Back</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/clothes-off-our-back/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/clothes-off-our-back/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Clothes Off Our Back&amp;rdquo; is a 501 &amp;copy; 3 organization that hosts charity auctions and private events showcasing today&amp;rsquo;s hottest celebrity attire. Items are put up for bid to the public with proceeds going to select children&amp;rsquo;s charities each year. Clothes Off Our Back was founded by actors and philanthropists Jane Kaczmarek (&amp;lsquo;Malcolm In The Middle&amp;rsquo;) and Bradley Whitford (&amp;lsquo;The West Wing&amp;rsquo;) whose efforts, along with their celebrity friends and auction participants, have helped spread awareness and improve the lives of children across the globe.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Earth Shoes</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/earth-shoes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/earth-shoes/</guid>
      <description>Earth shoes are extremely comfortable shoes, made in a &amp;#8216;negative heel&amp;rsquo; design that is reported to alleviate stress on the lower back and improve posture.
The Negative Heel technology was developed by Danish Yoga Master, Anne Kalso. This design positions the heel slightly lower than the toe to promote a more natural posture with the head straight, shoulders rolled back and spine and pelvis aligned, allowing the back to form its natural arch.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Equality California</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/eqca/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/eqca/</guid>
      <description>NO on H8! NO on H8! was a benefit for Equality California sponsored by Ian Harvie.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Five Acres</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/five-acres/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/five-acres/</guid>
      <description>Five Acres has served vulnerable children and families since 1888. They provide family-centered support services on campus and through outreach programs in homes, at schools and in off-site offices.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gal to Gal Virtual Walk</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/gal-to-gal/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/gal-to-gal/</guid>
      <description>Gal to Gal Virtual Walk was a 31-city virtual walk across the United States to benefit breast cancer courtesy of a computer, an avatar and a $3 donation. Jorja Fox was one of the initial 1500 walkers in 2007.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Huckleberry Foundation</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/huckleberry/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/huckleberry/</guid>
      <description>The Huckleberry Foundation is named after Huckleberry Finn, an 11-year-old who ran away from home to escape the abuse of his alcoholic father.
This Foundation supports the youth programs of the Division of Adolescent Medicine, Childrens&amp;rsquo; Hospital Los Angeles, which reach out to the &amp;lsquo;Huckleberry Finns&amp;rsquo; of today. For 20 years, the Division has led the way in providing integrated medical and psychological services to disadvantaged and disconnected youth of Los Angeles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Human Rights Watch</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/hrw/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/hrw/</guid>
      <description>The Human Rights Watch Annual Dinner, Voices for Justice, celebrates the valor of individuals who put their lives on the line to defend the rights of others.
Jorja Fox attended the dinner in 2003.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Humane Society of the United States</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/hsus/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/hsus/</guid>
      <description>The Humane Society of the United States is the nation&amp;rsquo;s largest and most effective animal protection organization &amp;ndash; backed by 11 million Americans, or one in every 28. Established in 1954, The HSUS seeks a humane and sustainable world for all animals &amp;ndash; a world that will also benefit people. We are America&amp;rsquo;s mainstream force against cruelty, exploitation and neglect, as well as the most trusted voice extolling the human-animal bond.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>In Defense of Animals</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/in-defense-animals/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/in-defense-animals/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;In Defense of Animals&amp;rdquo; (IDA)&amp;rsquo;s mission is to end animal exploitation, cruelty, and abuse by protecting and advocating for the rights, welfare, and habitats of animals, as well as to raise their status beyond mere property, commodities, or things.
International Day of Action for Elephants in Zoos (IDAEZ) June 19th 2010 was a global event aimed at bringing mammoth attention to the plight of elephants in zoos and ending their suffering.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>International Union for Conservation of Nature</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/iucn/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/iucn/</guid>
      <description>IUCN, the International Union for Conservation of Nature, helps the world find pragmatic solutions to our most pressing environment and development challenges. It supports scientific research, manages field projects all over the world and brings governments, non-government organizations, United Nations agencies, companies and local communities together to develop and implement policy, laws and best practice.
IUCN is the world&amp;rsquo;s oldest and largest global environmental network &amp;ndash; a democratic membership union with more than 1,000 government and NGO member organizations, and almost 11,000 volunteer scientists in more than 160 countries.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Macy&#39;s Passport Fund</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/macys-passport-fund/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/macys-passport-fund/</guid>
      <description>Macy’s Passport Fund supports agencies providing HIV/AIDS programming in certain counties with an operating Macy’s store location.
One of the nation&amp;rsquo;s longest-running HIV/AIDS fundraisers, The Macy&amp;rsquo;s and American Express HIV/AIDS Fundraiser (often referred to as Passport) has brought the excitement of live theatre and the best of Macy&amp;rsquo;s fall collections for men, women and children to audiences while raising over $10 million for HIV/AIDS agencies.
Jorja attended the fundraiser in 2002.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Orangutan Outreach</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/orangutan-outreach/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/orangutan-outreach/</guid>
      <description>Orangutan Outreach is part of BOS International. The purpose of Orangutan Outreach is:
* To conserve orangutans in their native habitat.
* To raise and promote public awareness of, and participation in, conservation strategies for orangutans through grassroots campaigns, community involvement and global communication.
* To collaborate with Indonesian conservationists in the running of orangutan rehabilitation centers.
* To fund rescue efforts of orangutans confiscated on palm oil plantations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PETA</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/peta/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/peta/</guid>
      <description>PETA (People for the Ethical Treatment of Animals) is the largest animal rights organization in the world.
PETA focuses its attention on the four areas in which the largest numbers of animals suffer the most intensely for the longest periods of time: on factory farms, in laboratories, in the clothing trade, and in the entertainment industry. We also work on a variety of other issues, including the cruel killing of beavers, birds and other &amp;lsquo;pests,&amp;rsquo; and the abuse of backyard dogs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Penny Lane</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/penny-lane/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/penny-lane/</guid>
      <description>Penny Lane Org cares for over 1,500 abused, neglect and abandoned children each year in the Los Angeles area and Antelope Valley, and Jorja For is one of the number one supporters.
Voices of Our Children They have an annual celebrity fund raiser called Voices of Our Children, which entails celebrities reading what those beautiful children have written about their life experiences. Jorja is one of the emotional and powerful celebrities who reads and has helped them now for several years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Racing Extinction</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/racing-extinction/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/racing-extinction/</guid>
      <description>In Racing Extinction, a team of artists and activists exposes the hidden world of extinction with never-before-seen images that will change the way we see the planet. Two worlds drive extinction across the globe, potentially resulting in the loss of half of all species. The international wildlife trade creates bogus markets at the expense of creatures that have survived on this planet for millions of years. And the other surrounds us, hiding in plain sight — a world that the oil and gas companies don’t want the rest of us to see.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rip Curl</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/rip-curl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/rip-curl/</guid>
      <description>While Rip Curl is primarily known for surfing equipment and events, their annual Malibu Pro contest has an ulterior motive. Their event is dedicated to the preservation of beaches. In Rip Curl hosted a female contest designed to promote the beauty, soul and excitement of not only women&amp;rsquo;s surfing, but the beauty, soul and excitement of the sacred Chumash Indian site that we call Malibu.
Jorja Fox attended on 30 September 2004.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Screen Actors Guild</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/sag/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/sag/</guid>
      <description>The Screen Actors Guild (aka SAG) is an American labor union representing over 120,000 film and television principal performers and background performers worldwide. According to SAG&amp;rsquo;s Mission Statement, the Guild seeks to: negotiate and enforce collective bargaining agreements that establish equitable levels of compensation, benefits, and working conditions for its performers; collect compensation for exploitation of recorded performances by its members, and provide protection against unauthorized use of those performances; and preserve and expand work opportunities for its members.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sea Shepherd Conservation Society</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/sea-shepherd/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/sea-shepherd/</guid>
      <description>The Sea Shepherd Conservation Society was formed when Captain Paul Watson founded the Earth Force Society in 1977 in Vancouver BC, Canada. The original mandate of both organizations was marine mammal protection and conservation with an immediate goal of shutting down illegal whaling and sealing operations, but Sea Shepherd later expanded its mission to include all marine wildlife. The Sea Shepherd Conservation Society was formally incorporated in the United States in 1981 in the state of Oregon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Surfrider Foundation</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/surfrider/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/surfrider/</guid>
      <description>The Surfrider Foundation is a non-profit grassroots organization dedicated to the protection and enjoyment of our world&amp;rsquo;s oceans, waves and beaches. The core activities and campaigns that the Surfrider Foundation uses to protect our oceans, waves and beaches fall into the categories of Clean Water, Beach Access, Beach Preservation and Protecting Special Places.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Susan G. Komen for the Cure</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/susan-g-komen/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/susan-g-komen/</guid>
      <description>Susan G. Komen fought breast cancer with her heart, body and soul. Throughout her diagnosis, treatments, and endless days in the hospital, she spent her time thinking of ways to make life better for other women battling breast cancer instead of worrying about her own situation. That concern for others continued even as Susan neared the end of her fight. Moved by Susan&amp;rsquo;s compassion for others and committed to making a difference, Nancy G.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Friends of El Faro</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/el-faro/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/el-faro/</guid>
      <description>Friends of El Faro has a simple mission &amp;#8212; to help improve the lives of the orphans at El Faro (in Mexico) in any way possible. El Faro 2 (The Lighthouse) was founded in the 1990, when Carmen and Jorge Gonzales opened the doors of their home to a few abandoned children living on the streets. Word spread and in a very short amount of time children were being dropped off in the middle of the night by relatives who could not care for them, or were frightened because of a history of abuse.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Campaign for Burma</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/us-campaign-for-burma/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/us-campaign-for-burma/</guid>
      <description>30 Hollywood celebrities ran a campaign from May 1 through May 30 to seek the release of Myanmar&amp;rsquo;s democracy icon Aung San Suu Kyi and push for freedom in the military-ruled nation.
The 30-day campaign will see stars such as Will Ferrell, Ellen Page, Judd Apatow, Anjelica Huston, Jennifer Aniston and Rosanna Arquette appearing in video clips on the Internet highlighting human rights issues in Myanmar.
Jorja filmed a video with Eric Szmanda which aired on May 11th (day 11).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Voice For The Animals Foundation</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/voice-for-the-animals/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/voice-for-the-animals/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Voice For The Animals Foundation&amp;rdquo; is devoted to creating respect and empathy for animals through education, rescue, legislation and advocacy.
Events LA City Hall (December 2008) Jorja spoke at LA City Hall to close the elephant exhibit:
 I&amp;rsquo;m really &amp;hellip; I would like to address, specifically, the issue of Billy. The sole surviving elephant at the Los Angeles zoo &amp;lsquo;exhibit.&amp;rsquo; I believe we have all evolved behind this primitive, misguided and brutally cruel containment of elephants.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What a Pair! (2006)</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/what-a-pair/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/what-a-pair/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The whole is more than the sum of its parts.&amp;rdquo; - Aristotle
 What A Pair! is a non-profit 501c3 that was created when a personal tragedy motivated three Hollywood producers to do something to give back. Co-founders Jo Levi DiSante, Jody Price, and Ruth Stalford believe that by partnering the right people with the right organizations, allowing folks to share their talent and expertise, we can make the world a better place and enrich lives.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>