<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>2005 on Fans of Le Fox Library</title>
    <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/tags/2005/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 2005 on Fans of Le Fox Library</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2005 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://jorjafox.net/library/tags/2005/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Guide</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2005/tv-guide-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2005/tv-guide-4/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
D | Double-Ups Ever find yourself puzzled (or elated) when a particular CSI episode features, say, only Grissom (William Petersen) and Nick (George Eads), and is followed the next week by one about only Sara (Jorja Fox) and Catherine (Helgenberger)? Such character divisions occasionally happen because of a production double-up &amp;#8212; when the show&amp;rsquo;s scheduling demands require the series to shoot two episodes simultaneously.
[&amp;hellip;]
X | *X-Files, The* How was the groundbreaking paranormal series CSI&amp;rsquo;s most kindred stylistic spirit?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Zone</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2005/tv-zone/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2005/tv-zone/</guid>
      <description>As CSI&amp;rsquo;s Sara Sidle, she has her hands full of blood, bugs and rotting parts &amp;#8212; but Fox&amp;rsquo;s passion for acting gives her the stomach to cope, as she explains to Jenny.
Over the last five years, CSI has been responsible for some of TV&amp;rsquo;s goriest scenes. From bone cracking autopsies to flesh piercing special effects and horrific murders, there.s no holding back when it comes to blood and guts. Yet star Jorja Fox, who plays Sara Sidle, admits that after five years the realistic looking bodies can still ruin her stomach.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Newswire</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2005/u-s/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2005/u-s/</guid>
      <description>On Nov. 19, Animal Acres, LA&amp;rsquo;s newly opened farm animal sanctuary, will celebrate Thanksgiving with a unique celebration called the &amp;ldquo;Feed A Turkey Ceremony&amp;rdquo; at the sanctuary in Acton, Calif.
At noon, special guests actresses Daryl Hannah and Jorja Fox (from the No. 1 hit television show CSI) will be helping feed the turkeys and speaking about the need to protect ALL animals from cruelty and neglect. Daryl and Jorja, who are vegetarians, are LA&amp;rsquo;s leading celebrity advocates for animals, and their support of Animal Acres is opening hearts and minds to the plight of turkeys and other farm animals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CBS News</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2005/cbs-news/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2005/cbs-news/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
In Thursday night&amp;rsquo;s episode, the sexual tension also continues between Sara Sidle (Jorja Fox) and Gil Grissom (William Peterson).
&amp;ldquo;I don&amp;rsquo;t know if I&amp;rsquo;d throw him out of my bed,&amp;rdquo; Fox says. &amp;ldquo;But I&amp;rsquo;m certainly not chasing him anymore. I think Sara&amp;rsquo;s done with sort of actively trying to pursue Grissom. But, I still think that the window is open if he came to her in several episodes and said that he wanted to start something.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Early Show</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2005/the-early-show-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2005/the-early-show-2/</guid>
      <description>Julie Chen: After six seasons and a pair of spin-offs, &amp;ldquo;CSI:&amp;rdquo; remains a true original. It&amp;rsquo;s still a ratings powerhouse too with nearly 30 million viewers tuning in every week. I sat down with some of the show&amp;rsquo;s stars inside the CSI autopsy room to dissect the secret of their success.
[&amp;hellip;]
Julie Chen: &amp;ldquo;(voiceover)&amp;rdquo; In tonight&amp;rsquo;s episode, the sexual tension also continues between Sara and Grissom.
Julie Chen: In season six you still kinda have a crush on Grissom, right?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NEWS.com.au</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2005/news-com-au/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2005/news-com-au/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
The Reservoir Dogs creator may be known for his fondness for graphic violence, but co-star Jorja Fox says the change in pace under his direction only intensified the emotional stakes.
&amp;ldquo;I was really surprised at how emotional it (the episode) was,&amp;rdquo; she says. &amp;ldquo;There were a couple of times I just had to sort of not cry and I didn&amp;rsquo;t ever imagine that I would get like that.&amp;rdquo;
[&amp;hellip;]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Guide</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2005/tv-guide-7/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2005/tv-guide-7/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
*CSI* PUTS SEX SCENE TO BED
It&amp;rsquo;s not often that CSI mixes business with pleasure, so when exec producer Carol Mendelsohn revealed in the September 25th issue of TV GUIDE that Grissom (William Petersen) and Sara (Jorja Fox) would &amp;ldquo;spend the night together&amp;rdquo; while out of town working on a possible quadruple-murder case, fans took notice. They also took notice when the episode aired on October 20, and there were three body bags but no naked bodies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Early Show</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2005/the-early-show/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2005/the-early-show/</guid>
      <description>Julie Chen: If you can&amp;rsquo;t get enough of TV&amp;rsquo;s hottest drama, CSI:, then you&amp;rsquo;re in luck. Every Friday, we&amp;rsquo;re going to take you behind the scenes to show you how they make it happen. In last night&amp;rsquo;s episode, called &amp;ldquo;Secrets and Flies&amp;rdquo;, star Jorja Fox came face to face with an actor&amp;rsquo;s big challenge: working with a baby. Or did she?
Jorja Fox: The camera comes in, you find a woman who&amp;rsquo;s obviously deceased, you don&amp;rsquo;t know what&amp;rsquo;s happened, there&amp;rsquo;s a pool of blood, and the only other sound in the house is of a baby crying.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Guide</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2005/tv-guide-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2005/tv-guide-6/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
Question: What happened to the Sara-Grissom motel scene that, according to TV Guide&amp;rsquo;s Oct. 1 cover story, was supposed to take place on last Thursday&amp;rsquo;s CSI?! William Peterson wasn&amp;rsquo;t even in that episode! &amp;#8212; Jennifer
Ausiello: There&amp;rsquo;s a really good explanation for this, and I&amp;rsquo;m going to let exec producer Carol Mendelsohn give it to you. &amp;ldquo;Billy had a death in the family and the script was rewritten to accommodate his absence,&amp;rdquo; she says.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Guide</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2005/tv-guide-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2005/tv-guide-5/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
Question: Is it true that Grissom on CSI sleeps with someone on his team this season? If so, please tell me it&amp;rsquo;s not Catherine. &amp;#8212; Susanne
Ausiello: It&amp;rsquo;s not Catherine. At least I don&amp;rsquo;t think it is. It appears producers are heading toward a Sara-Grissom-Sofia triangle instead. Next month, Grissom and Sofia (new series regular Louise Lombard) will share a heart-to-heart in his office, when Sara walks in and thinks she&amp;rsquo;s interrupting something more intimate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MSNBC</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2005/msnbc-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2005/msnbc-3/</guid>
      <description>The ABCs of &amp;lsquo;CSI&amp;rsquo;: Who&amp;rsquo;s dead, who dun it and who solved it.
CSI: Grissom, you lead, we&amp;rsquo;ll follow
[&amp;hellip;]
Sara, do you still work at CSI? Sara is getting less and less screen time this season. Coroner&amp;rsquo;s assistant Super Dave seems to log more screen time than she does. Does a CSI have to get buried alive to rate a little more storyline? Or is it time for Sara to move on to a new lab?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Market Wire</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2005/market-wire/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2005/market-wire/</guid>
      <description>Boots are a fashion must-have this fall and Earth has styles to accompany the biggest fall fashion looks as reported by Style.com, the online home of Vogue and W. The &amp;ldquo;Summit&amp;rdquo; is an over-the-calf, butter-soft Nubuk leather design with fleece trim and full-length laces traveling from the top to the bottom of the boot, blending the Boho and the fur (or faux fur) looks that are all the rage. The &amp;ldquo;Alaska&amp;rdquo; also features fur trim with leather laces that wrap the boot to customize the fit and add style.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Media Post</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2005/media-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2005/media-post/</guid>
      <description>IN AN ATTEMPT TO BUILD a TV audience for its show about first-time home buyers, &amp;ldquo;My First Place,&amp;rdquo; Scripps Networks will Webcast the premiere episode on HGTV.com on Monday, Oct. 17, five days before the show airs on TV. Scripps also has arranged for Webcasts of the show to run on TVGuide.com, said Charity Curley, director of HGTV&amp;rsquo;s Web site.
[&amp;hellip;]
The interviews are designed to &amp;ldquo;sex it up a little bit&amp;rdquo; Curley said, adding: &amp;ldquo;We&amp;rsquo;ve never done any celebrity programming online.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Matters of the Heart</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2005/matters-of-the-heart/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2005/matters-of-the-heart/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s kind of a funny thing about our show, &amp;lsquo;cause I say that the audience is almost split down the middle, where about 50% of the audience really just wants to, they want the stories. They don&amp;rsquo;t wanna get into the characters personal lives all that much. And then the whole other 50% of the audience wants always to know more about the characters. It&amp;rsquo;s a unique conundrum for the writers, and I think they handle it very gracefully and &amp;hellip; they&amp;rsquo;re always disappointing someone and they&amp;rsquo;re always making someone happy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MSNBC</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2005/msnbc-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2005/msnbc-2/</guid>
      <description>The ABCs of &amp;lsquo;CSI&amp;rsquo;: Who&amp;rsquo;s dead, who dun it and who solved it.
[&amp;hellip;]
The crush rears its ugly head again: When Grissom and Sara were processing the upstairs of the Lesters&amp;rsquo; house, there was an awkward moment when Sara said, &amp;ldquo;You don&amp;rsquo;t have to sleep in the same bed to have sex. Or to have romance.&amp;rdquo; Grissom couldn&amp;rsquo;t seem to get out of that room fast enough. Of course, this scene brings up another question I&amp;rsquo;ve had about &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; forever: Why do these guys always use their flashlights instead of just turning on the lights?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>USA Weekend Magazine</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2005/usa-weekend-magazine/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2005/usa-weekend-magazine/</guid>
      <description>What can you tell me about &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rsquo;s&amp;rdquo; Jorja Fox?
Larry Phillips, Bellbrook, Ohio
She grew up &amp;ldquo;a child of the &amp;lsquo;70s&amp;rdquo; in a Florida seaside community. She still loves the ocean, surfing and the outdoors. She played Doris Day&amp;rsquo;s role in her high school production of &amp;ldquo;Pillow Talk&amp;rdquo; and went to New York at 16 to model. She&amp;rsquo;s 37, a guitar player and singer, and she&amp;rsquo;s part of a group of &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; cast and crew members who spend their lunchtime making music.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Guide</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2005/tv-guide-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Sep 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2005/tv-guide-3/</guid>
      <description>What a difference a year (not to mention a coffin, a crazed killer and hundreds of fire ants) has made for CSI.
Last season was a rocky one, both behind and in front of the camera, whether it was one of the stars reportedly being fired and rehired after a contract spat or the show&amp;rsquo;s investigative team suddenly splintering into two squads. Then along came the sizzling season finale, which reunited the teams in order to save a kidnapped Nick (George Eads), who faced certain death trapped in an insect-filled casket.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MSNBC</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2005/msnbc-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2005/msnbc-1/</guid>
      <description>The ABCs of &amp;lsquo;CSI&amp;rsquo;: Who&amp;rsquo;s dead, who dun it and who solved it.
[&amp;hellip;]
Gooey buns with a kick: Sara discovers that one member of her dead couple was using gooey buns to transport cocaine. Now that&amp;rsquo;s original. Sara seems to be enjoying her role as Greg&amp;rsquo;s mentor, when he realizes that they may find the identity of the killer by checking for bite marks in the gooey buns, he tells her, &amp;ldquo;And the student becomes the master.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PETA Gala and Humanitarian Awards</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2005/peta-gala-and-humanitarian-awards/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Sep 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2005/peta-gala-and-humanitarian-awards/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
Jorja Fox I&amp;rsquo;ve been a vegetarian since I was nineteen. I come from like a French-Canadian family who ate meat and potatoes every day, three times a day for my entire youth, and I used to tease the heck out of my friends that were vegetarians, and I had a lot of &amp;lsquo;em, and then when I became a vegetarian I just decided that I was going to try and learn as much I could so that when people teased me, maybe I&amp;rsquo;d have a couple of things to say.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Star</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2005/the-star/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Sep 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2005/the-star/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
As a result, the opportunity to star in a TV show came soon after. Although [Emily Proctor] was having a great time on The West Wing, the lure of being a regular cast member in CSI: Miami was hard to resist. She consulted with her friend, former West Wing cast mate Jorja Fox (who plays Sara Sidle in CSI: Crime Scene Investigation), before accepting the part.
&amp;ldquo;Jorja and I have been friends for years since we did a movie together (called Forever Fabulous),&amp;rdquo; she reveals in a charming Southern accent.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>National Ledger</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2005/national-ledger/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Aug 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2005/national-ledger/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
DEAR STACY: I would like to know more about Jorja Fox of &amp;ldquo;CSI.&amp;rdquo; I think she is a lovely lady. What is her background, and has she played on other shows? I wish they would dress her up more instead of the bland clothes they make her wear. &amp;#8212; R.R., Cleveland
DEAR R.R.: This 37-year-old single actress got her start in modeling after being discovered in a model search in Florida, where she grew up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Star eCentral</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2005/star-ecentral/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2005/star-ecentral/</guid>
      <description>THE cast of CSI: Crime Scene Investigation talks about the show, its appeal and more.
[&amp;hellip;]
Jorja Fox, who plays Sara Sidle, on using her scriptwriting experience to come up with an episode: &amp;ldquo;I was almost going to get to write a script in Season Four. And then I ended up doing a play with my theatre company all year. So I was the one who slacked on that opportunity. Next year, maybe.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CSI Season 5 DVD extras</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2005/csi-season-5-dvd-extras/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2005/csi-season-5-dvd-extras/</guid>
      <description>Jorja Fox All bets are off, and on at the same time. Anything can happen to anybody, there&amp;rsquo;s lines that have been drawn, and uh, it does make it really fascinating.
[&amp;hellip;]
Jorja Fox It, we&amp;rsquo;re split almost down the middle, 50 percent of the people who watch &amp;ldquo;CSI:&amp;rdquo; want more character stuff, and 50 percent of the people who watch the show don&amp;rsquo;t want that much of it, they really like the stories and the science.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Galaxie Magazine</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2005/galaxie-magazine/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2005/galaxie-magazine/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
Meanwhile, Sara has her own share of men to deal with as well. On one hand, there is Grissom, emotionally distant and much older, and on the other is Greg, the young guy who had a crush on Sara a while back.
&amp;ldquo;Haven&amp;rsquo;t we all had crushes at work? Sara has always placed Grissom on a pedestal,&amp;rdquo; reasons Mendelsohn. &amp;ldquo;We found out this season that she didn&amp;rsquo;t have a father figure because her mother murdered her father.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Insider</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2005/insider-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2005/insider-2/</guid>
      <description>On &amp;ldquo;CSI: Crime Scene Investigation,&amp;rdquo; forensics expert Sara Sidle&amp;rsquo;s specialty is element and materials analysis. So, who better to gather some behind-the-scenes material of the hit CBS series than the woman who plays the ambitious investigator &amp;#8212; actress JORJA FOX.
&amp;rdquo;&amp;lsquo;The Insider&amp;rsquo; has given me a camera,&amp;rdquo; Jorja says directly into the lens as she prepares to record every single second of her work day. The result? A video diary that captures candid, albeit tongue-in-cheek, moments of her fellow cast mates.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>People Magazine</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2005/people-magazine/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2005/people-magazine/</guid>
      <description>Which Celebrity&amp;rsquo;s Closet Would You Love To Raid?
[&amp;hellip;]
Jorja Fox (CSI): Prince&amp;rsquo;s. All the sequins and the velvet? That would be fabulous.
[&amp;hellip;]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aversion Magazine</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2005/aversion-magazine/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2005/aversion-magazine/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
Speaking of VIPs, the celebs were out in force on Saturday: Danny De Vito, Cameron Diaz and crush Justin Timberlake, and actors Scott Speedman (Felicity Underworld), Jorja Fox (CSI, Memento), Linda Cardellini (Freaks and Geeks, ER and, Scooby Doo&amp;rsquo;s live-action Velma), and James Duval (Donnie Darko, The Doom Generation), just to name a few were among the festival&amp;rsquo;s big-names who weren&amp;rsquo;t on stage. Former N&amp;rsquo;Syncer JC Chasez had a very large gentleman with him who appeared to be a bodyguard.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Land&#39;s Top Ten Sexiest Men</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2005/tv-land-s-top-ten-sexiest-men/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2005/tv-land-s-top-ten-sexiest-men/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;TV Land&amp;rsquo;s Top Ten&amp;rdquo; is a show about the top ten .
Jorja Fox was on the June 15, 2005 episode for &amp;lsquo;Sexiest Men&amp;rsquo;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Morocco Times</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2005/morocco-times/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2005/morocco-times/</guid>
      <description>Jorja Fox, who plays Sara Sidle on the long-running American television hit series CSI (Crime Scene Investigation), will fulfill her lifelong dream by making a goodwill trip to Morocco early June, said a release of the &amp;ldquo;Friendship Caravan&amp;rdquo; who will coordinate the trip in cooperation with the Embassy of Morocco in Washington.
Cheri Shankar, board member of several non-profit organizations in Los Angeles, California, will join her friend Jorja Fox in her trip to Morocco.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Insider</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2005/insider-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2005/insider-1/</guid>
      <description>If you liked the &amp;lsquo;House on Haunted Hill,&amp;rsquo; then tonight&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; is just for you. TV&amp;rsquo;s hardnosed investigative team encounter dead bodies and deranged patients at a creepy state mental hospital in the hair-raising episode, called &amp;ldquo;Committed&amp;rdquo; (9 p.m. on CBS).
&amp;ldquo;It&amp;rsquo;s a very dark world and creepy in a horror movie kind of way,&amp;rdquo; says star JORJA FOX.
When a brutal murder is committed at a state mental hospital, Jorja&amp;rsquo;s Sara Sidle and Gil Grissom (WILLIAM PETERSEN) are assigned to investigate, and soon realize that only a handful of residents and staff could be responsible for the killing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TeleStar</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2005/telestar/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2005/telestar/</guid>
      <description>Jorja Fox - &amp;ldquo;Marriage? It gives me the shivers!&amp;rdquo;
At 36 years, this New Yorker is an atypical and secritive member of the CSIs. Thanks to this series&amp;rsquo; great acclaim, Jorja Fox achieved great popularity while preserving her mystery.
Tele Star: Recent rumours indicated that you were no longer part of CSI. True or false?
Jorja Fox: Both! In fact, I was fired. But they called me back within a week.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Futon Critic</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2005/the-futon-critic/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Apr 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2005/the-futon-critic/</guid>
      <description>CSI STARS AND PRODUCERS TALK ABOUT THE EXPLOSIVE TWO-HOUR SEASON FINALE OF &amp;ldquo;CSI: CRIME SCENE INVESTIGATION,&amp;rdquo; AND ABOUT WORKING WITH DIRECTOR QUENTIN TARANTINO
Tarantino Discusses Directing the Finale
&amp;ldquo;Grave Danger,&amp;rdquo; the two hour season finale of CSI: CRIME SCENE INVESTIGATION, will be broadcast Thursday, May 19 (8:00-10:00 PM, ET/PT) on the CBS Television Network. In the episode, the CSIs are in a desperate race against time to save a member of their team who has been kidnapped and buried alive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Guide</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2005/tv-guide-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Apr 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2005/tv-guide-2/</guid>
      <description>CSI (Thursday, 9pm/ET, CBS) Lusty lab rat Greg (Eric Szmanda) finally gets his chance to be naked with Sara (Jorja Fox) &amp;hellip; and he decides to be a gentleman?! For reasons that will be spelled out during the epiosde, the two CSIs must take a decontamination shower togeather. And it&amp;rsquo;s Sara, not Greg, who sneaks a peek. Will she wash and tell? Tune in to find out if what happens in the Las Vegas crime lab stays in the Las Vegas crime lab.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CMS Review</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2005/cms-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2005/cms-review/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
However, a more tangible problem that reality television has caused is a heavy increase in unemployment among actors and production crews. I was able to speak with two actresses, Jorja Fox of C.S.I. and Sami Reade an actress with 15 years of experience. They discussed how the changes have affected them and members of the acting and production community.
Jorja Fox explained how many actors, crew members, and writers have lost their jobs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cult Times</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2005/cult-times/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2005/cult-times/</guid>
      <description>She knows a swab from a cotton bud and a Glock from a&amp;hellip; er&amp;hellip; glockenspeil. Jorja Fox looks at the career of CSI Sara Sidle
JORJA FOX took a huge gamble when she left the critically acclaimed West Wing to try out for the CSI pilot. Although she was fascinated by the script, the talented actress was convinced the fledgling series would get cancelled after only eight episodes. Fortunately, Fox&amp;rsquo;s prediction was wrong, but looking back she wasn&amp;rsquo;t even sure she had nailed the role of crime investigator Sara Sidle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Globe and Mail</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2005/the-globe-and-mail/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Mar 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2005/the-globe-and-mail/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
Petersen and several of the members of his cast, such as Marg Helgenberger and Gary Dourdan, have been openly critical of the two CSI spinoffs, saying they dilute the brand. Matters got worse when two of the original CSI actors, Jorja Fox and George Eads, were fired (and then rehired) by CBS boss Les Moonves for making excessive wage demands. Hostility heightened between the show&amp;rsquo;s financiers (CBS and Toronto-based co-producer Alliance Atlantis) and its cast, half of whom got raises while the remainder did not, leaving more than a few bruised egos.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Guide</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2005/tv-guide-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2005/tv-guide-1/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
Question: I keep hearing rumors about a CSI episode taking place in London. Any truth? - Shelly
Ausiello: Yes and no. It was planned originally for November sweeps, but then all the cast upheaval squeezed the schedule and made it impossible. So, not only did George and Jorja screw themselves out of a raise, but their antics cost them - and their costars - a free trip across the pond as well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E Online</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2005/e-online-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2005/e-online-2/</guid>
      <description>OscarBit
I took a little (and I mean little) poll recently on Oscar ringleader and staunch Jamie Foxx-supporter Chris Rock. I asked this of a coupla famous performers: &amp;ldquo;Should a major Awards emcee be impartial or not?&amp;rdquo;
Jorja Fox of CSI: &amp;ldquo;Yes. But I think that folks should be good-humored about hosts making jokes and things.&amp;rdquo;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E Online</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2005/e-online-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2005/e-online-1/</guid>
      <description>You know, our lusty celebs used to have bigger problems than choosing between Prada and Oscar de la Renta. Hard to believe, I know, but most every actor wannabe has struggled with a (lack of) cash flow.
Back ovah at the SAG Awards, I asked a couple of work-steady folks, who have maybe forgotten about their days o&amp;rsquo; struggle, what was the most bizarre thing they&amp;rsquo;ve done to get their costly SAG dues paid?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Backstage.com</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2005/backstage-com/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2005/backstage-com/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
The winner for heaviest award goes to&amp;hellip;: Almost every actor who received a SAG Award felt the need to comment on the weight of the statue. Rush lifted his with one arm and noted, &amp;ldquo;My right bicep will be noticeably bigger now because this is really heavy.&amp;rdquo; CSI&amp;rsquo;s Jorja Fox, backstage with her fellow cast members, remarked, &amp;ldquo;We&amp;rsquo;re all going to be bruised tomorrow because we keep hitting each other with these.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ET Online</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2005/et/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2005/et/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
Mark also catches up with JORJA FOX, who reveals, &amp;ldquo;This is my favorite set on the show. It is a graphic, gruesome place.&amp;rdquo;
Jorja also fills Mark in that no animals or insects have ever been hurt on the show. They are under the protection of a Humane Society representative who makes sure they are well taken care of and that they recently switched the company that supplies their gloves.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>US Today</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2005/us-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2005/us-today/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
Petersen&amp;rsquo;s shortened workday is evident in tonight&amp;rsquo;s episode, &amp;ldquo;Nesting Dolls,&amp;rdquo; which intertwines domestic abuse with mail-order brides. However, his scenes are significant, marking one of the rare occasions in which CSI goes home with a character to peel back layers of personality.
In the episode, Grissom visits the apartment of suspended subordinate Sara Sidle (Jorja Fox) to ask why the abuse case triggered an outburst that endangered her job.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>US Weekly</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2005/us-weekly/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jan 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2005/us-weekly/</guid>
      <description>CSI&amp;rsquo;s Jorja Fox
&amp;bull; Bio 36; born in New York, grew up in Melbourne Beach, Florida; currently single
&amp;bull; Offscreen style &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m edgier than [my character],&amp;rdquo; confesses L.A. resident Fox. On her down days, she slips into 7 for All Mankind jeans and boots. But for going out, she favors outfits by BCBG, Prada or Theory. &amp;ldquo;BCBG fits me really well, and I can wear most of it off the rack,&amp;rdquo; the star tells Us.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Defamer</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2005/defamer/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2005/defamer/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
 Jorja Fox at WeHo Marix (cuter in person; if you like girls, i mean). Bend It Like Beckham&amp;rsquo;s Parminder Nagra at Buddah&amp;rsquo;s Belly (very cute and put-together in person,). [&amp;hellip;]  [&amp;hellip;]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Whittier Daily News</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2005/whittier-daily-news/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2005/whittier-daily-news/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
A hundred or so hearty fans -or maybe foolhardy fans -stood under umbrellas across the street from the Pasadena Civic Auditorium where in other years several hundred of screaming fans would gather to greet the stars in their caravan of limousines.
White canvas tenting sheltered fans lucky enough to get bleacher seats, as well as the pampered and preened stars.
&amp;ldquo;It&amp;rsquo;s one of those days you want to stay in, watch a movie, eat takeout, but this is too good to pass up,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; co-star Jorja Fox said in the hallway before the show started.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kern Valley Sun</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2005/kern-valley-sun/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2005/kern-valley-sun/</guid>
      <description>The Kern County District Attorney&amp;rsquo;s Office will hold &amp;ldquo;Crime Lab Day on Thursday, Jan. 13 at the DA&amp;rsquo;s Forensic Science Division, 1300 18th St. in Bakersfield. The DA&amp;rsquo;s office will have three celebrities from the hit television series &amp;ldquo;CSI: Crime Scene Investigation&amp;rdquo; at the event: Jorja Fox (who plays criminalist Sara Sidle), David Berman (Assistant Coroner David Phillips) and co-producer Josh Berman. The public is invited to participate in self-guided tours of the lab from 9 a.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>&#39;My First Place: Celebrity Style</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2005/my-first-place-celebrity-style/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2005/my-first-place-celebrity-style/</guid>
      <description>HGTV, in a interesting move, released excerpts from it&amp;rsquo;s new show &amp;ldquo;&amp;lsquo;My First Place: Celebrity Style&amp;rdquo;&amp;rsquo; online.
Jorja Fox was filmed for an upcoming episode and her quote on the main page is as follows:
 I was a bad teenager. I had to get out of there. My family was very old-fashioned and I knew quite young that I needed to get my own place. I was 16. I moved in with my friends.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>News Articles (2005)</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2005/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2005/</guid>
      <description>Date Source    January 05 Kern Valley Sun   January 09 Whittier Daily News   January 26 Defamer   January 28 US Weekly   February 02 US Today   February 03 ET Online   February 08 Backstage.com   February 10 E Online   February 17 E Online   March 09 TV Guide   March 19 The Globe and Mail   March 24 Cult Times   April 01 CMS Review   April 10 TV Guide   April 25 The Futon Critic   April 27 TeleStar   April 28 Insider   May 02 Morocco Times   May 23 Aversion Magazine   May 30 People Magazine   June 09 Insider   July 01 Galaxie Magazine   July 03 Star eCentral   August 27 National Ledger   September 04 The Star   September 22 MSNBC   September 25 TV Guide   October 02 USA Weekend Magazine   October 06 MSNBC   October 11 Market Wire   October 11 Media Post   October 13 MSNBC   October 19 TV Guide   October 26 TV Guide   November 07 TV Guide   November 16 NEWS.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>