<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tabloids on Jorja Fox Library</title>
    <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/tags/tabloids/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Tabloids on Jorja Fox Library</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 19 Sep 2004 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://jorjafox.net/library/tags/tabloids/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Star Magazine</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/star-magazine/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Sep 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2004/star-magazine/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;For three years, CSI investigators Sara Sidle (played by Jorja Fox, 34) and Warrick Brown (Gary Dourdan, 37) have worked side by side, exchanging polite professional words. But at the People&amp;rsquo;s Choice Awards on Jan 11, the actors Fox and Dourdan snuck off repeatedly to hold hands and share smokes. The couple was spotted kissing by several backstage guests. &amp;#8216;They couldn&amp;rsquo;t keep their hands off each other,&amp;rsquo; a backstage photographer tell Star. Hmmm, looks suspicious. Dourdan&amp;rsquo;s publicist, Jerry Weinman, tells Star , &amp;#8216;They&amp;rsquo;re co-stars on TV&amp;rsquo;s number one show and sure, they&amp;rsquo;ve friends, but that&amp;rsquo;s all. That&amp;rsquo;s as far as their affection for each other goes.&amp;rsquo; Maybe..maybe not. Twice, an eyewitness tells Star, a handler at the event had to step in to tell the couple to stop touching each other. We&amp;rsquo;re not going to call this case closed, but as they say on CSI, &amp;#8216;The evidence never lies.&amp;rsquo;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>National Examiner</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2003/national-examiner/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2003/national-examiner/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;There&amp;rsquo;s a battle royal going on behind the scenes at CSI: Crime Scene Investigation &amp;#8212; should Gil Grissom leap into the sack with Sara Sidle?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fans of TV&amp;rsquo;s top-rated show, now in its fourth season, think it&amp;rsquo;s a pretty hot drama. But backstage fights over what should happen between the characters played by William Petersen and Jorja Fox make the on-screen happenings seem like winter in Antarctica, say insiders.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;The production team has been torn apart,&amp;rdquo; a source says.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;One group believes workaholic Grissom is so emotionally stunted that he could never have an affair and that&amp;rsquo;s the way he should be played.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;But the rival faction is campaigning for some action between the sheets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;They point out that after all, it&amp;rsquo;s unrealistic to believe that when two available people flirt so much it won&amp;rsquo;t lead to an affair.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;To have them flirt without a sexy outcome is like kissing your sister, and the viewers will start to yawn, they say.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The stars who play the two characters involved can&amp;rsquo;t agree on how far to take things, either.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Petersen, 50, wants the pair to explore their growing attraction, as long as it doesn&amp;rsquo;t turn the show into a soap opera, say insiders.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But Fox, 35, believes that although their constant flirting is a great dynamic for creating tension, a segue into sex would detract from the show&amp;rsquo;s strong stories.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She admits she&amp;rsquo;ll be making goo-goo eyes at Grissom for the foreseeable future.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;I think we&amp;rsquo;re going to have a very personal year for the characters,&amp;rdquo; she reveals, &amp;ldquo;more-so that we&amp;rsquo;ve ever done.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The backstage bickering over the steamy issue has spilled onto the Internet, where fans are airing their opinions online. And now that the new CSI season is in full swing, the debate is healing up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One group of fans even posted an open letter to the shows producers, urging them to press ahead with the Grissom-Sara love match.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;We feel that a relationship would provide a human element to the show,&amp;rdquo; the petition says.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Other online fans agreed, licking their lips at the prospect of the two stodgy characters getting intimate for a change.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But some viewers are squarely against pairing up the investigators in the bedroom.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;It does nothing for the show,&amp;rdquo; one disappointed fan complains.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>