<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Missing Persons on Fans of Le Fox Library</title>
    <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/tags/missing-persons/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Missing Persons on Fans of Le Fox Library</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 17 Feb 1994 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://jorjafox.net/library/tags/missing-persons/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>What Do You Want, a Signed Confession ... ?</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/mp/what-do-you-want-a-signed-confession/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 1994 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/mp/what-do-you-want-a-signed-confession/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Bobby is still under investigation for a suspected bribe and perverting the course of justice. Also a little girl, Molly Jewett, is snatched in a department store.
Connie Karadzic Review Connie works with Carlos and Johnny to find the missing girl. Connie interviews the mother, keeping her company while Carlos and Johnny search the building. They find Molly&amp;rsquo;s jacket, and evidence she hasn&amp;rsquo;t been taken from the store.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tell Me You Didn&#39;t Do It ... I&#39;ll Go to the Wall for You</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/mp/tell-me-you-didnt-do-it-ill-go-to-the-wall-for-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 1994 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/mp/tell-me-you-didnt-do-it-ill-go-to-the-wall-for-you/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Ellen is making her mark on the department, buying doughnuts, making coffee, and being paired with Bobby on a seemingly straightforward parolee disappearance. Until Bobby is framed.
Connie Karadzic Review Connie looks into the case of David Roberts, 21-year old who is missing ten days from an upper Lakeview apartment. Mrs. Roberts explains that she and her son hadn&amp;rsquo;t talked in 3 years after his father threw him out for being gay.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>All They Had to Do Was Ask...</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/mp/all-they-had-to-do-was-ask/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Feb 1994 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/mp/all-they-had-to-do-was-ask/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Ray is shocked when he is told his ex-partner is being transferred into his department. Problem is she is female and rumours were rife that they were having an affair. Meanwhile a boy goes missing from party of schoolchildren on a museum tour.
Connie Karadzic Review Connie works the case of a disoriented woman brought in by a cabbie with no wallet, purse or ID, claiming her name is Minerva Fitzhugh.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Beautiful Son is Okay</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/mp/my-beautiful-son-is-okay/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 1994 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/mp/my-beautiful-son-is-okay/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Johnny and Connie look for two little boys who went missing on their way home from school, while Bobby has the mysterious disappearance of a woman he met on a recent case on his hands. Carlos, Anita, Ray and Barbara spend the whole episode worrying about baby Carlito Ray who is sick.
Connie Karadzic Review Two boys, Joel and Ronnie, were playing along the railroad tracks, accidentally end up stuck in a grain car when the train pulls out of the depot.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I&#39;ve Got a Siren</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/mp/ive-got-a-siren/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 1994 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/mp/ive-got-a-siren/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Connie helps a girl who is having a baby and is missing her boyfriend Jake, while Bobby meets an actress who models herself on Lauren Bacall and has driven her husband away with her constant role-playing games. Johnny is assigned desk duty after his father is investigated by internal affairs.
Connie Karadzic Review While interviewing Tamara Thorpe, the pregnant woman goes into labor and Connie rushes her to the hospital but it&amp;rsquo;s a false alarm.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>If You Could Pick Your Own Parents</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/mp/if-you-could-pick-your-own-parents/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 1994 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/mp/if-you-could-pick-your-own-parents/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Marsha and Phil Koppelman live upstairs from an older couple who don&amp;rsquo;t show up for a planned dinner. When Phil goes to check on them, he finds Bernice collapsed and Myron missing. Carlos goes looking for Myron, while Johnny looks for the full identity of a man named Dave, last seen leaping off a bridge. Connie has to sort through a high number of missing reports, most of them probably caused by a massive accident on the subway that has tied up trains for hours.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Hard Is It Just to Get Off at the Next Exit?</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/mp/how-hard-is-it-just-to-get-off-at-the-next-exit/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 1993 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/mp/how-hard-is-it-just-to-get-off-at-the-next-exit/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis A woman sees her missing son as she rides the bus, but by the time she gets off, he&amp;rsquo;s gone. Carlos goes to help the woman. Bobby looks for a missing express delivery man, while a councilman leans on Ray for a favor when his best-friend&amp;rsquo;s daughter goes missing right before her wedding. Johnny helps his family when his father, also a police officer, is shot.
Connie Karadzic Review Connie helps Ray on his case, interviewing Cilla&amp;rsquo;s fiancee while Ray talks with the parents.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Right Neighborhood ... Wrong Door</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/mp/right-neighborhood-wrong-door/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Dec 1993 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/mp/right-neighborhood-wrong-door/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Bobby helps his mother with a private matter when a member of her church goes missing. Connie looks into habitual runaway and train hopper, Joey Pender (age 8). Johnny looks into a missing rich Lake Shore Drive accountant.
Connie Karadzic Review While Joey has hopped on busses and trains before, he always turns himself in at the Kedzie station. His father is a long-distance truck driver, and since his mother makes a big deal about when his father comes home, Joey decided the best way to get attention was to go away.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sometimes You Can&#39;t Help Getting Involved</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/mp/sometimes-you-cant-help-getting-involved/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Nov 1993 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/mp/sometimes-you-cant-help-getting-involved/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Connie and Carlos both have to find missing children. Connie&amp;rsquo;s case is a 4-year old who disappeared at nursery school, and Carlos&amp;rsquo;s is an 8-year old, who is later found badly beaten. When an ex-school friend of Ray&amp;rsquo;s, who had been injured in an accident many years ago resulting in him have the mental age of a 6-year old, is accused of the beating, Ray breaks his own number 1 rule and becomes personally involved trying to clear him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I&#39;m Gonna Miss Him Too</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/mp/im-gonna-miss-him-too/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Nov 1993 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/mp/im-gonna-miss-him-too/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis A young boy runs away from home, returning to take his little brother with him, after his potential stepfather steals from their home and blames it on him, and then threatens his life. Connie has to trace the family of an heroic John Doe who saved a little girl&amp;rsquo;s life, in order to find out what his medical problems are, and along the way feels some chemistry with the surgeon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Some People&#39;s Priorities ...</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/mp/some-peoples-priorities/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Nov 1993 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/mp/some-peoples-priorities/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Bobby&amp;rsquo;s case of a missing dental student who apparently fell into voodoo returns when the parents decide they do want to find their wayward daughter, but she may be a victim of a serial killer. Connie looks into the case of a missing Indian woman who has been missing nine days. Johnny has a Tender Age case of an eleven year-old who went missing from a double-parked car in Lincoln Park.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Man&#39;s an Emotional Termite</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/mp/the-mans-an-emotional-termite/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 1993 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/mp/the-mans-an-emotional-termite/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis A girl living with her grandmother in Cabrini Green and goes missing, while an older man loses his family following a vacation, and another young girl into voodoo goes missing.
Connie Karadzic Review Connie works the case of a forgetful man who has lost his family following a month vacation. Victor Deely&amp;rsquo;s son Karl had gone to Florida but never returned. Victor presses Connie to learn about her personal life, and gets cagey when she says they&amp;rsquo;ll have to search his house.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>That&#39;s My Sister, Pal</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/mp/thats-my-sister-pal/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 1993 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/mp/thats-my-sister-pal/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis While Connie and Carlos investigate the disappearance of a young Latino newly arrived from Mexico, Johnny has assigned himself an &amp;#8220;unofficial&amp;#8221; case. He thinks Connie&amp;rsquo;s husband is cheating on her and decides to find out for sure. Enlisting an unwilling Bobby, who is working a case involving the disappearance of a middle-aged widower, they find out more than they want to know. Ray, contacted by the wife of a missing old colleague of his, has to find the man.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Can&#39;t Even Imagine</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/mp/i-cant-even-imagine/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 1993 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/mp/i-cant-even-imagine/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Connie works the case of Anne Conlin, whose parents find her apartment stripped clean, and Anne never got off the plane after a three month trip to Europe. Johnny works a case of kids who goe missing after a party on the South Side. Carlos hunts down Jerome Vincent, whose car is found abandoned in a parking lot with a suicide note, but no body. Meanwhile Bobby tries to find his mother the perfect birthday present.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>People Don&#39;t Talk to Cops, People Lie to Cops</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/mp/people-dont-talk-to-cops-people-lie-to-cops/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 1993 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/mp/people-dont-talk-to-cops-people-lie-to-cops/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis A young boy goes missing from his backyard, which Bobby works on. Johnny looks into a husband gone missing, and Connie works on a wife who vanished after shopping. In all three cases, the families declare that there&amp;rsquo;s nothing unsavory about their missing loved ones or themselves.
Connie Karadzic Review Connie brings in bagels instead of donuts, causing complaints from some of the other cops who aren&amp;rsquo;t as pleased about the health kick.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cabe?... What kind of name is that?</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/mp/cabe-what-kind-of-name-is-that/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 1993 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/mp/cabe-what-kind-of-name-is-that/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis A two year-old named Caleb (which Ray mishears as &amp;lsquo;Cabe&amp;rsquo;) is found wandering alone in a forest preserve. Ray and Barbara take him home until Carlos can find the parents. Bobby is assigned a missing 19 year old Phillipino who is embroiled in gang-related narcotics trafficking. Connie looks for a mysterious philanthropist, Mr. Hodgekiss. who suddenly disappeared while out for his nightly constitutional. Johnny gets dead body detail. He has to identify a homeless person found face down in an alley.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pilot (Missing Persons)</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/mp/pilot/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Aug 1993 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/mp/pilot/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis In the two hour premiere of Missing Persons, we meet the detectives of Chicago&amp;rsquo;s Missing Persons Bureau.
Det. Johnny Sandowski searches for a four year-old Polish girl who vanished after being separated from her mother on an &amp;#8220;El&amp;#8221; train. Det. Bobby Davison is assigned a missing University of Chicago co-ed. Det. Sgt. Carlos Marrone tracks a patient who has possibly wandered off from the convalescence home where she lived.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>