<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>2007 on JFO Library</title>
    <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/tags/2007/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 2007 on JFO Library</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2007 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://jorjafox.net/library/tags/2007/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Chicago Sun-Times</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/chicago-sun-times-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/chicago-sun-times-2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;REVIEW | Dazzling visuals set pace for TV procedurals, making departure of Fox or anyone else secondary&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jorja Fox fans surely will be bummed when &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; returns with a new episode tonight. Fox left the show a few weeks ago, and she took away her character, Sara Sidle. But don&amp;rsquo;t expect &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; to suffer much because, duh, the true star of America&amp;rsquo;s No. 1 drama is its sci-fi special effects.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And Fox &amp;#8212; who was named the 80th sexiest woman in the world by Stuff magazine in 2003 &amp;#8212; was great in her best moments. But she too was just a cog in the wheel of an ensemble show that (like &amp;ldquo;Law &amp;amp; Order&amp;rdquo;) barely notices its detectives have personal lives, including Sara&amp;rsquo;s long affair with Grissom.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This expensive style is taken for granted, since it&amp;rsquo;s changed the style of the TV procedural. But it&amp;rsquo;s really quite extraordinary. Several weeks ago, a guy was decapitated while racing a go-cart behind an 18-wheeler on a road. But you didn&amp;rsquo;t see the decapitation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Instead, the scene opened with a head in a helmet bouncing down the road, as the camera perspective swirled around it and the &amp;ldquo;Blue Danube&amp;rdquo; waltz toyed to the rhythm of the bounces.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This was played neither for drama nor for comedy. It was just a dash of commercial art, a form of art that at top form, like this, defends the capitalization of art.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Where &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; goes dumb is in the easy confessions cops get out of criminals. And the personal stories of detectives are too rare to give the show much depth.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That said, Sara&amp;rsquo;s departure brought about a sweet scene where Fox portrayed quiet despair. When she finally split the Las Vegas cop shop, Fox commanded long and lovely little scenes for Sara to just be, to just sit, to deteriorate on camera.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Buddy TV</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/buddy-tv-12/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/buddy-tv-12/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Though Sara Sidle has already left &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo;, fans of the forensic drama are still determined to convey their support to her portrayer, Jorja Fox.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Previously, fans combined their efforts to come up with a &amp;ldquo;Jorja Fox Appreciation Campaign&amp;rdquo; to prevent the 39-year-old actress from leaving the show. When Fox officially exited the CBS series, the excess money raised by the crusade was donated to charity. And now that the campaign is over, a new drive is being created that aims to thank the former &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; actress.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Thanking Jorja&amp;rdquo; is the latest gesture of gratitude instigated by the Fox&amp;rsquo;s fans. Instead of sending messages to CBS about Fox leaving &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo;, her supporters are now participating in a letter-writing campaign that invites fans to send stories and photos to be included in a scrapbook for the actress. The project also encourages fans to share stories about how they came to know Fox, how she has inspired their lives, their favorite &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; episode she was in, and other stories that express their appreciation for the actress.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fox, who left the show after seven yeas of playing the forensic scientist, is presently enjoying her break from the commitment of a weekly television series but also fears that quitting the hit series might be &amp;ldquo;the biggest mistake of her life.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;ve been thinking about leaving for a year and a half. I had to get up the courage. Maybe I&amp;rsquo;m just having a midlife crisis. Maybe this will be the worst decision I ever make,&amp;rdquo; Fox told the New York Post.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Theater is one of my loves, so I&amp;rsquo;m open for that after 11 and a half years of working in primetime TV for &amp;ldquo;ER&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;The West Wing&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo;. I&amp;rsquo;ve never been to college, and I think about that. But I kept putting it off, and I am also thinking about having a child, and that&amp;rsquo;s really important. Also, I want to do a lot of traveling and surfing - two of my hobbies. I have a one-woman little play about Dusty Springfield opening February 2 at the Renberg Theater in Hollywood,&amp;rdquo; Fox added.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Guide</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/tv-guide-27/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/tv-guide-27/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Question: Just wanted to thank you for your recent comments about &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; and Jorja Fox. Your response to Sandra S.&amp;rsquo; question about whether Grissom and Sara&amp;rsquo;s relationship hurt &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; was the most accurate evaluation of their romance and the last couple of seasons of the show that I&amp;rsquo;ve read. It was nice to see someone in the media not jumping on the &amp;ldquo;they turned the show into a soap opera!&amp;rdquo; bandwagon, which so many fans inexplicably have joined. Personally, I wonder if the &amp;ldquo;soap opera&amp;rdquo; people are watching the same show I&amp;rsquo;ve been watching.&amp;ndash; Melanie&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Matt Roush:&lt;/strong&gt; There is no trickier tightrope to walk in series TV than for those procedurals that balance casework with personal stories. Some of these shows do turn into soap operas, but I feel classic &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; managed to add these elements more successfully than most, without significantly altering or ruining the show. Which doesn&amp;rsquo;t stop people from obsessing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Take this over-the-top reaction from Barb C.: &amp;ldquo;I would suggest you visit the &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; message boards and chat rooms to get viewers&amp;rsquo; reaction; people are very disappointed with how Sara&amp;rsquo;s departure was written. Fans are angry and feel it was such a letdown. There was an indication a possible marriage could occur because of the proposal, but it did not. What were the writers thinking! It was not believable that she simply would kiss him, then go to her locker, remove her name badge and call a cab before Grissom goes looking for her. Now fans are losing interest and are planning to boycott the show. The whole storyline of Grissom and Sara was so popular and fans are not happy about this. Maybe the writers&amp;rsquo; strike will give them time to get their creative juices flowing again. I plan on watching the reruns and will return when I know that Grissom and Sara are together again.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks for the invitation, but it&amp;rsquo;s precisely because of overheated reactions like this that I tend to avoid message boards and chat rooms. An informed fan of the show would know that this departure was Jorja Fox&amp;rsquo;s decision, not the producers&amp;rsquo;. And while it may have been a mistake to dangle the proposal storyline as a possibility when it was already known she was leaving the show, the fact that the writers attempted to explain her departure in psychological rather than melodramatic or romance-novel terms impressed me. What, you&amp;rsquo;d rather they&amp;rsquo;d killed her in the cliffhanger? You should see the crazy mail I keep getting from those who can&amp;rsquo;t get over Prison Break killing off the Sara Tancredi character. Face it: She&amp;rsquo;s gone. I agree that the way they offed her was disgusting and insulting, and in this case, it may well be the sort of thing that could turn some people off the show forever. (I had already made my own escape, thank you.) But the idea that &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; fans en masse will boycott the show because of Sara&amp;rsquo;s departure? Not likely.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Guide</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/tv-guide-21/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/tv-guide-21/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Question: There has been speculation that in last week&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo;, the letter Sara left for Grissom wasn&amp;rsquo;t a breakup letter but a suicide note. Do you know anything about this? &amp;ndash; Ginny&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ausiello:&lt;/strong&gt; I know that&amp;rsquo;s a pretty silly theory, considering what Carol Mendelsohn told me last month.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The View</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2007/the-view/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Nov 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2007/the-view/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; Thank you, so honored to be here with all of you. &amp;ldquo;(to Whoopi)&amp;rdquo; And happy birthday to you, a day late.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Joy:&lt;/strong&gt; You&amp;rsquo;ve been here a few times&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; This is my fourth round. Second time in the hot seat &amp;ldquo;(pats the table)&amp;rdquo;, and I&amp;rsquo;m just very excited. And awake.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Whoopi:&lt;/strong&gt; Yeah. Well awake isn&amp;rsquo;t always important. Me, halfway. But let me ask you - you, you&amp;rsquo;re about to make a big change in your life, are you not?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; Yeah, change has come, a little bit. Ah, there&amp;rsquo;s a show on tomorrow night, &amp;ldquo;CSI:&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;(clips playing in the background from &amp;ldquo;[[Goodbye and Good Luck]]&amp;ldquo;)&amp;rdquo;, it&amp;rsquo;s a very very very big show for my character, Sara Sidle, and um, it&amp;rsquo;s one of those things, you know, everybody has times in their lives, and I&amp;rsquo;m speaking about the character right now, where you wake up in the morning, and you think your day&amp;rsquo;s going to be like any other, and by the time the sun has set your life has been changed forever. So, that&amp;rsquo;s all I&amp;rsquo;ll say about it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sherri:&lt;/strong&gt; Excellent.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Joy:&lt;/strong&gt; Things change &amp;ldquo;(snapping her fingers)&amp;rdquo; just like that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; Life&amp;hellip; does that to people.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Whoopi:&lt;/strong&gt; And, how about you, Jorja, you looking for other things also to occupy time or you going to take a break?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; I&amp;rsquo;ve been &amp;ldquo;so&amp;rdquo; fortunate, I&amp;rsquo;ve been eleven and a half years consistently on primetime TV, I was pretty young when I started, and, um, I&amp;rsquo;m just sort of at a place in my life where I want to breathe for a second, take a look around, uh, there&amp;rsquo;s a lot of thing I&amp;rsquo;d &amp;ldquo;love&amp;rdquo; to do, like-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Joy:&lt;/strong&gt; Like what?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; Um, well I&amp;rsquo;d love to take a surfing trip through the southern hemisphere-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Joy:&lt;/strong&gt; Oh, me too, I&amp;rsquo;ve been dying to do that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;ldquo;(laughs)&amp;rdquo; It&amp;rsquo;s summer. One of the upsides, I can date the cast now, &amp;ldquo;finally&amp;rdquo;, after seven and a half years. I can date the cast.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Joy:&lt;/strong&gt; Is there anyone in particular you want to date?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; There&amp;rsquo;s a couple I might start with, yeah, that are still hanging on to being single, I can think of one or two.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sherri:&lt;/strong&gt; Does the audience know that you are, uh, leaving?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; Um, maybe, maybe yes, maybe no, I mean yes, certainly&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Joy:&lt;/strong&gt; Oh, you don&amp;rsquo;t know yet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; Well, something&amp;rsquo;s gonna happen to Sara, what I can say is stay tuned, I believe she&amp;rsquo;ll be back. But as of tomorrow night-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Whoopi:&lt;/strong&gt; We don&amp;rsquo;t know.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; Yeah, and I can&amp;rsquo;t say anything really more than that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Joy:&lt;/strong&gt; There&amp;rsquo;s always so secretive on these shows.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sherri:&lt;/strong&gt; You&amp;rsquo;ve gotta do some stuff.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Whoopi:&lt;/strong&gt; It&amp;rsquo;s gotta be tough.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; Yeah, it&amp;rsquo;s gonna be fun. And interesting. It&amp;rsquo;s harder, it&amp;rsquo;s probably the hardest decision I&amp;rsquo;ve ever made in my life because I never got bored, I love it there so much, I love everyone so much. You guys know when you work with a group every day, and you love those people-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Joy:&lt;/strong&gt; Yeah.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; And you could do that forever.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;ldquo;(commenting on Whoopi&amp;rsquo;s outfit to Sherri)&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;ldquo;(laughs when Sherri does her Tina Turner imitation)&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;ldquo;(gets up and models her outfit for the audience - slinky black slacks, scoop neck black top, gray bolero jacket, black high heel sandals)&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Fashion Specialist:&lt;/strong&gt; And here her jacket is only $29.99&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; I&amp;rsquo;ll do a turn. &amp;ldquo;(turns around for the camera)&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Fashion Specialist:&lt;/strong&gt; The pants are $59.99, for a total - she&amp;rsquo;s wearing her own tank top - for a total, a total of $89.98.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;ldquo;(sitting back down; to Sherri)&amp;rdquo; I wanted to look smart, cause I&amp;rsquo;m not, but I wanted to look smart.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sherri:&lt;/strong&gt; It looks cute.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; Thanks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;ldquo;(reading from her notes)&amp;rdquo; Well the producers said there were three Protestant ministers there, and so maybe next time they do it, it would be great perhaps if there was a wider community, interdenominational, I think people would feel&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sherri:&lt;/strong&gt; Well I think that sometimes when you say, when you say I&amp;rsquo;m praying, or when you talk about God, people get really upset.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; Sensitive.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sherri:&lt;/strong&gt; They get very sensitive about that. And I go, I go what&amp;rsquo;ve you got to lose&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;ldquo;(smiling)&amp;rdquo; And absolutely invite Native American elders, uh, next time, cause if anyone can successfully bring rain&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;ldquo;(commenting to Sherri)&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Whoopi:&lt;/strong&gt; We are back. We are back with our special co-host, today, she&amp;rsquo;s the star of the hit show &amp;ldquo;CSI:&amp;ldquo;, Miss Jorja Fox. Welcome back.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Joy:&lt;/strong&gt; Hey the prompter-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Whoopi:&lt;/strong&gt; They spelled it that way so I would pronounce it correctly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Joy:&lt;/strong&gt; yeah, it&amp;rsquo;s spelled like the state of Georgia, &amp;ldquo;(turning to Jorja)&amp;rdquo; but you spell your name J-o-r-j-a.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; My mother did that. &amp;ldquo;(laughing)&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Joy:&lt;/strong&gt; Wait, it&amp;rsquo;s not a foreign spelling, it&amp;rsquo;s just-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; It&amp;rsquo;s, uh, it&amp;rsquo;s-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Joy:&lt;/strong&gt; -a hippy, dippy spelling maybe?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; Yeah, &amp;ldquo;(grimacing, talking out of the side of her mouth)&amp;rdquo; Yeah, I&amp;rsquo;m a child of the 70&amp;rsquo;s, or somethin&amp;rsquo; close to there, uh. &amp;ldquo;(smiling)&amp;rdquo; It&amp;rsquo;s Jorja-An, my mom was French, it&amp;rsquo;s Jorja-An, and she thought &amp;lsquo;J&amp;rsquo;s would be interesting.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Joy:&lt;/strong&gt; The J&amp;rsquo;s are French.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; No, not necessarily.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sherri:&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;ldquo;(talking about her appearance on &amp;ldquo;Wheel of Fortune&amp;rdquo;)&amp;rdquo; Big check?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; Did you write her a check? Did you write her a check?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; You&amp;rsquo;re so brave. I did &amp;ldquo;Hollywood Squares&amp;rdquo; when you were hosting once, and it was also a charity event, it was for women in Afghanistan, and I was the &amp;ldquo;(sitting up straight for a moment)&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;square&amp;rdquo; square, just praying that nobody would call on me, and I was like &amp;ldquo;please don&amp;rsquo;t call on me, please don&amp;rsquo;t call on me&amp;rdquo;, like there&amp;rsquo;s so much pressure, especially when you&amp;rsquo;re playing for charity, and you&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; Interestingly enough, I think more, more Republicans will come out to vote against Hillary Clinton than they would Barack Obama or John Edwards.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Joy:&lt;/strong&gt; Say that again?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; More Republicans will come out to vote against Hillary Clinton-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Joy:&lt;/strong&gt; Oh.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; -than they would against Obama or, or Edwards.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Joy:&lt;/strong&gt; You think so?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; That&amp;rsquo;s a news poll that I read, so, whereas if, if it&amp;rsquo;s, if it&amp;rsquo;s Obama or it&amp;rsquo;s Edwards, they might be less&amp;hellip; likely to jump out to the polls and say &amp;ldquo;we have to vote &amp;ldquo;against&amp;rdquo; someone&amp;rdquo;. Instead of voting, going out to vote for someone you&amp;rsquo;re going out to vote against someone that you&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; I&amp;rsquo;m glad that there&amp;rsquo;s a bunch of people that I like, you know, I&amp;rsquo;m sort, for me, I tend towards the left, and it&amp;rsquo;s nice to see a group of several people that I&amp;rsquo;m like &amp;ldquo;oh, wow, who&amp;rsquo;s it going to be it&amp;rsquo;s such a hard choice&amp;rdquo;. I&amp;rsquo;m thinking in years past-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Joy:&lt;/strong&gt; Well they could still lose it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; Well one of them, right, one, or someone, will represent the Democrats.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Molly Shannon:&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;ldquo;(to Jorja)&amp;rdquo; I love your new house.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; Thank you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; What did it take you, actually, to get into comedy?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Molly Shannon:&lt;/strong&gt; Oh, who..&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; Yeah, how did, how did you find this life for yourself?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;ldquo;(about Molly Shannon&amp;rsquo;s new film)&amp;rdquo; It&amp;rsquo;s fantastic.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Molly Shannon:&lt;/strong&gt; Thank you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; There&amp;rsquo;s three different parts and they&amp;rsquo;re all you. I mean, usually if you&amp;rsquo;re playing three different parts in the film they&amp;rsquo;re sort of three different people. And you&amp;rsquo;re&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; Well, &amp;ldquo;All My Children&amp;rdquo; is here, &amp;ldquo;Dancing with the Stars&amp;rdquo; is in L.A., you&amp;rsquo;ve been traveling back and forth from coast to coast, how, what was that like for you?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;ldquo;(end of episode)&amp;rdquo; Thank you.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BuddyTV</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/buddy-tv-11/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/buddy-tv-11/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ll preface this by admitting that I was not a big Sara fan. I think I turned against Jorja Fox after the first contract dispute. To me, &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; is more of an ensemble show, so even though I have my favorites, *cough* Warrick *cough*, I resented the impression I got that she thought she was more important than any of the others. Besides that, I kinda wanted Lady Heather to loosen Grissom up a bit. All that being said, I really felt for Sara tonight.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I remember thinking that Sara got her comeuppance the last time she ran into Hannah. She had an air of superiority, that know-it-all aura that really bugged me. This time, and it may have been because of her recent experiences, I saw a vulnerability in her. The writers did a good job of letting us go along for the final ride of Sara Sidle: CSI.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From the beginning of the episode when she was talking with Warrick about not sleeping, we saw a tired Sara. Not just a physically tired Sara, but emotionally tired. The first case, where she disassociated herself, was also another sign. Her final interactions with Hannah and her brother were a perfect way to say goodbye. Brandon was the one that got away and it was because Hannah played her.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She was determined to get them this time, and once she got Brandon, her determination to get Hannah was quite tangible. It was so important to her. But once Brandon committed suicide, her chance at Hannah was gone, legally at least. Making that little girl cry was one thing, but when her new teammate basically made her feel like crap, that was something different. She was losing her humanity, and she knew it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That goodbye letter to Grissom almost had me in tears. It was beautifully done. Watching him read it, hearing her read it, and watching her leave in the taxi was a very fitting end to the episode, and a fitting end to Grissom and Sara. Although the letter ending was quite final, there&amp;rsquo;s that little possibility that at some point she&amp;rsquo;ll return.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Before watching &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; tonight, I was ready to say good riddance to bad rubbish. This episode made me say &amp;ldquo;Fare thee well, Sara&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CTV</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/ctv-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/ctv-2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Last Thursday marked the departure of Sara Sidle (Jorja Fox) from the long-running hit drama &amp;ldquo;CSI.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Appearing as a guest co-host on &amp;ldquo;The View&amp;rdquo; this week, Fox says she&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;fortunate&amp;rdquo; to have been a part of the series. She went on to say that the decision to leave was &amp;ldquo;the hardest decision I ever made.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The actress is an original cast member from debut season in 2000, as a quasi love interest for lead investigator Gil Grissom.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Her departure was featured in an episode entitled &amp;ldquo;Goodbye and Goodnight.&amp;rdquo; Sidle revisits an earlier case in which killer got away.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Over the course of the investigation, Sidle&amp;rsquo;s mind grows dark and bleak &amp;#8212; and she finally makes it clear why she decides to leave the CSI crew.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fox didn&amp;rsquo;t say much about what she has planned next and says she &amp;ldquo;wants to breathe for a second and take a look around.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The actress also joked that now that she&amp;rsquo;s left the show, she can now &amp;ldquo;date the cast.&amp;rdquo; She didn&amp;rsquo;t say which actor she had in mind.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Last season &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; ended with a cliffhanger ending which left Sidle&amp;rsquo;s life in question. Fox reportedly did not show up to film the episode because she was upset at having her character killed off.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The actress returned to film the first eight episodes of this season and producers have indicated her character may return in the future.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chinaview.cn</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/chinaview-cn/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/chinaview-cn/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;After eight seasons on one of TV&amp;rsquo;s highest-rated shows, Jorja Fox left the CBS drama &amp;ldquo;CSI: Crime Scene Investigation&amp;rdquo; Thursday night.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fox, who played Sara Sidle in the hot TV series, has told several publications that she decided not to renew her contract so she could pursue other interests.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;It&amp;rsquo;s one of the hardest decisions I&amp;rsquo;ve made in my life,&amp;rdquo; Fox told Entertainment Weekly. &amp;ldquo;It has nothing to do with my contract, nothing to do with money. &amp;hellip; It could be the stupidest thing I&amp;rsquo;ve ever done in my life. Only time will tell.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fox had a history of butting heads with CBS brass over contract negotiations and was fired in 2004 before coming to an agreement with the network.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After that, her status on the show was the source of rampant rumors up until she confirmed her departure last month.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EFlux Media</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/eflux-media/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/eflux-media/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Goodbye and Good Luck&amp;rdquo; was Jorja Fox&amp;rsquo;s last appearance on the popular CBS series &amp;ldquo;CSI,&amp;rdquo; after a seven-year tenure on the show.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Forensic scientist Sara Sidle, the character Fox had portrayed since 2000, was very popular with fans – so much so that, when the actress was fired in 2004. It was a temporary dismissal, as the public reacted strongly, demanding that she return.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thursday night&amp;rsquo;s episode was the last Fox filmed as Sara Sidle and a worthy farewell for a notable character. Haunted by a suspect from a past case, the CSI ultimately decides to leave her harrowing job behind and sort out her emotional problems away from ever-present crime scenes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The actress talked to Entertainment Weekly in October and clarified that her decision to leave the show had nothing to do with discontent over money or any such things.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;There are all these things I want to do. Some are personal. Some are professional. And I really need to do some of them before I get too old,&amp;rdquo; the 40-year-old actress said. &amp;ldquo;If I thought the show were on its last legs, I would have tried harder to stay the course. But I feel like its going to be around for a while, so if I don&amp;rsquo;t want some of those dreams to pass me by. I have to get off the ride for a while.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fox also revealed that CBS had invited her to stay for the eighth season but she did not wish to prolong her contract, choosing to do only a few more episodes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The actress has also appeared in the NBC television series &amp;ldquo;ER,&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;The West Wing.&amp;rdquo; Her screen credits include &amp;ldquo;Memento,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;Down with the Joneses&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;The Kill-Off.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;According to a bio on CBS&amp;rsquo;s website, Fox is co-founder of Honeypot Productions, an independent theater company in Los Angeles.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Film.com</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/film-com/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/film-com/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; is probably a strong enough concept to survive cast changes, witness the success of the two spinoffs. But until now, its producers and CBS have never had to wonder. The original cast from the pilot episode-Petersen, Helgenberger, George Eads, Gary Dourdan, and Paul Guilfoyle-is still intact. Jorja Fox joined the cast for the second episode, and her Sara Sidle character becomes the first major departure from the show tonight. Sara&amp;rsquo;s disenchantment with the unending parade of crime has been one of the themes to the season so far, so tonight&amp;rsquo;s episode figures to be emotional. Her relationship with Petersen&amp;rsquo;s Grissom, the revelation of which may have been the biggest shocker ever for a show that deals with corpses, was controversial for a subgroup of fans who worried that &amp;ldquo;Grey&amp;rsquo;s Anatomymy&amp;rdquo; might scare the producers into soaping it up, but it has been handled in a way that respects what we&amp;rsquo;ve learned about both characters over eight seasons.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Leaving &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; could not have been an easy decision for Fox, who bounced around TV for years, most notably in a somewhat thankless semi-regular role on &amp;ldquo;ER&amp;rdquo;, before striking gold in Las Vegas. She may not be the last to leave. Petersen in particular has made noises about turning in his bugs, so it might behoove fans to keep looking for little signs, such as Grissom&amp;rsquo;s confession to Anthony LaPaglia&amp;rsquo;s Malone character at the end of last week&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Without a Trace&amp;rdquo; crossover, that &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; might soon be in for its biggest change yet.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Guide</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/tv-guide-14/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/tv-guide-14/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Question: Jorja Fox&amp;rsquo;s last &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; episode just aired, and that got me to thinking about all the brouhaha back when the relationship between Grissom and Sara was revealed in the Season 6 finale. At the time, there were dire predictions that this was the end of the rope for the series. It had become a soap, turned a corner, jumped the shark, etc. Looking back at it now, do you think that the romance &amp;ndash; its reveal, and the way it was woven into Seasons 7 and 8 &amp;ndash; was a detriment to the show? An asset? My personal opinion is that the creators did a very nice job of keeping the relationship believable and not letting it overtake the procedural nature that is the show&amp;rsquo;s hallmark. That said, Season 7 was perhaps one of &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo;&amp;rsquo;s best, not because of the romance storyline but because of the writing (the &amp;ldquo;miniature killer&amp;rdquo; and Liev Schreiber arcs) and the artistic gambles the creators took: dead bodies that spoke, a &amp;ldquo;monster movie&amp;rdquo;-style episode, the incredibly cute &amp;ldquo;clip show&amp;rdquo; featuring the lab rats. &amp;ndash; Sandra S.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Matt Roush: Couldn&amp;rsquo;t agree more. &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; is more nimble than most at balancing the procedural storylines (the real draw on this and nearly every crime franchise) with the personal subplots, which rarely intrude or overtake the series. Not only is &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; among the best of its type at telling clever and creepy crime stories (last season was among its most sustained), but the unusual relationship between Grissom and Sara ranks high as well in terms of the subtlety and complexity of the writing and performances of both William Petersen and Jorja Fox. Rare for this sort of show, the relationship didn&amp;rsquo;t cheapen the series but made the characters that much more intriguing. Allowing Sara to exit with dignity, while leaving the door open for the character to reappear eventually, was also a smart move.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Brandeis Hoot</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/the-brandeis-hoot/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/the-brandeis-hoot/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Wouldn&amp;rsquo;t you if you were married to Mrs. Roper?&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;I don&amp;rsquo;t even have to turn around. Sara Sidle.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With this brief interchange, crime scene investigator Sara Sidle made her first appearance on the CBS hit show, CSI: Crime Scene Investigation. Yesterday, she made her final appearance. After a tumultuous seven years on the show, actress Jorja Fox finally packed up her fingerprint kit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fox enjoyed a long run of success with the show as a materials and element analysis specialist who was originally brought in during the first season by Gil Grissom (actor William Petersen) to do an internal affairs investigation. Sidle ended up staying in Las Vegas for the next seven years (give or take a few episodes in season eight), developing close friendships with her team members and a romantic relationship in season five with Grissom.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Prior to last night&amp;rsquo;s episode, Sidle had been kidnapped by the &amp;ldquo;Miniature Killer&amp;rdquo; as a terrifying message to Grissom, nearly killed, and saved with only dehydration and a broken arm as testament to her story.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since then, Sara has been in the background as the season continues. I thought this was strange as she&amp;rsquo;s my favorite CSI character (after all, I played her in Rocky Horror last year!) and her absence did not go unnoticed. Originally, I believed her absence to be due to the shift change which she had to do because of her relationship with Grissom, as the show centers on the grave shift. Only after I read the article in Entertainment Weekly did I understand what was happening. Sara was being phased out.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Grissom&amp;rsquo;s proposal three weeks ago struck viewers as untimely if the lanky brunette was truly going leave the show. Maybe she would stay. Maybe this was a publicity stunt like when co-star George Eades (Nick Stokes on CSI) and her were fired by CBS for three days. But last night, it happened. Jorja Fox officially vacated her role as Sara Sidle.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First off, I&amp;rsquo;d like to warn all readers of spoilers ahead, so please if you don&amp;rsquo;t want to know what happened yet, stop reading. I sat on my bed, anticipating what was about to come on my television screen at 9 pm sharp. It began with a knife cutting the threads which held Sara&amp;rsquo;s name badge to her CSI vest and the aforementioned character holding the blade, slicing her own name off of the fabric. The scenes with Sara were intercut with the &amp;ldquo;main&amp;rdquo; case of the episode, Catherine and Nick&amp;rsquo;s defenestration. It was a little disappointing, since on her last episode, she should be the center of attention.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sara&amp;rsquo;s dialogue in the first half hour was contrived, clichéd, and to be quite honest, a little boring. Thankfully, she woke up and began to speak normally when she got into the case. The major twist in the episode was the reappearance of former sibling suspects Marlon and Hannah West from the season six episode, &amp;ldquo;The Unusual Suspect&amp;rdquo; in Catherine&amp;rsquo;s case. Sara demands to take over the case, as the original one from season six had haunted her since then. Needless to say, what Sara discovered further pushed her to resign from the crime lab.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I can&amp;rsquo;t stress enough how annoying the little hints that the writers dropped within the episode of Sara&amp;rsquo;s departure were. One of Hannah&amp;rsquo;s lines, which ran, &amp;ldquo;What&amp;rsquo;s wrong, Sara? You&amp;rsquo;re different then you used to be,&amp;rdquo; was only one of the obvious moments. Others were extreme close-ups on Sara in times of high emotion and even one of her own lines when she said that the CSIs would be back to collect the bodies of an abusive couple within a month because there&amp;rsquo;s nothing they could do to change things.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sadly, Jorja&amp;rsquo;s last performance as Sara Sidle seemed very unnatural and the whole episode was not up to the usual standard of the show. However, at least they gave Jorja what she said wanted in an interview three years ago. She kissed William Petersen on the show. Ah, I love those moments. After this touching moment, the show cut back to the beginning of the episode with the removal of her name tag. She wrote &amp;ldquo;good luck&amp;rdquo; on her vest where here name previously was, and threw the tag away. And then she left, leaving Grissom a note telling him how much she loves him but that she was leaving Las Vegas via voice over.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At least they didn&amp;rsquo;t kill her off like previous characters. This writer wishes Jorja good luck in her future endeavors and hopes that she&amp;rsquo;ll avoid the David Caruso post-NYPD Blues curse. And maybe, she&amp;rsquo;ll return to CSI someday, even if it&amp;rsquo;s only as a cameo.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zap2It.com</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/zap2it-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/zap2it-2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Which is the better way to go out, with a bang or a whimper? Unlike its Miami-based counterpart, &amp;ldquo;&lt;strong&gt;CSI&amp;rdquo;&lt;/strong&gt; has never been about the bang. The flagship show&amp;rsquo;s characters are more cerebral, its sets dressed in somber blues. It may have made for better storytelling to have Sara Sidle die at the hands of the Miniature Killer, but her actual departure fit better with the show&amp;rsquo;s sensibilities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[Sara didn&amp;rsquo;t have the sawdust to handle spoilers.]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We open with Sara alone in the dark, cutting at something. The background lights to reveal the LVPD locker room, and then we&amp;rsquo;re at a stereotypical college dorm. Not stereotypical is the girl falling to her death.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Want to see your favorite investigators this week? Too bad. They get less time than when Jack Malone stormed through last week. Instead, we&amp;rsquo;re all about Sara. To that end, the falling girl is connected to Marlon West, the killer from a few years ago whose super-genius little sister threw enough doubt into a jury to ruin Sara&amp;rsquo;s murder case. Now in college, Marlon was dating Kira (this week&amp;rsquo;s corpse) until a very public breakup that ended in a fistfight with Kira&amp;rsquo;s new boy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Supergenius sister Hannah is teaching and doing graduate studies at the same college, and no points for guessing she stymies Sara&amp;rsquo;s investigation again. Unfortunately for Marlon, a chip of his tooth is found in Kira&amp;rsquo;s hand, and Sara figures out (thanks to photos that may as well have giant flashing &amp;ldquo;Clue&amp;rdquo; signs) that Hannah took the chip from the fistfight, drugged Kira&amp;rsquo;s adult-use lubricant, planted the chip in the girl&amp;rsquo;s hand and then pushed her out the window. Why? Because Marlon was drifting away &amp;#8212; also known as developing a normal life &amp;#8212; and Hannah couldn&amp;rsquo;t stand not having him close by at all times.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don&amp;rsquo;t think she thought her cunning plan all the way through. While jail may indeed keep Marlon close, it also proves to be a convenient spot for suicide. Sara gets to destroy Hannah with the news.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Oh, there was a micro-subplot about an abused woman that served only to contrast Ronnie&amp;rsquo;s optimism with Sara&amp;rsquo;s cynicism. Feel free to ignore it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Gil_240 Anyway, at the end Sara pens a very sweet letter for Grissom and then leaves with no set destination. Poor Gil is devastated &amp;#8212; William Petersen&amp;rsquo;s one expression conveys more emotion than Sara has all season.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Really, we see Sara isn&amp;rsquo;t so different from Hannah. Both are brilliant but socially inept and so tend toward overly dramatic but ill-conceived gestures. That was my interpretation, anyway, and for me the heartfelt feelings in the letter were absolutely invalidated by the fact that Sara would rather just run away with no plan.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Albuquerque Tribune</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/albuquerque-tribune/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/albuquerque-tribune/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;For months, we&amp;rsquo;ve all known it was coming - the departure of a beloved &lt;strong&gt;&amp;ldquo;CSI: Crime Scene Investigation&amp;rdquo;&lt;/strong&gt; (8 p.m., KRQE News 13) character.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sara Sidle (Jorja Fox) makes her last appearance in tonight&amp;rsquo;s episode, and mostly this makes me sad.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She&amp;rsquo;s an interesting and complex character who truly bonds with people. I like her eccentricities, and while her hair will never be as cute as Catherine&amp;rsquo;s (Marg Helgenberger), she still manages to look good while knee deep in gross stuff.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The only plus I see in her leaving is that I&amp;rsquo;ll no longer be subjected to the stomach-churning romance between Sara and Grissom (William Petersen).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Seriously, the two of them together easily make the list of worst TV couples ever. They&amp;rsquo;re even more disgusting than Wilhemina and Bradford on &amp;ldquo;Ugly Betty.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Of course, there&amp;rsquo;s always hope that with a little bit of cold, hard cash as an incentive, Sara could reappear, because at least she&amp;rsquo;s not going to die some sort of icky death.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tonight, freakishly smart Hannah (Juliette Goglia) returns to back up her brother, Marlon (Douglas Smith), on yet another violent crime.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The case leads Sara to question her future as a CSI.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She should have started rethinking her profession during that whole &amp;ldquo;likely death at the hands of the miniature killer&amp;rdquo; storyline, but that&amp;rsquo;s just me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So long, Sara. It&amp;rsquo;s been nice knowing you for eight grisly years.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Boston Herald</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/boston-herald-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/boston-herald-2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Fans put through ringer on Jorja Fox&amp;rsquo;s farewell episode&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do the creators of &amp;ldquo;CSI: Crime Scene Investigation&amp;rdquo; enjoy torturing their fans?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jorja Fox&amp;rsquo;s last appearance as a regular (Wednesday night at 9 on WBZ, Ch. 4) was bound to be difficult. &amp;ldquo;Goodbye &amp;amp; Good Luck&amp;rdquo; is excruciating. Given the final moments, the title seems cruelly ironic.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;CBS has asked that I refrain from any potential spoilers. If the network were serious, it would have gagged both Fox and the &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; producers weeks ago. It&amp;rsquo;s no secret that Fox&amp;rsquo;s investigator Sara Sidle lives to see another day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As to what kind of day she&amp;rsquo;ll be waking up to, well, that&amp;rsquo;s something viewers will be pondering for some time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In Wednesday night&amp;rsquo;s episode, Sara shows obvious signs of post-traumatic stress disorder, a result of her recent kidnapping.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a battered wife stands in her blood-spattered living room - with a knife stuck in her back - Sara uncharacteristically shows no concern.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When Ronnie (Jessica Lucas) wants to intervene in the case of the brawling couple, Sara replies, &amp;ldquo;We&amp;rsquo;ll be back for her body next month. Or his. Or both.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The case of a co-ed pushed from her dorm room brings Sara back into contact with killer Marlon West (Douglas Smith) and his pint-sized prodigy of a sister, Hannah (Juliette Goglia). Marlon is a student at the college; Hannah is teaching and proves to be just as much a roadblock as she was the first time they crossed paths and helped Marlon escape justice. Sara is determined to right that wrong.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;You are not going to muddy the waters this time,&amp;rdquo; Sara tells the twerp.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Are you sure you&amp;rsquo;d know if I had?&amp;rdquo; Hannah replies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hannah, improbably, seems to be the only one to realize Sara is imploding emotionally.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At a key moment late in the episode, Sara walks into the CSI offices and plants a kiss on Gil Grissom (William Petersen). It&amp;rsquo;s a moment that will make devoted fans of the show squeal - until they realize, as Gil does, too late, that Sara is saying farewell.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The top-rated show about forensic detectives made the Sara/Grissom relationship the greatest mystery of the series. Viewers followed a faint trail of crumbs over the years that led to the reveal of their relationship. Sara&amp;rsquo;s moments tonight with Grissom are, in the tradition of the series, short and maddeningly frustrating.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fox decided not to renew her contract, but she deserved a better sendoff than this. The nature of her departure will stab at the hearts of viewers. But there remains a chance she could return.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Someday.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>