<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Politics on Jorja Fox Library</title>
    <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/tags/politics/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Politics on Jorja Fox Library</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="http://jorjafox.net/library/tags/politics/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Artists &amp; Athletes Alliance</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/artists-athletes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/artists-athletes/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The &amp;lsquo;Artists and Athletes Alliance&amp;rsquo; assists artists and athletes in navigating the halls of government, as well as helping them better understand the political process. By providing top-line educational information to artists and athletes through one-on-one meetings, private briefings, roundtable discussions, forums and other related events on the specific public policies and political issues of interest to them, the Alliance hopes to engage in productive dialogue with lawmakers, policymakers and opinion-leaders so the voices of the artistic and athletic community can be heard on the many important issues facing our nation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jorja serves on the Artists &amp;amp; Athletes Advisory Board and has attended many events.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Campaign for Burma</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/us-campaign-for-burma/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/us-campaign-for-burma/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;30 Hollywood celebrities ran a campaign from May 1 through May 30 to seek the release of Myanmar&amp;rsquo;s democracy icon Aung San Suu Kyi and push for freedom in the military-ruled nation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The 30-day campaign will see stars such as Will Ferrell, Ellen Page, Judd Apatow, Anjelica Huston, Jennifer Aniston and Rosanna Arquette appearing in video clips on the Internet highlighting human rights issues in Myanmar.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jorja filmed a video with Eric Szmanda which aired on May 11th (day 11). In it, the two CSI stars played a game called &amp;lsquo;forced labor&amp;rsquo; using cards with graphic pictures of alleged abuses in Myanmar.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;day-6:8ee0370e560b26a5fadc69e2bcad2ba9&#34;&gt;Day 6&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Eric Szmanda:&lt;/strong&gt; Alright, want to play a new game?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; Yeah, sure.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Eric:&lt;/strong&gt; Alright, this one&amp;rsquo;s called forced labor. I&amp;rsquo;ll be a Burmese soldier. You will be a Burmese civilian. First, I&amp;rsquo;ll beat and rape your wife. Then, I&amp;rsquo;ll murder your children. Then, I&amp;rsquo;ll burn your village to the ground. I&amp;rsquo;ll make you carry my supplies and ammunition for days, until your feet are raw and bleeding. You will not be fed, and as we walk, you will lead the way, so if we find any landmines, you&amp;rsquo;ll be the first to discover them. If you get sick and slow, I&amp;rsquo;ll beat you. And if you try to escape, I&amp;rsquo;ll kill you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; Why do I have to be the Burmese civilian?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Eric:&lt;/strong&gt; Since the illegal military regime took over? Those are the cards you&amp;rsquo;ve been dealt.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; I don&amp;rsquo;t think I like this game.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Eric:&lt;/strong&gt; No one does.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://link.brightcove.com/services/link/bcpid1517481413/bclid1527697194/bctid1533001469&#34;&gt;Jorja and Eric&amp;rsquo;s video&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>