<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>2011 on Fans of Le Fox Library</title>
    <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/tags/2011/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 2011 on Fans of Le Fox Library</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2011 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://jorjafox.net/library/tags/2011/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>ET Online</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2011/et-online/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2011/et-online/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
I like to think that I know Marg very well. And she&amp;rsquo;s one of the toughest, most stoic people &amp;lsquo; forget about woman or ladies &amp;lsquo; I mean one of the most stoic people I&amp;rsquo;ve ever met. And these moments where she&amp;rsquo;s kind of overcome are once in a blue moon. Probably the last time I ever saw that happen her dog died, probably six years ago. She&amp;rsquo;s got nerves of steel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AP Celebrity Extra</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2011/ap-celebrity-extra/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2011/ap-celebrity-extra/</guid>
      <description>When she&amp;rsquo;s not solving crimes on &amp;#8216;CSI,&amp;rsquo; you can find actress Jorja Fox on a surfboard. (Nov. 16)
I feel like I&amp;rsquo;m still learning to surf, you know? And that&amp;rsquo;s one of the things that I think makes it so fun, because it&amp;rsquo;s not really &amp;#8212; because I don&amp;rsquo;t do it competitively, I never feel like I&amp;rsquo;ve stopped learning. For me, it can lower my ambition, to go out and surf for a few hours, is so fulfilling and seems almost like an education.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily News</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/daily-news/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Nov 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/daily-news/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s a joke almost as old as show business itself. The aging actor - or, the more common stereotype, actress - who insists they can play characters decades younger than they are.
In our modern information age, though, it&amp;rsquo;s no laughing matter.
In October, an actress filed suit against Amazon and its subsidiary, the Internet Movie Database, for posting her birth date on the latter website.
The world&amp;rsquo;s most comprehensive repository of information about films, television shows and just about everybody who&amp;rsquo;s ever worked on them, IMDb has become the standard reference for not only journalists and fans, but increasingly for folks in the industry who want to check out potential hires.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AP</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/ap/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/ap/</guid>
      <description>WASHINGTON (AP) &amp;#8212; There&amp;rsquo;s a feeling of dread on the set of &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; and it has nothing to do with a murder. Jorja Fox says they&amp;rsquo;re starting to shoot the episodes leading up to Marg Helgenberger&amp;rsquo;s departure after 12 years. She says they&amp;rsquo;ve been on &amp;ldquo;this really fun high&amp;rdquo; since Ted Danson joined the show, but now, they&amp;rsquo;re &amp;ldquo;about to be devastated.&amp;rdquo; She says it&amp;rsquo;s getting &amp;ldquo;pretty emotional&amp;rdquo; on the set.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ecorazzi</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/ecorazzi/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/ecorazzi/</guid>
      <description>Jorja Fox spends her days investigating crimes on the TV show &amp;lsquo;CSI.&amp;rsquo; Now, she&amp;rsquo;s asking the public to do some investigating of their own. Not hair remnants or clothing fibers, but the way 10 billion farm animals are raised for food annually in the USA. She wants you to explore vegetarianism.
The actress debuted her new PETA ad at the vegan restaurant Sublime, and even helped with the cooking. They prepared spicy Singapore street noodles, &amp;ldquo;chicken picatta, and gourmet pizzas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WFMY News 2</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/wfmy-news-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/wfmy-news-2/</guid>
      <description>Washington, DC &amp;#8212; Ever wonder what&amp;rsquo;s happening with Sara and Gil and their long-distance, practically nonexistent relationship on &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo;? So does Jorja Fox. If she could write her own episode, she&amp;rsquo;d want to &amp;ldquo;look at her love affair more closely.&amp;rdquo; She says &amp;ldquo;it would be amazing if she traveled somewhere kind of exotic to see Grissom and see what he&amp;rsquo;s doing.&amp;rdquo; She says Sara may be happily married, but &amp;ldquo;she&amp;rsquo;s really lonely.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PETA</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/peta/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/peta/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; star Jorja Fox thinks that everyone should play detective and investigate how animals are killed for food. Jorja unveiled her pro-vegetarian PETA ad to an enthusiastic crowd Sunday at Fort Lauderdale&amp;rsquo;s gourmet vegan restaurant, Sublime.
She even got things cooking in the kitchen, helping the chefs with the evening&amp;rsquo;s delicious cruelty-free feast.
Jorja went vegetarian years agoâhalfway through a sandwich. &amp;ldquo;I was having a meatball sub one day in Brooklyn, and it just clicked,&amp;rdquo; she explains.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Boston Herald</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/boston-herald/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/boston-herald/</guid>
      <description>Animal activists and celebrities launched a new effort Wednesday to protect exotic animals by taking the &amp;ldquo;traveling&amp;rdquo; out of traveling circuses.
The proposed federal legislation would place sharp limits on the ability to transport lions, tigers and elephants around the country. Circuses say it would essentially shut down the animal portion of their shows.
Representatives from L.A.-based Animal Defenders International and Northern California&amp;rsquo;s Performing Animal Welfare Society, along with critter-friendly celebrities Bob Barker and Jorja Fox, held a press conference in Washington, D.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Inquisitr</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/inquisitr/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/inquisitr/</guid>
      <description>Bob Barker, the mythological horde of &amp;ldquo;Price is Right,&amp;rdquo; as well as &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; star Jorja Fox, assimilated with Animal Defenders International (ADI) as well as Performing Animal Welfare Society (PAWS) currently to deliver legislation to Congress to finish the pang as well as unsuitable conditions playground animals have been forced to endure.
Barker, the long-time animal rights romantic who late from the TV pricing diversion in 2006, trafficked to Washington to await the Traveling Exotic Animal Protection Act, which, once launched, will shorten the operate of outlandish as well as furious animals in roving circuses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ADI International</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/adi-international/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/adi-international/</guid>
      <description>Congressman Rep. Jim Moran, Bob Barker, and Jorja Fox announce new Bill to end animal suffering.
Measures that could see an end to elephants, lions, tigers, monkeys and bears touring with circuses have been unveiled today at a press conference attended by Bob Barker, Jorja Fox, Animal Defenders International (ADI), and the Performing Animal Welfare Society (PAWS). The Travelling Exotic Animal Protection Act, introduced by Rep. Jim Moran (D-Va.), will restrict the use of exotic and non-domesticated animals in traveling circuses and exhibitions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ADI Jorja Fox Addresses Congress</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2011/adi-addresses-congress/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2011/adi-addresses-congress/</guid>
      <description>I do think that a question that some of you may be asking right now is &amp;ldquo;Well what about my kids? Can&amp;rsquo;t my kids have the same chance I did to go to these traveling circuses?&amp;rdquo; Or maybe these circuses your parents went to. And I thought about this at length, and I think the truth is that our kids look to us for what is right, and our kids look to us for what is fun.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CNN</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/cnn/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/cnn/</guid>
      <description>Bob Barker, the former host of &amp;ldquo;The Price Is Right,&amp;rdquo; made an impassioned plea Wednesday for an end to what he described as an ugly side of entertainment: the mistreatment of exotic and wild animals in traveling circuses.
At a Capitol Hill news conference, Barker noted that traveling circuses rely heavily on animals that are trained to do tricks, which he said is accomplished with acts of cruelty.
&amp;ldquo;How do they train them?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FotoPeep</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/fotopeep/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/fotopeep/</guid>
      <description>Bob Barker, a well known animal enthusiast, and Jorja Fox, an animal advocate as well, had teamed up to help get three elephants moved to a sanctuary from a Toronto zoo where things were too cold.
And now they are in Washington, launching a bill called the Traveling Exotic Animal Protection Act.
The bill would:
&amp;ldquo;[â¦]restrict the use of exotic and wild animals in traveling circuses,&amp;rdquo; [and end the] &amp;lsquo;random cruelty and neglect&amp;rsquo; found in these circuses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Glittarazi</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2011/glittarazi/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2011/glittarazi/</guid>
      <description>Glittarazi: How does it feel to constantly be named one of PETA&amp;rsquo;s sexiest vegetarians?
Jorja Fox: It feels amazing and embarrassing at the same time. I&amp;rsquo;m thrilled that I get on the list, and I don&amp;rsquo;t even know how that happens. It may have to do with the little bit of green that I slip them to put me on it.
Glittarazi: Oh! Okay! I guess my other question is how would you like to expand or take this cause one step further?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Washington Examiner</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/washington-examiner/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/washington-examiner/</guid>
      <description>Former longtime &amp;ldquo;The Price Is Right&amp;rdquo; host Bob Barker joined &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; actress Jorja Fox and Rep. Jim Moran, D-Va., to introduce the &amp;ldquo;Traveling Exotic Animal Protection Act,&amp;rdquo; which will prohibit exotic animals from being able to travel with circuses.
&amp;ldquo;Our kids look to us for what is right and our kids look to us for what is fun and I think we can do more for our kids by doing the compassionate thing and the respectful thing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Hill</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/the-hill/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/the-hill/</guid>
      <description>Join CSI&amp;rsquo;s Jorja Fox and The Price is Right&amp;rsquo;s Bob Barker, as well as the Performing Animal Welfare Society, for a press conference regarding a congressional initiative to improve animal treatment in entertainment.
**Time: **10:30 am
**Place: **Interior Subcommittee Room B-308, Rayburn House Office Building, Independence Avenue and South Capitol St, DC 20003
Contact: Gary Smith at gary@evolotuspr.com or 818-783-0569</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CSI Files</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/csi-files-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/csi-files-02/</guid>
      <description>On Wednesday the 19th of October, Elisabeth Harnois (Morgan Brody) took part in a live chat session with CSI Files visitors, during which she answered questions about her character, Halloween pranks on the &amp;ldquo;CSI: Crime Scene Investigation&amp;rdquo; set and many more. Below you can find a transcript of the entire chat.
[&amp;hellip;]
Question from emmm: Are Ted, Eric, George, Marg and Jorja much like their characters and was it difficult or easy to gel with such a developed and seasoned cast?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>City Newspaper</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/city-newspaper/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/city-newspaper/</guid>
      <description>I can&amp;rsquo;t believe it, but I think I am starting to actually &amp;ldquo;like&amp;rdquo; D.B. Russell. Granted, the show&amp;rsquo;s new lead (played by Ted Danson) had a very good supporting story this episode, continuing the trend of the crimes getting more interesting, which is something the show hasn&amp;rsquo;t done for some time.
Two different scenes took the forefront this week. Morgan (Elisabeth Harnois) and Greg (Eric Szmanda) followed a man found dead on the streets, his lungs full of chocolate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Issues with Jane Velez-Mitchell</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2011/issues-with-jane-velez-mitchell-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2011/issues-with-jane-velez-mitchell-2/</guid>
      <description>(BEGIN VIDEO CLIP)
UNIDENTIFIED MALE: How do you train or break an elephant? That word, &amp;ldquo;break&amp;rdquo;.
UNIDENTIFIED FEMALE: Elephants are extremely social and they need the environment, they need movement, they need exercise.
UNIDENTIFIED FEMALE: Abused, 24 hours until the baby totally lost their mind. Many baby died.
Then the baby elephant fear the man. The man can control and the boy make baby elephant obey.
(END VIDEO CLIP)
VELEZ-MITCHELL: We&amp;rsquo;re talking about another kind of crime right now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Artists on Demand Radio</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2011/artists-on-demand-radio/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2011/artists-on-demand-radio/</guid>
      <description>ARTIST ON DEMAND: I&amp;rsquo;m Danni and I&amp;rsquo;ll be your host today. We have another very exciting show this afternoon. We&amp;rsquo;ll be talking to Jorja Fox who plays Sara Sidle on CSI. If you don&amp;rsquo;t know what CSI is, you must have been living under a rock. So. While we are waiting for her to call in, we&amp;rsquo;ll take a music break. So enjoy it. This is going to be Kimberly Cole, &amp;ldquo;Arrow through my Heart&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CSI Files</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/csi-files-03/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/csi-files-03/</guid>
      <description>Jorja Fox is excited about the new season of CSI: Crime Scene Investigation, premiering tonight on its new night and time. The Sara Sidle actress has nothing but high energy and enthusiasm just hours before the season premiere, and could not be more thrilled about the show&amp;rsquo;s twelfth season. CSI Files&amp;rsquo; Shane Saunders caught up with Fox to talk about her presence on the show this season, working with new cast members, a fellow co-star&amp;rsquo;s pending departure, and much more in this exclusive interview.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gather News - Celebs</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/gather-news-celebs/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/gather-news-celebs/</guid>
      <description>Ted Danson has built up a lot of goodwill among audiences after appearing on such hits as &amp;ldquo;Cheers,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;Damages,&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Becker.&amp;rdquo; But that goodwill might not extend to his new costars on &amp;ldquo;CSI.&amp;rdquo;
[..]
Is it possible that, in his zeal to help save the show from cancellation, Ted Danson is rubbing some castmates the wrong way? Sure. A lot of the &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; cast has been on the show from the beginning and probably have their own ways of working together.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Twitter</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/twitter/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/twitter/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to everyone. Don and I are excited to be here and talk about the new season #CSI
&amp;ldquo;A TO Q&amp;rdquo; means &amp;ldquo;Answer to Question&amp;rdquo;.
[..]
A TO Q: We&amp;rsquo;ve been talking to Jorja Fox about Sara and Grissom - Look for clues to where Grissom&amp;rsquo;s been and where he&amp;rsquo;s heading #CSI
[..]
A TO Q: Billy says Grissom has been working on perfecting his grilled cheese sandwiches. May surprise Sara with one.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Line</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/tv-line-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Aug 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/tv-line-01/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
**CSI - ** Given the news that the upcoming season is very likely Marg Helgenberger&amp;rsquo;s last, it&amp;rsquo;d stand to reason that William Petersen might put in an encore, playing Gil to her Catherine. But as of Wednesday, when I spoke to show boss Carol Mendelsohn, nothing yet seemed set in stone. &amp;ldquo;Listen, every year we go to Billy &amp;ndash; it&amp;rsquo;s sort of like a pilgrimage &amp;ndash; to say, &amp;lsquo;Will you come back?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Guide Magazine</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/tv-guide-06/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/tv-guide-06/</guid>
      <description>Ted Danson&amp;rsquo;s on the case with Marg Helgenberger (left) and Jorja Fox as the three filmed at the Golden Nugget Casino in Las Vegas on July 25. Danson joins the CBS series, currently filming its 12th season, playing the new head of the graveyard shift at the crime lab. CSI premieres on its new night, Wednesday, September 21, at 10pm.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About.com</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/about-com/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jul 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/about-com/</guid>
      <description>The merry-go-round that is Jorja Fox&amp;rsquo;s status on the hit CBS series CSI: Crime Scene Investigation has changed once again &amp;#8212; but this time the news is good.
Fox, who has been a guest star for the last four years, is returning to the show this fall as a series regular (as reported by TV Line). The actress was briefly fired from her role as CSI investigator Sara Sidle back in 2004 for failing to report to work (along with her co-star George Eads) during a contract dispute.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LA Times</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/la-times/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jul 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/la-times/</guid>
      <description>Jorja Fox is returning to &amp;ldquo;CSI: Crime Scene Investigation&amp;rdquo; as a series regular in the fall.
The actress was a series regular for the first seven seasons, playing tenacious forensic scientist Sara Sidle. Fox left at the beginning of Season 8 and returned only as a guest star the following seasons. But now she&amp;rsquo;s coming back to Clark County for good, TV Line reported.
Fox will be starring alongside Ted Danson, who recently replaced outgoing Laurence Fishburne as head of the investigation team for the procedural during the CBS show&amp;rsquo;s 12th-season shakeup.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Show Biz Renegade</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/show-biz-renegade/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jul 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/show-biz-renegade/</guid>
      <description>When she was abducted and buried alive, Grissom&amp;rsquo;s head spun. If he needed to kill someone to find her, he would have. When she left for good Grissom felt like his whole world fell apart &amp;ndash; no he felt like dying was a better punishment for his inability to set aside his career for his relationship with her.
Well, Sara Sidle is back. Unfortunately Grissom (played by William Petersen) will not be.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zap2It</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/zap2it-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/zap2it-01/</guid>
      <description>It appears that Jorja Fox&amp;rsquo;s on-again, off-again relationship with the long-running CBS hit &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; is on again. And this time it&amp;rsquo;s permanent &amp;hellip; for now.
The actress who plays crime scene investigator Sara Sidle has signed on as a series regular after four seasons as a guest star, according to a report from TV Line.
Fox has disappeared and re-appeared from the show seemingly as many times as the Miniature Killer that almost took the life of Fox&amp;rsquo;s character.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dose.ca</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/dose-ca/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/dose-ca/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s been two years since Jorja Fox returned to CSI, and considering her long history with the CBS crime procedural and the huge popularity of character Sara Sidle, you&amp;rsquo;d be forgiven for thinking the actress was already a series regular. Not so, TV Line revealed this week, as Fox has only just been promoted to regular status, coinciding with the start of CSI&amp;rsquo;s twelfth season this fall.
Fox, 43, used to be a series regular during the first seven seasons of CSI; however, she left the show at the start of Season 8.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pedro and the Watcher</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/pedro-and-the-watcher/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/pedro-and-the-watcher/</guid>
      <description>Jorja Fox&amp;rsquo;s on-again. off-again relationship with &amp;ldquo;CSI: Crime Scene Investigation&amp;rdquo; flipped to on-again, as CBS announced she will return to the series as a regular this fall.
After seven seasons as a regular &amp;ndash; and several contract disputes &amp;ndash; Jorja left &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo;, but she and her character, Sara Sidle, soon returned to the show as a recurring guest star for the next four seasons.
It&amp;rsquo;s the second major cast change for &amp;ldquo;CSI,&amp;rdquo; which announced last week that Ted Danson would join the cast, replacing Laurence Fishburne.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Guide</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/tv-guide-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/tv-guide-01/</guid>
      <description>Jorja Fox will no longer guest-star on her old haunt of CSI: Crime Scene Investigation â come next season, the show&amp;rsquo;s 12th, she&amp;rsquo;ll be considered a full-fledged regular, TVLine reports.
[&amp;hellip;]
Fox spent the show&amp;rsquo;s first seven seasons as a regular. She then left and made guest appearances for the next four seasons.
[&amp;hellip;]
CSI will return for its 12th season on Sept. 21 in its new time slot, Wednesdays at 10/9c.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TVLine</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/tvline/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/tvline/</guid>
      <description>After four seasons as a recurring guest star, Jorja Fox is returning to CSI this fall as a full-fledged series regular, sources confirm to TVLine exclusively.
The actress â who was a CSI regular for the show&amp;rsquo;s first seven seasons â left the procedural at the start of Season 8 after appearing in only a handful of episodes. She returned for Season 9, but opted to remain a guest star â until now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Hollywood Reporter</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/the-hollywood-reporter/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/the-hollywood-reporter/</guid>
      <description>The actress rejoins the crime procedural as a full-time cast member for its upcoming 12th season.
&amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; is officially welcoming back a familiar face.
&amp;ldquo;The Hollywood Reporter&amp;rdquo; has confirmed that former series regular &amp;ndash; and recent guest star &amp;#8212; Jorja Fox will appear full-time on the CBS crime procedural, as first reported by TV Line.
Fox first appeared as Sara Sidle on &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; in Season 1 and departed early in Season 8.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CSI Files</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/csi-files-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/csi-files-01/</guid>
      <description>Laurence Fishburne (Dr Ray Langston) will not be returning for season twelve of CSI: Crime Scene Investigation, but the rest of the show’s cast is readying to return. Details on who is returning and how after the jump!
As CSI Files previously reported, Fishburne will not be returning for the upcoming twelfth season. However, despite breathless Internet rumors, no one else will be absent when the show resumes September 21st.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ADI International</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/animal-defenders-international/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/animal-defenders-international/</guid>
      <description>Actress Jorja Fox, of the popular TV show CSI, undertook the work of compassion when she joined ADI in support of our landmark &amp;ldquo;Operation Lion Ark,&amp;rdquo; to airlift 25 ex-circus lions from Bolivia to a new home in the US.
After our dangerous undercover investigations and public and political campaigns to get all animals out of circus throughout Bolivia, Jorja came on board and embraced ADI&amp;rsquo;s cause to end animal suffering, and has inspired others to do likewise.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cosas Madres (07 01 2011)</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/cosas-madres/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/cosas-madres/</guid>
      <description>Famous for her performance on the show &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; and the renowned series &amp;ldquo;The West Wing&amp;rdquo;, actress Jorja Fox visited Ecuador. She toured Quito and the Galapagos Islands, participating in the filming of an animal rescue program and a special for the promotion of tourism in Ecuador.
Jorja Fox, when she was a young woman, with an elegant 1.75 in height, had a modeling career in the highly competitive New York City, lived in an apartment she shared with Madonna&amp;rsquo;s sister, was born there on July 7th.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Male Couple </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/the-male-couple/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/the-male-couple/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
How it was the experience working in a chapter of a prime time TV show CSI with Academy Oscar Winner Marlee Matlin or TV stars like Jorja Fox?
It was truly wonderful. Marlee is a genius, I was so jealous watching her work. Because it was a deaf themed episode (The Two Mrs. Grissoms) we had tons of deaf actors, including Phyllis Frelich, who won the Tony for the same role, Marlee won the Oscar (Sarah in &amp;ldquo;Children of a Lesser God&amp;rdquo;, Phyllis on Broadway and Marlee in the film).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UCLA Today</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/ucla-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/ucla-today/</guid>
      <description>The packet of photos of Japan seemed to take everyone by surprise. On each page of the packet were two photos: The top snapshot showed a scene snapped immediately after the devastating earthquake and tsunami of March 11. The bottom photo of the exact same area taken three months later showed that the debris had been almost completely cleared away, leaving everything looking â for all intents and purposes â normal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>El Comercio</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/el-comercio/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/el-comercio/</guid>
      <description>From the plane, the first thing that attracts people to the Galapagos is the feeling that you&amp;rsquo;ve come to a haunted island. Or you&amp;rsquo;re lost in the sea. It is a description not so far from reality. Those pieces of land have their charm.
Princes and famous scientists, from the stars of film and television, politicians and socialites, few are reluctant to know the land of &amp;#8216;Lonesome George&amp;rsquo;.&amp;ldquo;He is more famous than I am,&amp;rdquo; joked actress Jorja Fox, famous for CSI: Las Vegas, during her visit in February.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IDABlog </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/idablog/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/idablog/</guid>
      <description>On Saturday, June 11, activists in at least 24 cities around the world will take part in the International Day of Action for Elephants in Zoos, holding outreach events and demonstrations to send the message that it&amp;rsquo;s wrong to keep elephants in small zoo displays where these magnificent animals are suffering and dying prematurely. This year we&amp;rsquo;re also offering a surprise co-event, but you&amp;rsquo;ll have to stay tuned to this blog for more information later in the week.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Guide.com</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/tv-guide-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/tv-guide-02/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
Indeed, if Langston&amp;rsquo;s obsession with Haskell leads to murder, Langston&amp;rsquo;s career could be in jeopardy. Also at stake: the entire team&amp;rsquo;s reputation.
&amp;ldquo;If [Langston] goes to the darker side, where does the team stand in all of that? Do they have his back?&amp;rdquo; Mendelsohn says. Adds cast member Jorja Fox: &amp;ldquo;It&amp;rsquo;s going to put the team in a very unique place â a road that none of them have ever travelled down before.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Talk</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2011/the-talk/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2011/the-talk/</guid>
      <description>Julie Chen: Welcome back to &amp;ldquo;The Talk&amp;rdquo;. Our first guest is best known for her role as Sara Sidle on the hit CBS drama &amp;ldquo;CSI: Crime Scene Investigation&amp;rdquo;. Take a look.
&amp;rdquo;(clip from CSI)&amp;rdquo;
Julie: Please welcome Jorja Fox.
Jorja Fox: (walks in, waves to audience) Oh wow! (hugs hosts, sits down on the couch with Julie Chen, Sharon Osbourne and Sara Gilbert) I am so honored to be here, thanks for having me&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Guide.com</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/tv-guide-03/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/tv-guide-03/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
Got anything good about the CSI finale? â Jason
ADAM: The final Langston-Haskell showdown is personal. &amp;ldquo;Haskell kidnaps Langston&amp;rsquo;s ex-wife and she&amp;rsquo;s presumed dead,&amp;rdquo; Jorja Fox tells us. &amp;ldquo;It&amp;rsquo;s a harrowing story because [Ray&amp;rsquo;s] ex-wife is the love is his life. Haskell has really hit Langston at the core of his being.&amp;rdquo; But the lengths that Langston goes to stop Haskell will have an impact on the entire team. &amp;ldquo;All of the characters on the show have to examine or re-examine their beliefs about certain things, their ethics,&amp;rdquo; Fox says.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EW.com </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/ew-04/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/ew-04/</guid>
      <description>Melinda Clarke&amp;rsquo;s Lady Heather, one of the most cultishly beloved guest characters on CSI, returned to the series this week. Unfortunately, her appearance only reminded viewers how much dramatic tension this show has lost.
Lady Heather is now a sex therapist &amp;ndash; professional name: Dr. Heather Kessler â and she was visited by Laurence Fishburne&amp;rsquo;s Ray Langston and Jorja Fox&amp;rsquo;s Sara for background on a kinky case they were investigating about a dead girl who had acted out her neuroses as a kitty cat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Line</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/tv-line-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/tv-line-02/</guid>
      <description>Lady Heather rears her ugly gorgeous head on CSI this Thursday (CBS, 9/8c), but why the unexpected encore? The vexing vixen â played by Nikita&amp;rsquo;s Melinda Clarke â is back for two reasons: to solve a strange crime, and to provide insider knowledge on that &amp;ldquo;evil&amp;rdquo; DNA gene that Langston (Laurence Fishburne) shares with MIA murderer Nate Haskell (returning guest star Bill Irwin).
Of course, we already knew that Haskell&amp;rsquo;s season-ending reappearance is right around the corner, but here&amp;rsquo;s the twist: It&amp;rsquo;s Clarke&amp;rsquo;s sixth CSI guest spot that actually kick-starts this intense, killer arc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shane S Saunders </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/shane-s-saunders-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/shane-s-saunders-2/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
This season on CSI multiple actors have been in-and-out of episodes, most notably Marg Helgenberger (Catherine Willows), Jorja Fox (Sara Sidle), and Paul Guilfoyle (Captain Jim Brass). As the season grows closer to the finish line CSI writer Christopher Barbour reveals who will be missing from the final 5 episodes and says: &amp;ldquo;I sincerely hope fans of all the characters will tune in to each and every episode. It&amp;rsquo;ll be quite a ride to the end of the season.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shane S Saunders </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/shane-s-saunders-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/shane-s-saunders-1/</guid>
      <description>*CSI *fans got a real treat this season when former series-regular William Petersen returned for a brief cameo. The mastermind behind that story, 2008 Genesis Award Winner Christopher Barbour, graciously took a break from his busy schedule this afternoon to speak to me exclusively on how they got Grissom back, Catherine&amp;rsquo;s future, and a big showdown between Nate Haskell and Ray Langston. Spoilers a plenty after the jump!
&amp;#8212;-
Saunders: Some pretty major events happened in your last episode &amp;ldquo;The Two Mrs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CNN</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/cnn-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/cnn-2/</guid>
      <description>(CNN) &amp;#8212; Two dozen lions rescued from harrowing conditions at circuses in Bolivia have a new home in Colorado, where they will live outside of cages and roar at the distant Rocky Mountains.
Animal Defenders International (ADI) brought them last week to Denver, where they were transported to the Wild Animal Sanctuary, to conclude its &amp;ldquo;Operation Lion Ark.&amp;rdquo;
The flight followed the passage of a 2009 law in Bolivia that bans the use of any animals in circuses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Issues with Jane Velez-Mitchell</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2011/issues-with-jane-velez-mitchell-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2011/issues-with-jane-velez-mitchell-1/</guid>
      <description>(BEGIN VIDEO CLIP)
TIM PHILLIPS, ANIMAL DEFENDERS INTERNATIONAL: These lions have lived their life in a tiny, rusting, disgusting cage on the back of a lorry. Tomorrow they&amp;rsquo;re going to feel the wind blow in their face. They&amp;rsquo;re going to feel grass beneath their feet. They&amp;rsquo;re going to roam into the bushes. They&amp;rsquo;re going to do whatever they want. They&amp;rsquo;re going to be as lions, possibly for the first real time in their lives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Entertainment Weekly Magazine</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/ew-03/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Feb 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/ew-03/</guid>
      <description>These times are tough for CSI. Yeah, the show still does well in the ratings, but the series has lost its mojo since William Petersen&amp;rsquo;s Gil Grissom left two years ago. [&amp;hellip;]
[&amp;hellip;]
The return of Jorja for as Sara Sidle hasn&amp;rsquo;t really upped the energy level. (If anything, the shoe has suffered a bit by loosing another woman &amp;#8212; Liz Vassey as the sparky &amp;ldquo;lab rat&amp;rdquo; Wendy Simms.)
Now in its 11th season, CSI still airs good hours, and coexecutive producers Treena Hancock and Melissa R.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KSCW-TV</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/kscw-tv/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/kscw-tv/</guid>
      <description>DENVER &amp;#8212; More than two dozen Bolivian circus lions were getting accustomed to their new surroundings at The Wild Animal Sanctuary in Keenesburg, Colo., Thursday.
They arrived at their new permanent home on 80 acres of open space Wednesday evening, after a long flight from Bolivia to Denver.
The lions were greeted by a couple of well-known celebrity animal activists, Bob Barker from &amp;ldquo;The Price is Right,&amp;rdquo; and actress Jorja Fox from CSI: Crime Scene Investigation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Denver Post</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/denver-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Feb 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/denver-post/</guid>
      <description>DENVER â international airport U.S. agriculture and customs officials have completed their inspection and now crates carrying 25 lions rescued from small traveling circuses in Bolivia are being unloaded.
The animals, ferried to Colorado by Animal Defenders International&amp;rsquo;s Operation Lion Ark, are en route to the Wild Animal Sanctuary near Keensburg.
About 100 ADI and sanctuary volunteers, media and law enforcement officials met the Bolivian cargo plane at United Airlines&amp;rsquo; maintenance hangar at the north end of Denver International Airport.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Huffington Post</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/huffington-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Feb 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/huffington-post/</guid>
      <description>Twenty-five lions, most of them rescued from Bolivian circuses, are heading to Colorado to start their new lives at a wildlife sanctuary.
The 13 males and 12 females were scheduled to land at Denver International Airport on Wednesday afternoon.
Animal Defenders International say the lions were rescued from deplorable conditions after a law was passed last year in Bolivia prohibiting performances that involve animals.
Television personality Bob Barker financed the rescue.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EON: Enhanced Online News</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/eon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/eon/</guid>
      <description>Bob Barker and CSI Actress Jorja Fox to Greet Lions
##WHAT
&amp;lsquo;OPERATION LION ARK&amp;rsquo; TO LAND AT DENVER INTERNATIONAL AIRPORT
Animal Defenders International Media Briefing/Photo Opportunity/Record Breaking Rescued Bolivian Lion Arrival
A world record breaking airlift carrying 25 lions rescued by Animal Defenders International (ADI) following Bolivia&amp;rsquo;s ban on animal circuses is scheduled to arrive at Denver International Airport via TAB Airlines on Wednesday, February 16, 2011 at approximately 2:00 p.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Guide Magazine</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/tv-guide-05/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/tv-guide-05/</guid>
      <description>It was a reunion of sorts, when after almost two years of absence, Gil Grissom [William Petersen] appeared on the February 3 episode of CSI, titled &amp;ldquo;The Two Mrs. Grissoms.&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;We had the perfect story&amp;rdquo;, says ex. producer Carol Mendelsohn tells TV Guide Magazine about the timing of Petersen&amp;rsquo;s return, &amp;ldquo;The Two Mrs. Grissoms&amp;rdquo; in conflict, and the peacemaker was MIA. &amp;ldquo;In fact, it was Grissom&amp;rsquo;s on-screen wife, Jorja Fox, who reached out to Petersen and convinced him to do a cameo with her and guest star Phyllis Frelich, who played his mom.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pets In The City</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2011/pets-in-the-city/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2011/pets-in-the-city/</guid>
      <description>**Pets In The City: **For many of us, the circus brings back fond memories of lions, tigers, and other large, beautiful creatures performing incredible acts of courage and agility usually with their tamers and trainers on board. But in recent years, the ability of some circuses to properly care for these large beasts has been under scrutiny. This scrutiny has not been limited to the United States. Joining us today is Jorja Fox, who plays the popular character Sara Sidle on the mega hit *CSI *Las Vegas, to talk about her personal work on behalf of some very special and now globe-trotting lions that she and other notable stars have helped move from Bolivia to the U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CraveOnline.com</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/craveonline.com/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Feb 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/craveonline.com/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
Story:
While attending a scholarship benefit party for the hearing impaired with Gil&amp;rsquo;s mother Betty (Phyllis Frelich), Sara (Jorja Fox) is first on the scene when a car bomb goes off. The man inside is Dr. Eric Lambert (Anthony Natale), a colleague of Prof. Julia Holden (Marlee Matlin), who we later learn is Gil&amp;rsquo;s ex.
After learning that Julia, who was at the scene when the car was discovered, lied about her whereabouts at the time of the explosion, Sara puts her in the crosshairs as the prime suspect.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TVGuide.com</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/tv-guide-07/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Feb 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/tv-guide-07/</guid>
      <description>It was a reunion of sorts when, after almost two years of absence, Gil Grissom (William Petersen) appeared on the February 3 episode of CSI, titled &amp;ldquo;The Two Mrs. Grissoms.&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;We had the perfect story,&amp;rdquo; executive producer Carol Mendelsohn tells TV Guide Magazine about the timing of Petersen&amp;rsquo;s return. &amp;ldquo;The two Mrs. Grissoms in conflict, and the peacemaker was MIA.&amp;rdquo; In fact, it was Grissom&amp;rsquo;s on-screen wife, Jorja Fox, who reached out to Petersen and convinced him to do a cameo with her and guest star Phyllis Frelich, who plays his mom.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TVGuide.com - Today&#39;s News</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/tv-guide-08/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Feb 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/tv-guide-08/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
&amp;rdquo;&amp;lsquo;THE GIL FACTOR:&amp;ldquo;&amp;rsquo; As rumored, the much-missed William Petersen is heard (over the phone), then seen (in a Skype computer chat) â but always from an aggravating distance â for the first time since leaving &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo;, during this week&amp;rsquo;s above-par mystery on the campus of the college for the deaf where Sara tangles with Grissom&amp;rsquo;s mother (Phyllis Frelich) and ex-girlfriend (Marlee Matlin, who won an Oscar for the &amp;ldquo;Children of a Lesser God&amp;rdquo; role that previously won Frelich a Tony).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zap2It - Zap 2 News and Buzz</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/zap2it-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Feb 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/zap2it-02/</guid>
      <description>As implicitly promised in all the teases leading up to the show, Thursday&amp;rsquo;s (Feb. 3) episode of &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; featured the return of the show&amp;rsquo;s original lead character, Gil Grissom (William Petersen) &amp;#8212; at least for a couple minutes.
It was not, however, a particularly splashy comeback. Grissom appeared only at the end of the episode (the scene is above) to chat with his wife, Sara (Jorja Fox) and mom (guest star Phyllis Frelich), via video conference.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BusinessWire</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/businesswire/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/businesswire/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;I am so impressed with ADI that I am going to make another investment in their mind-boggling work, and I invite you, in fact, I urge you to &amp;lsquo;man-up&amp;rsquo; and join me, too.&amp;rdquo;- Bob Barker, former host of the Price Is Right and ADI supporter
LOS ANGELES-(BUSINESS WIRE)-It is called &amp;lsquo;Operation Lion Ark.&amp;rsquo; It&amp;rsquo;s the biggest-ever animal rescue of its kind, and now a host of celebrities are urging people to get behind the cause and send a donation to help &amp;ldquo;save the lions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Entertainment Weekly</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/ew-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jan 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/ew-02/</guid>
      <description>Now here&amp;rsquo;s a love letter to &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; devotees: EW has learned exclusively that William Petersen will reprise his role as Gil Grissom with a cameo in an upcoming episode. The actor &amp;ndash; who left the show in January 2009 &amp;ndash; already shot his appearance on the CBS drama and we&amp;rsquo;re told his return involves Jorja Fox, who plays Gil&amp;rsquo;s on-screen wife Sara. It&amp;rsquo;s unclear exactly when he&amp;rsquo;ll appear back in or around the lab, but TV Line teased that it may occur this week.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Fanatic</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/tv-fanatic/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jan 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/tv-fanatic/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s been confirmed: William Petersen will make a cameo as Gil Grissom on CSI this season. The only question remaining: might this take place as early as Thursday?
Sources tell Entertainment Weekly that the actor - who departed the drama a year ago &amp;ndash; has already shot his upcoming scene, which will involve Grissom&amp;rsquo;s on-screen wife, Sara.
Considering the storyline of &amp;ldquo;The Two Mrs. Grissoms,&amp;rdquo; which will feature Gil&amp;rsquo;s mother and ex-girlfriend, there&amp;rsquo;s a good chance the appearances goes down this week.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Line</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/tv-line-03/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jan 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/tv-line-03/</guid>
      <description>Something tells me Sara/Grissom fans will not want to miss next week&amp;rsquo;s CSI.
The following promotional clip from the Feb. 3 episode â which finds Jorja Fox&amp;rsquo;s Sara working through some issues with her disapproving mother-in-law â strongly suggests that William Petersen&amp;rsquo;s MIA Grissom will figure into the family squabble.
But will William Petersen actually be making an appearance â as CSI Files is reporting? Or will Grissom remain an off screen presence?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Herald</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/daily-herald/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jan 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/daily-herald/</guid>
      <description>As hard-core fans of CBS&amp;rsquo; &amp;ldquo;CSI: Crime Scene Investigation&amp;rdquo; know, former CSI boss Gil Grissom (William Petersen) had deaf parents and therefore is adept at American Sign Language. They also know he married fellow CSI Sara Sidle (Jorja Fox) and is in the jungle doing research, while Sara is back in Las Vegas working crime scenes.
But what they probably don&amp;rsquo;t know is that Grissom had another woman in his past, something that Sara discovers in a rather uncomfortable way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dawg Sports</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/dawg-sports/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/dawg-sports/</guid>
      <description>I feel safe in stating that, at this juncture, every denizen of Bulldog Nation is a fan of Mark Fox. Whether you were a Georgia Bulldogs basketball booster in the first place or have become more enthusiastic in your support of the sport as a result of the Hoop Hounds&amp;rsquo; recent success, you doubtless have discovered that there is a lot to like about Coach Fox. Since there is little sense in comparing him to past Georgia basketball coaches&amp;#8212;that would be to damn him with faint praise, indeed&amp;#8212;the only other way to evaluate him is, of course, to compare him to other Foxes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vegetarian Times (01 December 2011)</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/vegetarian-times/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/vegetarian-times/</guid>
      <description>CSI: Crime Scene Investigation fans breathed a sign of relief when Jorja Fox returned this season as criminologist Sara Sidle. More gregarious than her on-screen character, the veg actress applies her equally sharp mind and big heart in real life to activism on behalf of animals. She&amp;rsquo;s an executive producer of the upcoming documentary How I Became an Elephant, which follows a 14-year-old girl on her mission to save the planet&amp;rsquo;s gentle giants.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Entertainment Weekly </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/ew-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/ew-01/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
Status Report: TV&amp;rsquo;s big burning questions
Now that Jorja Fox is back for at least 11 episodes of &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; this season, will William Petersen, who played her onscreen husband, Gil Grissom, appear? Answer&amp;hellip;.&amp;ldquo;Sadly, no. &amp;ldquo;We&amp;rsquo;re bugged by it,&amp;rdquo; admits exec producer Carol Mendelsohn. &amp;ldquo;Gil is the legacy of &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo;. You can never say he&amp;rsquo;s the one who shall not be named. We constantly bug him (about returning).&amp;rdquo; Until then, fans will have to settle for meeting Grissom&amp;rsquo;s long-lost mother, played by deaf actress Phyllis Frelich, in the Feb.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MSN Entertainment </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/msn-entertainment/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/msn-entertainment/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Glee&amp;rdquo; star Matthew Morrison&amp;rsquo;s recent comments to E! Online that his character Will will finally get together with his lady love Emma (Jayma Mays) &amp;ldquo;by season 14&amp;rdquo; got us thinking about that eternal TV dilemma: should TV couples consummate their unconsummated sexual tension and risk ruining their show? Here are ten TV duos where the question wasn&amp;rsquo;t &amp;ldquo;will they or won&amp;rsquo;t they,&amp;rdquo; it&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;should they or shouldn&amp;rsquo;t they?&amp;rdquo;
[&amp;hellip;]
With its gruesome autopsy and crime scenes, never has a show been less about sex and romance than &amp;ldquo;CSI: Crime Scene Investigation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>News Articles (2011)</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/</guid>
      <description>Date Source    January 01 TV Guide Magazine   January 06 MSN Entertainment    January 07 Entertainment Weekly    January 12 Vegetarian Times (01 December 2011)   January 18 Dawg Sports   January 24 Daily Herald   January 28 TV Line   January 31 Entertainment Weekly   January 31 TV Fanatic   February 01 BusinessWire   February 04 TVGuide.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Guide Magazine</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/tv-guide-04/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/tv-guide-04/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
Also heading to the lab: Jorja Fox, who appeared in 14 episodes last season, rejoins the team as a &amp;ldquo;series regular&amp;rdquo;. One show insider says CSI will feel quite different this year, the first script just came in, there&amp;rsquo;s a noticeable change&amp;rdquo;, he says. &amp;ldquo;It recaptures the show&amp;rsquo;s whimsy.&amp;rdquo;
[&amp;hellip;]</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>