<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>2013 on Fans of Le Fox Library</title>
    <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/tags/2013/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 2013 on Fans of Le Fox Library</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2013 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://jorjafox.net/library/tags/2013/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>USA Today</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2013/usa-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2013/usa-today/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; actress Jorja Fox has made rescuing lions one of her life&amp;rsquo;s missions.
&amp;rdquo;&amp;lsquo;What:&amp;ldquo;&amp;rsquo; Animal Defenders International (ADI) ambassador
&amp;rdquo;&amp;lsquo;Why:&amp;ldquo;&amp;rsquo; &amp;#8216;I&amp;rsquo;ve been passionate about habitats, preservation and animals in captivity for a long time,&amp;rdquo; says Fox, who appears in and is an associate producer of the documentary Lion Ark. &amp;ldquo;We&amp;rsquo;re at a very critical time for this work to happen. We can do a lot better by these animals. We all know that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ecorazzi</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2013/ecorazzi/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2013/ecorazzi/</guid>
      <description>&amp;rdquo;&amp;lsquo;Jorja Fox&amp;rdquo;&amp;rsquo; has a new best friend that she wasnt expecting to find.
The actress recently told People magazine that after losing her beloved dog, she didnt feel ready yet to welcome a new dog into her heart when she ended up rescuing a poodle mix named Bexar (the name is pronounced &amp;ldquo;bear&amp;rdquo;).&amp;ldquo;When we found each other, I had just lost my dog of 14 years. I actually spent the first months kind of pushing her away a bit and she did the same to me,&amp;rdquo; she said.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>People Pets</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2013/people-pets/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2013/people-pets/</guid>
      <description>Jorja Fox wasn&amp;rsquo;t quite ready to adopt a new dog. The &amp;ldquo;CSI: Crime Scene Investigation&amp;rdquo; star was still mourning the loss of her old pet, who died in January, when a scruffy little mutt came into her life.
&amp;ldquo;When we found each other, I had just lost my dog of 14 years,&amp;rdquo; she reveals in an interview with Sweden with Love. Bexar (pronounded &amp;ldquo;bear&amp;rdquo;) had been found roaming the streets of San Antonio, Texas, but it wasn&amp;rsquo;t exactly love at first sight.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sweden With Love</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2013/sweden-with-love/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2013/sweden-with-love/</guid>
      <description>Actress** Jorja Fox** is standing in the middle of an airplane hangar in Boulder, Colorado, watching the doors of a Bolivian cargo jet open up. While the sun sets over the Rocky Mountains, individual crates housing twenty-five African lions are unloaded. Although from different prides, the lions share the same fate: rescued from circus abuse, they&amp;rsquo;re about to embark on a new life. All of a sudden, one lion after the other starts roaring, the sound bouncing off the walls in the giant hangar.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ISSUES with Jane Velez-Mitchell</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2013/issues-with-jane-velez-mitchell/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2013/issues-with-jane-velez-mitchell/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
Jane Velez-Mitchell: CSI star Jorja Fox plays a determined crime scene investigator, who won&amp;rsquo;t let anything stand in her pursuit of the truth. When she&amp;rsquo;s off the set, she&amp;rsquo;s just as determined to free animals from captivity. I talked to Jorja about why she thinks Blackfish is a giant step for all animals in captivity.
[Clip of CSI]
Jane Velez-Mitchell: Jorja Fox, you play Sara Sidle on CSI and you do such a great job of investigating.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TVGuide.com</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2013/tvguide-06/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2013/tvguide-06/</guid>
      <description>Wednesday&amp;rsquo;s episode of CSI marks the CBS procedural&amp;rsquo;s 300th episode, and no matter how you slice it, that&amp;rsquo;s a lot of murder.
[&amp;hellip;]
Realizing the show would reach the milestone this season, executive producer Don McGill says they wanted this entire season in general, and the 300th episode in particular, to look back at the show&amp;rsquo;s history. &amp;ldquo;When Carol and I talked about the season, [we thought,] &amp;#8216;Back to the beginning,&amp;ldquo;] McGill says.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Talk (23 October 2013)</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2013/the-talk-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2013/the-talk-2/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
Sara Gilbert: I have to congratulate you guys on 300 episodes.
[audience cheers]
Jorja Fox: [pointing at Eric] He&amp;rsquo;s the only man in the pilot. Right here. All 300.
Sara Gilbert: You&amp;rsquo;ve been there since the first season, but I heard, Jorja, that you didn&amp;rsquo;t think the show was gonna take off.
Jorja Fox: No, and I can say that we&amp;rsquo;re [Jorja and Eric] getting old. [laughter] I can&amp;rsquo;t speak for you guys [Elisabeth and Ted] at all.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CBS CSI300 EPK</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2013/cbs-csi300-epk/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2013/cbs-csi300-epk/</guid>
      <description>&amp;hellip;
Jorja Fox: I was blown away by it, it was so different and I hadn&amp;rsquo;t seen anything ever like it. A show about death, on a Friday night? This is going to be canceled in six weeks, no one&amp;rsquo;s going to watch this! America&amp;rsquo;s not gonna watch this show! And boy was I &amp;hellip; that was extremely wrong about that! [breaks up laughing]
&amp;hellip;
Jorja Fox: It&amp;rsquo;s a great place to go back to.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TVGuide.com</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2013/tvguide-05/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2013/tvguide-05/</guid>
      <description>Over 14 seasons and 300 episodes, &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; has concocted some wild plots and brought in memorable guest stars to keep the body-bagging business fresh and fun. We asked the cast - including Marg Helgenberger, who reprises her role as Catherine Willows for Wednesday&amp;rsquo;s landmark 300th episode, which flashes back to a case the team failed to crack in 2000 - to reflect on the show&amp;rsquo;s best installments, selected by longtime executive producer Carol Mendelsohn.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CableTV.com</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2013/cabletv-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2013/cabletv-2/</guid>
      <description>Jorja Fox is best known for her role as Dr. Maggie Doyle in the television medical drama ER. Since then, Fox has had many successful appearances in television shows including The West Wing and most recently CSI: Crime Scene Investigation playing Sara Sidle. Fox talks about her career, how CSI changed her life, and what fans could expect this season.
Q: What does it feel like to reflect on your career and know that you have been on some of the biggest shows in history like ER</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Honolulu Pulse</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2013/honolulu-pulse/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2013/honolulu-pulse/</guid>
      <description>The 33rd Hawaii International Film Festival started off with a buzz of energy on Thursday, Oct. 10.
A cheery crowd of filmmakers, actors, producers and staunch film fans mixed over stylish small bites, wine and cocktails at an opening night party at the Halekulani in Waikiki, as organizers flitted about and dignitaries, including Mayor Kirk Caldwell, greeted the fest.
The evening was especially fantastic for me, as I was able to sit down for an animated and uplifting talk with Jorja Fox, who plays Sara on &amp;ldquo;CSI,&amp;rdquo; one of contemporary televisions most popular and long-running series.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mill Valley Film Festival Screening (05 October 2013)</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2013/mill-valley-film-festival-screening/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Oct 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2013/mill-valley-film-festival-screening/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Announcer: Please, before we start anything, give a big hand to Pacific Sun, who is responsible for letting Lion Ark be here today. The film is co-presented by Animal Defenders International, which had, obviously you&amp;rsquo;ll see, an integral part in the creation of Lion Ark. We&amp;rsquo;re very happy to have this film, it&amp;rsquo;s a powerful film, it&amp;rsquo;s an exciting film. It&amp;rsquo;s going to subvert a lot of your expectations about both seeing a documentary and about some of the assumptions we had growing up or seeing in our culture.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TVGuide.com</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2013/tvguide-04/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2013/tvguide-04/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
&amp;rdquo;&amp;lsquo;Is there any chance of Grissom popping up in CSI&amp;#8216;s 300th episode? &amp;ldquo;Selena&amp;rdquo;&amp;rsquo;
&amp;rdquo;&amp;lsquo;ADAM:&amp;ldquo;&amp;rsquo; In the flesh? Nah. But the episode, which flashes back to a 14-year-old case, does feature a full-circle shout-out to the man who started it all. &amp;ldquo;[The writers] pay a very sound and beautiful homage to [Grissom],&amp;rdquo; Jorja Fox says. Speaking of Grissom, how is Sara handling the couple&amp;rsquo;s separation this season? &amp;ldquo;Sara is too young to sleep alone,&amp;rdquo; Fox says.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Guide Magazine</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2013/tvguide-03/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2013/tvguide-03/</guid>
      <description>&amp;rdquo;&amp;lsquo;Marg Helgenberger and Jorja Fox answer burning questions about Sara&amp;rsquo;s return and the crime show&amp;rsquo;s killer new season&amp;rdquo;&amp;rsquo;
The most baffling crime on CSI last season wasn&amp;rsquo;t a stabbing or shooting. It was a missing persons case: The show&amp;rsquo;s lead investigator for its first nine seasons, William Petersen (Gil Grissom), left the series halfway through the year, sending CSI&amp;#8216;s ratings slipping and causing concern for its cast and producers.
&amp;ldquo;We look at last season in a way not dissimilar from the fans,&amp;rdquo; admits executive producer Carol Mendelsohn.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CableTV.com</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2013/cabletv-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2013/cabletv-1/</guid>
      <description>Monica Gleberman .. and just ask you, how did you get involved in acting to begin with?
Jorja Fox Oh my goodness. I wanted to act since I was probably four or five years old. I think that the television that sat in the living room of my house was one of the bigger influences in my life. It was definitely a babysitter for me. You know, I grew up in a small town, so there weren&amp;rsquo;t many acting programs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Parade Magazine</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2013/parade-magazine/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2013/parade-magazine/</guid>
      <description>Dog fighting rings, canned hunting, factory farming, and even the cruelty behind shark fin soup have all been topics on the popular CBS drama &amp;ldquo;CSI: Crime Scene Investigation&amp;rdquo;, and actress &amp;ldquo;&amp;lsquo;Jorja Fox&amp;rdquo;&amp;rsquo; takes pride in her shows coverage of these issues. Jorja plays forensic scientist Sara Sidle on the long running series. In real life, she volunteers as an ambassador for Animal Defenders International.
&amp;ldquo;Calling attention to these issueswhether it is on &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; or with Animal Defenders Internationalis a passion of mine,&amp;rdquo; says Jorja.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NewNowNext</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2013/newnownext/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2013/newnownext/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
Looking at your filmography, you’ve been on a ton of great shows with some amazing actors, Reaper, House, Buffy. Was there an actor you worked with that really surprised you?
I’ve been so lucky that I just walked on set after set with just such welcoming actors, and that’s great because you hear horror stories. But I remember having to do a very emotional scene on CSI, and at the time, CSI was the #1 show, 30 million viewers each week, absurd numbers, you would think that if there was one set there would be big egos, it would be that set.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vegan Health and Fitness Magazine</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2013/vegan-health-and-fitness-magazine/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2013/vegan-health-and-fitness-magazine/</guid>
      <description>As per usual, our cover models are more than just pretty faces. They are co-producers of an important new film called How I Became an Elephant. This powerful documentary follows 14-year-old Juliette West who embarks on a journey to learn more about elephants in their native land. After single-handedly raising the funs for her journey, she finds herself in Southeast Asia, meeting and working with her hero, Lek Chailert. Lek is known as &amp;ldquo;The Elephand Lady,&amp;rdquo; and has risked her life and freedom for more than three decades to protect elephants from illegal trade and abuse.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Radio Times</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2013/radio-times/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2013/radio-times/</guid>
      <description>title = &amp;ldquo;Radio Times Its not unheard of in the annals of crime drama for a member of a tight-knit law-enforcement team suddenly to find the tables turned. One of our heroes is a murder suspect themselves. How will they prove their innocence?
Tonight these classic woes befall poor Sara Sidle when a man chats her up in a hotel dining room and is then found dead the next day, with Saras hair in his shower drain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Fanatic</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2013/tv-fanatic/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2013/tv-fanatic/</guid>
      <description>How will CSI shake things up to conclude its 13th season? By putting one of their own in jeopardy, thats how.
On tonights finale Elisabeth Harnoiss Morgan Brody will go undercover (as a hooker, no less) and - SPOILER ALERT! - she may find herself in harms way.
In this exclusive Q&amp;amp;A, actress tells me how the episode is laid out, who shed love to have more scenes with next season and a lot more&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Choice</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2013/tv-choice/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2013/tv-choice/</guid>
      <description>Jorja Fox plays forensic scientist Sara Sidle in CSI: Crime Scene Investigation, a crime drama series that has more than 60 million viewers worldwide. Here, she tells TV Choice how it feels to have such an amazing fan base. But she also reflects on her other roles in ER and The West Wing, and talks about her work as a conservationist campaigner
**CSI: Crime Scene Investigation is currently in its 13th season.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Talk (2 April 2013)</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2013/the-talk/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2013/the-talk/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
Sara Gilbert: Our first guest made a name for herself playing strong female characters on shows like ER and The West Wing, and has been solving crimes for more than a decade as analyst Sara Sidle on the most watched TV show in the world: CSI: Crime Scene Investigation. Take a look.
[Clip from &amp;ldquo;Sheltered&amp;rdquo;]
Gilbert: Please welcome Jorja Fox!
Jorja Fox: &amp;hellip; two hour The Talk special today?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Total TVguide</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2013/total-tvguide/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2013/total-tvguide/</guid>
      <description>Jorja Fox, who plays Sara Sidle, is proud to be part of the planet&amp;rsquo;s favourite show
This week, the CSI team is spooked by a case that brings back memories of their murdered colleague, Warrick Brown. How does that store compare to the rest of this series?
This season is unique, because almost every episode impacts on one of the characters in a personal level. In an episode we shot recently, Sara&amp;rsquo;s ex-boyfriend comes to town, and she has to grapple with that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CSI Files</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2013/csifiles-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2013/csifiles-2/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
&amp;rdquo;&amp;lsquo;CSI Files:&amp;ldquo;&amp;rsquo; The season is winding down. What are some of your favorite moments from this season? Anything you would have liked to do, but werent able to?
&amp;rdquo;&amp;lsquo;Daley:&amp;ldquo;&amp;rsquo; I was happy we brought the dog on the team. Im a real dog lover (as is over half the staff) and Sam was great in his episode. SPOILER: You may even see him in mine!
I personally loved what we did with Saras character this year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Guide</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2013/tvguide-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2013/tvguide-01/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
Question: I know you will probably give me your stock answer about &amp;ldquo;ships&amp;rdquo; and the realities of TV business, but don&amp;rsquo;t you think the break-up of Sara and Grissom on *CSI* was unusually cruel to the long suffering fans of this couple? I know William Petersen won&amp;rsquo;t be back on the show, but would it have been so bad to keep him off-screen like he has been, and let the writers keep their marriage safe and in the background?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Female First</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2013/female-first/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2013/female-first/</guid>
      <description>CSI returns to UK TV tonight, with the American goliath that&amp;rsquo;s spawned not only the rise of the pathology TV show, but also thousands of careers in forensics back to defend its crown on Channel 5.
As she begins to start her latest tour of duty as the devoted Sara Silde on the show, we chatted to star Jorja Fox about being on the show for more than a decade, the world of forensics and her dreams of being a rock and roll star.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Guide</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2013/tvguide-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2013/tvguide-02/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
I&amp;rsquo;m crushed that the *CSI *writers broke up Sara and Grissom! What are they thinking?
Lisa
ADAM: Hopefully, this news will console you. &amp;ldquo;We don&amp;rsquo;t feel like it&amp;rsquo;s over,&amp;rdquo; executive producer Don McGill tells us. &amp;ldquo;We felt the relationship had hit the true rocks and things were really at a breaking point. But they&amp;rsquo;re not divorced or even separated. They&amp;rsquo;re really just taking a very big time out.&amp;rdquo; More good news: The writers aren&amp;rsquo;t planning to throw Sara into any rebound flings and are actually hoping that this relationship hiccup might lure Grissom himself, William Petersen, back to the show.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Digital Spy</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2013/digital-spy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2013/digital-spy/</guid>
      <description>CSI returns to UK screens early next week - Channel 5 will begin airing season 13, which kicks off with thrill-packed premiere &amp;#8216;Karma to Burn&amp;rsquo;, this coming Tuesday. After the events of the season 12 finale, the CSI team find themselves in crisis, but must overcome the odds to rescue Russell&amp;rsquo;s granddaughter and bring the kidnappers to justice.
To mark the show&amp;rsquo;s triumphant return, Digital Spy spoke with CSI star Jorja Fox - who plays Sara Sidle - to get all the scoop on the new season, the show&amp;rsquo;s future and the possibility of a Sara / Grissom reunion&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>&#39;CSI Star Jorja Fox Spills Show Secrets - OMG Insider</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2013/csi-star-jorja-fox-spills-show-secrets-omg-insider/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2013/csi-star-jorja-fox-spills-show-secrets-omg-insider/</guid>
      <description>Thea Andrews: Oh dear! Jorja Fox, who plays Sara Sidle, seems to be in some hot water tonight on CSI
Kevin Fraizer: Jorja, welcome.
Jorja Fox: Hi.
Kevin Fraizer: And your character seems to be in a little bit of trouble. What&amp;rsquo;s going on?
Jorja Fox: You know, I don&amp;rsquo;t know what you&amp;rsquo;re talking about. It&amp;rsquo;s just a little misunderstanding!
Thea Andrews: What&amp;rsquo;d you get up to?
Jorja Fox: It gets completely blown out of proportion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CBS Live Chat</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2013/cbs-live-chat/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2013/cbs-live-chat/</guid>
      <description>[The following is saved quotes]
Q - @ThatIsNotAnExit
@CSI_CBS We&amp;rsquo;ve made a message page to jorja so were wondering if there&amp;rsquo;s a way she could get the link? It&amp;rsquo;s http://weloveyoujorjafox.tumblr.com/ #askjorja
A - @CSI_CBS
.@ThatIsNotAnExit We&amp;rsquo;re up and running in a few minutes. Send us your questions #AskJorja xx.
Q - @JulesSweetzer
working on the show for so long, do you feel like you could be a CSI in real life #AskJorja</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E!Online</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2013/e-online/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2013/e-online/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
Darn it&amp;rsquo;s hard to be a TV fan these days, no? It seems like showrunners are just out to toy with our emotions and &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; was a perfect example tonight as a longstanding fan favorite couple took a (seemingly) one-way trip to splitsville. These are dark days, our friends!
[&amp;hellip;]
Couples Watch: In sad, sad TV couples news, CSI&amp;#8216;s Sara (Jorja Fox) and Grissom (William Petersen) are splitting up. After 13 years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Equals</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2013/tv-equals/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2013/tv-equals/</guid>
      <description>There has always been a great divide amongst the fans of CSI, between those who love Grissom and Sara together and those who, I don’t know, hate romance and kick puppies for fun. Up until last night, the fans of GSR had pretty much won most of the battles in this cold war, but with “Forget Me Not,” this week’s episode, the other side landed a major, heart-breaking victory when Sara revealed that she and Grissom have separated.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EW.com</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2013/ew/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Feb 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2013/ew/</guid>
      <description>Why so sad, Sara?
In Wednesdays episode of &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; on CBS, Sara (Jorja Fox) will deal with her long-distance marriage with Gil (William Petersen) in an episode titled &amp;ldquo;Forget Me Not.&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;The implication is that they have been having a sort of beautiful if not stuck romantic, long-distance marriage,&amp;rdquo; Fox tells EW exclusively. &amp;ldquo;Hes been on the move, leading his nomadic life. But there comes a time when you cant leave a pivotal story suspended forever.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Huffington Post</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2013/huffington-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Feb 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2013/huffington-post/</guid>
      <description>The February 20 episode of &amp;ldquo;CSI: Crime Scene Investigation&amp;rdquo; sees Sara (Jorja Fox) in hot water after a brief encounter with a man leaves her as the prime suspect in his murder case. Even worse &amp;#8212; her interaction with the victim has the team suspecting she&amp;rsquo;s cheating on Grissom (William Petersen).
In The Huffington Post&amp;rsquo;s exclusive clip from Wednesday&amp;rsquo;s Sara/Grissom-centric episode, Morgan (Elisabeth Harnois) points out that as far as the rest of the team is concerned, if Sara cheated on her much-beloved husband, she &amp;ldquo;may as well have cheated on God.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CSI Files</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2013/csifiles-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Feb 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2013/csifiles-1/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
This season has put focus on Jorja Fox&amp;#8216;s Sara Sidle. Despite returning to the lab in Season Ten&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;[[Family Affair]] after a relatively brief exit and marrying her former crime lab supervisor Gil Grissom (William Petersen), the long-distance arrangement for her marriage has taken a toll. &amp;ldquo;We are moving toward some understanding of where Sara is and where the strains are within the relationship,&amp;rdquo; a source close to the show tells CSI Files.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Entertainment Weekly</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2013/entertainment-weekly/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2013/entertainment-weekly/</guid>
      <description>If you&amp;rsquo;re wondering whether Gil Grissoms&amp;rsquo;s heart remains in Las Vegas, you&amp;rsquo;ll finally get an answer on February 20. In the CSI episode titled &amp;ldquo;Forget Me Not,&amp;rdquo; the long-distance &amp;#8212; and recently troubled &amp;#8212; marriage between Sara (Jorja Fox) and Gil (William Petersen, who was last seen on the show via a Skype conversation in 2011) will hit a major turning point. Divorce or reunion? Fox won&amp;rsquo;t spill, but she&amp;rsquo;s glad fans of the romance will get some resolution.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>News Articles (2013)</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2013/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2013/</guid>
      <description>Date Source    February 15 Entertainment Weekly   February 18 CSI Files   February 19 EW.com   February 19 Huffington Post   February 20 E!Online   February 20 TV Equals   February 22 Digital Spy   February 26 Female First   February 26 TV Guide   March 04 TV Guide   April 01 CSI Files   April 02 TV Choice   April 02 Total TVguide   May 15 TV Fanatic   June 02 Radio Times   June 11 NewNowNext   June 11 Vegan Health and Fitness Magazine   August 12 Parade Magazine   September 28 TV Guide Magazine   October 01 TVGuide.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ohio.com</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/ohio-com/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Dec 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/ohio-com/</guid>
      <description>Can you please enlighten me about Jorja Fox/Sara leaving on &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo;? Surely CBS is not abandoning the romance story between her and Grissom after teasing us about it for over a year?! Will Sarah come back to the &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; show or have we seen the last of her? It would be a real bummer if she disappears from the show. I may quit watching if she goes!
1p6,1p6 Before Fox&amp;rsquo;s departure, it was widely reported that she and &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; could not agree on a new contract.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Guide Magazine</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/tv-guide-06/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Dec 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/tv-guide-06/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Doing this show was one of the most rewarding things in my life. I&amp;rsquo;ve been one of the luckiest people in the history of TV getting to play Sara. My character had a full personal life, with a couple boyfriends, a couple meltdowns. She was almost killed a couple of times. They almost blew me up one! I feel like the writers were extremely generous in terms of giving me a lot to do, especially all the interesting relationship stuff between Sara and Grissom.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New York Post</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/new-york-post-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/new-york-post-4/</guid>
      <description>&amp;lsquo;I&amp;rsquo;D WALK through fire for the &amp;#8216;guys&amp;rsquo; I worked with on &amp;#8216;CSI.&amp;rsquo; I could never be sick of them!&amp;rdquo; says Jorja Fox, who has left the popular TV series.
What happens when - after several seasons of making the TV-viewing public come to love and adore you, to feel they know you and, indeed, that they own you - you disappear of your own free will from their screens and their lives?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Philadelphia Inquirer</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/philadelphia-inquirer-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/philadelphia-inquirer-3/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
FD: What a lame way to get Sara off the show. No way would she have done that if she was a real person.
Stan Givens: I loved the Sara Sidle on CSI; I&amp;rsquo;d get rid of Eckley.
[&amp;hellip;]
bklyntransplant: Jonathan, Too bad there&amp;rsquo;s no one cute and perky on CSI &amp;#8212; You&amp;rsquo;d remember her name!
Ellen: Funny, I&amp;rsquo;m from Brooklyn, too, and I was about to say the same thing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pittsburgh Post-Gazette</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/pittsburgh-post-gazette-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/pittsburgh-post-gazette-3/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
Q: Last week, the character Sara Sidle departed &amp;ldquo;CSI,&amp;rdquo; leaving behind a very confused Grissom. Will she be returning or is she out of the show?
- Peggy, Bridgeville
Rob: She&amp;rsquo;s gone as a series regular, but she may return as a guest star.
[&amp;hellip;]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Guide Magazine</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/tv-guide-05/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Oct 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/tv-guide-05/</guid>
      <description>9 Sara Sidle lives on &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; [&amp;hellip;] but now she has competition. Jessica Lucas joins the cast October 11 as curious intern Ronnie Lake. &amp;ldquo;Sara&amp;rsquo;s the one I annoy the most, becuase I ask so many questions,&amp;rdquo; Lucas says. &amp;ldquo;But Jorja&amp;rsquo;s been fantastic, showing me the roles.&amp;rdquo; Ronnie investigates the murder of a homeless man with Sara in her first episode [&amp;hellip;]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Everyday Health</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/everyday-health/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Apr 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2007/everyday-health/</guid>
      <description>How celebs satisfy their cravings without packing on the pounds.
Power Bar Star
&amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; star Jorja Fox needs plenty of energy whether she&amp;rsquo;s surfing or spending on long days on the set.
Fave Snack? &amp;ldquo;I do a lot of the Power Bars and veggies, peanut butter and crackers, and vegetarian beef jerky.&amp;rdquo;
Snack Facts: A Fit &amp;#8216;n Lite Power Bar contains 133 fat-free calories, 6.5 grams of protein, and 18.2 grams of carbs.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>