<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Human Rights on JFO Library</title>
    <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/tags/human-rights/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Human Rights on JFO Library</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 05 Dec 2004 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://jorjafox.net/library/tags/human-rights/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Huckleberry Fund Benefit</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2004/huckleberry-fund-benefit/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Dec 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2004/huckleberry-fund-benefit/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;rdquo;&amp;lsquo;Jorja Fox:&amp;ldquo;&amp;rsquo; Um, the Huckleberry Fund is an amazing organization, they help a lot of teenagers in the Los Angeles area. It&amp;rsquo;s a very, uh, it&amp;rsquo;s a group that gets overlooked a lot and obviously a group with a lot of special needs, very specific needs, um, taking care of medical as well as psychological, developmental stuff. Um, I&amp;rsquo;m lucky enough to have a photograph inside, it&amp;rsquo;s one of my favorite things to get to do, it&amp;rsquo;s my second time doing it. And they just give you a camera and they send you out and you can take pictures of whatever you want; mine are not that good, but uh, then you send it back to them and they develop it and uh, I think it&amp;rsquo;s going to be a night of amazing artwork, uh, not only by the kids, ah, that are represented by the Huckleberry Fund, but professional photographers and, you know, dorks like me that got lucky because we got a camera. &amp;ldquo;(laughs)&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Have a Dream Foundation</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/i-have-a-dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/i-have-a-dream/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The &amp;ldquo;I Have a Dream&amp;rdquo; Program helps children from low-income areas reach their education and career goals by providing a long-term program of mentoring, tutoring, and enrichment with an assured opportunity for higher education.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jorja Fox attended their 6th annual brunch on 18 January 2004.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Five Acres</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/five-acres/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/five-acres/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Five Acres has served vulnerable children and families since 1888. They provide family-centered support services on campus and through outreach programs in homes, at schools and in off-site offices.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Huckleberry Foundation</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/huckleberry/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/huckleberry/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Huckleberry Foundation is named after Huckleberry Finn, an 11-year-old who ran away from home to escape the abuse of his alcoholic father.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This Foundation supports the youth programs of the Division of Adolescent Medicine, Childrens&amp;rsquo; Hospital Los Angeles, which reach out to the &amp;lsquo;Huckleberry Finns&amp;rsquo; of today. For 20 years, the Division has led the way in providing integrated medical and psychological services to disadvantaged and disconnected youth of Los Angeles.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Part of the Huckleberry Fund Benefit is an annual auction; photographs by amateurs and professionals are auctioned off, with the money going to the hospital. Twice now (2003, 2004) Jorja has contributed photographs to the auction.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Penny Lane</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/penny-lane/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/penny-lane/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;Penny Lane Org cares for over 1,500 abused, neglect and abandoned children each year in the Los Angeles area and Antelope Valley, and Jorja For is one of the number one supporters.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;voices-of-our-children:7c15cfa225a1ff3578c57c8ef8ff48ae&#34;&gt;Voices of Our Children&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They have an annual celebrity fund raiser called Voices of Our Children, which entails celebrities reading what those beautiful children have written about their life experiences. Jorja is one of the emotional and powerful celebrities who reads and has helped them now for several years.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jorja has attended the following events:&lt;br /&gt;
* Voices of Our Children 2004&lt;br /&gt;
* Voices of Our Children 2005&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Friends of El Faro</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/el-faro/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/el-faro/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Friends of El Faro has a simple mission &amp;#8212; to help improve the lives of the orphans at El Faro (in Mexico) in any way possible. El Faro 2 (The Lighthouse) was founded in the 1990, when Carmen and Jorge Gonzales opened the doors of their home to a few abandoned children living on the streets. Word spread and in a very short amount of time children were being dropped off in the middle of the night by relatives who could not care for them, or were frightened because of a history of abuse.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In November of 2000, Adam and Leigh Smith started taking trips to visit the children at an orphanage called El Faro 2 in Tijuana, Mexico. Word spread and people from all over Los Angeles began to ask how they could help, and soon &amp;ldquo;Friends of El Faro&amp;rdquo; was born.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Campaign for Burma</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/us-campaign-for-burma/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/us-campaign-for-burma/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;30 Hollywood celebrities ran a campaign from May 1 through May 30 to seek the release of Myanmar&amp;rsquo;s democracy icon Aung San Suu Kyi and push for freedom in the military-ruled nation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The 30-day campaign will see stars such as Will Ferrell, Ellen Page, Judd Apatow, Anjelica Huston, Jennifer Aniston and Rosanna Arquette appearing in video clips on the Internet highlighting human rights issues in Myanmar.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jorja filmed a video with Eric Szmanda which aired on May 11th (day 11). In it, the two CSI stars played a game called &amp;lsquo;forced labor&amp;rsquo; using cards with graphic pictures of alleged abuses in Myanmar.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;day-6:8ee0370e560b26a5fadc69e2bcad2ba9&#34;&gt;Day 6&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Eric Szmanda:&lt;/strong&gt; Alright, want to play a new game?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; Yeah, sure.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Eric:&lt;/strong&gt; Alright, this one&amp;rsquo;s called forced labor. I&amp;rsquo;ll be a Burmese soldier. You will be a Burmese civilian. First, I&amp;rsquo;ll beat and rape your wife. Then, I&amp;rsquo;ll murder your children. Then, I&amp;rsquo;ll burn your village to the ground. I&amp;rsquo;ll make you carry my supplies and ammunition for days, until your feet are raw and bleeding. You will not be fed, and as we walk, you will lead the way, so if we find any landmines, you&amp;rsquo;ll be the first to discover them. If you get sick and slow, I&amp;rsquo;ll beat you. And if you try to escape, I&amp;rsquo;ll kill you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; Why do I have to be the Burmese civilian?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Eric:&lt;/strong&gt; Since the illegal military regime took over? Those are the cards you&amp;rsquo;ve been dealt.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja:&lt;/strong&gt; I don&amp;rsquo;t think I like this game.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Eric:&lt;/strong&gt; No one does.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://link.brightcove.com/services/link/bcpid1517481413/bclid1527697194/bctid1533001469&#34;&gt;Jorja and Eric&amp;rsquo;s video&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Until the Violence Stops: Los Angeles</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/until-violence-stops/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/until-violence-stops/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Until the Violence Stops: Los Angeles&amp;rdquo; (aka UTVS:LA) is the LA organization who organizes and promotes V-Day. A coalition of activists, artists, entertainers, educators, civic leaders and concerned citizens who reside in Los Angeles County, UTVS:LA wants to see Los Angeles become the safest city on earth for women and girls.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;V-Day is a global movement to stop violence against women and girls. V-Day is a catalyst that promotes creative events to increase awareness, raise money and revitalize the spirit of existing anti-violence organizations. V-Day generates broader attention for the fight to stop violence against women and girls, including rape, battery, incest, female genital mutilation (FGM) and sexual slavery.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;see-also:af3d7c55b9feea136b2748fd720254d7&#34;&gt;See Also&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.vday.org&#34;&gt;VDay.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>