<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Online Chat on JFO Library</title>
    <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/tags/online-chat/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Online Chat on JFO Library</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Apr 2001 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://jorjafox.net/library/tags/online-chat/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Yahoo Chat</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2001/yahoo-chat/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Apr 2001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2001/yahoo-chat/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;This chat log was cut short by technical difficulties (dialup connection crashed). Despite promises to provide the full log, Yahoo! never did.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;csi-star-jorja-fox:5200b9530cdc71d40170f5e4ba0d0db4&#34;&gt;&amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; star Jorja Fox&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s got to be a fabulous Spring for actress Jorja Fox. She&amp;rsquo;s in the coolest TV show of the season &amp;#8212; CSI: Crime Scene Investigation &amp;#8212; and one of the most talked about movies of the year &amp;#8212; Memento. But you know, the last few years couldn&amp;rsquo;t have sucked&amp;hellip; In the 99-00 season, she portrayed Secret Service Special Agent Gina Toscano on The West Wing, protecting President Bartlet&amp;rsquo;s youngest daughter. She also spent a few seasons in the late 90s as Dr. Maggie Doyle on ER. Don&amp;rsquo;t miss this chance to chat with Jorja on Tuesday, April 24 at 6pET/3pPT!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;chat:5200b9530cdc71d40170f5e4ba0d0db4&#34;&gt;Chat&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;y_chat_diva:&lt;/strong&gt; Hello! Thanks for joining our chat today with Jorja Fox. Prior to her casting on CSI, Jorja had a recurring role of Secret Service Agent Gina Toscano on The West Wing and prior to that she was Dr. Maggie Doyle on ER. She&amp;rsquo;s also got a role in the cool new flick &amp;ldquo;Memento.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;y_chat_diva&lt;/strong&gt;: Hello everyone, thanks for joining us. Jorja Fox is our guest. She is here and we&amp;rsquo;re almost ready to start, remember, she can only get the questions you type in the &amp;ldquo;ask a question&amp;rdquo; box. So be sure you use that box to talk to Jorja.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;y_chat_diva&lt;/strong&gt;: Okay, let&amp;rsquo;s go. Please welcome Jorja Fox to Yahoo! Chat. Hello and welcome.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;jorja_fox_chat&lt;/strong&gt;: Thanks for hanging out! And I&amp;rsquo;m excited to talk to everybody&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SEZARIN&lt;/strong&gt;: tell me how did you started in this business&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;jorja_fox_chat&lt;/strong&gt;: Oh boy! I knew when I was like five that I wanted to be an actress, and I was one of those kids that would put on shows for anyone in the neighborhood or my family that would watch them! I grew up in a really small town and when I was 16 I moved to New YOrk City. I took classes in New York, and I was really lucky because the first agency I went to had a sign on the door that said &amp;#8216;Do Not Enter, Just Leave Your Package,&amp;rsquo; and I pretended that I didn&amp;rsquo;t see it, and I walked in and they let me in. I was 20 when that happened, and I had been there for about four years distracted&amp;hellip;. And they sent me out on auditions. The first movie I got was called The Kill-Off, and then I didn&amp;rsquo;t work again for about a year after that. And that&amp;rsquo;s how I got started I guess&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ipstenu&lt;/strong&gt;: You said that you wish you were a vegan (in the Venice Magazine article from April 2001), why?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;jorja_fox_chat&lt;/strong&gt;: LOL! I think ultimately because it&amp;rsquo;s an even better way to practice pacifism, but it&amp;rsquo;s really hard on sets to be a strict vegan. So even though I don&amp;rsquo;t eat a lot of dairy, I&amp;rsquo;ll eat things that have dairy products in them like bread, cake, pasta, stuff like that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;dogcat_8&lt;/strong&gt;: Hello Jorja! I love the show and I was wondering&amp;hellip;Have you taken an interest in the work of a CSI being exposed to all the technical terms and tools that go with the job?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;jorja_fox_chat&lt;/strong&gt;: Yes. I&amp;rsquo;ve always been interested in real crime, and the psychology of criminal behavior, and sci fi. And the horror genre. So it&amp;rsquo;s something that I&amp;rsquo;ve continued to be interested in, I read all the time stuff that applies to that and also watch stuff on TV that everybody watches, like The New Detectives&amp;hellip; It&amp;rsquo;s actually really good.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;scottyameron4life&lt;/strong&gt;: are there going to be more seasons of csi&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;jorja_fox_chat&lt;/strong&gt;: Not officially. But we&amp;rsquo;ve done a couple of publicity things that people don&amp;rsquo;t usually get to do unless they&amp;rsquo;ve been renewed. I think it&amp;rsquo;s fairly safe to say that we&amp;rsquo;ll be on next year.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;sawas_sweetheart78&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>