<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Charity on Jorja Fox Library</title>
    <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/tags/charity/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Charity on Jorja Fox Library</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="http://jorjafox.net/library/tags/charity/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Charity Folks</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/charity-folks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/charity-folks/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Charity Folks is the leading online charity auction venue. Inspired by the belief that there&amp;rsquo;s nothing more important than the work nonprofits are doing to improve people&amp;rsquo;s lives, they strive to provide innovative ePhilanthropy solutions that help raise the money &amp;amp; awareness needed for nonprofits to accomplish their mission.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the American Red Cross Disaster Relief Auction for Hurricane Katrina, Jorja Fox donated four items to raise money.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;*Signed Head Shot from CSI star Jorja Fox with a special message&lt;br /&gt;
*Sony DVP-FX1021 - Portable DVD/CD player with 10.2&amp;#8243; LCD, Donated by CSI star Jorja Fox&lt;br /&gt;
*CSI Crew &amp;ldquo;Scrubs&amp;rdquo; Signed and Donated by Jorja Fox&lt;br /&gt;
*CSI DVD&amp;rsquo;s and Signed Hat Donated by Jorja Fox&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jorja Fox, who plays Sara Sidle on CSI, generously donated this signed head shot with a special message&amp;hellip;&amp;ldquo;For the beautiful gulf coast&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Clothes Off Our Back</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/clothes-off-our-back/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/clothes-off-our-back/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;The Clothes Off Our Back&amp;rdquo; is a 501 &amp;copy; 3 organization that hosts charity auctions and private events showcasing today&amp;rsquo;s hottest celebrity attire. Items are put up for bid to the public with proceeds going to select children&amp;rsquo;s charities each year. Clothes Off Our Back was founded by actors and philanthropists Jane Kaczmarek (&amp;lsquo;Malcolm In The Middle&amp;rsquo;) and Bradley Whitford (&amp;lsquo;The West Wing&amp;rsquo;) whose efforts, along with their celebrity friends and auction participants, have helped spread awareness and improve the lives of children across the globe.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In 2003, Jorja Fox donated to raise money for Autism.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>