<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Animal Rights on Jorja Fox Library</title>
    <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/tags/animal-rights/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Animal Rights on Jorja Fox Library</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2011 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://jorjafox.net/library/tags/animal-rights/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>ADI Jorja Fox Addresses Congress</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2011/adi-addresses-congress/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2011/adi-addresses-congress/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I do think that a question that some of you may be asking right now is &amp;ldquo;Well what about my kids? Can&amp;rsquo;t my kids have the same chance I did to go to these traveling circuses?&amp;rdquo; Or maybe these circuses your parents went to. And I thought about this at length, and I think the truth is that our kids look to us for what is right, and our kids look to us for what is fun.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And I think we can do more for our kids if we do the compassionate thing, the respectful thing. These animals do deserve our kindness, and they do deserve our respect. And I think that often our kids understand that better than us most of the time/&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If our kids knew how cruel and violent these events were, I think they&amp;rsquo;d be very disappointed in us, for bringing us to these places.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This bill is the right thing to do, and I urge you to let your congresspeople know that you support it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank you very much.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KPIX - Rescued Lions from Bolivia Arrive at SFO (27 May 2010)</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2010/kpix-rescued-lions-from-bolivia-arrive-at-sfo/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 May 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2010/kpix-rescued-lions-from-bolivia-arrive-at-sfo/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Don Knapp&lt;/strong&gt; And along for the trip tonight was Jorja Fox, of &lt;em&gt;CSI&lt;/em&gt;, she&amp;rsquo;s lending her celebrity and her back.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; I know I am, I&amp;rsquo;m sure all of us are very concerned about everything that&amp;rsquo;s going on in the gulf. The news is so bad, so devastating, and this is just a very small moment where we can look at ourselves as people and say, &amp;ldquo;You know, we&amp;rsquo;re doing something good.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PETA Vegetarian Thanksgiving</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2006/peta-vegetarian-thanksgiving/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2006/peta-vegetarian-thanksgiving/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; One of the most amazing things about today, not only is the food gonna be way better than it ever is at my place &amp;ldquo;(laughs)&amp;rdquo;, and, and, and, far more beautifully prepared, uh, I don&amp;rsquo;t have to cook or do any dishes I don&amp;rsquo;t think - maybe I do, but nobody&amp;rsquo;s told me yet so that&amp;rsquo;d be really fun. &amp;ldquo;(laughs)&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; What a better way to spend this holiday that we really sorta celebrate peace and in a really peaceful way eating vegetarian.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;ldquo;(Jorja is holding a turkey in her lap)&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Off-camera voice&lt;/strong&gt; That&amp;rsquo;s nice.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; You wanna hold her?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Off-camera voice&lt;/strong&gt; I think that you&amp;rsquo;re it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; Okay. &amp;ldquo;(off-camera laughter)&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Off-camera voice&lt;/strong&gt; When you&amp;rsquo;re ready.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; Turkey holding duty. Okay. She&amp;rsquo;s pretty cool.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PETA Gala and Humanitarian Awards</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2005/peta-gala-and-humanitarian-awards/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Sep 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2005/peta-gala-and-humanitarian-awards/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; I&amp;rsquo;ve been a vegetarian since I was nineteen. I come from like a French-Canadian family who ate meat and potatoes every day, three times a day for my entire youth, and I used to tease the heck out of my friends that were vegetarians, and I had a lot of &amp;lsquo;em, and then when I became a vegetarian I just decided that I was going to try and learn as much I could so that when people teased me, maybe I&amp;rsquo;d have a couple of things to say. So PETA very quickly in New York City was an organization that I&amp;rsquo;d heard about, and I read about, and I started going to rallies, and demonstrations, and protests. Um, and I&amp;rsquo;ve been a huge supporter and fan of ever since, y&amp;rsquo;know, you guys rock and I think, you know, you, you do it in such a sort of an alternatively exciting, and fresh, and, um, confrontational way, and that&amp;rsquo;s awesome.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; Hi, I&amp;rsquo;m Jorja Fox, I&amp;rsquo;m an actor, I&amp;rsquo;m a guitar player, I&amp;rsquo;m a surfer, uh, I&amp;rsquo;m a sister and a daughter, and I am a vegetarian.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;VegTV&lt;/strong&gt; How long have you been involved with PETA?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; Well I&amp;rsquo;ve been a fan and supporter and rally-er from many many years, since I&amp;rsquo;ve been a vegetarian, so that&amp;rsquo;s like forty years ago, you know, fifty.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;VegTV&lt;/strong&gt; You haven&amp;rsquo;t been a vegetarian for forty years, you haven&amp;rsquo;t been on this planet for forty years. &amp;ldquo;(Jorja laughs)&amp;rdquo; How long have you been a vegetarian?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; Uh, you&amp;rsquo;re gonna laugh, um, I&amp;rsquo;d say six- eighteen years, yeah.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;VegTV&lt;/strong&gt; Most of your life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; Yeah, yeah, since I was a teenager or so, there you go.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;VegTV&lt;/strong&gt; What was the epiphany, what, what was it made you become vegetarian?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; Y&amp;rsquo;know, it was a meatball sandwich in Brooklyn one afternoon and I don&amp;rsquo;t know what it was about it, but y&amp;rsquo;know I, those little moments, I had friends, and people I&amp;rsquo;d gone out with who were vegetarians and bands that I liked that were vegetarian, Morrisey&amp;rsquo;s here tonight, I&amp;rsquo;m very excited to see them, and uh, and it just kinda all came together over a meatball hero in Brooklyn one day and that was that. And then I was really that person who would tease those people quite a bit, you know, the type of person that&amp;rsquo;d be &amp;#8216;oh, y&amp;rsquo;know, well vegetables are alive too and you&amp;rsquo;re killing vegetables if you eat them&amp;rsquo;, and so I decided to get as educated as I could, cause I, I, you know, didn&amp;rsquo;t want to get the same teasing back at me after I was a vegetarian, so I found PETA very quickly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;VegTV&lt;/strong&gt; Would you do one of those ads for PETA, would you take off your clothes?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; Go naked? Maybe. I might, yeah. I haven&amp;rsquo;t been naked yet actually, so I might. I wouldn&amp;rsquo;t look good enough, but I&amp;rsquo;ll do it, yeah. &amp;ldquo;(laughs)&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;VegTV&lt;/strong&gt; Anything new, anything upcoming for you?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; Um, we got a bunch of CSI coming out, and it&amp;rsquo;s all very horrible, and there&amp;rsquo;s lots of dead people, and we&amp;rsquo;re excited. I have a little play I&amp;rsquo;m producing that&amp;rsquo;s going to London in March 2006.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;VegTV&lt;/strong&gt; What&amp;rsquo;s the play about?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; Uh, it&amp;rsquo;s the story, it&amp;rsquo;s actually based on a true story of a young woman from a small town in England that comes to America in the late sixties to follow her dreams, so it&amp;rsquo;s very, yeah, takes advantage of New York City in the early seventies; it&amp;rsquo;s a good story, lotta heart.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;VegTV&lt;/strong&gt; Anywhere we can follow that? Is it on the Internet?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; Uh, yeah, &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.dearbernard.com/&#34;&gt;dearbernard.com&lt;/a&gt;, it&amp;rsquo;s on the Internet, it&amp;rsquo;s a full length original musical, so we&amp;rsquo;ll see. We put it up in L.A. last year, and we&amp;rsquo;re taking, slowly getting to London in March.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Andean Bear Conservation Project</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/andean-bear/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/andean-bear/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Andean Bear Foundation is a 501&amp;copy;(3) registered non-profit in the USA, and funds the Andean Bear Project&amp;rsquo;s research, conservation, rescue, rehabilitation and release of Andean bears in Ecuador.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jorja Fox narrated a documentary about the bears.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Animal Acres</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/animal-acres/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/animal-acres/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;Animal Acres is a farmed animal sanctuary and compassionate living center located just 45 minutes from Los Angeles. Animal Acres works to promote compassionate living through its farmed animal rescue and refuge efforts, public education and outreach, and advocacy projects to prevent cruelty to farmed animals.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jorja Fox has attended many events for Animal Acres. She is also a supporter of &amp;ldquo;ACI: Animal Cruelty Investigations&amp;rdquo;, a sub-site of Animal Acres.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;lsquo;The way animals are treated to produce meat, milk, and eggs needs to be investigated, exposed, and stopped. I&amp;rsquo;m pleased to be a supporter of ANIMAL CRUELTY INVESTIGATIONS. ACI investigators go to animal &amp;lsquo;crime scenes&amp;rsquo; in our nation&amp;rsquo;s stockyards, factory farms, and slaughterhouses. Documenting what most of us don&amp;rsquo;t want to see, their undercover video footage and evidence of blatant animal cruelty is helping gain needed humane protection for cows, pigs, and chickens, too.&amp;lsquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Actress &amp;amp; Advocate
Jorja Fox&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;2005:d07626381af40fc49883596a6afd8ef0&#34;&gt;2005&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On November 19th, Animal Acres celebrated Thanksgiving in their own way, where guests get to feed a turkey rather than eating one. Special guests included Jorja Fox and Daryl Hannah.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;2007:d07626381af40fc49883596a6afd8ef0&#34;&gt;2007&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jorja Fox was the Gala Chairperson of this year&amp;rsquo;s Animal Acres Gala, which was held to raise money for a farmed animal sanctuary in Los Angeles. August 25th, 2007.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;2008:d07626381af40fc49883596a6afd8ef0&#34;&gt;2008&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jorja Fox attended the Country Hoe Down on Saturday, May 3. She was also a recipient of the 2008 Gandhi Award.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We have all heard the expression &amp;lsquo;STAR POWER&amp;rsquo;, but actress and animal advocate Jorja Fox, has given that phrase new meaning.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a leading actress on West Win, ER, and most recently, CSI, Jorja Fox used her celebrity status to educate millions of viewers about animal abuse &amp;ndash; both by working with producers and writers to air animal issues and video on episodes, and convincing the show to make her character a vegetarian. Her audience is in the millions &amp;ndash; and thanks to Jorja &amp;ndash; millions of people have been educated about the cruelties of canned hunting, dog fighting, and food animal slaughter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jorja was one of Animal Acres first celebrity supporters, lending her voice and participation for our &amp;lsquo;Thankful Turkey Celebration&amp;rsquo; in 2005. In addition to addressing the audience about her personal commitment to vegetarianism, Jorja jumped right into farm chores, helping feed the turkeys and giving bottles to rescued piglets. Jorja has always rolled up her sleeves on other &amp;lsquo;farm chore days&amp;rsquo; too, and she is always willing to do whatever is needed around the farm, from mucking barns to cleaning pigs&amp;rsquo; ears!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Last year, we were honored to have Jorja serve as our 2007 Gala Chair, where she played a vital role is helping us raise over $100,000 for farmed animal rescue and humane enforcement efforts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is hard to find the words to thank Jorja for being such a dedicated friend of Animal Acres, so we gave her our highest honor &amp;ndash; we named a farmed animal after her! We are also honored to give Jorja this year&amp;rsquo;s GANDHI AWARD for her outstanding commitment to providing rescue, sanctuary, and hope for farmed animals.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Animal Defenders International</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/adi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/adi/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Animal Defenders International&lt;/strong&gt; (ADI) is an animal welfare organization, dedicated to international campaigning group that lobbies on issues such as animals in circuses; worldwide traffic in endangered species; vegetarian/vegan diet; factory farming; and pollution. ADI involves itself in international animal rescues as well as educational work on animal welfare, conservation and the environment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;animals-in-entertainment:d6d0d44f5b3165ea450d22e8faf52cca&#34;&gt;Animals in entertainment&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jorja Fox joined ADI when they went to Austin, Texas to look into the issue of circus animal cruelty in Austin. Meeting with City Hall, Jorja Fox presented the Council with scientific evidence and video proof of the mistreatment of animals in the circus. Accepting a letter, report and DVD from Jorja Fox, on behalf of the campaigning group, the City Council agreed to research and consider a ban on animal circuses in light of the evidence presented by ADIs report and undercover footage.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;bolivian-lion-rescue:d6d0d44f5b3165ea450d22e8faf52cca&#34;&gt;Bolivian Lion Rescue&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In May of 2010, Jorja took part in the ADI rescue of former circus lions from Bolivia. Working with ADI San Francisco, Jorja assisted with the media releases, as well as being on hand when the lions were brought to San Francisco.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;operation-lion-ark:d6d0d44f5b3165ea450d22e8faf52cca&#34;&gt;Operation: Lion Ark&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On February 16th, 2011, Jorja was on hand with Bob Barker when the rescue of 25 lions from Bolivia was completed. Both Jorja and Bob personally funded the rescue of the former circus lions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;traveling-exotic-animal-protection-act:d6d0d44f5b3165ea450d22e8faf52cca&#34;&gt;Traveling Exotic Animal Protection Act&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On November 2nd, 2011, Jorja and Bob Barker went to Washington DC to address Congress about the Traveling Exotic Animal Protection Act, which has been introduced to prevent circuses from using exotic (non-native) animals.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Californians for Humane Farms</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/ca-for-humane-farms/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/ca-for-humane-farms/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Californians for Humane Farms is sponsored by the Humane Society of the United States, Farm Sanctuary and other animal protection groups, family farmers, veterinarians, and public health professionals, who have joined together in an effort to launch a statewide initiative for the November 2008 ballot &amp;ndash; one that will improve the lives of millions of farm animals in California.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jorja Fox (among other celebrities) endorses the campaign.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Humane Society of the United States</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/hsus/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/hsus/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;The Humane Society of the United States is the nation&amp;rsquo;s largest and most effective animal protection organization &amp;ndash; backed by 11 million Americans, or one in every 28. Established in 1954, The HSUS seeks a humane and sustainable world for all animals &amp;ndash; a world that will also benefit people. We are America&amp;rsquo;s mainstream force against cruelty, exploitation and neglect, as well as the most trusted voice extolling the human-animal bond.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jorja has attended multiple events for the Humane Society, and in 2010 was given an Animal Advocate Award.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;9-02-10-day:f6962f7e6a1b91b0d67b5b217d2c209e&#34;&gt;9-02-10 Day&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On September 2nd, 2010, Jorja was presented with an award for her work with and for animals, by the Humane Society of the United States.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Wayne Pacelle:&lt;/strong&gt; Well, we&amp;rsquo;re here in Beverly Hills, at the Taste of Beverly Hills. This is a dinner and Gala and event that we&amp;rsquo;re actually giving out three advocates awards to celebrities who are great supporters of the Humane Society and great advocates for animal protection.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; I think for me, right now, especially in leiu of the Gulf disaster and I&amp;rsquo;m very concerned with the world&amp;rsquo;s oceans and the state of the fishing indisutry today, those are issues that are really important to me, I&amp;rsquo;m also personally, really concerned with zoos and circuses. If I had my way, traveling circuses would become a thing of the past, the same way as lead paint and asbestos has become a thing of the past. I think we&amp;rsquo;ve all evolved beyond them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Wayne Pacelle:&lt;/strong&gt; Beverly Hills has always been an outstanding advocate for animal protection. So we&amp;rsquo;re privileged, very priviledged to be here, so we&amp;rsquo;re going to recognize three of our outstanding supporters. Three celebrities who are doing great work, not only in this community but all across the country. We are giving out Animal Advocate Awards to these ambasadors for the community and for animal protection.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; What an amazingly festive and fun event. Thank you, Mr. Mayor for throwing this party, thank you, Humane Society. Beverly Hills is a glamorous city, it&amp;rsquo;s a beautiful city, it&amp;rsquo;s a city of good fortune and where American dreams are realized. And I think it&amp;rsquo;s a testament to this city to have the Humane Society here tonight. It shows Beverly Hills is also a compassionate city and a very kind and progressive looking city. Thank you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>In Defense of Animals</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/in-defense-animals/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/in-defense-animals/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;In Defense of Animals&amp;rdquo; (IDA)&amp;rsquo;s mission is to end animal exploitation, cruelty, and abuse by protecting and advocating for the rights, welfare, and habitats of animals, as well as to raise their status beyond mere property, commodities, or things.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;international-day-of-action-for-elephants-in-zoos-idaez:2ed1aefe37a6eaf54a75bdc5abc9b030&#34;&gt;International Day of Action for Elephants in Zoos (IDAEZ)&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;June 19th 2010 was a global event aimed at bringing mammoth attention to the plight of elephants in zoos and ending their suffering. Jorja was a supporter and said:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hi, Jorja Fox here asking you to support this year&amp;rsquo;s International Day of Action for Elephants in Zoos. These magnificent, magical creatures are some of the world&amp;rsquo;s smartest and also one of the world&amp;rsquo;s most endangered animals. Yet they have long suffered from manâs brutality, including in zoos. Let&amp;rsquo;s evolve beyond zoos. They are arcane, cruel and a tragic waste of an elephant&amp;rsquo;s life. We need to put the focus where it belongs &amp;ndash; on protecting elephants in their natural habitats &amp;ndash; and stop wasting hundreds of millions of dollars on artificial and inadequate zoo displays that will never meet their needs. Instead of cruel confinement and domination, let&amp;rsquo;s offer sanctuary, peace, compassion and hope. The elephants are depending on us, our children our looking to us, and our very own survival as a species depends on it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;see-also:2ed1aefe37a6eaf54a75bdc5abc9b030&#34;&gt;See Also&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.helpelephants.com&#34;&gt;Help Elephants&lt;/a&gt; &amp;ndash; Ban zoos from having elephants&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Orangutan Outreach</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/orangutan-outreach/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/orangutan-outreach/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;Orangutan Outreach is part of BOS International. The purpose of Orangutan Outreach is:&lt;br /&gt;
* To conserve orangutans in their native habitat.&lt;br /&gt;
* To raise and promote public awareness of, and participation in, conservation strategies for orangutans through grassroots campaigns, community involvement and global communication.&lt;br /&gt;
* To collaborate with Indonesian conservationists in the running of orangutan rehabilitation centers.&lt;br /&gt;
* To fund rescue efforts of orangutans confiscated on palm oil plantations.&lt;br /&gt;
* To fund rescue efforts of orangutans held illegally by private owners, whether commercial or individual, who are in direct violation of CITES.&lt;br /&gt;
* To collaborate with zoos and animal parks in North America to promote awareness of orangutan conservation efforts.&lt;br /&gt;
* To use the Internet to provide orangutan-related curriculum materials free of charge.&lt;br /&gt;
* To fundraise locally and globally to support these goals.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;psa:e1d6620919fb073ac96a318252b16d12&#34;&gt;PSA&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jorja Fox recorded a PSA for Orangutan Outreach in the spring of 2008.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jorja Fox: Can you hear that? The Earth. Home to millions of species. Take a moment. Listen. In the rainforests of Borneo, orphan orangutans are being given a second chance, but they need out help. Or we&amp;rsquo;ll be left here all alone. Save the forest, save the planet, reach out and save the orangutans. To find out how you can help, please visit us online at redapes.org.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PETA</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/Peta/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/Peta/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;PETA (People for the Ethical Treatment of Animals) is the largest animal rights organization in the world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;PETA focuses its attention on the four areas in which the largest numbers of animals suffer the most intensely for the longest periods of time: on factory farms, in laboratories, in the clothing trade, and in the entertainment industry. We also work on a variety of other issues, including the cruel killing of beavers, birds and other &amp;lsquo;pests,&amp;rsquo; and the abuse of backyard dogs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jorja Fox is a supporter of PETA and has attended many functions, as well as appearing in a celebrity vegetarian testimonial campaign.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;see-also:4f8b5d445b26942ef8f8eba68543b5a4&#34;&gt;See Also&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://veggietestimonial.peta.org/psa.aspx?CID=a3493023-a4f4-4309-961c-8e4e3528908c&#34;&gt;Investigate Vegetarianism&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Racing Extinction</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/racing-extinction/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/racing-extinction/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In Racing Extinction, a team of artists and activists exposes the hidden world of extinction with never-before-seen images that will change the way we see the planet. Two worlds drive extinction across the globe, potentially resulting in the loss of half of all species. The international wildlife trade creates bogus markets at the expense of creatures that have survived on this planet for millions of years. And the other surrounds us, hiding in plain sight — a world that the oil and gas companies don’t want the rest of us to see. Using covert tactics and state-of-the-art technology, the Racing Extinction team exposes these two worlds in an inspiring affirmation to preserve life as we know it. From the Academy Award® Winning Filmmakers of &amp;ldquo;The Cove&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jorja hosted the premiere of the movie, and has been a vocal advocate for it since 2015.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sea Shepherd Conservation Society</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/sea-shepherd/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/advocacy/sea-shepherd/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Sea Shepherd Conservation Society was formed when Captain Paul Watson founded the Earth Force Society in 1977 in Vancouver BC, Canada. The original mandate of both organizations was marine mammal protection and conservation with an immediate goal of shutting down illegal whaling and sealing operations, but Sea Shepherd later expanded its mission to include all marine wildlife. The Sea Shepherd Conservation Society was formally incorporated in the United States in 1981 in the state of Oregon.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Skin Trade</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/self/skin-trade/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/self/skin-trade/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;Originally titled Pets on Your Plate, Skin Trade is a documentary.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;synopsis:8a298d70b64dc609fcf2b22e90659c9d&#34;&gt;Synopsis&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All of the dead animals in California &amp;ndash; including out pets &amp;ndash; along with their diseases, chemicals and drugs, toxins and bacteria, are cooked in a stew pot and rendered into protein meal and fat, and then fed to animals in the human food chain.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;review:8a298d70b64dc609fcf2b22e90659c9d&#34;&gt;Review&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The documentary film “Skin Trade”, an exposé of the fur industry, recently premiered in Los Angeles. It seems absurd that in 2010, there is a need for a documentary film about fur. Fur is one of the most obvious cruelties perpetuated against animals. It’s shocking that people still wear fur, but unfortunately they do.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Skin Trade” covers the fur industry like no other film has ever done – from the history of the fur trade to consumer fraud to the environmental toll of tanneries to truth-in-labeling legislation – and features several activists and celebrities who explain why fur sucks, such as Rory Freedman, John Feldmann, Alexandra Paul, James Cromwell, Jorja Fox, Peter Young, Matt Rossell, Ingrid Newkirk and Dennis Kucinich. An extremely well made film, “Skin Trade” is comprehensive, thought provoking, entertaining and enraging.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Producer Shannon Keith, an animal rights attorney who defends activists and pursues justice for abused animals, spoke with me about the concept behind “Skin Trade,” her second documentary (her first, “Behind the Mask”, covered the animal liberation movement in the U.S. and U.K).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I wanted to make a film about an issue that is winnable for us. If we can end the fur trade, it will be one big step towards ending animal cruelty. No one can argue there’s any good reason for fur.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Skin Trade” systematically debunks the most common myths around fur, such as warmth, fashion, and the Canadian Fur Council’s laughable “Fur is Green” campaign. The film features designer Donna Salyers, whose luxurious faux furs have the same heat retention value as animal furs. Lab tests compare the “R value” of different pile lengths, and show that animal fur and faux fur retain heat at same value.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Other interviews with designer Todd Oldham, former fashion journalist Julia Szabo, and Patrick Byrne, CEO of Overstock.com, reveal the economic pressures placed on designers and retailers by the fashion industry’s lust for animal fur. Oldham in particular speaks frankly about the financial consequences and the fashion magazine “media blackout” he endured when he opted to forgo fur. Another fashion scandal, well detailed in the film, erupted when clothing made in China and labeled “faux” was proven to be cat, dog, raccoon or wolf fur. Fortunately ethical style maven Joshua Katcher is on hand to provide hilarious ‘person on the street’ interviews with New Yorkers on why they wear, or don’t wear, animal fur.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The claim that fur is “green” is one of the latest marketing tricks perpetuated by the fur industry. In truth processing fur uses vast amounts of water, chemicals, metals, dyes, solvents and acids. Jan Schlichtmann, an attorney whose high-profile case against corporate polluters was dramatized in the feature film “A Civil Action”, explains that leather and fur tanneries use hundreds of toxic chemicals that end up in the soil and water. Chemicals are necessary so the skin and hair does not smell, rot and decompose. (After all, it is the skin of a dead animal.) Also debunked by several experts is the fur industry’s marketing claim that they support the preservation of Native American culture and provide aid to North American tribes. Aside from rock-solid evidence from these and other authoritative sources, “Skin Trade” includes archival and new undercover footage exposing the cruelty, fraud and deceptions of fur farmers, trappers, and retailers. The film took close to three years to complete, in part because the producers insisted on presenting the most accurate and updated information on the practices used in obtaining and raising animals for fur. No film on the subject would be complete without some heartbreaking scenes of the cruel and unhealthy conditions that animals endure, and the brutal ways they are killed. Perhaps the most enraging scenes in the film are hidden-camera footage from fur salons, where people posing as customers are repeatedly told by salespeople that the animals are well cared for and that they are humanely euthanized just like a dog or cat at a veterinarian’s office. Sadly, that is nowhere near how the animals are actually killed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As difficult as it can be to watch some scenes, for Shannon Keith, making the film was itself an ordeal. “I definitely had my ups and downs. Some of the footage really got to me. We had undercover footage, shot in China, of a worker killing a dog for fur. I couldn’t function for a little while. But no matter how hard it is to watch, I owe it to each and every one of these animals that are no longer with us. I have to tell their story. I had to do it. I had no other choice. I just had to keep on going.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The most powerful documentaries alI inspire the viewer to challenge their beliefs and take action. I asked Shannon if she had any advice for people who have seen “Skin Trade.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“In the film I interviewed Representative Jim Moran, who is sponsoring a bill called The Truth in Fur Labeling Act, H.R. 2480. Currently items of clothing that cost under $150 do not have to be labeled if they are animal fur, which is how real fur was sold to consumers who thought it was faux. This bill will require every product to be accurately labeled. I suggest that people hop on this legislation right now and get on your reps to cosponsor it.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Also, there is an anti-fur protest in practically every city all over the country every weekend. If you see someone wearing a fur coat, don’t just walk by. Ask them if they know how their fur was killed. Get the message out. There are people who just don’t know. They don’t. If they knew, they’d probably stop supporting the industry. Fur is ridiculous, cruel, not fashionable, and if you buy it, you’re being defrauded.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ndash; Credit: &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.elephantjournal.com/2010/03/skin-trade-how-much-is-your-skin-worth/&#34;&gt;Elephant Journal&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>