<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Recaps on Fans of Le Fox Library</title>
    <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/categories/recaps/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Recaps on Fans of Le Fox Library</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 27 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://jorjafox.net/library/categories/recaps/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Immortality (Part 1)</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/immortality-part-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/immortality-part-1/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis## We start with a &amp;lsquo;normal&amp;rsquo; episode of CSI. Finn is dead, D.B. Russell is leaving to work for the CSI: Cyber people, Sara is applying for a &amp;lsquo;key position&amp;rsquo; And then it all goes to hell with a suicide bomber.
We find Grissom working on a boat in San Diego, helping catch people illegally trapping sharks for shark fin soup. The CSIs that show up don&amp;rsquo;t mention Nick, who is their head last we heard.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Immortality (Part 2)</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/immortality-part-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/immortality-part-2/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Unlike the last time Grissom was mentioned in the lab , this time everyone is angry at Grissom because of Lady Heather. However they allow him in the room when Heather is interrogated.
She claims there was an intruder in her home whom she attacked and then ran off, not calling the cops because of recent experiences. Heather needles Sara until Sara breaks and leaves the room, promising to get Heather.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The End Game</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/the-end-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/the-end-game/</guid>
      <description>George Eads&amp;rsquo; final episode*  Synopsis## The CSI unit faces the final showdown with the Gig Harbor killer whose motives are finally revealed. Also, Nick makes a decision that will affect the entire team moving forward.
With Nick being courted by San Diego to lead up their lab, Finn gets a package from her mother that is actually from Paul Winthrop, the Gig Harbor Killer, last seen limping away from the fatal shooting of his brother, Jared Briscoe can help.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Under My Skin</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/under-my-skin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/under-my-skin/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis## The CSI team investigates a murder with ties to two teenaged kidnapped girls.
Cara and Lexi Nolan are in Vegas with their dad&amp;rsquo;s credit card. When Pete Corday (aged 23), a young man who went off with the younger sister, Cara (aged 13), turns up dead, the hunt is on for the girls, who happen to the the daughters of John Nolan, director for the crime lab in San Diego.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Last Ride</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/the-last-ride/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/the-last-ride/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis## A woman, Eva Montrose, is found dead of asphyxiation from being painted solid silver and swallowing it. The paint used was special, eco-friendly, car chrome paint. Based on the bruise pattern on her back and the shards of headlamp in her arm, the CSIs track down a classic Packard car and it&amp;rsquo;s owner&amp;hellip; Eva&amp;rsquo;s ex-boyfriend, Carlo Derosa.
Sara and Finn talk to Carlo and his brother, Aron, who own a collection of classic cars, including the Packard.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hero to Zero</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/hero-to-zero/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/hero-to-zero/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis## A homeless man is harassed by some masked street thugs, only to be saved by a young man dressed as a superhero. Sara and Nick find the hero, beaten to death, but are able to identify the barefoot homeless man when he returns to try and get his cart, and learn that the assailants drove off in a red truck.
While looking for more evidence, Morgan Brody and Greg stumble across two more heroes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Merchants of Menace</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/merchants-of-menace/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/merchants-of-menace/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis## The CSI team investigates a homicide at a convention for people who collect macabre murder memorabilia. Morgan Brody and D.B. Russell are first on the scene to investigate a man found dead in the car at his own own convention. Damon Harlow, a student of the psychology of serial killers, was dating the sister of a victim of the killer whose car he was found dead in.
Damon was found dead in the car of Lucas Reem, the killer who&amp;rsquo;d killed Nora Water&amp;rsquo;s sister, stabbed to death by a bone from Lucas, sharpened into a blade.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Greater Good</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/the-greater-good/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/the-greater-good/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Russell&amp;rsquo;s daughter, Maya (the mother of Kaitlyn who was once kidnapped
Hodges finds out that Rebecca was not just a kidnapped victim turned Stockholm, but the maker of the fake evidence strings the Gig Harbor boys used. In addition, she ran an escort service, from which the killers selected their victims. He and Morgan discover the bodies of the missing girls and Shaw&amp;rsquo;s prints.
Shaw, working with the brothers, picks up Maya at the Russell house, but doesn&amp;rsquo;t know Maya&amp;rsquo;s wearing a wire.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dead Woods</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/dead-woods/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/dead-woods/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Abby Fisher, the sole survivor of a mass murder when her father, Barry. killed the family on a camping trip, is involved in a robbery gone bad with her bad-boy-boyfriend, Slade. While Sara, who worked the case a decade ago, is upset (she hates Slade), she&amp;rsquo;s stunned to learn that Abby now remembers details about the case. Abby remembers that someone picked her up and put her in the sleeping bag, not knowing she was still alive, but the man had a beard and a smell that was not her father&amp;rsquo;s.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Angle of Attack</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/angle-of-attack/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/angle-of-attack/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis## A &amp;lsquo;hit and run&amp;rsquo; is found on the streets of Vegas, but curiously matches none of the markers one would expect. The case only gets odder when they determine the man fell from a building blocks away, being thrown through glass thick enough to take a bullet. At first the lab suspects a missile, but they determine it&amp;rsquo;s a Squirrel Suit and manage to ID the deceased: Captain Robert Holland, Air Force.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dead Rails</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/dead-rails/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/dead-rails/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis## After digging his way out of a shallow grave, Jimmy Turelli stumbled out of the desert and to a road, only to be hit by a speeding car and killed. The trace evidence puts him as a billiards player, likely a member of a tournament run by Elise Massey (special guest Sharon Osbourne), but instead he paid for the entry of a player named &amp;lsquo;The Hornet&amp;rsquo; for Elise Massey (who neglected to mention this before).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Let&#39;s Make A Deal</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/lets-make-a-deal/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/lets-make-a-deal/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis## The CSIs investigate a murder at the Clark County jail after an inmate stumbles upon a body while running away from officers.
Sara Sidle Review## Sara Sidle does not appear in this episode.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rubbery Homicide</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/rubbery-homicide/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/rubbery-homicide/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis## A man, Nelson Kern, is found stripped to his boxers in an alley, having been slashed to death. But with so little blood on his person, the scene is very odd. It gets odder when they find a life sized rubber outfit in the dumpster. An outfit that fits Mr. Kern.
The outfit is based on a model from the 80s named Charlene, which is the same name Kern used when dressed up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Road To Recovery</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/road-to-recovery/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/road-to-recovery/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis## The CSI team investigates the death of a woman full of alcohol and drugs in a pool at a rehab facility
Sara Sidle Review## Sara Sidle does not appear in this episode.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Twin Paradox</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/the-twin-paradox/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/the-twin-paradox/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis## The Gig Harbor Killer is back. Twin brothers Jared Brisco (the confessed killer) and Paul Winthrope (the free lawyer) both argue that Jared is innocent.
This time he calls 911 before he murders a woman, and like before, stages the crime scene. Sara and Nick are first on the scene and collect the evidence. Since D.B. Russell believes the initial killing was done by the brothers together, they now feel than the one un-jailed brother has a new partner.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Girls Gone Wilder</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/girls-gone-wilder/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/girls-gone-wilder/</guid>
      <description>This episode was delayed two weeks due to football*  Synopsis Sara, Morgan, and Finn are attending a CSI conference in town and go the hotel early to enjoy mimosas, a spa treatment, and relaxation before getting down to work. While there, they see Jane Snyder. Sara does not want to see Jane, but alas the woman is excited to see her old friend. On the other hand, Finn runs into an old friend with whom she regularly hooks up at conventions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Book Of Shadows</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/the-book-of-shadows/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/the-book-of-shadows/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis The CSI team suspects foul play when a chemistry teacher’s science experiment goes horribly wrong.
Sara Sidle Review## Sara Sidle does not appear in this episode.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bad Blood</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/bad-blood/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/bad-blood/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Sara and Greg arrive on scene to find the dead &amp;lsquo;Jack Smith&amp;rsquo; in a pool of blood, shot in the neck, in an apartment covered in blood. When they examine the body, Sara notices the victim&amp;rsquo;s eyes were bleeding and calls the CDC. The two are quickly put in special suits and transported to a hospital as they may be infected. The evidence from the case is at risk, since the CDC generally destroys everything to prevent contamination.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Buzz Kill</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/buzz-kill/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/buzz-kill/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Sara and Nick work the case of the children and wife of a marijuana dispensary owner who are abducted. As he scrambled to get the money for their safe return, the security guard noticed and shoot the abductor&amp;rsquo;s messenger. Curiously, the dead woman has no fingerprints and no ID so she cannot be identified easily. When they do track her down, she too was being blackmailed into the work, her brother having been kidnapped and later killed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The CSI Effect</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/the-csi-effect/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/the-csi-effect/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis A notorious serial slayer, brought to justice by Russell and Finn years ago, faces imminent execution &amp;ndash; until a cunning copycat casts his guilt into serious doubt &amp;ndash; and casts a shadow over Russell&amp;rsquo;s previous investigation.
The Gig Harbor Killer, Jared Briscoe, murdered 7 college students and staged his last three crime scenes to look like CSI had already been there.
Sara Sidle Review Sara and Nick process the primary crime scene, with Sara working the blood.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dead In His Tracks</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/dead-in-his-tracks/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/dead-in-his-tracks/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis The CSIs investigate a present-day crime with ties to a mob heist that occurred 25 years ago, out in Ellis Springs. Back in 1989, a trio of local kids got tangled in a heist, where the loot was never recovered and one of them (Scotty Gates) was presumably killed as he was never seen again. Of the survivors, Roger Mathers had moved to Texas, but when his solar-panel company started failing, high-tailed it back to Nevada, and ended up dead near the shack where the kids ran into the mob all that time ago.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kitty</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/kitty/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/kitty/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis The CSIs investigate the cyber-related murder of a prominent casino owner’s wife and receive help from the FBI’s Cyber Crime Division.
Sara Sidle Review Sara Sidle does not appear in this episode.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Consumed</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/consumed/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/consumed/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis A somewhat disturbed man named Owen Linder claims he was abducted and a hunk of flesh cut off his leg and eaten in front of him. While Nick and Greg are dismissive, Dr. Robbins is not. After all, he&amp;rsquo;s got a partly eaten arm in the morgue with the same wound pattern as Owen. Not only is Owen telling the truth, and is a member of &amp;lsquo;Vore&amp;rsquo; culture (vorarephilia &amp;ndash; aka people who get off on eating/being eaten by other people), he knows the arm&amp;rsquo;s owner: Dennis Hagel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Fallen</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/the-fallen/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/the-fallen/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Jacob Baker, one of the kids who pointed lasers at airplanes in &amp;ldquo;Keep Calm and Carry-On&amp;rdquo; has been arrested for totaling a politician&amp;rsquo;s BMW. While D.B. Russell is collecting him, a teenager walks into the police department and starts shooting people. He ends up in an interrogation room with the shooter and an injured Baker.
The station is on lockdown, but Russell is allowed to call Jim Brass so the shooter can make demands.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Uninvited</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/uninvited/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/uninvited/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis The CSIs are called to investigate when an entire family is reported to have been missing for a month.
Sara Sidle Review Sara Sidle does not appear in this episode.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Long Road Home</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/long-road-home/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/long-road-home/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis A woman is found dead in a tour bus, after a night with a band, and another woman named Tangerine is missing. The driver of the bus is found, but no one actually knows the name of the band (they paid for the bus in cash) or how to get a hold of them. When a signature on the dead woman&amp;rsquo;s breast is ID&amp;rsquo;d as Gene Simmons, he&amp;rsquo;s brought in and explains the event was fake.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Killer Moves</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/killer-moves/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Mar 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/killer-moves/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis The CSIs investigate the murders of an Elvis impersonator and a bird that are strangely connected. Multiple killings in multiple cities lead the CSIs to find a connection between Greg&amp;rsquo;s former pastime, chess, a chess tour, and a disgraced chess grand master. But the clues are not what they seem, when Greg&amp;rsquo;s former mentor becomes a suspect and then a clue.
The killer turns out to be the woman running the chess tour, murdering out of hatred of the misogyny of the chess world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Love For Sale</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/love-for-sale/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/love-for-sale/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Nick and Greg investigate the death of a 16-year-old girl with ties to a brothel.
Sara Sidle Review Sara Sidle does not appear in this episode.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>De Los Muertos</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/de-los-muertos/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/de-los-muertos/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis When Doc Robbins attends a funeral for a friend&amp;rsquo;s daughter, he gets wrapped up in helping determine how Ana Ortiz died. Nick goes with him to a border town in Mexico being torn apart by drug wars. Sadly, Doc Robbins determines the girl suffered symptoms of drug use, but it turns out to be heavy metal poisoning. They find the same trace on Ana as they do on dead drug cartel members, and prove that she was at the same crime scene.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Boston Brakes</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/boston-brakes/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/boston-brakes/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis The CSIs are called to investigate a car crash and are shocked to discover the victim is someone they know.
Sara Sidle Review Sara Sidle does not appear in this episode.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Keep Calm and Carry-on</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/keep-calm-and-carry-on/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/keep-calm-and-carry-on/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis An inbound plane&amp;rsquo;s passengers become the victims of an onboard thief, but when one of the passengers is found dead, the petty crime turns into a murder investigation.
On a flight to from Newark to Las Vegas, Janet Riggins (a local) is hit on by a young man (Kenny Green) who is later robbed on the flight. While she does not appear to be missing anything, she is found dead on the side of the road by the airport, seemingly having been thrown from a fast moving vehicle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lost Reindeer</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/lost-reindeer/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/lost-reindeer/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis When a man is found murdered at an elaborate holiday party complete with real snow and live reindeer, the CSI team is brought in to investigate.
Sara Sidle Review Sara Sidle does not appear in this episode.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Girls Gone Wild</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/girls-gone-wild/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/girls-gone-wild/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis## The episode opens with Morgan Brody rushing through the lab to tell D.B. Russell that Sara was involved in a shooting in Larkston, but there&amp;rsquo;s still no word on Finn. DB and Nick take a helicopter out to find Sara has been grazed by a bullet, but Finn is missing. We cut to Finn, who is beaten and bloodied, walking down a desert road, only to be hit by a car.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Check In and Check Out</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/check-in-and-check-out/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/check-in-and-check-out/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis A series of grisly but apparently unrelated murders, which all take place in the same seedy motel room, have the team wondering if the room really is a demonic an deadly site that &amp;lsquo;possesses&amp;rsquo; its inhabitants.
Sara Sidle Review Sara Sidle does not appear in this episode.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Helpless</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/helpless/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/helpless/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis The discovery of a bludgeoned, bloody corpse inside a &amp;lsquo;human hamster ball&amp;rsquo; (a six-foot tall, clear plastic ball) has the CSIs scratching their heads. Zach Fisk was a purveyor of the sexual arts, and made videos helping to teach people some &amp;hellip; exotic ways of orgasming. But Lady Heather he is not. Not only does Fisk die, but so does Melody Davis, his playmate.
Meanwhile, Sara and Morgan Brody team up with Dawn Banks (played by Sherry Stringfield) of swing shift to handle an unsolved, serial, rape case.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Under a Cloud</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/under-a-cloud/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/under-a-cloud/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis During a torrential downpour, Sara pulls the case of a man pulled out of a flood channel with a &amp;lsquo;suspicious&amp;rsquo; head injury. While he&amp;rsquo;s alive, they treat it like a crime scene, and Sara is at the hospital when he arrives. While the ER staff works on the patient, Sara begins to go through his belongings, only to find a bomb in his backpack. As she announces this to the crowded ER, the power (which had been flickering all across Las Vegas due to the storm) goes out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Passed Pawns</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/passed-pawns/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/passed-pawns/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis After a homeless man picks up a quick $350,000 at the blackjack tables, he&amp;rsquo;s found dead in an alley and the money is missing &amp;ndash; but it&amp;rsquo;s not a simple mugging.
Sara Sidle Review Sara appears in one scene and overlooks the crime scene photos with Morgan Brody. In doing so, she spots inconsistencies with the current theory, and gives Morgan an idea that perhaps they&amp;rsquo;ve arrested the wrong man.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Frame by Frame</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/frame-by-frame/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/frame-by-frame/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis## Gwen Onetto is found murdered in front of a miniature casino model. The model is of the Premiere, a casino that never was, because Jack Witten was accused of murdering a young woman fourteen years ago.
When D.B. Russell arrives, Jim Brass explains that fourteen years ago, Jack was a suspect in a similar murder, but they had no evidence. Sara , having wandered away from Greg, is exploring the house alone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Last Supper</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/last-supper/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/last-supper/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis## The name of the hit cooking show, &amp;lsquo;Slice and Dice,&amp;rsquo; takes on a grim new meaning when a sliced-and-diced former contestant is incorporated into a &amp;lsquo;special challenge&amp;rsquo;.
Sara Sidle Review Sara Sidle does not appear in this episode.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Torch Song</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/torch-song/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/torch-song/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis## When a fire breaks out at a Las Vegas nightclub, it&amp;rsquo;s every man for himself, resulting in multiple deaths not from the fire itself but from the escaping mob and smoke inhalation. Among the dead include two band members (front man and bass player), a white 18-year old Kevin, and a young Latino man named Timo Pedia. The kicker? The band is a white supremacist hate core band: White Rising.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Take the Money and Run</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/take-the-money-and-run/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/take-the-money-and-run/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis## A high stakes game of Texas No-Limit Hold&amp;rsquo;em at the Four Kings Casino ends with a heist, when a motorcyclist, Clint Tyree, steals over a million in cash and kills the guard, Paul Branston. He doesn&amp;rsquo;t make out alive, however, as a security guard shoots at him causing him to crash on Fremont street. The shots don&amp;rsquo;t kill him, or even hit him, but the thief collapses anyway, dead.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Devil and D.B. Russell</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/the-devil-and-db-russell/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/the-devil-and-db-russell/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis The episode cuts between past and present, flashing back to the events immediatly following &amp;lsquo;Skin in the Game&amp;rsquo; while showing us a funeral where the CSIs are noticably distraught.
In the past, both Jim Brass and Conrad Ecklie have trouble keeping their emotions in check, as their daughters, Morgan and Ellie, are held hostage by serial killer intent on completing his twisted homage to &amp;lsquo;Dante&amp;rsquo;s Inferno&amp;rsquo;. The entire lab takes the case personally, with even David Hodges complaining that Morgan was undercover (not a role for a CSI).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Skin in the Game</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/skin-in-the-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/skin-in-the-game/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis As Russell and his team investigate a series of murders, one of their own confronts peril on a dangerous undercover mission to get close to the killer.
Sara Sidle Review Sara Sidle does not appear in this episode.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ghost of the Past</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/ghost-of-the-past/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/ghost-of-the-past/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis A group of ghost hunters explore the lair of deceased serial killer, Walter Simms, trying to contact his spirit and film it to put on the Internet. Instead, one of them is brutally murdered, strung up on a meat hook just like the boys Simms killed twenty years ago. Jim Brass worked on the original case. The ghost hunters claim it&amp;rsquo;s proof of the &amp;lsquo;other side&amp;rsquo; contacting the living.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fearless</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/fearless/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/fearless/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis David Hodges fiancee, Elisabetta, is at a spiritual seminar/retreat run by Alan Quinn, sans Hodges. While she&amp;rsquo;s in the all natural mud springs with another man, Santo, the dead body floats to the surface.
Justin Wade had attended as part of a corporate retreat, but wasn&amp;rsquo;t a fan of the New Agey aspects, and skipped out on the firewalk, upsetting his teammates. After spending some time in the mud springs (and spurning the advances of a coworker), Justin went back to the firewalk and attempted it and somehow fell into the coals, killing himself in the process.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Backfire</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/backfire/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/backfire/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis When the CSIs investigate a triple homicide, Russell has to find a way to connect with a 6-year-old girl who was the sole survivor and witness.
Sara Sidle Review Sara Sidle does not appear in this episode.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sheltered</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/sheltered/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/sheltered/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis When a young camper, Carl Abrams, is stalked and slain in a remote area populated by Doomsday Preppers, the team investigates an underground bunker that holds several shocking surprises. Carl was dumped by an underpass by a man wearing night vision goggles, and died from having one of his hands cut off (the other was cut off anti-mortem). His leg had also been ripped apart by a bear trap.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dead of the Class</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/dead-of-the-class/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/dead-of-the-class/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis The CSIs join David Phillips at his high school reunion when he discovers the prom queen’s been murdered.
Sara Sidle Review Sara Sidle does not appear in this episode.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Last Woman Standing</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/last-woman-standing/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Feb 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/last-woman-standing/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Peter Coe, a professional poker player, lost big in the Palermo Poker Classic (PPC) before dying from having his neck cut open in the elevator of his hotel. The only problem? He was in the elevator alone. His friend (and virtual neice) Eva Rendell, the only woman left in the PPC, was at the hotel with Coe, but left before he got on the elevator. David Hodges solves the locked room mystery by determining the killer threw a playing card (the Ace of Spades) to slice Coe&amp;rsquo;s throat as the doors closed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Forget Me Not</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/forget-me-not/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/forget-me-not/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Sara is accused of murder of her aquantaince Taylor Wynard, with whom she had celebrated her birthday. Taylor&amp;rsquo;s murder was part of an elaborate plot created by Ronald Basderic to discredit Sara and pave the way for her own murder. Basderic planned the murder for months and in the end is tripped up by the CSIs working together.
Sara Sidle Review## Celebrating her birthday alone at a hotel, Sara is approached by Taylor Wynard, who buys her a mini-cake.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Exile</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/exile/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Feb 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/exile/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Cuban singing sensation Silvana is about to make her U.S. debut at Estefan&amp;rsquo;s Vegas nightclub, much to the ire of the Cuban exile community, led by Willie, who considers her a tool of the Cuban government. But when Silvana&amp;rsquo;s sister Marta is tortured, poisoned and killed, it seems that Silvana has also become the target of a vengeful killer. Marta was killed elsewhere and her body brought to Silvana&amp;rsquo;s dressing room, staged in one of her dresses at her vanity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>In Vino Veritas</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/in-vino-veritas/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Feb 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/in-vino-veritas/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis A couple goes to a party with the passcode of &amp;lsquo;decadance.&amp;rsquo; As one might suspect, it’s a party for wealthy dilletants. As one may not guess, it was a private auction for rare wine, held at the Vogel mansion. In the wine celler, some expensive wine is revealed to a party goer, who says he’ll pay anything for it. Of course, that doesn’t work out when the seller is found dead in a wine barrel, shot at by some young punks in an alley, well decomposed and grotesque.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Double Fault</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/double-fault/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jan 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/double-fault/</guid>
      <description> Synopsis The CSIs need to ace the case involving a rising tennis star. Meanwhile, the CSIs are surprised to hear Hodges is engaged to an Italian bombshell.
Sara Sidle Review  Sara Sidle does not appear in this episode.*  Character Notes  Coming Soon  Quotes  Coming Soon*  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dead Air</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/dead-air/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/dead-air/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis It was a dark and stormy night in Las Vegas, when Theresa Shea, a news anchor for KVKC died on set, on a closed set. While presenting the news on the storm, the power went out. When it came back up, Theresa was dead of a single puncture wound to the back of the neck. No one else was in the room.
Sara and D.B. Russell are the leads on the case, but it&amp;rsquo;s an all-hands-on-deck case, especially since almost everyone has a motive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Risky Business Class</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/risky-business-class/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Dec 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/risky-business-class/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis It&amp;rsquo;s a relatively slow night for the CSIs, until a plane crashes at Tresser Park, a mile away from the Strip. NTSB Investigator Doug Wilson is brought in to help work the case. The plane took off from Las Vegas airport, headed to Chicago, but cited an unspecified emergency. Then there was radio silence, and the plane just missed running into a tower at the Mediterranean Hotel before crashing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Strip Maul</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/strip-maul/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/strip-maul/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis It&amp;rsquo;s a busy night in Vegas and the CSIs are working the Strip with the police to help keep the peace. Nick bags a hooker and a drug dealer, while Sara finds a drugged out kid wearing a stuffed horse head. Then they&amp;rsquo;re both called to the scene of a guy swinging his father&amp;rsquo;s severed head around outside a casino. The head is fake, but in the chase to arrest him, the CSIs find Keith Dobson shot dead in a car.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CSI on Fire</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/csi-on-fire/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/csi-on-fire/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis When five bodies are found in what appears to be a meteor site in the middle of the desert, CSI Finlay recognizes one of the casualties, prompting her to revisit her past.
Sara Sidle Review Sara Sidle does not appear in this episode.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fallen Angels</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/fallen-angels/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/fallen-angels/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis A reverend is found dead on Warrick&amp;rsquo;s gravestone, sending the CSIs into turmoil as they investigate the life of Warrick&amp;rsquo;s widow, Tina. Tina&amp;rsquo;s life has gone downhill. After Warrick&amp;rsquo;s death, she quit her job as a nurse and now lives with Eli in Warrick&amp;rsquo;s old house. The reverend, who was none too clean himself, was killed by the local crime boss in a convoluted punishment for his son&amp;rsquo;s life of non-crime.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pick and Roll</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/pick-and-roll/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/pick-and-roll/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis The coach of the WLVU basketball team is murdered not long after he has an argument with DB&amp;rsquo;s son, Charlie, who happens to be on the team. Making matters worse, Charlie&amp;rsquo;s new girlfriend is a hooker who is also sleeping with the coach. As the case unfolds, the murders were committed by a prominent booster, upset with the team.
Sara Sidle Review Sara works with Finn on the blood spatter, Hodges on recreation of evidence and trace, and Nick.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Play Dead</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/play-dead/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/play-dead/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis A police officer is killed, and the only living witness is his dog; a predatory divorce attorney is murdered, and the world seems just a little sweeter.
Sara Sidle Review Sara does not appear in this episode.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It Was a Very Good Year</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/it-was-a-very-good-year/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Oct 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/it-was-a-very-good-year/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Someone Greg knows is found cut to ribbons in a piano in the middle of the desert. Alison Bailey helped Greg with his Vegas book, and they quasi-dated for a week. It appears Alison was killed due to her research into the Vegas good-old-boy crime network, concerning the death of Ledo Wright, a pianist. Matters become more convoluted when the piano containing her body was that of Ledo&amp;rsquo;s.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wild Flowers</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/wild-flowers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/wild-flowers/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Two girls run away from human traffickers, only to have one die at a rave in the middle of the desert when one of their abductors shoots at them. The CSIs notice the previous injury patterns, and begin looking for the other girl, however most of the witnesses were drugged out of their minds. Doc Robbins quickly verifies their fears, the deceased was involved in human trafficking and was likely a sex slave.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Code Blue Plate Special</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/code-blue-plate-special/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Oct 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/code-blue-plate-special/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis The staff and patrons of Frank&amp;rsquo;s Diner are found dead, not long after the stalker of the waitress, Edie, is scared off by the cops. The only survivor is the owner&amp;rsquo;s brother (Vincent), who locked himself in the walk in freezer. Sara, Nick and Greg happen upon the scene, coming by for a meal.
The cops who had seen the stalker, Ronald Basderic, admit they did nothing, since he was gone by the time he went outside.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Karma to Burn</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/karma-to-burn/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Sep 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/karma-to-burn/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis In the wake of the season 12 finale, Russell&amp;rsquo;s granddaughter (Katie) has been kidnapped, Ecklie has been shot, Nick quit, and Finn may be in danger.
Ecklie is rushed to the hospital, where the pellets from his injuries match a rifle in the backseat of a car which matches the description of the car fleeing the scene. Curiously, his injury starts to heal the fractured relationship between him and his daughter, Morgan.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Homecoming</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/homecoming/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 May 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/homecoming/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis DB Russell, his wife, Ecklie, Hodges, Hodges mother, and Morgan all go to the fundraiser for the Sheriff&amp;rsquo;s reelection campaign. While they&amp;rsquo;re there, a triple homicide occurs down the road. One of the victims is the wife of Jack Gilmore, who just so happens to be running the event for the sheriff. The wife was beaten so badly, her internal organs liquified.
Finn and Nick suspect the husband, and when they find bloody a warmup suit and hockey shaft with the logo of Jack&amp;rsquo;s team, they&amp;rsquo;re sure it&amp;rsquo;s him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dune and Gloom</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/dune-and-gloom/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 May 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/dune-and-gloom/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis A driver for A Pharaoh&amp;rsquo;s Motorist in an off-road race is killed when is car explodes, but his co-driver is missing, and they were all racing under assumed names. Signs imply the men were military. They track down the car to a man, Art Webber, who was helped by the dead man and his friends. For free, they fixed his car and took away some of the broke parts, which they later used on their own car.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Altered Stakes</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/altered-stakes/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/altered-stakes/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis When Nick learns that a man he helped put in prison is going to have his conviction overturned, the CSI team needs to prove the killer is guilty again or he will be released.
Sara Sidle Review Sara Sidle does not appear in this episode._</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Split Decisions</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/split-decisions/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Apr 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/split-decisions/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis A shooter in a Las Vegas casino manages to evade the lockdown and cameras, after killing a man on the casino floor. Once he escapes into the stairwell, the CSIs are forced to do a room to room search. Going by the name X-Man, the man killed Mr. Kiel, who had brought his son to see Kanye. During the search, they find a woman who had a one night stand with him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Malice In Wonderland</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/malice-in-wonderland/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Mar 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/malice-in-wonderland/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis When an &amp;lsquo;Alice in Wonderland&amp;rsquo; wedding ends in a robbery and a murder, the CSIs must solve the crime made more complicated by another wedding robbery the next day. Video evidence suggests its the same people. The first murder is proven to be accidental, as the robbers used blanks. Their actual target was to steal the rings.
The robbers stole the rings for the gold, as well as bracelets and car decals, to melt them down.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trends With Benefits</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/trends-with-benefits/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Mar 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/trends-with-benefits/</guid>
      <description> Synopsis The CSIs are brought in to solve the case of a recently murdered student whose death photo ends up trending on the Internet
Sara Sidle Review Sara does not appear in this episode.
Quotes## </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CSI Unplugged</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/csi-unplugged/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Feb 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/csi-unplugged/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis A young boy, Harper Reardon, is stolen from his home, and his nanny, Shelby Buress, has gone missing. All that&amp;rsquo;s found is blood covering the room when the father, TC, wakes up hours later. Just as the CSIs begin to investigate, the power goes out, forcing them to go old-school and use their heads. The nanny is found dead, with a note saying &amp;lsquo;they&amp;rsquo; have Harper.
Shelby turns out to be the birth mother of Harper, with whom TJ was having an affair while married to another woman, Natalie, who died five years ago.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stealing Home</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/stealing-home/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/stealing-home/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Dwayne Hicks calls the police when his wife, Debbie, and house are missing. He went to work that night and his wife was in his house, but now they&amp;rsquo;re both gone. Dwayne, his brother Jimmy, and their sister Marla all argue over who might have stolen the house. The house is found in the hills, with Dennis Hutchings, a construction worker, dead underneath. Marla asked Dennis to steal the house for her so her family would stop fighting after their mother, Lois, died in the house (termite riddled beams dropped a flowerpot on her head).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seeing Red</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/seeing-red/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/seeing-red/</guid>
      <description>This is Elisabeth Shue&amp;rsquo;s first episode as Julie &amp;lsquo;Finn&amp;rsquo; Finlay
Synopsis## A shot man, Wes Clybourn, crashes into a billboard near where the CSIs are eating. The man lives, but was shot in the head and has limited memory of the event, or why the blood of multiple victims is found on his shirt. DB Reaches out to a former coworker, Julie &amp;lsquo;Finn&amp;rsquo; Finlay, asking her to come help. The convoluted case involves two missing women, a missing ex-con, and a father and son having an affair with the same women, though not at the same time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tressed To Kill</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/tressed-to-kill/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/tressed-to-kill/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Eleven girls have had their hair mysteriously cut by an unknown assailiant, dubbed the Shear Stalker, in public places. But hair cutting turns to murder when a previous victim is found dead in her home, with her eyes cut out. She was killed by an overdose of morphine, and then bleached her hair and styled her in retro clothes, shoving a small braid of hair down her throat. A second woman is killed after her makeup is applied, and instead of her eyes being gouged out, she&amp;rsquo;s been blinded.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Willows In The Wind</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/willows-in-the-wind/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/willows-in-the-wind/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis When a report of shots fired near Catherine&amp;rsquo;s house comes in, the CSIs immediately fear the worst and investigate. They find Russell&amp;rsquo;s SUV and his and Catherine&amp;rsquo;s cell phones, abandoned nearby, with blood on the scene. The bullet holes in her house match the FN-P90 which make Mark Gabriel a likely suspect. However the incompetence of the hitmen make them think Mark Gabriel is being set up.
Catherine survives being shot , thanks to Doc Robbins and an old stripper friend, but has to stay on the run because of a leak in police department communications.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ms. Willows Regrets</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/ms-willows-regrets/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/ms-willows-regrets/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Lawyer Malcom Turner and his staff are all murdered by people armed with FN-P90. Their deaths were a professional hit, arranged by Mark Gabriel, looking to prevent his wife Laura (who is Catherine&amp;rsquo;s childhood friend) from spilling his secrets. The lawyer was one Catherine sent Laura too, and after following the trail left by Laura, they find her hiding in the crawlspace of a house. The FBI take Laura into protective custody, as it seems Mark is conducting terrorist affairs on US soil.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Genetic Disorders</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/genetic-disorders/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/genetic-disorders/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis A dead man is found in the bed of Dr. Al Robbins, by his wife Judy. The implication is that she was cheating on Dr. Robbins.
Sara Sidle Review Sara Sidle does not appear in this episode.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zippered</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/zippered/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/zippered/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis The FBI get involved when 144 high powered guns (the FN-P90) are stolen and shipped to Nevada. One is used to kill Michael Newbury, retired Army Ranger, and cut him in half. His body is found in the hills near his home, his tattoo defaced to hide it. It&amp;rsquo;s only after one of the guns shows up in a robbery that the FBI admit to how many guns may be in Las Vegas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crime After Crime</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/crime-after-crime/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/crime-after-crime/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Three separate cases are all committed by the same revenge-seeking retired police officer, Stan Richardson. Dying of cancer, Richardson arranged for his friend, Detective Sam Vega, to perform the killing for him. When caught in the act, Vega choses to suicide by cop and is shot and killed.
Kevin Fetzer, a well-off entrepreneur who created Joystick Jungle, an arcade for adults, is beaten to death with an arcade ball (aka skeeball), which Kevin himself once used in a fight with a younger boy, Mikey Moran, killing him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brain Doe</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/brain-doe/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/brain-doe/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis When a car with no driver goes through the drive-in window at Tasty Time, the CSIs are on a surprising case with an extra brain. The brain was in the car of a junkie and former MMA fighter named Danny Clegg, who had it in a cooler in his passenger seat when he OD&amp;rsquo;d at the fast food joint.
The brain had been removed by a doctor in Seneca, Hanson Eller, and belonged to an MMA fighter named Ryan Dempsey.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Freaks and Geeks</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/freaks-and-geeks/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/freaks-and-geeks/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis When a Jane Doe is found near the freakish attractions of a 19th-century-inspired traveling sideshow, the team investigates a cast of unusual characters.
Sara Sidle Review Sara does not appear in this episode.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CSI Down</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/csi-down/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/csi-down/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis The episode concerns Morgan Brody, who is in a helicopter that crashes. The CSIs had been called to a murder in the desert, but 30 minutes before their arrival, the victim (who had no pulse) groans and a rescue chopper is called. Morgan goes on the helicopter to fly to the hospital, intending to continue on to help Nick in Northtown where two gang members from the Mad-10s were killed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Maid Man</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/maid-man/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/maid-man/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis While Catherine, Greg, DB and Ecklie attend new mobster exhibit, an ex mayor is shot four times, mobster style, while he’s giving a speech. Upon further investigation, Catherine and D.B. find a dead security guard. Meanwhile, on the B case, Nick and Morgan investigate the murder of a maid in a hotel room.
Sara Sidle Review Sara Sidle does not appear in this episode.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bittersweet</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/bittersweet/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/bittersweet/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Nick takes Doc Robbins&amp;rsquo; niece out on a date to a museum, where he runs into a crime scene. A piece of art is dripping decomposed human goo. The artist, Slade, claims he found it &amp;lsquo;as is&amp;rsquo; so the CSIs go to his junkyard, and find more body parts encased in cement. This reminds Nick of an old case of Sara&amp;rsquo;s, where a husband and wife team kidnapped girls, killed them, dismembered them and encased them in cement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tell-Tale Hearts</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/tell-tale-hearts/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/tell-tale-hearts/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis A teenage couple, making out in a car, are sprayed with blood from the sprinkler system. Inside the house is a quadruple homicide that has, literally, painted the Chambliss house red. Due to the water recycling system (grey water is reused to water the lawn), the blood that went down the drain came out the sprinklers. The youngest child in the house, a small girl, Fiona, was cleaned up in fresh clothes after she was killed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>73 Seconds</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/73-seconds/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Sep 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/73-seconds/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis A normal night in Las Vegas turns into a killing spree, when a young boy is the critical witness to a shoot out that least two men dead on the tram. Nick tries to bond with the boy, but it&amp;rsquo;s the new supervisor, D.B. Russell, who connects with an invisible tennis ball. The autopsy shows that one of the dead men from the shoot out was actually stabbed to death, and the evidence shows that an octopus was on the tram.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>In A Dark, Dark House</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/in-a-dark-dark-house/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/in-a-dark-dark-house/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis The episode picks up where last week&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Cello and Goodbye&amp;rdquo; left off. Nate Haskell (real name Warner Thorpe) has killed his father and now has Ray at gunpoint. When Haskell turns his back for a moment, Ray jumps him, disarms him, and brutally punches him into submission. Even bound, Haskell antagonizes Ray about what he did to Gloria, until Ray cuts the plastic cuffs off and they fight to the death.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cello and Goodbye</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/cello-and-goodbye/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/cello-and-goodbye/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis The CSI team investigates serial killer Nate Haskell in Los Angeles. Langston becomes more determined than ever to track down Nake Haskell, the notorious &amp;lsquo;Dick and Jane&amp;rsquo; killer, after discovering that he&amp;rsquo;s kidnapped his ex-wife, Gloria and killed her new husband, Phil Baker. Thinking Gloria is dead, Langston decides he cannot live without the one woman he loves still being in the world, and goes after Haskell alone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Father of the Bride</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/father-of-the-bride/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/father-of-the-bride/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Nick and Greg have a barn full of scattered body parts to piece together &amp;ndash; without names or heads to identify them. Langston&amp;rsquo;s old nemesis, Nate Haskell, is back in action and playing his usual game of five-level chess against the LVPD.
Sara Sidle Review Sara Sidle does not appear in this episode.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unleashed</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/unleashed/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/unleashed/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Iona Vail, a social worker at a battered women&amp;rsquo;s shelter, is killed, mauled by a mountain lion, dressed in skin-tight attire with indications of restraint use on her ankles, and bruises on her face. Iona had been shot with a stun gun before being dumped, which causes more trace than normal to cling to her.
After breaking up with her boyfriend, Iona quit the shelter. Her datebook last says she was seeing Dr.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hitting for the Cycle</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/hitting-for-the-cycle/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/hitting-for-the-cycle/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Henry notices that the Graveyard shift is one natural death away from &amp;lsquo;cycle&amp;rsquo; &amp;ndash; a homicide, a suicide, an accidental and a natural death all in one night. Nick, Hodges and Greg all begin betting on who will close out the cycle, Nick or Greg.
Greg&amp;rsquo;s death is a woman who died of a ruptured, puss filled intestine, due to swallowing a paperclip which perforated her. Her death declared an accident, Greg and Sara go to a 419 where a gamer named Stevie (DV8Avenger) is found dead on his couch.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The List</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/the-list/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/the-list/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis While investigating the murder of a convicted ex-cop, the CSIs stumble upon a list in his prison cell with names of several individuals he believed might have been his wife&amp;rsquo;s true killer.
The surprising truth is that the wife faked her own death and framed her husband. After she kills her sister, the CSIs are able to track her down and arrest her.
Sara Sidle Review Sara Sidle does not appear in this episode.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Turn On, Tune In, Drop Dead</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/turn-on-tune-in-drop-dead/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/turn-on-tune-in-drop-dead/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis The CSIs are on zombie alert when two men initially pronounced dead mysteriously come back to life. The first dead body walks out of the morgue, while the second is found in an alley and vanishes by the time CSI gets there. The CSIs trace the evidence to Dr. Elliot Davis Aden, a discredited psychoanalyst who worked for the government during the Red Scare, until he fell into the lure of drugs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Targets of Obsession</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/targets-of-obsession/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/targets-of-obsession/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Langston testifies against the notorious &amp;lsquo;Dick &amp;amp; Jane&amp;rsquo; killer, Nate Haskell. The trial doesn&amp;rsquo;t go well and is touch and go for a while. Haskell escapes with the help of the many women he&amp;rsquo;s seduced to his cause.
Meanwhile, Nick receives a call from troubled teen Jason McCann to warn him of impending danger. During the investigation, Catherine, Nick, Vartann and a bomb tech are trapped in a warehouse with a bomb.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>All That Cremains</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/all-that-cremains/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/all-that-cremains/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis A thrift store donation turns gruesome when a dead body is found in a box; meanwhile, Ray&amp;rsquo;s ex-wife pays a surprise visit to the crime lab when she&amp;rsquo;s getting remarried and wants Ray to come.
Trace ashes from the dead body at the thrift store imply that the body was at a crematorium. They manage to find all the pieces and autopsy shows the dead man was alive when ashes were introduced.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Two Mrs. Grissoms</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/the-two-mrs-grissoms/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/the-two-mrs-grissoms/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis A night full of celebration ends with a bang when the director of a scholarship foundation for the deaf is killed by a deadly car bomb, prompting Sara to interrogate the students and faculty of the college where her mother-in-law, Betty Grissom, works.
Grissom&amp;rsquo;s ex girlfriend, Julia Holden, is on the selection committed for the grant to be given out by Dr. Eric Lambert (the head of the Gilbert Foundation).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Kiss Before Frying</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/a-kiss-before-frying/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/a-kiss-before-frying/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis The CSIs link a body with severe burn marks to possible execution by electric chair – and to a legendary Vegas murder. Meanwhile, Greg asks out Ellen, a pretty schoolteacher and forensics enthusiast who has been touring the crime lab.
Sara Sidle Review Sara Sidle does not appear in this episode.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Man Up</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/man-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/man-up/</guid>
      <description> Synopsis The CSIs question the validity of an online picture depicting a murdered call girl until they find the same woman strangled to death in the dumpster that appears in the photo.
Sara Sidle Review  Jorja Fox did not appear in this episode.*  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>418/427</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/418-427/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/418-427/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Christine Moore is shot three times, execution style, and her daughter kidnapped, outside a grocery store. Her husband, Daniel, is an FBI agent. Daniel suspects a pedophile named Rylan Gauss is to blame, after his son Trent (from a previous marriage) is also kidnapped. The CSI&amp;rsquo;s track Gauss to a park, following evidence in his apartment, and barely prevent Agent Moore from killing him. In the course of the investigation, the CSIs find that Moore is getting a divorce, his wife is suing for custody of their daughter and Trent, her 18 year-old stepson.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wild Life</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/wild-life/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/wild-life/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Brad Malone, after loosing 100 grand at the Eclipse Casino, falls and splatters his brains over the floor. Nick, Ray and Catherine determine he fell from the balcony of the room next to his own. The two women in the room had been &amp;lsquo;celebrating&amp;rsquo; ones recent divorce, and the night had gotten out of hand, with alcohol, a little GHB, and some consensual, if later regretted, sex, which ended with Brad accidentally falling off the balcony mid-coitus.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fracked</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/fracked/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/fracked/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis A large explosion at a gas company gives the CSI team further evidence in their investigation into the murders of two men who were about to accuse the company of poisoning the water in a farming town.
Sara Sidle Review Sara Sidle does not appear in this episode.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bump and Grind</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/bump-and-grind/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Nov 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/bump-and-grind/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis A man is forced to eat a soup consisting of a credit card and his own ear, before being tossed into a landfill shredder, where his oozing remains are called into the police. The find the credit card bits, along with the body, and trace it back to Larry LaMotte, an identity theft expert who runs the company I.D.-Preserve. Larry is not, however dead (nor is he the face of his company, a man in the mail room &amp;lsquo;plays&amp;rsquo; him on TV), nor are his credit cards missing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cold Blooded</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/cold-blooded/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/cold-blooded/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis When a college student ends up dead after a &amp;lsquo;Walking with Dinosaurs&amp;rsquo; show, the CSIs must determine if his death was murder or accidental.
Sara Sidle Review Sara Sidle does not appear in this episode.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blood Moon</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/blood-moon/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Oct 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/blood-moon/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis A headless body is found, propped up against a barbed-wire fence with the head on a post, in a field, under the harvest (aka blood) moon. Wax left on the body from an extensive manscaping leads the CSIs to a hotel where a vampire and werewolf convention is taking place and a man named Michael Wilson is missing. Michael had come to a Clans and Covens convention with his fiance to get married with all their friends but was killed by his fiance when she learned that Michael had formerly been a werewolf, but had fallen in love with her, a vampire, and converted.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>House of Hoarders</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/house-of-hoarders/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Oct 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/house-of-hoarders/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis A woman, Mrs. Santiago, who suffers from a condition called &amp;lsquo;hording&amp;rsquo; becomes a murder suspect when a dead body is found buried under piles of trash and debris inside her home. Initially the cops are called in due to complaints of too many cats (and the resultant smell), but when they can&amp;rsquo;t get in the front door, the case takes a turn for the worse and a liquified body is found.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sqweegel</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/sqweegel/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Oct 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/sqweegel/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Sqweegel, a serial killer who is punishing local heroes that harbor hidden secrets, is on the hunt in Las Vegas.
Sara Sidle Review While in the main credits, Jorja does not appear in this episode.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pool Shark</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/pool-shark/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/pool-shark/</guid>
      <description>Note: This is Liz Vassey&amp;rsquo;s final episode as Wendy Simms.*  Synopsis Hysteria ensues when a shark attacks a woman, Desiree McQuire, in the pool at a Las Vegas casino &amp;lsquo;day club&amp;rsquo; and the CSIs must determine if the killer is human or shark. At the scene of the crime, Catherine runs into one of her father&amp;rsquo;s old friends Earnest Boozell (played by Elliot Gould), and she has to forcibly remove him from the scene.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shock Waves</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/shock-waves/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/shock-waves/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Multiple bombs go off at the funeral of Officer Clark, killed by Dr. Jekyll at the end of last season, leading Jim Brass to suspect Nate Haskell, who is still in the hospital as well, having been roughly restrained following his attack on Ray Langston. Ray assists the case from the hospital, and does not agree that Haskell has anything to do with the funeral bombing. They trace one of the bombs to a far right-wing anti-government group (where special guest star, Justin Bieber as Jason McCann is in attendance).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Doctor Who</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/doctor-who/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 May 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/doctor-who/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Heidi Custer, a reporter from New York, is found dead, a body dump. Surveillance footage shows she met with Langston at a hotel. Her husband accuses Langston of being a murderer, claiming his wife determined Langston was involved with &amp;lsquo;Angel of Death&amp;rsquo; from a hospital in Delaware. Langston is kicked off the case, due to conflict of interests, and thinks that Heidi was following him and got killed for it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meat Jekyll</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/meat-jekyll/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 May 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/meat-jekyll/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Nate Haskell, the Dick and Jane killer, tells Langston he knows who Dr. Jekyll is, and agrees to work with the CSIs to capture him, for a price. Using his information, that Jekyll was a chef, the CSIs track Jekyll to Venetti&amp;rsquo;s, an Italian restaurant closed these last 5 years, where all his victims once ate and had their photos on the wall. After wheedling a steak dinner and a strip dance, Haskell gives them a name: Carlo Perinni.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Take My Life, Please!</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/take-my-life-please/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/take-my-life-please/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Knuckles, a legendary comic from the good old days of Las Vegas is set to reunite with his partner, Bernie Nash, on stage for one night only, until one half of the famous duo is found dead. Nash is dead in his dressing room on opening night with alcohol and oxycodine in his system, and evidence of sexual activity scratched into his back. Nash&amp;rsquo;s death looks to be natural (an accidental overdose) until Doc Robbins determines he drowned in his own dressing room, 12 feet from a toilet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>World&#39;s End</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/worlds-end/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Apr 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/worlds-end/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Sean Becker, a racist, is found dead by a high school, practicing Cabaret as their musical (with Catherine&amp;rsquo;s daughter, Lindsey as the star Sally Bowles, dead in the storm drain. Sean was not, however drowned, having been stabbed by a Phillip&amp;rsquo;s head screwdriver beforehand. In searching Sean&amp;rsquo;s home, turns out to be a rather well read intellectual.
Nick and Greg find the murder weapon, while Sara and Ray go over the history of injuries found on Sean.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Irradiator</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/irradiator/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Apr 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/irradiator/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis A husband and wife are brutally murdered in their own home, survived by their young daughter. The evidence leads them to the house next door, seemingly deserted, of a retired machinist Jack Herson, who fits the profile of the killer and happens to have homemade surgical equipment in his home. The evident suggest Herson is the mysterious &amp;lsquo;Dr. Jekyll&amp;rsquo; serial killer. The more the examine his house, the more the evidence supports their theory, until they find out that Herson is actually the latest victim.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Neverland</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/neverland/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/neverland/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Fourteen year-old Will Sutter is found dead in the field, his body dumped, with snacks, a pocket knife, and a compass. The case takes an off turn when the blood under Will&amp;rsquo;s nails was that of Simon Rose, a man Sara put in jail two and a half years ago.
Simon was accused and convicted him of murdering his wife. He choked her to death on the kitchen floor, while he claimed to be asleep upstairs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unshockable</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/unshockable/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Mar 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/unshockable/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis When a band member of Rascal Flatts is electrocuted by his own guitar during a concert, the CSI team investigates if it was a case of foul play. The bassist, Jay DeMarcus, suffers from a mild case of amnesia after the electrocution. The guitar is swapped out before the CSIs can get to it and has to be rescued from a fan before they can determine the guitar tech set Jay up in order to play one more time on stage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Internal Combustion</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/internal-combustion/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/internal-combustion/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis The case of two high school students, one dead and one missing, lead the CSIs into the underbelly of streetcar racing and a tangled web of deadly competition.
Trevor Beck, a high school senior, dropped dead in the school hallway for no obvious cause. In the autopsy, they determine it was caused by cerebral menigina, however there was no injury sufficient to cause the damage. His girlfriend, Cindy Warner, has also gone missing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Long Ball</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/long-ball/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/long-ball/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis During a high-profile tournament, Russell Huntley is found dead in his own golf cart. The former course record holder (now held by his son, Danny Nagano), Russell was an antagonistic drunk who was angry towards his son Danny, his ex-wife and many other people.
Russell&amp;rsquo;s ex-wife&amp;rsquo;s sister, Erin, left her prints on a ball found in his golf cart. She buys the balls every time Danny, her step-nephew, plays a tournament.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Better Off Dead</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/better-off-dead/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Dec 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/better-off-dead/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis A shoot out during a robbery at a mom and son gun shop leads to a dead mother killed by a mysterious guy in a red shirt, while a body is dumped down a ravine and cozily wrapped in a blanket. The gun shop sells illegal gun parts on the side and the killer of the dummped body was one of the attempted robbers of the gun shop.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lover&#39;s Lanes</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/lovers-lanes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Nov 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/lovers-lanes/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis At a critical juncture in a bowling tournament, a head comes out of the ball feed. The victim, Ronny Tobin, works at the bowling alley, but no body is found on the premise. Ronny&amp;rsquo;s head was sawn off by hand and transported in a bag used by Kevin X, one of the players in the tournament, who had also lost to Ronny in a pick-up game. Blood spatter and the rest of Ronny&amp;rsquo;s body, indicates that Ronny was shot at the employment of his homeless friend, Vitas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Death and the Maiden</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/death-and-the-maiden/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Nov 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/death-and-the-maiden/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis The CSIs discover that two seemingly unrelated crimes are actually part of a revenge plot.
Sara Sidle Review Sara Sidle does not appear in this episode
Sara is working a quintuple homicide in Parumph and will be there all night.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bloodsport</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/bloodsport/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Oct 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/bloodsport/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis The morning after a fantastic football game, the much loved coach of WLVU&amp;rsquo;s football team wakes up bloody and beaten. Coach Miller somehow managed to half stagger through his morning routine and walk out of his on campus house, only to collapse dead on the doorstep in front of campus security. Spatter and cast off indicates that he was beaten nearly to death in his bed by a blunt and sharp object.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coup de Grace</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/coup-de-grace/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Oct 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/coup-de-grace/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis An undercover cop is killed by a possibly racist police officer under suspicious circumstances. The witnesses, who are primarily black, claim the white officer who shot the black cop did so when the deceased was already down, contradicting what the officer says. The evidence backs up the witnesses, and the rookie officer didn&amp;rsquo;t see what happened. A second case at a school appears to be a gang execution of a snitch, but the cases intersect when the two victims turn out to have been talking regularly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ghost Town</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/ghost-town/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Oct 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/ghost-town/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Ryan Lester is a porn producer, killed in the tub similarly to the Paul Millander killings in a relatively upscale Vegas area. The economic downturn has led to more renters and people of shadier incomes. The investigation leads them to a peeping tom by the name of Craig Mason, adopted son of Judge Mason (aka Paul Millander), now a teenaged goth with a penchant to heavy metal music. They find a second body, his throat slit similarly to Lester, but on the ground outside his house, which he&amp;rsquo;s using as a drug house.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Family Affair</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/family-affair/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/family-affair/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis The CSI lab is shorthanded after the abrupt quitting of Riley Adams, causing everyone to be under a bit more stress than normal. Ray Langston has taken the opportunity to take many classes and is promoted to a CSI level 2, while Nick has adopted a tarantula, following in Grissom&amp;rsquo;s footsteps. Ecklie&amp;rsquo;s not as happy about all this, as always, concerned with the budget, when a high priority case comes in.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Retrospective</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/retrospective/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/retrospective/</guid>
      <description>Note: This episode is a clip show/retrospective and introduces no new material. All appearances include the actors as themselves.
Summary Clips from memorable episodes; interviews with past and present cast members.
Jorja returned to talk about being on the show.
Quotes On watching the show:
Jorja: When you watched the show, you felt smarter.
On filming the show:
Jorja: It was absolutely terrifying for me.
What it felt like:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shifting Equilbrium</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/shifting-equilbrium/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/shifting-equilbrium/</guid>
      <description>Note: Jorja Fox does not appear in this episode.
Summary It&amp;rsquo;s Neela&amp;rsquo;s last day and everyone in the ER seems to have forgotten that she is leaving. Neela proves she is ready to be an attending when she and Dr. Dubenko argue about the treatment of two surgical cases. Meanwhile, Brenner has an epiphany about his troubled past.
Character Review Doyle&amp;rsquo;s name is seen when Neela puts her nameplate on the wall of departed doctors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>One To Go</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/one-to-go/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/one-to-go/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Dr. Raymond Langston joins the CSI team, on retainer, to help solve the &amp;lsquo;Dick &amp;amp; Jane&amp;rsquo; murders. One of his students is accomplice to Nathan Haskill, the already convicted killer. Knowing that this is Grissom&amp;rsquo;s last case in the lab, the team avows to solve this one for him.
In the end, Langston is offered a position as a CSI, Ecklie becomes the new Undersherrif and Catherine takes over Grissom&amp;rsquo;s position in charge of the Night Shift.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Leave Out All The Rest</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/leave-out-all-the-rest/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/leave-out-all-the-rest/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis After receiving a video message from Sara, Grissom is distracted at work, and Catherine has to help cover for him. When the case involves the world of S&amp;amp;M, Grissom pays a visit to Lady Heather, looking for answers in both his professional and personal life. Heather is now a licensed therapist, specializing in sex therapy.
Sara Sidle Review Sara Sidle appear in a video message to Grissom in this episode.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Let It Bleed</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/let-it-bleed/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/let-it-bleed/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Nick and Riley witness a man in a police costume rob a convenience store. They then must help the rest of the team investigate the death of a young woman who turns out to be the daughter of a big time drug lord wanted by FBI, CIA, and DEA. They discover with security camera footage that she was thrown out of a club by two bouncers earlier that night.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Book Of Abby</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/the-book-of-abby/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/the-book-of-abby/</guid>
      <description>Note: Jorja Fox does not appear in this episode.
Summary Neela finds out Abby&amp;rsquo;s good news second hand. Catherine Banfield and Abby butt heads on how to treat the victim of a gun shot wound, that has just been admitted into the ER. Finally, Abby comes to Sam&amp;rsquo;s defense before a nurses&amp;rsquo; disciplinary board.
Character Review Doyle&amp;rsquo;s name is seen when Abby puts her nameplate on the wall of departed doctors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Happy Place</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/the-happy-place/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/the-happy-place/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis While still recovering from the loss of Warrick, the CSIs go back to work with a pair of difficult cases: an apparent suicide and a brutal murder.
Catherine and Nick work the suicide, who threw herself off of her balcony, however the evidence contradicts the initial analysis as she had arranged a dinner with her soon to be in-laws for the next day and was getting married in two weeks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>For Warrick</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/for-warrick/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/for-warrick/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis After being shot by Undersheriff McKeen, who calls in the crime, Warrick is found by Grissom and dies in his arms. McKeen tries to frame another dirty cop, Pritchard, who killed Gedda and tried to frame Warrick. The CSIs try to solve the crime, and quickly exclude Pritchard from their suspect list and replace him with McKeen due to inconsistencies in McKeen&amp;rsquo;s report. From his phone records and the tiny partial off the bullets in the murder weapon, the CSIs trace McKeen to a hotel where he happens to have Pritchard holed up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grissom&#39;s Divine Comedy</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/grissoms-divine-comedy/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/grissoms-divine-comedy/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Grissom is called while he has walking pneumonia, in order to solve a gang case after the grand jury&amp;rsquo;s witness is murdered.
Sara Sidle Review Sara Sidle does not appear in this episode.
In a deleted scene, Catherine comes over to prep Grissom for the court visitation. While there, she snoops through his apartment, greeting Hank the Dog by name. Catherine finds a photograph of the CSI team, all in their vests, but also one of much younger Grissom and Sara on the refrigerator.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Kill Me</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/you-kill-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/you-kill-me/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Hodges stages hypothetical murders in the lab in order to give his fellow lab techs a chance to play CSI, but unbenownst to them he has other motives behind his actions. Meanwhile, after Sara&amp;rsquo;s farewell, everyone tries to comfort Grissom.
Sara Sidle Review Sara Sidle does not appear in this episode.
Character Notes  Grissom is still in contact with Sara
 Sara is in San Francisco, visiting her mother  Quotes Brass: Have you been in touch with Sara?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Goodbye and Good Luck</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/goodbye-and-good-luck/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/goodbye-and-good-luck/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Hannah and Marlon West return as the prime suspects in the death of a college girl. Hannah killed the girl, Marlon&amp;rsquo;s girlfriend, because she was in love with him. When Marlon learned of his sister&amp;rsquo;s co-dependent adoration and that she was framing him for the murder (in order to lock him away so that only she could see him), he kills himself.
The two cases are just the final straws for Sara &amp;ndash; she leaves Las Vegas, and she leaves Grissom.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who &amp; What</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/who-what/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Nov 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/who-what/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis A boy and his babysitter are brutally murdered during a home invasion. FBI Special Agent Jack Malone (from &amp;lsquo;Without a Trace&amp;rsquo;) flies in when the strongest evidence, a bloody palm print, matches where the boy was kidnapped from six years ago. While the boy is not the child kidnapped from New York, his murderer is the kidnapper and now a serial killer.
The episode concluded on Without a Trace.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Chick Chop Flick Shop</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/the-chick-chop-flick-shop/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/the-chick-chop-flick-shop/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis A successful horror-film actress, Weatherly Adams, goes missing and the CSIs are brought in to find her. In their investigation, they find Weatherly wasn&amp;rsquo;t missing at all, but was killed and left staged with other (fake) bodies on the set, an axe lodged in her back. Nick and Catherine search the scene, while Brass interrogates various suspects, including Zarco (a former set worker who had been dating Weatherly. was burned at work and now stalked her) and Vaughn Krunty (aka Zack Putrid, the director who was sleeping with Weatherly).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Case of the Cross-Dressing Carp</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/the-case-of-the-cross-dressing-carp/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/the-case-of-the-cross-dressing-carp/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Brian Towne was a young man who grew breasts, due to polluted water, which affected his genetics, as well as those of the carp in the lake. When Brian and his Hydrologist friend got close to the truth, that the water treatment plant was knowingly polluting the water, they died. Brian killed himself out of shame when girls mocked him for having the man-boobs. After he died, his mother found out what was going on and shot the hydrologist, thinking he&amp;rsquo;d poisioned her son, not that he was trying to save him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Go To Hell</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/go-to-hell/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/go-to-hell/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis As the weather breaks 110+ in Las Vegas, deaths are more common but less common place. A homeless man dies in an alley, a married couple are killed in a seedy hotel room, and a bee dies in mid-flight.
The couple in the hotel room were killed by their 12 year-old daughter, who they thought was possessed by a devil, and kept her locked in an attic room much of the time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A La Cart</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/a-la-cart/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Oct 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/a-la-cart/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis The CSIs work two cases, one of a high school student, Vincent Bartley, whose head is found along side the road, and the other of a rich pornographer, Huxley, found dead in a blind eatery. Vinnie was a Go-Kart enthusiast who&amp;rsquo;d lost his head in a race on the streets, getting it and his hand severed by a blown out truck tire. Huxley was killed out of a waiter&amp;rsquo;s revenge on the restaurant&amp;rsquo;s chef, who had made her living off his ideas and their past relationship.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dead Doll</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/dead-doll/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/dead-doll/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis The miniature serial killer, Natalie Davis, kidnapped Sara and left her in the desert, trapped under a car. While the CSIs try to determine how Natalie kidnapped her and where Sara might be, three thunderstorms converge on the Las Vegas area, promising flash floods.
Through flashbacks, the story of Sara&amp;rsquo;s kidnapping and the perils she faced in the desert are told, intercut with her teammates hunt for her and with all the CSIs remembering past cases where they worked with Sara.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Living Doll</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/living-doll/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 May 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/living-doll/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis The miniature serial killer is revealed to be Natalie Davis, foster daughter to Ernie Dell , who has an aversion to bleach. Having killed some of her foster siblings, including Trevor just 12 days ago, she caps her crime spree by abducting and trapping Sara under a car.
Natalie&amp;rsquo;s story is told with many flashbacks to how she got the job cleaning the CSI lab, as well as that Ernie knew she was killing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Good, the Bad, and the Dominatrix</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/the-good-the-bad-and-the-dominatrix/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 May 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/the-good-the-bad-and-the-dominatrix/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Lady Heather is nearly strangled to death, while acting out a Wild West fantasy. Heather claimed to have been at the theme park to arrange for a private party, when the man arrived and strangled her. Later the night guard is found dead as well. When Brass comes to serve Heather with a warrant, Grissom serves as her alibi. Heather had sold her business to raise money to set up a trust fund to put her infant granddaughter, of whom she did not have custody, through college.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Leapin&#39; Lizards</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/leapin-lizards/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 May 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/leapin-lizards/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis A group of cultists who believe that alien reptiles are breeding with humans in a vast government conspiracy fall prey to their own neuroses and start to kill each other. Chyna De Vere is killed by Shannon Turner and her boyfriend, Hank Conners, the latter of whom commits suicide as the police raid his house, for being a Reptillian. There they find Chyna&amp;rsquo;s head, mounted like a hunting trophy, and her body burried with both rings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ending Happy</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/ending-happy/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/ending-happy/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Boxer Lorenzo Morales, nicknamed Happy, is found dead at Binky&amp;rsquo;s World Famouse Sugar Cane Ranch, where he is living and training. Too fond of drugs and whores, he pissed off most of the prostitutes at the Ranch. Binky was angry with Happy for taking liberties with the girls, while his wife Doris had a &amp;lsquo;thing&amp;rsquo; for Happy. All the girls had various weapons in their rooms, but the multitude of injuries and attacks on Happy make it difficult to determine how he died.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lab Rats</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/lab-rats/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Apr 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/lab-rats/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis This episode revolves around the tertiary characters of the CSI lab: Archie, Hodges, Henry, Mandy and Wendy. After Grissom assigns out all the CSIs and goes to the morgue to work with Doc Robbins, Hodges collects the other &amp;lsquo;lab rats&amp;rsquo; to go over the miniature crime scenes. Implying that Grissom has asked him to work on the case, Hodges leads the other techs through the crimes and the history.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Big Shots</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/big-shots/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Apr 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/big-shots/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis After a man is killed in his limousine, Greg finds that the murder victim has ties to the man he had to kill in self-defense. The team finds that the brother is involved in this investigation and has to deal with him and his hostile mother.
Sara Sidle Review Sara joins the rest of the CSIs in going over the cases when the evidence links the two. Grissom and Sara go over the limo together and verify the crimes are connected.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Empty Eyes</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/empty-eyes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Mar 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/empty-eyes/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Six showgirls, who are also roommates, are all found murdered in their home. All six were tied up and five died from having their throats cut. One of the girls was raped. The killer was recently released from a California prison, and Sara is able to match his DNA to a wine bottle.
Sara Sidle Review After her date is canceled, Sara arrives to help with the scene. She is attacked by the last victim, who is hiding under the bed, but then asked to help her.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fallen Idols</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/fallen-idols/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/fallen-idols/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Two high school students go missing after the big game: basketball hero and photography lover, Ryan, and his cheerleader girlfriend, Megan.
Ryan turns out to have been a sexual fiend, sleeping with much of the school&amp;rsquo;s female population, as well as his photography teacher, Diane. Because of that, Charlie and Sheila, Megan&amp;rsquo;s friends, had decided to pull a prank on Ryan by tying him up and making him admit he had crabs and was a sexual pervert.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Monster in the Box</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/monster-in-the-box/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/monster-in-the-box/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Grissom finally opens a packaged delivered shortly after he left for sabbatical, and it turns out to be another miniature from the miniature crime scene killer. A note left, in pieces on the various miniatures, reads &amp;lsquo;You were wrong.&amp;rsquo; Since the package was sent after Ernie Dell suicided, the real killer is still at large. The miniature has the murder planned for two days time, and the CSIs are able to find Dr.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Law of Gravity</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/law-of-gravity/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/law-of-gravity/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Keppler&amp;rsquo;s past comes back to haunt him. Plagued by nightmares, Keppler&amp;rsquo;s father in law, Frank McCarty, comes to Vegas and asks Keppler for help. Retired Trenton cop, Dennis Graves, is going to turn them all in for the murder of a Puerto Rican drug dealer back in Trenton. Keppler had shot the dealer in retaliation for the rape of his fiancee, Amy, who was also Frank&amp;rsquo;s daughter. Frank then leaves the murder weapon for both Dennis&amp;rsquo; death and the Puerto Ricans in his hotel room, knowing that it has Keppler&amp;rsquo;s prints on it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meet Market</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/meet-market/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/meet-market/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis## A faked death turns into a case of body-part trafficking, when a Jewish body turns up with his bones replaced with pipe. Orthodox Jews don&amp;rsquo;t believe in donating their body parts, and the dead body found had leukemia. The body part clinic caused the death of over thirty people, having used unhealthy body parts.
Margo Darton is found, killed in her home, beaten by a champagne bottle. She&amp;rsquo;d been seeing a &amp;lsquo;Host&amp;rsquo; at the Over/Under Club, who acted as a pretend relationship, named Jesse.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Redrum</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/redrum/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/redrum/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis After the killer of Danilo Zamesca goes into hiding, Catherine, Keppler and Brass stage a fake crime scene to smoke him out. They send the other CSIs off on unrelated cases, however Sara&amp;rsquo;s case is actually related. Nick, Sara, and Warrick are suspicious of the faked case, and with Greg, form their own team to look into it. As they determine that the scene was faked, the killer (Thomas Simon) is found and arrested.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sweet Jane</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/sweet-jane/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/sweet-jane/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis A dentist is a serial killer, and has been murdering women in Las Vegas since the 1970s, leaving three as Jane Does. Complicating the matter, the killers MO has changed over the years, and not all the cases are precisely the same. Doc Robbins connects the dental work between two of the cases, which leads the CSIs to their killer, Dr. Dave. Dr. Dave chooses not to tell the CSI&amp;rsquo;s the names of his victims, claiming that doing so would tarnish his memories.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Leaving Las Vegas</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/leaving-las-vegas/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/leaving-las-vegas/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Catherine reviews a crime scene in court, where she faces Adam Novak, who gets the defended a verdict of not guilty. Catherine doesn&amp;rsquo;t give up and finds a related case with a bullet that ties multiple cases together. The currently imprisoned suspect turns out to be innocent, and the guy Novak got off is indeed the killer.
Grissom is leaving Vegas for a month on sabbatical to teach. He tells each member of the team, as well as some lab members, in turn.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Loco Motives</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/loco-motives/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/loco-motives/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis A man is found, waist deep in cement, after having tried to toss a body to sink into the cement, only to find it had hardened too much. Brass, Catherine and Grissom find the predicament very funny. The man refuses to say anything informative, and the woman was killed by a stab wound to the heart. It turns out the case is connected to another. Warrick and Nick work the case of an elderly woman, beaten in the head, and staged with her head in an oven.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Living Legend</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/living-legend/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/living-legend/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis The ghost of Mickey Dunn, a famous Vegas mob boss from the 70s, seemingly returns to life and kills off the four men who saw him leave the casino the night he vanished. Using a variety of disguises, he&amp;rsquo;s able to keep the CSIs at bay long enough to complete his vendetta. The body found in Dunn&amp;rsquo;s car was the cop who went missing, chasing Dunn. A bullet was lodged in Dunn&amp;rsquo;s heart, causing a heart attack while he was being interrogated by the cops.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happenstance</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/happenstance/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/happenstance/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Identical twins, who had never met, nor ever learned of the other&amp;rsquo;s existence are murdered when one twin plans to expose a photographer who had faked a Pulitzer winning photograph. Planning on killing one twin, he accidentally kills the other and winds up having to kill both, making one look like a suicide.
Sara Sidle Review Sara spent the day waiting for her court case to be called up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Post-Mortem</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/post-mortem/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/post-mortem/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Penny Garden, 65, is found smashed through a window and impaled on the glass in her house, with her nephew missing. The nephew is a recovering drug addict, and finds a miniature of the crime scene on his stoop the next day and brings it into Headquarters, which clears both him and the neighbor, the drug trafficker, who had been buying drugs from Penny.
The miniature scene is as exact as the first one, with the same photograph of a doll with a bloody forehead.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Burn Out</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/burn-out/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/burn-out/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Only by working with a convicted pedophile are the CSI&amp;rsquo;s able to find out what happened to two young boys who go missing. Both come from homes where they don&amp;rsquo;t feel loved and the pedophile confesses, after being spotted in a lineup, that he had been acting as a father figure to the boys. One of the boys is found dead, the other on a bus trying to escape.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Double-Cross</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/double-cross/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/double-cross/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Singer Charlotte Danville is murdered, crucified above a statue of Jesus in a church, killed by Cody, owner of Hombre Motors. Frank Berlin (now Father Frank of the church in question) and Charlotte had been high school sweethearts, but had split up before prom, with her attending with her other best friend Cody. Years later, Cody uses his car dealership to help fund Father Frank&amp;rsquo;s church, while providing a car and condo for Charlotte.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fannysmackin&#39;</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/fannysmackin/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/fannysmackin/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis A series of people, seemingly at random, are beaten and kicked to the point that they need serious hospitalization by an unknown cadre of assailants, wearing pig snouts as masks. One of the victims is Greg, on his way to pick up evidence. By getting hold of a cellphone of one of the gang members, the CSIs are able to lead them into a trap and arrest the gang.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Toe Tags</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/toe-tags/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/toe-tags/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis This episode is told partly from the perspective of the dead, as five bodies in the morgue &amp;lsquo;come to life&amp;rsquo; in the afterlife. Meanwhile, Grissom teaches a class to the students from UNLV, showing them around the CSI labs and morgues.
#An escort (who was also a cop) is killed by a high-roller for causing him bad luck.
#A woman is killed by her husband for being too attractive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Built to Kill (Part 2)</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/built-to-kill-part-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/built-to-kill-part-2/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Catherine&amp;rsquo;s father, Sam Braun , is killed in an act of revenge for being the percieved cause of another investors suicide. Before Sam&amp;rsquo;s death, his killers make Catherine believe she&amp;rsquo;s been raped, and hold her daughter for ransom. Sam&amp;rsquo;s killer is, in turn, killed by Sam&amp;rsquo;s bodyguards.
Rock star Izzy Delancy has been killed by a blow to the head, and an identical miniature of the crime scene has been left behind.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Built to Kill (Part 1)</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/built-to-kill-part-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/built-to-kill-part-1/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Robert O&amp;rsquo;Brien commits suicide at a Sam Braun&amp;rsquo;s party, with alprazolam in his system. Robert&amp;rsquo;s life-partner has the bottle of pills, and the gun used is registered in his name, making him a suspect. Sesame seeds in the gun, Robert&amp;rsquo;s mouth, Robert&amp;rsquo;s pockets, and an oven mitt with trace GSR prove that it really was a suicide.
A performer at Cirque du Soleil&amp;rsquo;s KA finds a dead body just off backstage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Way to Go</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/way-to-go/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/way-to-go/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis The episode opens where &amp;ldquo;Bang-Bang&amp;rdquo; left off. Brass has been shot and is being rushed by the EMTs to the hospital. His blood pressure is dangerously low and Brass flatlines on the table. The doctors bring him back, and Brass hallucinates, remembering when he asked Grissom to be his emergency contact and to have power of attorney in case something happens, because there&amp;rsquo;s no one he trusts more with his life or death.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bang-Bang</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/bang-bang/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/bang-bang/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis It starts out in a casino with a guard having his gun stolen and a guest shoots him with it. The shooter takes a hostage and the casino calls in the SWAT team. Jim Brass arrives with SWAT as the negotiator. Once the floor is cleared, they try and open the door. The shooter shoots through the door and we flash back to 15 hours before.
Brass, Grissom, Warrick, David and Doc Robbins are on the scene of a domestic homicide case, where the wife (Janice Cutler) was shot in the face.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Time of Your Death</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/time-of-your-death/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/time-of-your-death/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis A well-to-do man is found dead, far from his hotel, in fancy, party clothes. He was on a scripted night of fantasy and entertainment, which included hustling people at pool, being chased in a high speed car race, and getting the beautiful girl. What was not a part of the script is his death.
The team follows the victim via hotel surveillance, discovering who he was with and where he went; a banged-up Ferarri gives them more clues.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rashomama</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/rashomama/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/rashomama/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Solving the case of wealthy defense attorney Diane Chase &amp;ndash; killed at her son&amp;rsquo;s wedding &amp;ndash; is compromised when all of the evidence from the case is stolen along with Nick&amp;rsquo;s car, while he, Greg and Sara are having breakfast at their traditional restaurant (the same as seen in &amp;ldquo;The Strip Strangler&amp;rdquo; back in season one).
Confined to the lab until Internal Affairs arrives, and without the evidence, the three reconstruct the case from their memories and the videographer&amp;rsquo;s DVD of the event.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Poppin&#39; Tags</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/poppin-tags/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Apr 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/poppin-tags/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Three members of a rap artist Hi-Def&amp;rsquo;s street team are found dead after attempting to hang posters of rival rapper, Dollar, in a bikini and a &amp;lsquo;Dude&amp;rsquo;s Gone Wild&amp;rsquo; pose. The poster was made off a video taken while Dollar was held at gunpoint, which was orchestrated by one of Dollar&amp;rsquo;s own street team; Dante. Dante had only joined up to get close to Dollar. His sister, Trish, had been in a &amp;lsquo;Girls Gone Nuts&amp;rsquo; video, made by Dollar, and when their father saw it, beat Trish nearly to death.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spellbound</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/spellbound/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Apr 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/spellbound/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Grissom and his team investigate the case of psychic Sedona Wiley who envisioned her own death. During a &amp;lsquo;reading&amp;rsquo; with two young women (Anah Leah and Lori from Evaluation Day), the psychic begins to see visions of her own murder instead of information pertaining to her clients. When she is later found dead in her occult shop, it is up to the CSI team to determine her true cause of death.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Unusual Suspect</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/the-unusual-suspect/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/the-unusual-suspect/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis 17 year-old Stacy was found wrapped in a shower curtain, in her school&amp;rsquo;s flower bed, having last been seen alone at tennis practice. Marlon West, her classmate, is accused of her murder, based on the evidence of Stacy&amp;rsquo;s hair in his shower and sink drains. However, on the stand it is his 12 year-old sister, Hannah, who confesses to the crime.
What is known is that there were fake &amp;lsquo;out of order&amp;rsquo; signs in the girls&amp;rsquo; locker room, and the only non-labeled showerhead was packed with sodium, so that it exploded when Stacy used it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Like to Watch</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/i-like-to-watch/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/i-like-to-watch/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis The forensics reality show Hard Crime follows the CSIs as they work on the rape case of Christina Hollis. Raped in the very condo building she worked and lived in, Christina had been tied to her bed by duct tape and assaulted by Richard McQueen, a man posing as a fireman. The rapist&amp;rsquo;s MO was to light smoke bombs in the building, knock on the door of a woman, knock her out with the lorazepam and to rape her over hours, multiple times.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Up in Smoke</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/up-in-smoke/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/up-in-smoke/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis A cold case dovetails with a hot one, when a John Doe is found in the chimney of a canoodling couple. The home owner, Martin Sidley, was a suspect in the missing persons case of sixteen year-old Caroline Fiztgibbons one year previously, but is stunned to learn the body in his chimney is his son. Catherine and Warrick, who worked on Caroline&amp;rsquo;s case, join Sara and Nick on the Sidley case, with the intent to found evidence in their old case.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pirates of the Third Reich</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/pirates-of-the-third-reich/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/pirates-of-the-third-reich/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Ina complicated and disturbing episode, Lady Heather returns when her daughter, Zoe Kessler, is found dead in the desert wearing only a bra and panties. Zoe is emaciated, branded with the number 19, her hair has been shaved off and her right hand chewed off.
At the autopsy, they determine one of her eyes was severed at the optic nerve, and Zoe had necrotizing faciitis, which had been injected into her blood stream causing her to rot from the inside out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Killer</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/killer/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/killer/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis In a twist to the normal CSI format, this episode was told from two perspectives: that of the CSIs and that of the killers.
Karl &amp;lsquo;Red&amp;rsquo; Cooper is a former bank robber and thief who served time when his former friend, Clayton Nash, finked on him and a bunch of their fellow criminals. Karl shoots and kills Clayton in retribution, after Nash contacts him as a part of the 12-step process to cure one&amp;rsquo;s self of dependency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kiss-Kiss, Bye-Bye</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/kiss-kiss-bye-bye/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/kiss-kiss-bye-bye/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis At her birthday party, Lois O&amp;rsquo;Neill, a former Vegas show girl and ex of one of Vegas&amp;rsquo; founders, is having a bash. Dancing with handsome men and dolling out advice to the younger set. So it&amp;rsquo;s surprising when one of her waiters, Tim Duke, is found dead by her assistant later that night and Lois is nowhere to be seen. When the assistant, Eve Girard, is asked to open the closet/safe, Lois is found cowering within, and evidence points to her being shot at as she went to hide.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daddy&#39;s Little Girl</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/daddys-little-girl/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/daddys-little-girl/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Two Daddy&amp;rsquo;s girls pay high prices when their worlds invite murder and mayhem.
Bianca Desmond, daughter of &amp;lsquo;Gas &amp;amp; Sip&amp;rsquo; king, Happy Harry Desmond, lives with her boyfriend Ahren, who is found dead in her garage after a night of partying with Bianca and Chelsea Wannamaker. Bianca demonstrates a bit of a cleaning jag, prompting the CSIs to suspect she&amp;rsquo;s a speed freak. Chelsea claims they only use drugs recreationally.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Werewolves</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/werewolves/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/werewolves/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis An anonymous phone call informs 911 that a man is dead in his house. When the CSIs arrive, they find a dead Hayden Bradford, who puts new meaning to the term hirsute. Hayden had Hypertrichosis, and was killed via a silver bullet through the heart.
Warrick and Sara explore the inside of the house and find that a woman named Michelle (who had called Hayden 6 times that night) was in pictures and appeared to be his girlfriend.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Still Life</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/still-life/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/still-life/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Karen Matthews, a widow to a soldier who died in Afghanistan, reports her son, 6 year-old Jesse, has gone missing from a playground. Other parents at the park report they saw a boy looking like Jesse being watched by a white male with a 51&amp;rsquo;s baseball cap, as does a necropheliac who saw the boy in the restroom.
When Jesse is found in the company of the man and his wife, his DNA matches theirs and he refers to them as his parents.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dog Eat Dog</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/dog-eat-dog/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Nov 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/dog-eat-dog/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Grissom and Catherine confront a case of a man with [http://www.pwsausa.org/ Prader-Willi Syndrome] who literally ate himself to death. Jerry Gable required constant supervision all his life, or he would eat non-stop. He lived with his sister, but when she went to the hospital for surgery, she left her boyfriend to watch Jerry. Jerry manipulated the boyfriend to take him to a buffet, where he chowed down at the buffet itself and was kicked out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Bullet Runs Through It (Part 2)</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/a-bullet-runs-through-it-part-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/a-bullet-runs-through-it-part-2/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis In the conclusion of &amp;ldquo;A Bullet Runs Through It (Part 1)&amp;rdquo;, the detectives and CSI follow the questions of who shot officer Bell, who shot the young boy on his bicycle, and why would a car open fire on a police squad car.
The criminals opened fire on the cop car to distract them from the car the police had originally intended to pull over. Having seen a man strong-arm a pregnant woman into a car, the police had signaled them to pull over, not knowing they were really trafficking drugs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Bullet Runs Through It (Part 1)</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/a-bullet-runs-through-it-part-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/a-bullet-runs-through-it-part-1/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis In a two-part case that highlights the possible ways for a community to be divided over a shooting, the CSIs find themselves in the unenviable position of having to be neutral parties between the police and the citizens they protect.
A routine traffic stop is interrupted by a high speed car chase, and Sofia Curtis and Jim Brass join the uniforms in the pursuit. The criminals are armed with automatic rifles and nine-millimeters, and are firing on the police vehicles from the start.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Secrets and Flies</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/secrets-and-flies/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/secrets-and-flies/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Two cases, both surrounded by secrets and lies. Or at least flies.
Catherine runs with the main case, of a woman, Christina Adalian, found dead in front of her baby, Joey, by her sister. While the scene appears to be a suicide, there&amp;rsquo;s no blood spatter on Christina&amp;rsquo;s hand. Another catch is that she&amp;rsquo;s still a virgin and had the baby via Cesarean. Doc Robbins initially suspects frottage, but Sara digs up news that Christina was affiliated with Project Sunflower.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gum Drops</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/gum-drops/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/gum-drops/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Told with the whispery voice-over of a little girl, Nick, Sara, Warrick and Greg delve into the tale of what appears to be a quadruple homicide with no bodies. The McBride family (mother, father, son and daughter) live a quiet life and are known in their community. When the local doctor calls in a 911 call, spotting blood on the floor, the local police are stunned at the amount of blood in the house.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shooting Stars</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/shooting-stars/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/shooting-stars/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis A fairly straightforward case, in so far as they go. After dumping they body of Ty Bently in someone&amp;rsquo;s yard, a dozen of unwashed cult members retreat to their compound and eleven of the twelve die by ritual suicide (spiked vodka) to ascend via the mother ship during the [http://comets.amsmeteors.org/meteors/showers/orionidhistory.html Orionid meteor shower].
The cult members broke into the house by slashing the screen door, and proceeded to raid the fridge for junk food.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bite Me</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/bite-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/bite-me/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis## A husband and wife, unhappily married, have a night alone which ends when the wife is found dead at the bottom of the stairs in a pool of blood. The case unfolds ambiguously, as the evidence points to an accident or a murder, but neither conclusively. The husband, Ray, was married before and his first wife died of a stroke, falling on the stairs; this is later proven correct by exhumation and autopsy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Room Service</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/room-service/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Sep 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/room-service/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Two cases are well tied together in this episode, aptly showing how, in the end, we all end up in the same place. The episode is filmed with a lot of split screen, allowing one case to mirror the other and to hi-light the class differences between the dead men. It&amp;rsquo;s interesting to note that the CSI&amp;rsquo;s seem to treat each case as equally important.
One case is of Julian Harper, and up and coming actor who was found dead in his hotel room by his best friend, Blinky.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bodies in Motion</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/bodies-in-motion/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/bodies-in-motion/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis The two forensic teams come back together under the leadership of Grissom and Catherine just in time to tackle three separate investigations: a murdered couple found in bed in a suspicious trailer explosion; a beautiful stripper discovered dead and dumped in the worst part of town; and two bodies found baked and decomposed after spending five days in the trunk of a car exposed to the hot Vegas sun, forcing the CSIs to &amp;lsquo;wrap&amp;rsquo; up the evidence and bring it back to the lab for further analysis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grave Danger</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/grave-danger/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/grave-danger/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis The CSI teams come together to save one of their own when they learn one team member has been kidnapped and buried alive, and now they must find him before he suffocates under 5 feet of dirt.
Sara Sidle Review When Grissom determines that the insects on Nick are fire ants, and that they&amp;rsquo;re only found in certain areas, Sara remembers that the suspect&amp;rsquo;s daughter worked in a nursery and pin-points which one, allowing them to find Nick.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Iced</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/iced/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/iced/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Two amorous freshmen are found dead on a sleeping bag in a dorm room, and Sara and Greg run into one dead end after another as they try to determine why the students were killed. Warrick, Nick and Catherine figure out how a man is found dead in the center of a crop circle. Ecklie is called into duty for a man found dead in his car and his body later goes missing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Committed</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/committed/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/committed/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Grissom and Sara investigate the murder of a mental-hospital patient and quickly narrow down the suspects to a handful of other patients and staff members.
Sara Sidle Review Sara is attacked by the main suspect when Grissom walks off and leaves her all alone in the nurse&amp;rsquo;s station. Later, we learn that Sara&amp;rsquo;s mother spent a few months in a psychiatric hospital, and that Sara used to visit her.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weeping Willows</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/weeping-willows/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/weeping-willows/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis A man whom Catherine flirted with at a bar reappears in her life as a suspect in a murder investigation.
Quotes Sidle: So, Judge Wilson tells me I&amp;rsquo;d have better luck with a blue suit than a gray suit. What is that? Do you think he meant that? Do you think he was flirting with me or &amp;hellip; ?
Willows: I thought judges were supposed to be color blind.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hollywood Brass</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/hollywood-brass/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/hollywood-brass/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Brass travels to Hollywood, California to try to track down his estranged daughter&amp;rsquo;s friend, meanwhile trying to rekindle some kind of relationship with her.
Sara Sidle Review Sara does not appear in this episode.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>4x4</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/4x4/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Apr 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/4x4/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis A wild day in Las Vegas has the CSIs simultaneously investigating four fatalities. Catherine and Warrick look into the death of an auto convention model found murdered in a camper on display, as Nick examines the death of a boy found beaten and burned on a bus bench outside a mini-mall. Across town, the investigation into a car accident leads Grissom to suspect the driver was aiming at his victim, and Greg and Sara discover that toxic mold has eaten away at a body builder from the inside out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spark of Life</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/spark-of-life/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/spark-of-life/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Two CSI investigations intertwine when a woman&amp;rsquo;s suicide in the Vegas wilderness is linked through evidence to the murder of a suburban family. Grissom discovers a connection between the fiery suicide of a woman in the Vegas wilderness and the slaughter of an entire family in a suburban home. The evidence exposes a couple&amp;rsquo;s infidelity, as well as the unthinkable results of one woman&amp;rsquo;s desperate attempt to get pregnant.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Compulsion</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/compulsion/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/compulsion/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis A serial killer strikes again, and the CSI team tries new technology using evidence from a prior killing. They find a fingerprint belonging to Jesse Acheson, who becomes the prime suspect. A boy confesses to the killing of his brother, but evidence suggests that he may not have committed the crime.
Quotes Sidle: Only geeks still say &amp;lsquo;da bomb&amp;rsquo;, but, uh, if you ask me, geeks should be revered.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Big Middle</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/big-middle/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/big-middle/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Catherine, Nick, and Warrick investigate a badly mutilated body in the woods. The cause of death was a shotgun blast. Nearby is a beaver dam made in part with cash. Grissom, Sara, and Greg try to determine how a man was killed in a hotel room. It leads them to a convention of big women.
Sara Sidle Review There&amp;rsquo;s not much for Sara in this episode. She reprimands the cops at the station when they make fat jokes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>King Baby</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/king-baby/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/king-baby/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Now that Catherine heads up a swing-shift crew that includes Warrick and Nick, the three of them rarely get a chance to work alongside Grissom anymore. Tonight, however, the whole gang is thrown back togeather to investigate a high-profile murder, but Catherine isn&amp;rsquo;t too happy about it. A powerful casino owner, who claimed to have dirt on almost every prominent person in Vegas, is found dead in his driveway.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unbearable</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/unbearable/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/unbearable/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Grissom, Sofia, Sara and Greg investigate the disappearance of a woman coming home from a night out with a friend, her abandoned car found on the edge of a highway. Catherine, Warrick and Nick investigate the deaths of a hunter and his prey, a Kodiak bear.
Note: this episode of CSI was the winner of a Genesis Award (Humane Society) for its protrayal of canned hunts.
Sara Sidle Review Sara, Greg, Grissom and Sofia check out a body dump.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nesting Dolls</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/nesting-dolls/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/nesting-dolls/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Two female bodies, buried together and covered in tar, are discovered by construction workers out in the desert. The investigation reveals that both victims&amp;rsquo; fingertips have been cut off and that they were apparently buried years apart. Later, Sara treats one suspect with such distain that it jeopardizes her job and she reveals to Grissom a dark family secret that is at the root of her recurring personal problems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Snakes</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/snakes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/snakes/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis The swing shift has a busy time. Warrick looks into the murder of man by someone who apparently needs a wheelchair. Nick looks into the murder of woman in the subculture of the narcocorrido, songs about drug murders. The night shift is slow and lends help to Catherine&amp;rsquo;s team.
Character Notes  Even though Sara told Ecklie it was already done in &amp;ldquo;Mea Culpa&amp;rdquo;, she only now has her post PEAP talk with Grissom.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who Shot Sherlock?</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/who-shot-sherlock/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/who-shot-sherlock/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Greg, for his final proficiency, has to determine how the Sherlock Holmes of a Sherlock Holmes club was killed. Nick and Warrick try to determine how the driver of jeep was killed when the car ran off the road. They have to do this under budget while Catherine is watched by Ecklie.
Sara Sidle Review Greg works his final proficiency with a little help from both Sara and Grissom.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>No Humans Involved</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/no-humans-involved/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/no-humans-involved/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Sara&amp;rsquo;s mysterious background becomes a bit more clear as she helps investigate the starvation death of a 5-year-old boy whose body is discovered near a trash dumpster. At the county lock-up, Warrick and Nick probe the beating of a prisoner in an overcrowded cell. Later, Catherine learns that being the boss isn&amp;rsquo;t all it&amp;rsquo;s cracked up to be when she has to reprimand Warrick for what she deems unprofessional behavior.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mea Culpa</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/mea-culpa/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Nov 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/mea-culpa/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Grissom is confronted with new evidence while on the stand of a murder trial of a restaurant owner. This development requires the reopening of the case and Eckley initiates an inquiry into Grissom and his team. The results of the inquiry lead to dramatic changes of the CSI team, with Catherine being promoted to head of the Swing Shift, with Warrick and Nick to work for her.
Note: Warrick states that swing shift starts at 4 (pm), meaning that Graveyard (Sara, Greg and Grissom) is from midnight to 8 am.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ch-Ch-Changes</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/ch-ch-changes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/ch-ch-changes/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis A woman who was pulled over by police is found murdered two miles up the road from the stop. It&amp;rsquo;s not long before Doc Robbins determines that the woman is, genetically speaking, not a woman.
Character Notes *Sara doesn&amp;rsquo;t have any problems dealing with transgendered or transsexual people.
Quotes Brown: Wow. Mascara, tweezers &amp;hellip; under-eye cream &amp;hellip; &amp;hellip; neck-firming lotion. (He shakes his head and mutters.) Girls. Pads &amp;hellip; one, two, three, four jars of depilatory cream?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Formalities</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/formalities/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/formalities/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Grissom is called to a murder of a 17-year-old in a casino penthouse. Sofia Curtis joins him in his research, she normally works in the day-shift. The entire team gets involved when its discovered that a kiddnapping took place along with the murder.
Sara Sidle Review Sara does not appear in this episode.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What&#39;s Eating Gilbert Grissom?</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/whats-eating-gilbert-grissom/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Nov 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/whats-eating-gilbert-grissom/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis The killer from &amp;ldquo;The Execution of Catherine Willows&amp;rdquo; returns with deadly results. The entire team is engaged in a race against time to stop this sadistic killer from succeeding again. Grissom is additionally distraugh by the idea that this killer is smarter than he is.
Sara Sidle Review Sara is tasked to decipher the psychological clues in the bondage comic book. Later she realizes that the last &amp;lsquo;victims&amp;rsquo; name is actually an anagram for &amp;lsquo;Miss October&amp;rsquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Swap Meet</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/swap-meet/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/swap-meet/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Grissom and Sara investigate the murder of a woman after a swap party. The married couples in the neighborhood meet and switch partners. With the help of a crime scene cleaner, Nick and Warrick find there was more to their crime scene than they first thought. Catherine wants a promotion to day shift supervisor.
Sara Sidle Review Sara works with Grissom on the &amp;lsquo;swapping&amp;rsquo; case, and admits that she has trouble understanding that lifestyle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crow&#39;s Feet</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/crows-feet/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Oct 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/crows-feet/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis A woman is found dead in a hotel suite with what appears to be symptoms of the ebola virus. Another woman is found dead with similar symptoms. Catherine and Nick investigate. Sara and Greg Sanders (with help from Grissom) try to determine how a the owner of a home was killed; his home was tented for infestation.
Sara Sidle Review Grissom, Sara and Greg investigate the death of a man who died in his house, which was tented by an extermination company.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Harvest</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/harvest/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/harvest/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis A child is abducted. As the Amber Alert goes out, the entire team investigates in a race against time. Lindsay Willows is found hitchiking to the alarm of Catherine.
Sara Sidle Review Sara and Grissom work the angle of the missing child, and her personal possessions; Sara discovers the child&amp;rsquo;s diary and her web browsing.
Character Notes  The quote below is only the second time that Grissom has ever complimented Sara, which sheds some light on their relationship.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Down the Drain</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/down-the-drain/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Oct 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/down-the-drain/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Heavy rains in Vegas wash up a body in the storm drains. As the team investigates, they find bones from another murder.
Sara Sidle Review Sara risks her life (and Warrick&amp;rsquo;s) to remove a door from a closet loaded with pipe bombs.
Character Notes  Stubborn Sara surfaces again.
 Sara assures Grissom that she doesn&amp;rsquo;t have a drinking problem (re. &amp;ldquo;Bloodlines&amp;rdquo; and that she doesn&amp;rsquo;t have a death wish.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Viva Las Vegas</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/viva-las-vegas/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/viva-las-vegas/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis A feverish night in Las Vegas results in one dead male in an alien suit, one more dead male in a bathtub, one dead female with two suspicous men at the scene, and another dead male with a polaroid of yet another dead male, but on the other hand, we get to meet Greg&amp;rsquo;s replacement DNA person.
Sara Sidle Review Greg is the only one to inquire about Sara&amp;rsquo;s summer (she took some vacation time), but Grissom is apparently the only one who knows she saw a PEAP (Police Employees Assistance Program) counselor &amp;ndash; sessions that were mandatory as a result of her drunk driving arrest the previous season.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bloodlines</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/bloodlines/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 May 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/bloodlines/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis A casino employee is beaten and raped on her way home from work, but she survives and identifies her attacker. Unfortunately, a DNA test sets him free and Grissom must wrestle with whether evidence can ever lie. Later, Grissom comes to the rescue of a coworker who ends up on the other side of the law.
Sara Sidle Review After they discover that the promotion was cancelled, Sara, Nick and Warrick go out for a few drinks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>No More Bets</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/no-more-bets/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 May 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/no-more-bets/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Sam Braun is at it again. Based on a real life case of a several MIT engineering students who, in the 1970s, figured how to beat roullette by using physics. The results of this tactic prove deadly. Catherine learned last year that he&amp;rsquo;s her dad after comparing her DNA with his blood when he was a murder suspect, and unwittingly helped him beat that charge. He later gave her a hefty check, which she cashed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Turn of the Screws</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/turn-of-the-screws/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 May 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/turn-of-the-screws/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis A roller coaster runs off track leaving 6 people dead. The CSI team must uncover whether this was an accident, or foul play. Warrick and Catherine try to find the killer of a 13 year old girl.
Note: This episode was originally titled &amp;lsquo;A Turn of the Screws&amp;rsquo; and then &amp;lsquo;A Screw Turned Loose&amp;rsquo; before being titled &amp;lsquo;Turning of the Screw&amp;rsquo;. After going through so many titles, they decided to stick closer to the original and titled it &amp;lsquo;Turn of the Screws&amp;rsquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dead Ringer</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/dead-ringer/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/dead-ringer/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Grissom, Catherine and Nick investigate the death of a runner during a competition. Meanwhile Sara and Warrick investigate the death of couple in a hotel room, initially thought to be a murder-suicide. Both cases take place during this &amp;lsquo;cop&amp;rsquo; competition , with more than 20.000 attendants (all of them cops). This gives the investigations an interesting turn, as almost all the suspects and all dead people are cops.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bad Words</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/bad-words/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Apr 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/bad-words/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Warrick, Catherine, and Nick try to determine the cause of a house fire that kills a teenage kill. The fire is in the same neighborhood as a similar arson fire. Grissom and Sara investigate a man found dead with letter tiles in his stomach. The man was a competitor in a word game tournament.
Sara Sidle Review Sara and Grissom investigate the death of a man in a hotel bathroom, which leads them to a Logos tournament taking place there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bad to the Bone</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/bad-to-the-bone/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Apr 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/bad-to-the-bone/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis A violent murder in a casino parking garage and another episode in the police interview room lead the CSIs to one shocking discovery after another. The case involves a missing woman, a long dead body and a missing child.
Sara Sidle Review Sara has very little to do in this ep, and is fairly low key throughout it. She and Nick review the casino video tapes, and discover the suspect &amp;lsquo;snaking&amp;rsquo; (stealing chips from) the victim.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>XX</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/xx/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/xx/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis A mutilated female body is discovered tied to the undercarriage of a bus carrying prisoners from a women&amp;rsquo;s correctional facility after a severed arm flies out from beneath the vehicle and strikes a car. Catherine leads the investigation and at first believes the woman was escaping, but the evidence increasingly points to murder. Back in town, Warrick probes the death of a gambler who was stabbed multiple times in his brother&amp;rsquo;s kitchen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Off</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/getting-off/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/getting-off/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Catherine and Sara deal with the death of what at first seems to be a transvestite. Later during autopsy they find out that the make-up he seemed to be wearing was actually facepaint, he was a clown. Grissom, Nick, and Warrick deal with the death of a man in a homeless area. They found out he worked in a recovery center for drug users.
Sara Sidle Review During the autopsy it&amp;rsquo;s discovered that what they thought was makeup is actually face paint: the victim is a clown.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Early Rollout</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/early-rollout/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/early-rollout/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis The whole team is called in from off-duty to investigate a crime where a husband and his porn star wife were murdered execution style. Things get personal for Catherine when Grissom talks to her about her evaluation. Brass believes that Sara may have a drinking problem.
Sara Sidle Review Brass notices that Sara is popping cough drops at the scene, and later confronts her about it, wondering if she has a drinking problem (as a result of what he witnessed in &amp;ldquo;Butterflied&amp;rdquo;).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Paper or Plastic</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/paper-or-plastic/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/paper-or-plastic/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis A robbery at a grocery store results in a shootout leaving five dead. The police officer at the scene believes Grissom has a grudge against him. The entire team has to process the enormous amount of evidence at the scene.
Sara Sidle Review Grissom appears to be avoiding Sara at the crime scene, a result of the events in &amp;ldquo;Butterflied&amp;rdquo;.
Note: this episode was originally scheduled to air the week after &amp;ldquo;Butterflied&amp;rdquo; aired, explaining why Grissom is uncomfortable working with Sara.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Suckers</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/suckers/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/suckers/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Three little CSIs (Grissom, Sara, and Nick) respond to an electrocution at a casino. The casino is hosting Japanese antiquities. The electroctution is just a ruse to steal the central piece of the exhibit. Catherine and Warrick deal with a &amp;lsquo;vampire&amp;rsquo; murder.
Sara Sidle Review Sara works closely with Grissom on the antiquities case, despite recent events . Together, she, Nick and Grissom discover that the antiques are fake.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Butterflied</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/butterflied/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/butterflied/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis A woman found murdered in her home. Her resemblance to Sara causes Grissom to take a personal interest in the case and forces him to examine the decisions he has made in his life.
Sara Sidle Review Interrogating the murder suspect, Grissom confesses that he chose his career over Sara, unaware that she and Jim Brass are listening outside. This scene is the reason that Brass later asks if Sara has a drinking problem in &amp;ldquo;Early Rollout.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eleven Angry Jurors</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/eleven-angry-jurors/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/eleven-angry-jurors/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis The lone holdout on a jury is found dead in the jury room. The eleven jurors who were voting guilty and who hated the dead juror are the natural suspects. Nick reopens a four year old case when the sister of the victim comes forward with new evidence.
Sara Sidle Review Sara is fairly nondescript in this &amp;ndash; a good, general workman-like job with nothing standing out. She works with Warrick and Grissom on the jury case &amp;ndash; she is the one that finds the peanut butter in the victim&amp;rsquo;s chili, and later she discovers the carcass of the &amp;lsquo;killer&amp;rsquo; bee.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coming of Rage</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/coming-of-rage/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/coming-of-rage/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis A teenager is found murdered on a construction site. Grissom, Sara, and Warrick follow the lead of blood on a hammer. Nick, with an assist from Catherine, tries to find how a woman was killed by a gunshot on her lawn when no one nearby had a gun.
Sara Sidle Review Sara cuts the construction workers cold when they try to flirt with her at the crime scene. Later, when she discovers that the girl lied about being raped, she&amp;rsquo;s angry and hurt because she believed in her.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grissom vs. Volcano</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/grissom-vs-volcano/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/grissom-vs-volcano/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis The sheriff is under political pressure to find who killed a Air Marshal with a car bomb that the sheriff witnessed. Grissom, Catherine and Nick are pressured to produce results. Warrick and Sara try to find the murderer of the wife of a singer who headlines on the strip.
Sara Sidle Review Sara and Warrick discover that the singer&amp;rsquo;s wife committed suicide. During the investigation, Sara comments on the lonely lives of celebrities and the media exposure they face.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>After the Show</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/after-the-show/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/after-the-show/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis A suspect&amp;rsquo;s infatuation with Catherine results in her taking over a high profile case. The case is a missing woman who aspired to be a showgirl. Sara and Nick are angered since it takes the career making case away from them.
Sara Sidle Review Sara shows no real emotion when the suspect says he&amp;rsquo;ll only talk to &amp;hellip;the pretty one_ (Catherine), not to her or Brass. Sara and Nick had the original missing persons case, but since the suspect has a fascination for Catherine, Grissom gives the case to her.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Invisible Evidence</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/invisible-evidence/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/invisible-evidence/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Warrick&amp;rsquo;s appearance at the preliminary hearing on a rape and murder case goes terribly wrong when the only piece of evidence is thrown out on a technicality. Grissom and the team have 24 hours to make the case with new evidence or the killer will go free.
Note: This episode was pre-empted on October 16th because of a US Presidental Address in some cities, and re-aired November 13th.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jackpot</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/jackpot/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/jackpot/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis A severed head is shipped to Dr. Robbins from Jackpot, Nevada. Grissom goes to Jackpot to find the rest of the body and gets very little cooperation from the locals. Catherine gets an unexpected gift from her father.
Sara Sidle Review Sara does not appear in this episode.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fur and Loathing</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/fur-and-loathing/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/fur-and-loathing/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis The team is introduced to the &amp;lsquo;Furry&amp;rsquo; side of Vegas when a man is found dead on the side of the road, dressed in a raccoon suit. Elsewhere in Vegas, a gunshot victim is found in a deep-freezer, frozen solid.
Sara Sidle Review Sara and Nick investigate the freezer shooting. They find blood spatter, and eventually they find the shooter. They share several &amp;lsquo;you&amp;rsquo;ve got to be kidding&amp;rsquo; moments during the case when they discover that the suspect used granite glue to repair his rifle, and used house paint on his car.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Feeling the Heat</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/feeling-the-heat/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/feeling-the-heat/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis During Vegas&amp;rsquo;s latest Heat wave of triple digit temperatures, Gil and Catherine investigate a baby locked in a car. Warrick investigates a man dead of an apparent heat stroke in his house. Nick and Sarah investigate a woman&amp;rsquo;s body found floating in the lake with a blow to the head.
Sara Sidle Review Sara is suspicious of the boyfriend until he&amp;rsquo;s found dead, having tried to rescue the girl.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Homebodies</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/homebodies/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/homebodies/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Grissom and Warrick work a case of an old woman found mummified in her closet. Sara and Nick arrive to investigate a breaking and entering, only to find a raped teen. These cases are not as disparate as they first seem. Catherine looks into a gun found by a boy. The gun is connected to a week old murder across town that Warrick caught.
Sara Sidle Review Sara works the second break-in, and is affected when she discovers that the daughter has been raped.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>All For Our Country</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/all-for-our-country/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/all-for-our-country/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis When the lead suspects in Grissom&amp;rsquo;s serial killer case are murdered, Grissom suspects an inside job. Grissom and Brass are at odds when Grissom suggests it was a cop. Catherine and Sara investigate what happened to a college football fan when his bloated body is found in a bathtub.
Note This episode is continued from &amp;ldquo;Assume Nothing&amp;rdquo;
Sara Sidle Review Sara and Catherine get pulled off the serial killer case, and are given the chore of investigating a bloated body found in a bathtub.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Assume Nothing</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/assume-nothing/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/assume-nothing/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis The detectives hunt down a serial killer who has left a woman dead in a hotel room with her throat slit. The case turns to a double homicide when her husband is later found dead in his car. Nick jeopardizes the investigation when he discusses some of the case &amp;ndash; and it turns up on the local news.
Note: This episode is conlcuded in &amp;ldquo;All For Our Country&amp;rdquo;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Inside the Box</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/inside-the-box/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/inside-the-box/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Things get personal for the CSIs in the top-rated series&amp;rsquo; third-season finale, which explores the intersection of the investigators&amp;rsquo; work and their personal lives. Three masked bandits steal a safe-deposit box from a Las Vegas bank in a daring daytime heist, during which Det. Lockwood is killed.
Lockwood&amp;rsquo;s death provides Grissom and his crew with added incentive to find the murderous culprits. But the case really hits home for Catherine when the evidence leads to casino owner Sam Braun, who is like a father to her.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Play With Fire</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/play-with-fire/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/play-with-fire/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis A woman&amp;rsquo;s body is discovered in a small press box at a high-school football field, apparently the victim of strangulation. The evidence leads investigators to two convicts, one of whom is still in prison. At the crime lab, an explosion destroys key evidence and leaves Greg and Sara injured.
Sara Sidle Review Sara follows Grissom around the lab, curious, which results in her being caught in the explosion. Sitting outside on the curb, in shock from the explosion, Sara wants to begin clean up on the lab until Grissom forces medical attention on her.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Forever</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/forever/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/forever/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis A murder aboard a luxurious 747 and the discovery of two formally attired teens in the desert confound Grissom and his crew in this absorbing episode. First, a horse trainer is found dead in the cargo bay of a private jet carrying 12 well-heeled passengers and a million-dollar show horse. Initially, it appears the victim was trampled to death, but Grissom and Catherine uncover evidence of foul play.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Last Laugh</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/last-laugh/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/last-laugh/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Grissom and Catherine investigate the murder of a despised comic who died on stage, apparently after drinking from a tainted bottle of water. The case grows more puzzling when a 15-year-old boy dies in a convenience store after drinking the same brand of water.
Also: Brass reopens a woman&amp;rsquo;s accidental-death case after spotting the deceased&amp;rsquo;s husband in a flashy new car with a trophy date on his arm.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Night at the Movies</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/a-night-at-the-movies/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/a-night-at-the-movies/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Grissom and Catherine are called to an art house movie theater, where a dentist was killed during a showing of the Alfred Hitchcock film Strangers on a Train. Under the victim&amp;rsquo;s seat, Grissom finds a cell phone, with all the recent calls from a private number, and Catherine a bloody Phillips head screw driver. One of the theater&amp;rsquo;s staff says he saw a tall, blond woman leave the cinema during the movie, and she never returned.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Precious Metal</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/precious-metal/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/precious-metal/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Catherine, Nick, and Sara investigate a seemingly months old body found in the mountains. Discovery of the man&amp;rsquo;s identity lead the team to the world of robot wars. Warrick and Grissom look into the case of a man found murdered in an alley. Complicating their efforts, the medical examiner &amp;lsquo;lost&amp;rsquo; the body for 11 days. Greg helps this case by doing some undercover work.
Sara Sidle Review Nick has apparently heard about Sara&amp;rsquo;s breakup with Hank, and tries to set her up with his buddy; she firmly rejects the idea.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crash &amp; Burn</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/crash-burn/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/crash-burn/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Sara&amp;rsquo;s personal life takes a hit when she investigates a deadly car crash. The accident is a bizarre and seemingly random one involving an elderly woman who killed and injured several people when she drove her car through the front of a bar crowded with happy-hour patrons. Among those hurt is Sara&amp;rsquo;s EMT boyfriend, Hank Peddigrew. While Sara is rocked by his injury at first, she soon manages to work the case in her usual professional manner.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lucky Strike</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/lucky-strike/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/lucky-strike/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis The 5-year-old son of a professional basketball player is kidnapped while his father is at a casino, and a $5 million ransom is demanded. Elsewhere, Grissom and Nick investigate when a man with a wooden stake lodged in the back of his head stumbles out of his car and dies.
Character Notes  Sara knows the smell of menthol cigarettes.  Quotes Sidle: So you&amp;rsquo;ve got nothing.
Brown: Nothing I can see.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lady Heather&#39;s Box</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/lady-heathers-box/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/lady-heathers-box/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Two cases get very personal for Grissom and Catherine in this pivotal episode. In the first, Grissom discovers that the murders of a party guest at a nightclub and a man who was working out in his apartment are related. The deaths were similar and both victims were employees of Lady Heather, a dominatrix who penetrates Grissom&amp;rsquo;s cold exterior to reveal his vulnerability. The second case involves Catherine&amp;rsquo;s ex-husband, Eddie, who vanishes after his car crashes while he&amp;rsquo;s traveling with their daughter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>One-hit Wonder</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/one-hit-wonder/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/one-hit-wonder/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Catherine tries to track down a sexual predator who breaks into single women&amp;rsquo;s apartments and terrorizes them. Meanwhile, Sara reopens a cold case in which a colleague&amp;rsquo;s husband was murdered, but the killer was never caught. Sara is troubled with personal ties, as her colleague has a potentially fatal affliction. Grissom&amp;rsquo;s hearing further deteriorates.
Sara Sidle Review Sara stops by court to visit a wheelchair-bound prosecutor friend of hers, Melissa Winters &amp;ndash; who tells Sara that she&amp;rsquo;ll be dead soon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Random Acts of Violence</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/random-acts-of-violence/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/random-acts-of-violence/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Warrick is the focus of this intense hour in which he allows emotion to trump evidence when he investigates a drive-by shooting in his old neighborhood. Gunfire rips through the house of Warrick&amp;rsquo;s former mentor, who runs a recreational center, killing his 9-year-old daughter in her bedroom. Officers believe the actual target was a white teen who was dropping off his black girlfriend next door. One of the key suspects was once a school bully who tormented Warrick as a youth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Got Murder?</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/got-murder/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/got-murder/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Some bird watchers find a raven with a human eyeball in its mouth. This eventually leads our CSIs to a divorced man and his 2 children but not much else. Warrick and Grissom look into the circumstances of David&amp;rsquo;s unusual and first autopsy. This takes them to a car dealership where the man worked.
Sara Sidle Review Sara works with Catherine and Nick on the body found in the dump, and she is the one to find the bloodstains in the kitchen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recipe for Murder</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/recipe-for-murder/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/recipe-for-murder/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Grissom and Catherine investigate the grisly meat grinder murder at a slaughterhouse. Warrick and Sara look into the apparent suicide of a troubled young woman.
Sara Sidle Review Sara and Warrick investigate an apparent suicide at an apartment complex. At the scene, Sara inadvertantly calls Hank &amp;lsquo;baby&amp;rsquo; (she apologizes later) &amp;ndash; embarrassed, she ducks into the closet, where she finds still-wet stains on the victim&amp;rsquo;s clothing. At the autopsy, she finds tinted glass in the victim&amp;rsquo;s hair; later in Trace, she trades comments with the new tech, Hodges.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>High and Low</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/high-and-low/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/high-and-low/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Grissom, Warrick, and Nick investigate the case of man who apparently was murdered and pushed off a six story building. Grissom&amp;rsquo;s involvement is cut short by renewed hearing problems. Catherine looks into the murder of man outside of his regular bar.
Sara Sidle Review Sara only appears in the scene quoted below, having maxed out on her overtime and is not permitted in the field for a while.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blood Lust</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/blood-lust/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/blood-lust/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Grissom encounters a crime scene unlike any he has ever investigated before in this taut, twist-filled episode. Distracted by an attractive passenger, an Indian taxi driver feels his cab strike something at a suburban intersection. When he gets out to check, he finds a teenage boy pinned beneath the left rear tire, apparently killed on impact. The cabbie jumps back into the taxi to call for help, but a mob of angry onlookers&amp;ndash;all of them white&amp;ndash;drags him out and beats him for the crime.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Snuff</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/snuff/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/snuff/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis A horrific murder caught on film and the discovery of a skeleton covered with fire ants are the focus of this first-rate episode. Catherine is called in by a pornographic-film developer to view graphic footage from a snuff movie in which a woman is brutally slain. But the clues are scant: The murderer isn&amp;rsquo;t clearly seen, the cheap-looking hotel room could be almost anywhere and the film was sent to the developer anonymously.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fight Night</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/fight-night/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/fight-night/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis &amp;lsquo;Fight Night&amp;rsquo; in Las Vegas: busy, busy, busy. A boxing champ dies in the ring after taking a brutal beating from his nemesis, but Grissom finds evidence that points to murder. Outside, in a nearby parking lot, Catherine works a crime scene where a Los Angeles gang member was gunned down, apparently by a rival gang. Also, Nick investigates a jewelry-store robbery.
Sara Sidle Review Sara processes the boxing ring with Warrick, showing one of her only aversions: saliva.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Execution of Catherine Willows</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/the-execution-of-catherine-willows/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Nov 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/the-execution-of-catherine-willows/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis A triple murder case from Catherine&amp;rsquo;s rookie year is the focus of this intriguing installment. Fifteen years ago, Catherine helped put John Mathers on death row for the rape and murder of a coed at a nearby college. Her body was dumped in a trash bag, and two other girls found the same way were also linked to the suspect. As the episode opens, Mathers is about to be executed when he&amp;rsquo;s granted a stay based on new DNA evidence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Abra-Cadaver</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/abra-cadaver/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/abra-cadaver/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis## The strange worlds of magic and rock music are explored in this creepy episode. Grissom investigates when a woman vanishes while taking part in a magician&amp;rsquo;s act. The female volunteer is placed inside the Amazing Zephyr&amp;rsquo;s Chamber of Doom and the illusionist thrusts swords through the box. When it&amp;rsquo;s opened, she&amp;rsquo;s gone&amp;ndash;and doesn&amp;rsquo;t reappear in her seat as she&amp;rsquo;s supposed to. Only traces of blood are left inside the chamber.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Little Murder</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/a-little-murder/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/a-little-murder/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Grissom suspects murder when the body of a dwarf is found hanging from a rope high above a stage in a casino hotel where a convention of little people is being held. Across town, Catherine is attacked at a crime scene where a man was murdered during what appears to have been a home robbery.
Sara Sidle Review Sara and Nick help Grissom on the little people murder, discovering how the victim was killed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Let the Seller Beware</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/let-the-seller-beware/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/let-the-seller-beware/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Grissom and Catherine investigate the murder of a wealthy couple who are discovered in the swimming pool of their glamorous Las Vegas house, which was up for sale. The house sale turns sour and Suspects abound, including the the wife, ex-wife, son, and a Realtors who just may have been robbing his own clients. Meanwhile, Sara probes the death of a cheerleader who is found eviscerated on a soccer field, her organs having been ingested by her killer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Accused is Entitled</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/the-accused-is-entitled/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/the-accused-is-entitled/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis## The tables are turned on the CSIs, who are the ones put under the microscope when movie star is on trial for murder. Grissom and his crew are called in to investigate the death of a young woman found in the hotel room of popular actor Tom Haviland. Haviland admits that he slept with her, but denies killing her. Grissom believes otherwise, however, after finding blood evidence on the celebrity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Revenge is Best Served Cold</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/revenge-is-best-served-cold/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/revenge-is-best-served-cold/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis The top-rated drama gets off to a speedy start in its third-season opener, in which the teams investigate the murder of a street racer and the untimely death of a legendary poker player. Catherine and Nick become absorbed in the dangerous world of street racing after one of the illegal sport&amp;rsquo;s hotshot drivers is found dead out in the desert at an abandoned airstrip. Back in town, Grissom and his crew probe the sudden death of a renowned poker player who suffered a violent convulsion in the middle of a high-stakes game with three others.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Hunger Artist</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/the-hunger-artist/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/the-hunger-artist/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Season Finale. The CSIs investigate when the body of an unidentified young woman is discovered stuffed in an overturned shopping cart near a freeway underpass. Her horribly disfigured and partially decomposed face is a nightmare of blood, scabs and scars, as if she&amp;rsquo;d been shoved into a fan. A huge circular hole dominates her left cheek. Someone not only wanted her dead, Grissom reasons, but &amp;lsquo;they wanted her ugly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cross Jurisdictions</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/cross-jurisdictions/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/cross-jurisdictions/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Grissom and his crew handle their highest profile case to date when the city&amp;rsquo;s former chief of detectives is slain execution-style in his house following a wild party. Missing from the residence are the chief&amp;rsquo;s trophy wife and their 7-year-old daughter. When several motorists report seeing the girl along an access road near Miami, Catherine and Warrick fly there and meet that city&amp;rsquo;s top CSI, Horatio Caine, who aids them in the investigation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Anatomy of a Lye</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/anatomy-of-a-lye/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/anatomy-of-a-lye/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Grissom and Sara investigate when a man&amp;rsquo;s body, which has been doused with lye, is found buried in a park; Nick tries to determine how a hiker apparently drowned in a desert.
Sara Sidle Review Sara provides a solid job, working with Grissom on the body found in the park which becomes a hit-and-run/homicide. Sara appears irritated when the suspect keeps changing their story.
Quotes Sidle: Take off your shirt &amp;hellip; The warrant is for the whole shirt.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cats in the Cradle</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/cats-in-the-cradle/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/cats-in-the-cradle/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Grissom and Catherine investigate the stabbing death of an 80-year-old woman who lived in a run-down house full of cats; Nick and Sara comb through the remains of a car bombing that was, apparently, a murder plot gone awry.
Quotes Stokes: Wow. You look &amp;hellip;
Sidle: Happy?
Stokes: Smug.
Sidle: I got a perfect print.
Sidle: Liar, liar car on fire.
Sidle: Sometimes a shot in the dark hits anyway.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stalker</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/stalker/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/stalker/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis The hunt for a deadly stalker is the focus of a tense episode that builds to a nail-biting conclusion. Jane Galloway lives in fear. Her doors are triple-locked. Every shade is drawn. The bathroom window is nailed shut. An alarm system is activated. But none of Jane&amp;rsquo;s precautions keep a stalker from killing her. When the CSIs arrive at the scene, they discover the victim with her hair dyed and her face shoved in a toilet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chasing the Bus</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/chasing-the-bus/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/chasing-the-bus/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Grissom and the entire crew investigate a deadly tour-bus accident in this change-of-pace episode. A bus carrying 23 passengers from Los Angeles to Las Vegas crashes less than 40 miles from its destination, killing nine people. Before he dies, the driver recalls that, moments before the wreck, the steering wheel began vibrating like a jackhammer in his hands, making it impossible for him to control the speeding vehicle. When the bus finally did come to a stop, it was on its right side on top of a sports car that was following it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Felonious Monk</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/felonious-monk/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/felonious-monk/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis The CSI investigate the disturbing case of the execution-style slaying of four Buddhist Monks, found shot point blank while chanting in their monastery near Las Vegas. Tensions in the neighborhood bring obvious suspects into the picture. Gil and Nick investigate the owners of a butcher shop who appear to resent the diversity the temple brought to their neighborhood. The culprit is someone less obvious, though and with the murder weapon is left in plain sight begging the question: is the killer an insider?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Primum Non Nocere</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/primum-non-nocere/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/primum-non-nocere/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis When Terry Rivers barrels into the opposing team&amp;rsquo;s goalie, a fight breaks out and Terry ends up at the bottom of a huge pile of bodies. After the players are separated, he is found dead&amp;hellip;with a deep, bloody gash across his neck. Grissom, Catherine and Sara are called in to investigate. Across town, Warrick and Nick look into the apparent drug-related death of a sax player at a casino.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Burden of Proof</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/burden-of-proof/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/burden-of-proof/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis A body hidden in the Western Las Vegas Anthropology Department leads the CSI team to a disturbing case of child abuse. The CSI team is called to investigate an apparent gun shot victim found hidden in a &amp;lsquo;body farm&amp;rsquo; &amp;ndash; a controlled environment where human decomposition is studied by scientists. The investigation leads them back to the victim&amp;rsquo;s home where they discover a disturbing piece of evidence&amp;ndash; a photograph of a naked 12-year-old girl.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Finger</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/the-finger/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jan 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/the-finger/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis When a man withdraws one million dollars cash from his bank, and he&amp;rsquo;s got blood on his hands, he draws attention from the police, and soon Catherine ends up an unwitting participant in a kidnapping gone awry in which the only lead to the victim is a severed finger. Catherine is ordered by a kidnapper to accompany a man who is to deliver $1 million in ransom to him or else he will kill the man&amp;rsquo;s mistress.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Identity Crisis</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/identity-crisis/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jan 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/identity-crisis/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Grissom&amp;rsquo;s nemesis, serial killer Paul Millander, reappears and claims a third victim. The latest slaying matches Millander&amp;rsquo;s previous killings in that it recreates his father&amp;rsquo;s murder, which Millander witnessed as a boy. In each case, the victim is shot once through the chest while lying in a bathtub. A nearby tape recorder contains the person&amp;rsquo;s supposed suicide message.
All three victims share the same birthday of Aug. 17&amp;ndash;the date Millander&amp;rsquo;s father was slain&amp;ndash;with the years in descending order from 1959.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You&#39;ve Got Male</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/youve-got-male/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Dec 2001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/youve-got-male/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Grissom and Sara are called to the crime scene when two murder victims are found hidden in pipes at a construction site in the middle of an alfalfa field, while Catherine and Nick investigate an ostensible hunting accident.
The investigation of the construction site murder reveals that the victims were sisters and the relationship of one of the sisters to a former prison inmate is a cause for suspicion &amp;ndash; especially when his presence is traced to the scene of the crime.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Organ Grinder</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/organ-grinder/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Dec 2001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/organ-grinder/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis## The CSI team is called in when a famous real estate entrepreneur is found dead in a hotel elevator.
When the body of Bob Fairmont, the real estate developer, is found, the team discovers that the crime scene has been tampered with and that the victim has been re-dressed. After tracing the cause of death to a lethal poison, the team is shocked to discover that Fairmont&amp;rsquo;s organs have already been removed and donated, making the case a bit more difficult to solve.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ellie</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/ellie/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/ellie/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Warrick heads the investigation of the murder of a con artist who turns out to be involved with Brass&amp;rsquo; daughter, and the evidence leads Sara on a counterfeit investigation.
With Grissom away, Warrick is in charge for the first time as the team investigates the murder of the con artist, who has run off with some tourists&amp;rsquo; money only to get shot and killed in the parking lot. The prime suspect in the case turns out to be Captain Brass&amp;rsquo; daughter, which causes Brass to take himself off the investigation professionally, but not personally.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>And Then There Were None</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/and-then-there-were-none/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/and-then-there-were-none/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Grissom and his team investigate a casino heist during which innocent victims were shot, while Catherine and Sara are called to the scene of a murder in a remote part of the desert.
The evidence found at both crime scenes &amp;ndash; the crowded local casino and the isolated desert convenience store where a clerk was murdered &amp;ndash; has the CSI team drawing a correlation between the two crimes. Featuring the return of Tammy Felton.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Slaves of Las Vegas</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/slaves-of-las-vegas/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/slaves-of-las-vegas/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Grissom and Catherine investigate the apparent violent death of a woman found in a sandbox. Their investigation leads them to the underground world of S&amp;amp;M clubs. Meanwhile, Warrick and Sara are called to a crime scene to investigate a shooting, which initially appears to have taken place during a robbery.
Quotes Victim I can&amp;rsquo;t find my pants!
Sidle: You can&amp;rsquo;t wear them out of here. What did you want them for?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Caged</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/caged/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Nov 2001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/caged/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Grissom and Nick investigate the death of a book restorer while Catherine and Sara are called to the scene of a fatal train crash.
When the female book restorer is found dead and locked inside a &amp;lsquo;cage&amp;rsquo; a temperature-controlled workspace, Grissom and Nick attempt to determine whether this is a case of suicide or homicide. They discover that the key to solving the case may be a co-worker who suffers from autism.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alter Boys</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/alter-boys/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/alter-boys/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Grissom and his team investigate a murder suspect who is caught red-handed &amp;ndash; burying the victims &amp;ndash; while Catherine and Warrick take on the case of a woman found dead in a hotel spa.
As Grissom, Nick and Sara investigate the seemingly clear-cut murder case, Grissom questions the simplicity of the evidence when he discovers that the suspect burying the victims is the brother of a convicted felon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scuba Doobie-Doo</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/scuba-doobie-doo/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Oct 2001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/scuba-doobie-doo/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Grissom, Sara and Warrick are called on to investigate an abandoned, blood-splattered apartment and Nick and Catherine must examine a dead scuba diver lodged in a tree. The former tenant of the bloody apartment claims that his missing girlfriend is visiting her parents &amp;ndash; and the parents say she never showed up.
Meanwhile, Nick and Catherine are called to the site of a large fire and are confronted with the scuba diver found dead in the top of a tree near Lake Mead.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bully for You</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/bully-for-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/bully-for-you/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis When the class clown at the local high school is found murdered, the CSI team is called to investigate, while Nick and Sara respond to the crime scene of a decomposed body found in a bag.
The student, who is also the top jock on campus, is found shot in the back in the school bathroom. The CSI team quickly discovers that the victim was also the class bully, and Grissom is convinced that he is looking for a classmate who was finally pushed to end the abuse once and for all.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Overload</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/overload/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/overload/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Grissom investigates a possible suicide at a high-profile construction site. Against the wishes of the Sheriff, Grissom pushes to get at the truth of the matter-he thinks the suicide was actually a homicide, and uses theories on electrocution to look for his killer.
Meanwhile, Nick and Catherine take on a case with little more than angora fibers to follow. A teenage boy dies while in session with his female psychologist, and traces of angora on his underwear make them believe the psychologist may be practicing very unconventional methods of &amp;lsquo;therapy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chaos Theory</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/chaos-theory/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Oct 2001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/chaos-theory/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis The entire CSI team investigates a disappearance at a local university. A young woman vanished, seemingly off the face of the earth. Forensics leads them to possible suspects, and possible suspects all have probable motives, but nothing seems to pan out. This leads our team to discuss the &amp;lsquo;chaos theory&amp;rsquo; that, when combined, many seemingly-innocuous events may have a deadly outcome. And closure is not always within reach.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Burked</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/burked/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/burked/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Grissom and crew are called in after high roller Tony Braun, a known drug addict and the son of a Las Vegas Mogul, is found dead in his house by a gardener. Since drug paraphernalia is discovered near his body and it is also determined that he had recently inhaled heroin, the cause of death is at first thought to be an overdose. But further examination of the corpse reveals that Braun had been restrained at some point with duct tape, leading Grissom to believe that the victim was forced to ingest lethal amounts of heroin and, perhaps, other drugs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Strip Strangler</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/strip-strangler/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 May 2001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/strip-strangler/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Grissom and his crew investigate when a young woman is strangled in her home, apparently the third victim of a serial killer. The crime scenes all have a common, mystifying element: this murderer really cleans them up, removing all traces of hair or fibers, and even plants misleading evidence. Just when things couldn&amp;rsquo;t get any worse, Grissom learns that the sheriff has called in the FBI to take over the investigation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Evaluation Day</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/evaluation-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 May 2001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/evaluation-day/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Las Vegas Police discover a disembodied head in a truck driven by two scantily clad girls after a high-speed chase, and a seemingly related decapitated corpse turns up in the desert. But Grissom and Catehrine are puzzled when the head doesn&amp;rsquo;t match the body &amp;ndash; a body that may not even be human. Warrick tries to help a young inmate who witnessed the murder of a gang member.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Justice is Served</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/justice-is-served/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/justice-is-served/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Grissom, Warrick and Nick investigate the brutal death of a jogger who was apparently killed by a mountain lion or a large dog and then had his organs removed with a scalpel, with a striking number of grisly, yet entirely possible conclusions, including evidence of cannibalism and organ harvesting, and their efforts to find out what caused the person&amp;rsquo;s demise leads them to a startling discovery. Catherine becomes convinced that a 6-year-old girl&amp;rsquo;s death was no accident when she and Sara examine a crime scene inside the Tunnel of Love ride at an amusement park.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sounds of Silence</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/sounds-of-silence/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Apr 2001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/sounds-of-silence/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis An apparent vehicular-manslaughter case turns into a murder investigation when Grissom discovers that the victim, who was deaf, was actually killed before a car hit him. Also, a shoot-out at a coffee shop, which may have been a professional hit, leaves five people dead, including a local high roller.
Sara Sidle Review A dead kid is in the street, apparently run over by a car, but Sara notes that the differences in tread marks shows that the victim was hit twice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gentle, Gentle</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/gentle-gentle/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Apr 2001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/gentle-gentle/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Grissom finds it difficult to control his emotions when he investigates the alleged kidnapping of the infant son of a Dot-Com Las Vegas millionaire family, especially when the evidence begins pointing to various family members who may be involved in the disappearance.
Sara Sidle Review## Sara arrives at the scene, and Grissom has her run the ransom note over to QD (Questionable Documents). Sara goes to QD and they determine the printers from the house don&amp;rsquo;t match the note.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>$35K O.B.O.</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/35k-obo/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Mar 2001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/35k-obo/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis A sudden rainstorm washes away the evidence Grissom, Warrick, Sara and Nick are collecting after an apparent car jacking that ended in a triple homicide. Meanwhile, Catherine investigates a collapse of a building that killed three senior citizens.
Sara Sidle Review## The case appears to be a carjacking/murder, but a sudden rain storm threatens to wash away the evidence. Despite what he told her earlier about getting a life outside the lab, Grissom calls Sara in on her day off.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Face Lift</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/face-lift/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Mar 2001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/face-lift/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Grissom investigates the murder of a man who was apparently killed while robbing a store; Catherine searches for a girl who was kidnapped 16 years earlier; Warrick and Sara probe the strange death of a woman who was reduced to ashes while sitting in her house.
Sara Sidle Review## Sara and Warrick get the case of a woman who burned to death while sitting in a chair &amp;ndash; Sara thinks that it might be spontaneous human combustion, a theory which Warrick poo-poos as science fiction, while Sara claims to be open to the possibility.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Too Tough To Die</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/too-tough-to-die/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Mar 2001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/too-tough-to-die/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Sara gets a little too personally involved when she investigates the rape and shooting of a young woman who was left for dead, but who still fights for her life in a nearby hospital; Catherine and Warrick try to determine whether a fatal shooting involving two neighbors was committed in self-defense.
Sara Sidle Review## At the scene, Grissom tells Sara to go to the hospital and collect evidence from the victim, even though she says she&amp;rsquo;d rather stay at the scene.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Table Stakes</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/table-stakes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/table-stakes/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis An elite fund-raising party at a legendary showgirl&amp;rsquo;s elegant Las Vegas mansion turns deadly in a twist-filled episode. Grissom, Catherine, Sara and Nick investigate when the body of a leggy brunette is discovered floating in the mansion&amp;rsquo;s pool. Their suspicions soon focus on the brash couple, Patrick and Amanda Haynes, who hosted the party and are house-sitting for the absent owner. They claim the former entertainer, now a wealthy older woman, is vacationing in Europe and can&amp;rsquo;t be reached, but the CSI team isn&amp;rsquo;t so sure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>To Halve and to Hold</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/to-halve-and-to-hold/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/to-halve-and-to-hold/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Grissom and Catherine piece together clues while assembling parts of a skeleton that was apparently cut up with a saw and then scattered on a mountain; Warrick and Sara investigate the death of a male stripper who died shortly after performing at a bachelorette party.
Sara Sidle Review Sara and Warrick get the case of a dead man in a hotel room &amp;ndash; the one with the &amp;lsquo;weird pool&amp;rsquo;, as Sara puts it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Boom</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/boom/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/boom/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Grissom, Warrick and Sara investigate a bombing that occurred in the lobby of a Las Vegas business building; Nick spends the night with a prostitute who is later found murdered in her house and he becomes the chief suspect, and only Catherine can exonerate him.
Sara Sidle Review At the bomb scene, Sara is wrapped up against the cold. Sara and Catherine examine the bomb debris at the lab, then Grissom has Sara check out an orange substance melted on to the clock gear of the timing device.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fahrenheit 932</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/fahrenheit-932/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/fahrenheit-932/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis A man convicted of arson and the murder of his wife and child seeks assistance from Grissom (aided by Warrick and Sara) to help prove his innocence. Meanwhile, Catherine and Nick investigate the underground world of sports gambling when a teenager is murdered at close range.
_Note: This was the first episode to air on Thursday night.
Sara Sidle Review Sara is laughing at Nick&amp;rsquo;s jokes when Grissom asks her and Warrick to work on a re-opened arson case.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I-15 Murders</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/i-15-murders/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/i-15-murders/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Grissom, Catherine and Nick investigate a woman who is kidnapped from a grocery store, and her disappearance points to a serial murderer. Sara and Warrick work on an apparent burglary gone wrong that may be more than it seems.
_Note: This episode was originally filmed to air third (after &amp;ldquo;Cool Change&amp;rdquo; and before &amp;ldquo;Crate &amp;lsquo;n Burial&amp;rdquo;), explaining Sara&amp;rsquo;s attitude towards Warrick.
Sara Sidle Review Sara works the apartment murder by herself until Warrick is assigned to help her &amp;ndash; something she is not happy about.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sex, Lies and Larvae</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/sex-lies-and-larvae/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/sex-lies-and-larvae/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis The investigators work a trio of diverse cases that involve a murder, a theft and a disappearance in this intriguing episode. Grissom investigates the shooting death of a young woman when her bloodied and bug-infested body is found on a nearby mountain. Most of the circumstantial evidence points to the woman&amp;rsquo;s abusive husband as the likely killer. But Grissom&amp;rsquo;s not so sure, since his analysis of the bugs indicates that the victim was killed three days prior&amp;ndash;when the hubby was out of town.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unfriendly Skies</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/unfriendly-skies/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/unfriendly-skies/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis The whole team works to solve the case of a man who was murdered in an airplane while in flight.
Sara Sidle Review Sara and Grissom process the plane, discovering who sat where and what they did. During their investigation, they discover &amp;lsquo;biologicals&amp;rsquo; in the bathroom, which leads Sara to recount her own &amp;lsquo;sex in the skies&amp;rsquo; experience. During the recreation, Sara plays the role of the flight attendant.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Anonymous</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/anonymous/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/anonymous/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis When a man is found dead in a setting disturbingly similar to a previous case (in the Pilot episode), Grissom realizes that a serial killer is on the loose. The Killer begins leaving clues to taunt Grissom, while Sara and Catherine work with Grissom. Warrick and Nick clash when they investigate a peculiar car accident.
Character Notes  While Sara loves the hotel bathroom here, in later episodes she displays a phobia of germs in public places.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blood Drops</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/blood-drops/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/blood-drops/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis An 18-year-old girl bolts from her suburban Las Vegas house screaming for help. Shortly thereafter, Grissom arrives at the home and discovers an especially gruesome scene: four family members &amp;ndash; the father, mother and two teenage boys &amp;ndash; are dead, butchered with a kitchen knife. The family&amp;rsquo;s two daughters, the teen who ran for help and her 4-year-old sister, are traumatized but otherwise unhurt. What initially looks like a bizarre cult murder becomes more disturbing when they discover the motive behind the massacre.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who Are You?</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/who-are-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/who-are-you/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Catherine violates department protocol when she takes the case of a rape accusation against her ex-husband. Warrick and Sara search for the missing bullet that will either exonerate or indict a cop for murder. Grissom and Nick investigate when a female skeleton is found under a house buried in cement.
Sara Sidle Review Sara and Warrick work the police shooting. At first, Sara is sympathetic towards the cop suspect, but later gets aggressive when questioning him when they discover that he has a round missing from his gun.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Friends &amp; Lovers</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/friends-lovers/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/friends-lovers/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Grissom and Warrick investigate a case of an apparently terrorized teen found dead in the desert; Sara examines the circumstances surrounding the body of a woman who was buried the week before and is found in a garbage dumpster; Nick and Catherine look into the claim by a teacher that she killed the dean of the school in self-defense.
Sara Sidle Review Sara investigates a dumped body in Henderson, dumpster dives and realizes the corpse has been embalmed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pledging Mr. Johnson</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/pledging-mr-johnson/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/pledging-mr-johnson/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis When Grissom and Catherine investigate when a leg is found severed from a body in a lake, they suspect the husband and boyfriend. Meanwhile Sara and Nick investigate a fraternity pledging that ended in the death of a pledge.
Sara Sidle Review A bit of flirtatious chatter in the locker room between Sara and Nick. Sara and Nick investigate a hanging in a fraternity; they question the fraternity president.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crate &#39;n Burial</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/crate-n-burial/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/crate-n-burial/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis When the wife of a well-to-do business man is kidnapped, Grissom, Sara and Nick investigate her disappearance, eventually saving her after she was buried underground, only to find the deceptions are deeper than they thought. Meanwhile, Warrick and Catherine investigate a hit-and-run.
Sara Sidle Review Sara, Nick and Grissom investigate a kidnapping, once Grissom realizes (from evidence found at the scene that Sara doesn&amp;rsquo;t think is much) that the victim is buried near a gold mine, Sara and Grissom check out gold mines with infrared via helicopter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cool Change</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/cool-change/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/cool-change/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis A man is killed after winning a fortune and then dumping his girlfriend; Grissom and Nick investigate this one. Holly Gribbs is in the hospital and Warrick is up for suspension for leaving her at the crime scene by herself. Newcomer to the CSI team, Sara, investigates Warrick&amp;rsquo;s actions. When Holly later dies in the hospital, Sara and Catherine track down the killer with some innovative pager work; Grissom refuses to suspend Warrick.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pilot</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/pilot/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/csi/pilot/</guid>
      <description>Summary Grissom investigates a suicide that presents little evidence. A tape recording of the man&amp;rsquo;s suicide note is put in to doubt when is mother insists that it&amp;rsquo;s not his voice. Warrick and Catherine investigate the shooting of a man during a break-in. Warrick is also assigned to shadowing newcomer Holly Gribbs during a routine fingerprint dust, something he is not too keen on doing. Nick talks to a man who was drugged and robbed by a prostitute.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>In the Shadow of Two Gunmen: Part I</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/ww/in-the-shadow-of-two-gunmen-i/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/ww/in-the-shadow-of-two-gunmen-i/</guid>
      <description>Summary Part One: An assassination attempt yields casualties; a military crisis looms in Iraq.
While the staff awaits news regarding the injuries to Jed and Josh, they recall how Josh, Sam, and Toby became involved in the campaign three years earlier; Leo, Toby, and C.J. deal with inquiries on Secret Service protection policies, as well as the absence of executive authority while Jed was in surgery.
Quotes Gina White male, twenty twenty-five, maybe five-ten.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>In the Shadow of Two Gunmen: Part II</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/ww/in-the-shadow-of-two-gunmen-ii/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/ww/in-the-shadow-of-two-gunmen-ii/</guid>
      <description>Summary Part Two: All the President&amp;rsquo;s men and women scramble in the chaotic wake of an assassination attempt that leaves some victims fighting for their lives. Meanwhile, as a manhunt continues, the wounded drift in and out of surgery recalling how Bartlet&amp;rsquo;s team came together during the dark months of his long shot primary campaign. Elsewhere, the press department is hounded by the media for details of the shooting while a military crisis looms in Iraq.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Kind of Day has it Been</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/ww/what-kind-of-day-has-it-been/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/ww/what-kind-of-day-has-it-been/</guid>
      <description>Summary The president prepares for a town-hall meeting with college students, while the military searches for a downed pilot in the Iraqi desert.
The staff deals with an American pilot who was shot down in Iraq; Toby&amp;rsquo;s brother is in danger on a space shuttle whose doors won&amp;rsquo;t close; Bartlet and the senior staff walk into a hail of bullets as they leave a town meeting.
Character Review Gina sees the shooter, but makes sure to protect Zoey first.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Six Meetings before Lunch</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/ww/six-meetings-before-lunch/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/ww/six-meetings-before-lunch/</guid>
      <description>Summary Mendoza is confirmed by the Senate; Mandy needs Toby&amp;rsquo;s help to replace a dead panda bear; Sam angers Mallory when she reads a position paper that he wrote supporting school vouchers; Josh meets with Jeff Breckenridge, who is irritating certain Congressmen with his stance on slavery reparations. Police make arrests at a fraternity party attended by the president&amp;rsquo;s daughter; Sam and Mallory clash over the issue of private-school vouchers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The White House Pro-Am</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/ww/the-white-house-pro-am/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/ww/the-white-house-pro-am/</guid>
      <description>Summary Abbey keeps the staff busy with the fallout when she leaks her personal preference for a Federal Reserve Board appointment and discusses child labor on a talk show, prompting a Congresswoman to offer an amendment which could shoot down the entire international tariff bill; Charlie&amp;rsquo;s date with Zoey is canceled because of threats by a white supremacist group.
Character Review Gina doesn&amp;rsquo;t seem to care if Zoey dates Charlie or not.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>20 Hours in LA</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/ww/20-hours-in-la/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/ww/20-hours-in-la/</guid>
      <description>Summary The President and his staff head to Los Angeles for a whirlwind visit and a celebrity fund raiser, and Bartlet meets his daughter Zoey&amp;rsquo;s new Secret Service agent.
Character Review A direct person, Gina takes the role of protecting &amp;#8216;Bookbag&amp;rsquo; seriously.
Character Notes  Gina was in the Army ROTC at U of Virginia (Criminology)
 She holds the rank of 2nd Lt. in MP
 Was the first person to sign up for the detail.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sticks and Stones</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/sticks-and-stones/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Mar 1999 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/sticks-and-stones/</guid>
      <description>Note: This is Maggie Doyle&amp;rsquo;s last appearance on ER.
Summary During a paramedic ride-along, Carter is forced to drive the ambulance while fleeing a riot scene and inadvertently runs over a teenage boy. Later, a paramedic is shot by an angry mob looking for the driver of the ambulance. Carol is despondent following Doug&amp;rsquo;s departure. She later discloses that she&amp;rsquo;s pregnant. Kerry is intrigued by an injured pro wrestler and his relationship with his father.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Storm, Part II</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/the-storm-part-ii/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Feb 1999 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/the-storm-part-ii/</guid>
      <description>Summary Greene assists paramedics in treating injured children at a school bus accident. En route, Doug and Jeanie survive their own accident. Kerry stops Doug from treating Jeanie&amp;ndash;or any other patient. Doug decides to resign and leave Chicago for the Northwest and asks Carol to come with him. She decides against it, but he leaves anyway. Carol steps down from running the clinic so that Anspaugh will keep it open.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Storm, Part I</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/the-storm-part-i/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Feb 1999 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/the-storm-part-i/</guid>
      <description>Summary Doug faces possible criminal charges after Ricky Abbott dies when Ross shows Joi how to bypass system lockouts to give Ricky a lethal dosage of dilaudin. Doug is delegated to desk duty, Carol&amp;rsquo;s clinic is shut down for acquiring the P.C.A. machine for Ricky, and Greene and Weaver face future disciplinary action for not reporting Doug&amp;rsquo;s tampering with the double blind study. Carter and Lucy discover a mutual attraction.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Double Blind</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/double-blind/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 1999 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/double-blind/</guid>
      <description>Summary Doug jeopardizes future federal grants for the entire ER when he breaks a double blind study by giving a sample drug to an ailing patient. Doyle lodges a sexual harassment complaint against Romano, hoping Dr. Corday will lend support. Lucy begins her surgery rotation under Benton&amp;rsquo;s tutelage. The two of them treat a man claiming to be 140-years-old. Mark declines to proceed in the NASA program. Carol questions Lynette&amp;rsquo;s intentions when she hosts a women&amp;rsquo;s health clinic for African American women only.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Good Luck, Ruth Johnson</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/good-luck-ruth-johnson/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 1998 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/good-luck-ruth-johnson/</guid>
      <description>Note: This was ER&amp;rsquo;s 100th episode
Summary Carter plays tour guide for Ruth Johnson, who was born in the hospital 100 years ago to the day, and her large family. Carol treats a boy who was hit by a car and tells a story of being chased, his friend being shot in the process. Peter observes Kotlowitz install a cochlear implant and decides to wait before scheduling an operation for Reese.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Good Fight</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/the-good-fight/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Nov 1998 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/the-good-fight/</guid>
      <description>Summary A girl and her father are brought into the ER after a car accident. Her father abandons her in the ER, and he is the only match for her rare blood type. This forces Benton to operate on her without blood and Carter and Lucy to travel all through the city to find the father. They encounter a number of obstacles including Carter dislocating his shoulder, and end up across the street from the hospital.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hazed and Confused</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/hazed-and-confused/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Nov 1998 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/hazed-and-confused/</guid>
      <description>Summary Corday commits a deadly error after being on-call for nearly 36 hours straight. Peter visits Dr. Kotlowitz and receives encouragement regarding a cochlear implant for Reese. Dr. Amanda Lee, a prospective new ER chief, visits. In the wake of a failed pregnancy attempt, Carol lashes out at a mother using abortion as a means of selective birth control. Carter and Lucy feud when Carter accidentally uses her palm computer and finds out what she thinks of him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day For Knight</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/day-for-knight/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 1998 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/day-for-knight/</guid>
      <description>Summary Third-year med student Lucy Knight reports to the ER. Doug hits the nail on the head when he describes her as a &amp;lsquo;hit-the-book&amp;rsquo; student. Lucy&amp;rsquo;s first day finds her informing a wife of her husbands terminal condition, comforting a pregnant woman, getting locked on the roof and trying to figure out Kerry Weaver&amp;rsquo;s &amp;lsquo;Tour on Tape.&amp;rsquo; Greene extends a protective wing over Lucy, who&amp;rsquo;s forced to endure Carter&amp;rsquo;s irritation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Of Past Regret and Future Fear</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/of-past-regret-and-future-fear/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Apr 1998 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/of-past-regret-and-future-fear/</guid>
      <description>Summary It&amp;rsquo;s another busy night in the ER, as case after case comes through the doors. Hathaway comforts a burn victim in his dying hours. Carter and Anna struggle with a man afflicted with cerebral palsy. Dr. Ross deals with an infant&amp;rsquo;s heroin addiction and its drug-addicted mother. Weaver cares for an elderly couple who may have AIDS. Peter and Elizabeth decide to keep their relationship a secret. Anna&amp;rsquo;s old boyfriend comes to town.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Brother&#39;s Keeper</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/my-brothers-keeper/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 1998 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/my-brothers-keeper/</guid>
      <description>Summary Several heroin ODs are brought into the ER, including Chase Carter. Mark tries to track down Cynthia. Anna treats a John Doe sent from another hospital because he had no insurance. Doug accuses two parents of child abuse, but finds out that their child is disturbed. Benton and Corday run into his sister Jackie. Scott Anspaugh finishes his chemotherapy.
Character Review Doyle is working the night shift, and is seen briefly at the beginning and end of the episode.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Obstruction of Justice</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/obstruction-of-justice/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 1997 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/obstruction-of-justice/</guid>
      <description>Summary Carter is arrested when he refuses to honor a warrant seeking evidence in a domestic abuse incident. Corday is overjoyed to be able to perform a rare femoral transplant. Doug returns from California. Benton and Corday discover that they have a lot in common. Cynthia takes Rachel to the dentist and other places. Jeanie threatens to sue to get her job back, to Kerry&amp;rsquo;s dismay. Anspaugh rehires her, and Al leaves for Atlanta without her.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Freak Show</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/freak-show/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 1997 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/freak-show/</guid>
      <description>Summary Benton takes advantage of a grieving father for a chance to write a paper on a boy with reversed internal organs. George Henry returns to complete his clerkship and suffers a near fatal attack. Jeanie confronts Kerry and Anspaugh over what she perceives as wrongful termination. Cynthia&amp;rsquo;s error forces the free clinic to open a week early; Carol enlists new ER nurse Yosh to help out. Mark strikes a deal with attorney Herb Spivak for legal representation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Good Touch, Bad Touch</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/good-touch-bad-touch/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 1997 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/good-touch-bad-touch/</guid>
      <description>Summary Mark undergoes deposition with the Law family for their lawsuit. Jeanie and Al are involved in a barroom brawl. Carol mulls the idea of opening a free health care clinic. Carter successfully diagnoses a serious injury, only to have Edson steal the credit. Benton&amp;rsquo;s familial duties earn him a waist-high stack of back paperwork. Dr. Romano returns from a European sabbatical, pioneering the latest in robotics technology. Anna treats a young man with testicular cancer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Friendly Fire</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/friendly-fire/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 1997 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/friendly-fire/</guid>
      <description>Summary Carol&amp;rsquo;s trust in Doug is strained when she overhears an errant comment. Weaver puts her newfound power to use immediately. Jerry commits a large-scale blunder with a patient&amp;rsquo;s rocket launcher; Weaver advises him to take some vacation time. Carter suspects Doyle of giving Anna preferential treatment. Cynthia Hooper works her first day as a desk clerk. Benton and Carla argue over circumcision. Mark can&amp;rsquo;t get it up with Heather Morgan.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Something New</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/something-new/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 1997 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/something-new/</guid>
      <description>Summary Greene hires a new desk clerk. High on morphine, Dr. Morganstern gives Weaver increased authority while he recuperates from his heart attack. Doug asks Carol for a drawer at her place. Dr. Corday adjusts to the differences between British and U.S. ERs. Dr. Greene is served with a wrongful death suit from the Law family. Carter trains a med student who is better at research than treating patients. Mark and Carol interview applicants for a vacant desk clerk position.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>One More For The Road</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/one-more-for-the-road/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 1997 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/one-more-for-the-road/</guid>
      <description>Summary Mark, still recovering from the attack, vents his emotions in a violent fit in the break room and buys a gun for protection. Carter decides his future lies in emergency medicine, not surgery, and tries to convince an irate Anspaugh likewise. Drs. Ross and Del Amico work together when Charlie is brought back into the ER. Peter&amp;rsquo;s child strengthens. Doug and Carol share a kiss. Jeanie and Al are back together.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Make A Wish</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/make-a-wish/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 1997 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/make-a-wish/</guid>
      <description>Summary Mark returns to work, scarred both physically and emotionally. Carla goes in labor again, four weeks prematurely, and delivers a baby boy. Doug thwarts Carol&amp;rsquo;s efforts to quietly celebrate her birthday. Carter begins to doubt that his future lies in surgery.
Character Review Doyle tries to help Mark feel better by bringing him a small arsenal of weapons from her family stash, including handguns, tasers and pepper spray. Carter sprays his own face with the spray.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Random Acts</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/random-acts/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 1997 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/random-acts/</guid>
      <description>Summary The staff springs into action when Dr. Greene is violently beaten by an unknown assailant. Dr. Ross treats the son of a wealthy man, leading Carol to suspect Doug of giving the child special treatment. Greg demands that Jeanie choose between him and Al. Speculation runs rampant when a torrid novella, author unknown, is found at the admit desk. A new pediatrician arrives from Philadelphia. Olbes shows up out of uniform for a change, bringing in her grandfather, who has suffered a stroke.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Calling Dr. Hathaway</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/calling-dr-hathaway/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 1997 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/calling-dr-hathaway/</guid>
      <description>Summary Carol finds herself at a career crossroads when her MCAT results come back. She&amp;rsquo;s torn between nursing and becoming a doctor, with Kerry grooming her for medicine, while Carol tries to care for a mother with a dying child. Carter debates whether to report Edson for falsifying a patient&amp;rsquo;s chart. Benton takes a personal day to care for Carla. Dr. Greene treats a couple concocting odd situations to see how quickly the staff finds a solution.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Bet Your Life</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/you-bet-your-life/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 1997 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/you-bet-your-life/</guid>
      <description>Summary Carter goes behind Anspaugh&amp;rsquo;s back to get a gambler admitted for surgery, earning Anspaugh and Hicks&amp;rsquo; wrath and jeopardizing his residency. Carol clashes with Doyle, angered that a 25-year-old intern is able to order her around. Peter illegally obtains Carla&amp;rsquo;s ultrasound to look for abnormalities. Doug treats an ill teenager who doesn&amp;rsquo;t want to miss her prom. Greene deals with a patient who feigns symptoms because she likes having surgeries.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tribes</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/tribes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 1997 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/tribes/</guid>
      <description>Summary Mark examines his prejudices when he&amp;rsquo;s accused of neglecting a black gunshot victim, Kenny Law, in favor of a white victim. Jeanie discovers Peter&amp;rsquo;s impending parenthood when Carla comes into the ER. Carter spends the entire day treating a hopeless case. Kerry tries to persuade a disabled junkie to enter a rehab program. Carol treats a college student who was drugged with roofies. After Jenn&amp;rsquo;s mother has a stroke, Rachel comes to stay with Mark for a while.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Faith</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/faith/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 1997 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/faith/</guid>
      <description>Summary Mark examines his prejudices when he&amp;rsquo;s accused of neglecting a black gunshot victim, Kenny Law, in favor of a white victim. Jeanie discovers Peter&amp;rsquo;s impending parenthood when Carla comes into the ER. Carter spends the entire day treating a hopeless case. Kerry tries to persuade a disabled junkie to enter a rehab program. Carol treats a college student who was drugged with roofies. After Jenn&amp;rsquo;s mother has a stroke, Rachel comes to stay with Mark for a while.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Whose Appy Now?</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/whose-appy-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 1997 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/whose-appy-now/</guid>
      <description>Summary A gleeful Carter removes Benton&amp;rsquo;s appendix. Dr. Ross treats a 17-year-old cystic fibrosis patient who wants to die, but isn&amp;rsquo;t old enough to sign a DNR. Mark juggles dates with three women, including psychiatrist Nina Pomerantz. Jeanie and Greg team up to find the culprit behind a rash of staph infections. Haleh has a tough time filling Carol&amp;rsquo;s shoes.
Character Review Yet again, Carter and Doyle&amp;rsquo;s friendly rivalry rears its head, as the two clash over some early cases.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fortune&#39;s Fools</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/fortunes-fools/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 1997 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/fortunes-fools/</guid>
      <description>Summary Carol takes an interest in an ailing police sergeant who&amp;rsquo;s hiding a degenerative ailment. She also meets with a newspaper reporter to air the complete story on her fatal mistake and is subsequently suspended. Peter runs into a pregnant Carla, upsetting the rest of his day. Carter, already fed up with Benton&amp;rsquo;s lackluster attitude, accepts a transfer to Hicks&amp;rsquo; team after Peter fails to show up at a lecture the two were to give.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Night Shift</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/night-shift/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 1997 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/night-shift/</guid>
      <description>Summary A long, cold night finds ER staffers with hours of time to kill. Kerry recruits staffers to participate in a study on sleep deprivation combined with physical activity. Gant appeals to Anspaugh after a public scolding from Benton. Carter ditches Dennis again to escape his whining, only to discover deadly results. Peter is denied a recommendation from Keaton one last time before she leaves for Pakistan. Mark and Chuny discover that they have a lot in common.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Homeless For The Holidays</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/homeless-for-the-holidays/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 1996 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/homeless-for-the-holidays/</guid>
      <description>Summary Rumors sweep the ER when Kerry and Mark cloister themselves to discuss policy regarding HIV-positive employees, prompting Jeanie to publicize her illness. Charlie brings the child she has been caring for into the ER. Doug treats the child and feels obligated to report the child&amp;rsquo;s mother for neglect. Doyle treats an abused woman, and conspires to help her escape her husband. Carter blows off an evening with Gant to spend the night with Keaton.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Union Station</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/union-station/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 1996 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/union-station/</guid>
      <description>Note: Jorja Fox credited as Jorjan Fox
Summary Susan&amp;rsquo;s last day in the ER finds Mark unsure of himself. Despite Doug&amp;rsquo;s urgings, Mark still finds himself afraid to admit his feelings for her. He chases her all over the city until he finds her at the train station. He declares his love for her, but she decides to leave for Phoenix anyway. Grabarsky and Lydia finally get married. Carol agrees to become &amp;lsquo;management&amp;rsquo; in exchange for an end to the policy of floating ER nurses elsewhere.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>No Brain, No Gain</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/no-brain-no-gain/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 1996 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/no-brain-no-gain/</guid>
      <description>Note: Jorja Fox credited as Jorjan Fox
Summary Benton fights to save the life of a gangbanger already declared dead by Doug. Nurse Rhonda Sterling floats down to the ER again and makes another critical mistake. Carter fights Edson for the rights of an incompetent patient and bonds with Anspaugh in the meantime. E. Ray worries that an MRI test gave him negative karma. Carter and Keaton get closer. Mark fears Susan is dating Morganstern; she tells him that she&amp;rsquo;s moving to Phoenix.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fear of Flying</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/fear-of-flying/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Nov 1996 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/fear-of-flying/</guid>
      <description>Note: Jorja Fox credited as Jorjan Fox
Summary Mark and Susan take to the air for helicopter flight rotation, which brings to the ER an entire family injured in an accident. Benton&amp;rsquo;s overconfidence during Keaton&amp;rsquo;s absence results in a dire mistake. Carol deals with a &amp;lsquo;floater&amp;rsquo; nurse who can&amp;rsquo;t cope with the speed of the ER. Jeanie and Maggie are given the task of keeping a dead man on ice in anticipation of cryogenic storage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ghosts</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/ghosts/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 1996 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/ghosts/</guid>
      <description>Note: Jorja Fox credited as Jorjan Fox
Summary Doug and Carol man the Healthmobile, a roving medical van that caters to the homeless. Benton tries to be more warm and friendly towards children, even taking a group of hospitalized youngsters trick-or-treating. Gant demands more respect from Benton. Mark anxiously waits for Susan to return from vacation.
Character Review Doyle and Jeanie treat Sophie Jennings, an elderly woman, suffering from end stage Lou Gehrig&amp;rsquo;s disease.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Last Call</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/last-call/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 1996 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/last-call/</guid>
      <description>Note: Jorja Fox credited as Jorjan Fox
Summary Dr. Ross brings a one-night-stand into the hospital when she has an epileptic seizure, earning him the stares of his colleagues when he can&amp;rsquo;t remember her name. Carter screws up Benton&amp;rsquo;s lecture when he realizes his presentation materials were in his apartment fire. Keaton takes a shine to Carter, meanwhile, when he persuades a teenage girl to undergo surgery. Carter also finds a place to live, with Dennis Gant.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Don&#39;t Ask, Don&#39;t Tell</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/dont-ask-dont-tell/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 1996 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/er/dont-ask-dont-tell/</guid>
      <description>Note: Jorja Fox credited as Jorjan Fox
Summary Mark is befuddled by an invitation from Susan to go on a joint vacation to Hawaii. The ER is filled with more refugees from South Side, Drs. Maggie Doyle and Abby Keaton among them. Peter decides to join Keaton&amp;rsquo;s pediatric surgery team. Carter gets on Anspaugh&amp;rsquo;s bad side when he exaggerates a patient&amp;rsquo;s condition to book an operating room. Jeanie tries to keep her HIV status a secret in the face of Weaver&amp;rsquo;s queries.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Do You Want, a Signed Confession ... ?</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/mp/what-do-you-want-a-signed-confession/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 1994 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/mp/what-do-you-want-a-signed-confession/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Bobby is still under investigation for a suspected bribe and perverting the course of justice. Also a little girl, Molly Jewett, is snatched in a department store.
Connie Karadzic Review Connie works with Carlos and Johnny to find the missing girl. Connie interviews the mother, keeping her company while Carlos and Johnny search the building. They find Molly&amp;rsquo;s jacket, and evidence she hasn&amp;rsquo;t been taken from the store.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tell Me You Didn&#39;t Do It ... I&#39;ll Go to the Wall for You</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/mp/tell-me-you-didnt-do-it-ill-go-to-the-wall-for-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 1994 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/mp/tell-me-you-didnt-do-it-ill-go-to-the-wall-for-you/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Ellen is making her mark on the department, buying doughnuts, making coffee, and being paired with Bobby on a seemingly straightforward parolee disappearance. Until Bobby is framed.
Connie Karadzic Review Connie looks into the case of David Roberts, 21-year old who is missing ten days from an upper Lakeview apartment. Mrs. Roberts explains that she and her son hadn&amp;rsquo;t talked in 3 years after his father threw him out for being gay.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>All They Had to Do Was Ask...</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/mp/all-they-had-to-do-was-ask/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Feb 1994 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/mp/all-they-had-to-do-was-ask/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Ray is shocked when he is told his ex-partner is being transferred into his department. Problem is she is female and rumours were rife that they were having an affair. Meanwhile a boy goes missing from party of schoolchildren on a museum tour.
Connie Karadzic Review Connie works the case of a disoriented woman brought in by a cabbie with no wallet, purse or ID, claiming her name is Minerva Fitzhugh.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Beautiful Son is Okay</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/mp/my-beautiful-son-is-okay/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 1994 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/mp/my-beautiful-son-is-okay/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Johnny and Connie look for two little boys who went missing on their way home from school, while Bobby has the mysterious disappearance of a woman he met on a recent case on his hands. Carlos, Anita, Ray and Barbara spend the whole episode worrying about baby Carlito Ray who is sick.
Connie Karadzic Review Two boys, Joel and Ronnie, were playing along the railroad tracks, accidentally end up stuck in a grain car when the train pulls out of the depot.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I&#39;ve Got a Siren</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/mp/ive-got-a-siren/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 1994 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/mp/ive-got-a-siren/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Connie helps a girl who is having a baby and is missing her boyfriend Jake, while Bobby meets an actress who models herself on Lauren Bacall and has driven her husband away with her constant role-playing games. Johnny is assigned desk duty after his father is investigated by internal affairs.
Connie Karadzic Review While interviewing Tamara Thorpe, the pregnant woman goes into labor and Connie rushes her to the hospital but it&amp;rsquo;s a false alarm.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>If You Could Pick Your Own Parents</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/mp/if-you-could-pick-your-own-parents/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 1994 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/mp/if-you-could-pick-your-own-parents/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Marsha and Phil Koppelman live upstairs from an older couple who don&amp;rsquo;t show up for a planned dinner. When Phil goes to check on them, he finds Bernice collapsed and Myron missing. Carlos goes looking for Myron, while Johnny looks for the full identity of a man named Dave, last seen leaping off a bridge. Connie has to sort through a high number of missing reports, most of them probably caused by a massive accident on the subway that has tied up trains for hours.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Hard Is It Just to Get Off at the Next Exit?</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/mp/how-hard-is-it-just-to-get-off-at-the-next-exit/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 1993 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/mp/how-hard-is-it-just-to-get-off-at-the-next-exit/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis A woman sees her missing son as she rides the bus, but by the time she gets off, he&amp;rsquo;s gone. Carlos goes to help the woman. Bobby looks for a missing express delivery man, while a councilman leans on Ray for a favor when his best-friend&amp;rsquo;s daughter goes missing right before her wedding. Johnny helps his family when his father, also a police officer, is shot.
Connie Karadzic Review Connie helps Ray on his case, interviewing Cilla&amp;rsquo;s fiancee while Ray talks with the parents.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Right Neighborhood ... Wrong Door</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/mp/right-neighborhood-wrong-door/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Dec 1993 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/mp/right-neighborhood-wrong-door/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Bobby helps his mother with a private matter when a member of her church goes missing. Connie looks into habitual runaway and train hopper, Joey Pender (age 8). Johnny looks into a missing rich Lake Shore Drive accountant.
Connie Karadzic Review While Joey has hopped on busses and trains before, he always turns himself in at the Kedzie station. His father is a long-distance truck driver, and since his mother makes a big deal about when his father comes home, Joey decided the best way to get attention was to go away.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sometimes You Can&#39;t Help Getting Involved</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/mp/sometimes-you-cant-help-getting-involved/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Nov 1993 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/mp/sometimes-you-cant-help-getting-involved/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Connie and Carlos both have to find missing children. Connie&amp;rsquo;s case is a 4-year old who disappeared at nursery school, and Carlos&amp;rsquo;s is an 8-year old, who is later found badly beaten. When an ex-school friend of Ray&amp;rsquo;s, who had been injured in an accident many years ago resulting in him have the mental age of a 6-year old, is accused of the beating, Ray breaks his own number 1 rule and becomes personally involved trying to clear him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I&#39;m Gonna Miss Him Too</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/mp/im-gonna-miss-him-too/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Nov 1993 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/mp/im-gonna-miss-him-too/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis A young boy runs away from home, returning to take his little brother with him, after his potential stepfather steals from their home and blames it on him, and then threatens his life. Connie has to trace the family of an heroic John Doe who saved a little girl&amp;rsquo;s life, in order to find out what his medical problems are, and along the way feels some chemistry with the surgeon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Some People&#39;s Priorities ...</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/mp/some-peoples-priorities/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Nov 1993 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/mp/some-peoples-priorities/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Bobby&amp;rsquo;s case of a missing dental student who apparently fell into voodoo returns when the parents decide they do want to find their wayward daughter, but she may be a victim of a serial killer. Connie looks into the case of a missing Indian woman who has been missing nine days. Johnny has a Tender Age case of an eleven year-old who went missing from a double-parked car in Lincoln Park.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Man&#39;s an Emotional Termite</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/mp/the-mans-an-emotional-termite/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 1993 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/mp/the-mans-an-emotional-termite/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis A girl living with her grandmother in Cabrini Green and goes missing, while an older man loses his family following a vacation, and another young girl into voodoo goes missing.
Connie Karadzic Review Connie works the case of a forgetful man who has lost his family following a month vacation. Victor Deely&amp;rsquo;s son Karl had gone to Florida but never returned. Victor presses Connie to learn about her personal life, and gets cagey when she says they&amp;rsquo;ll have to search his house.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>That&#39;s My Sister, Pal</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/mp/thats-my-sister-pal/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 1993 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/mp/thats-my-sister-pal/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis While Connie and Carlos investigate the disappearance of a young Latino newly arrived from Mexico, Johnny has assigned himself an &amp;#8220;unofficial&amp;#8221; case. He thinks Connie&amp;rsquo;s husband is cheating on her and decides to find out for sure. Enlisting an unwilling Bobby, who is working a case involving the disappearance of a middle-aged widower, they find out more than they want to know. Ray, contacted by the wife of a missing old colleague of his, has to find the man.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Can&#39;t Even Imagine</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/mp/i-cant-even-imagine/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 1993 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/mp/i-cant-even-imagine/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Connie works the case of Anne Conlin, whose parents find her apartment stripped clean, and Anne never got off the plane after a three month trip to Europe. Johnny works a case of kids who goe missing after a party on the South Side. Carlos hunts down Jerome Vincent, whose car is found abandoned in a parking lot with a suicide note, but no body. Meanwhile Bobby tries to find his mother the perfect birthday present.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>People Don&#39;t Talk to Cops, People Lie to Cops</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/mp/people-dont-talk-to-cops-people-lie-to-cops/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 1993 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/mp/people-dont-talk-to-cops-people-lie-to-cops/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis A young boy goes missing from his backyard, which Bobby works on. Johnny looks into a husband gone missing, and Connie works on a wife who vanished after shopping. In all three cases, the families declare that there&amp;rsquo;s nothing unsavory about their missing loved ones or themselves.
Connie Karadzic Review Connie brings in bagels instead of donuts, causing complaints from some of the other cops who aren&amp;rsquo;t as pleased about the health kick.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cabe?... What kind of name is that?</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/mp/cabe-what-kind-of-name-is-that/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 1993 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/mp/cabe-what-kind-of-name-is-that/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis A two year-old named Caleb (which Ray mishears as &amp;lsquo;Cabe&amp;rsquo;) is found wandering alone in a forest preserve. Ray and Barbara take him home until Carlos can find the parents. Bobby is assigned a missing 19 year old Phillipino who is embroiled in gang-related narcotics trafficking. Connie looks for a mysterious philanthropist, Mr. Hodgekiss. who suddenly disappeared while out for his nightly constitutional. Johnny gets dead body detail. He has to identify a homeless person found face down in an alley.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pilot (Missing Persons)</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/mp/pilot/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Aug 1993 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/mp/pilot/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis In the two hour premiere of Missing Persons, we meet the detectives of Chicago&amp;rsquo;s Missing Persons Bureau.
Det. Johnny Sandowski searches for a four year-old Polish girl who vanished after being separated from her mother on an &amp;#8220;El&amp;#8221; train. Det. Bobby Davison is assigned a missing University of Chicago co-ed. Det. Sgt. Carlos Marrone tracks a patient who has possibly wandered off from the convalescence home where she lived.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recaps</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/recaps/</guid>
      <description>Television show recaps have been made available after hours and years of watching.
The follow shows are currently recapped here:
 Missing Persons ER The West Wing CSI: Crime Scene Investigation  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>