<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>2001 on Jorja Fox Library</title>
    <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/tags/2001/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 2001 on Jorja Fox Library</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2001 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://jorjafox.net/library/tags/2001/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Channels</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2001/channels/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2001/channels/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Fox heads the network war and forces CBS ratings to exploit all grounds. No stranger to television &amp;#8212; this brunette meets more than just the average eye.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thursday TV is the talk of two networks: one that hopes it&amp;rsquo;s still on the way up, and one that&amp;rsquo;s trying to halt its slide down. For nearly two decades, NBC dominated Thursday nights with its &amp;ldquo;Must See TV&amp;rdquo; lineup &amp;#8212; until last year, when CBS&amp;rsquo; combination of &lt;em&gt;&amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo;&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;&amp;ldquo;Survivor&amp;rdquo;&lt;/em&gt; put the night in play. With both brains and beauty, Fox manages to convey sexiness and sweetness; validating her acting talent she has co-founded Honeypot Productions. Speaking to Jorja Fox, television&amp;rsquo;s most valuable acress since Angie Dickinson, I realized how she has come to symbolize that tough-but-sweet independent woman with her roles. Fox plays &lt;em&gt;&amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rsquo;s&amp;rdquo;&lt;/em&gt; Sara Sidle, who hails from San Francisco and was brought in by Gil Grissom to investigate the shooting and subsequent death of Holly Gribbs. Since then, Sidle has remained on the team as the new kid on the block, and quickly established a strong reputation for the series.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fox admits she has been lucky to be casted in award winning series, such as &lt;em&gt;&amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo;&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;&amp;ldquo;ER.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/em&gt; &amp;ldquo;It&amp;rsquo;s very hard to digest the stardom I have recieved &amp;#8212; it still hasn&amp;rsquo;t sunk in,&amp;rdquo; she says. &amp;ldquo;It&amp;rsquo;s a miracle I get paid to do what I love most.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ever since she was five years old, she wanted to be an actress of a rockstar. &amp;ldquo;Even though I knew how to play the guitar, as a child I couldn&amp;rsquo;t get myself on talent shows &amp;#8212; when I got into New Your city I kept getting offers to act for money and I never did becuase of my music,&amp;rdquo; Fox says.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Growing up in Florida&amp;rsquo;s small town, Melbourne, Fox moved to her birth town of NYC upon completion of high school. &amp;ldquo;Sometimes your dream is in you and you could manifest your dream without having to leave home, but there are a couple things, such as acting that ultimately find yourself leaving home.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Nothing really scared me when I would think of the big city. Also, I was lucky enough to know how to stay safe. Those two things kept me together, and moving to New York was probably the best thing I ever did,&amp;rdquo; adds Fox.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She makes no secret of her chubby-childhood years. Her French-Canadian mother, who grew up around the Great Depression, taught her and her brother the importance of food and the terror of being without it. &amp;ldquo;The best possible thing my Mom could say was that her kids had meat on them,&amp;rdquo; Fox says, laughing. &amp;ldquo;I was a heavy kid, probably from eight to about 16 and it definitely taight me how to be humble.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;I was lucky because I sprouted. Where I grew up, everyone was lean and blonde. Right around 15, I made a conscience decisions. I wanted to be that lean-fighting-machine.&amp;rdquo; A youthful innocent crush led her to take the weight off in pursuit of the class heartthrob&amp;rsquo;s attention. Despite her white-Irish skin, she tried to tan, lost some weight, picked up the guitar for the first time and after the school break she was asked out on a date. &amp;ldquo;Immediately I knew he was so far ahead of me &amp;#8212; I was 15 in my brain and he was 23. The guy whom I was head over heels for asked me out a couple of times, and after that we became very good friends.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;I love bodies &amp;#8212; of all shapes, sizes and ages. It might be hokey, but it&amp;rsquo;s like a fingerprint &amp;#8212; no two bodies are the same. Occasionaly in LA, much more so than NY &amp;#8212; that might be making a sterotype, but &amp;#8212; people can get trapped or petty in what they perceive as perfect in the way they have to look,&amp;rdquo; Fox says. nothing is more interesting or sexy to her than all the different ways human beings can impress. When this fair-skinned-chubby schoolgirl left Melbourne, New York immediately accepted her pale skin and dark hair &amp;#8212; instead, she quickly fit in.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Consider continuity: Fox stays true to her career by giving her roles her soul. From a very young age her grandmother told her stories, and Fox&amp;rsquo;s continual interest in storytelling has ranked her a potent actress, although she believes otherwise. &amp;ldquo;I am really kind of simple, but this moment, being four months into the taping of the second season, I am more this Sara person than I am myself. She&amp;rsquo;s a lot smarter than I am, much cooler, more adventurous &amp;#8212; obviously I am not. I kind of make believe I am commendable. One thing&amp;rsquo;s for sure &amp;#8212; we both put our feet in our mouths a lot, we both have a lot of heart and we both want to do the right thing by getting to the bottom of the truth,&amp;rdquo; Fox says.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But when Fox is asked about the countless episodes she had with George Clooney on &lt;em&gt;&amp;ldquo;ER,&amp;rdquo;&lt;/em&gt; she begins to laugh and I feel her cheeks blush. &amp;ldquo;It was really hard to concentrate,&amp;rdquo; she says with a big sigh. &amp;ldquo;And, on top of that &amp;#8212; besides him being in the room &amp;#8212; he is always playing practical jokes on people. You are never completely sure what he&amp;rsquo;s going to do. He really is the guy that people describe him as: fun, energetic and down-to-earth. A lot of the practical jokes he would pull on me involed lubricants and plastic gloves.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fox has also managed to carve out some impressive film credits including this year&amp;rsquo;s Sundance Film Festival where she portrays the wife of lead Guy Pearce. Directed by Christopher Nolan, &lt;em&gt;&amp;ldquo;Memento&amp;rdquo;&lt;/em&gt; unfolds its story in reverse order. &amp;ldquo;This was the most complicated and crazy movie I had ever been asked to perform in. And if I were to be sterotyped &amp;#8212; which I would be grateful if that would happen &amp;#8212; I would like to be know as the gun-totting, intense one,&amp;rdquo; she says.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With &lt;em&gt;&amp;ldquo;Memento&amp;rdquo;&lt;/em&gt; being her third foray into Sundance, her role in the offbeat comedy &lt;em&gt;&amp;ldquo;How to Make he Cruelest Month,&amp;rdquo;&lt;/em&gt; and town gossip queen in &lt;em&gt;&amp;ldquo;The Kill-Off&amp;rdquo;&lt;/em&gt; cannot be forgotten. Although it&amp;rsquo;s a tough question for Fox to answer, she ranks &lt;em&gt;&amp;ldquo;How to Make he Cruelest Month&amp;rdquo;&lt;/em&gt; as her personal favorite &amp;#8212; only because she is very good friends with Clea Duvall, who played her sister. In the latter, she remembers that was the first movie she ever did utside New York.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But Fox&amp;rsquo;s light doesn&amp;rsquo;t fade with acting or with her &amp;#8216;famous guitar&amp;rsquo; &amp;#8212; instead, she has expanded by co-founding a production house. With a pleasantly puzzling name such as Honeypot Productions, Fox is interrogated many times for the true meaning behind the name. &amp;ldquo;I go way back with the reast of my team &amp;#8212; there are six of us in total and we all live in LA. One day we sat down [and] threw out a couple of names for the company &amp;#8212; we pretty much stayed with [fellow founder] Suzanne [Mara&amp;rsquo;s] idea. It was so sweet &amp;#8212; for us, it was like sugar working together,&amp;rdquo; says Fox. Keeping their spirits high, these workaholics work for themselves in this theater venture. Honeypot put up three plays to date, two of which have been scribed by Fox. The fourth play, &lt;em&gt;&amp;ldquo;Loving Stanley,&amp;rdquo;&lt;/em&gt; which she also penned, offers a comedic romp about the women&amp;rsquo;s bowling circut and will soon be released.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fox bemoans pomposity of any sort. As versatile as she is, come this new year, Fox believes she should worry less and chant for world peace.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FW</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2001/fw/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2001/fw/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Fresh for the fall and taking over living rooms across North America, FW brings you the rising stars from the hottest TV shows this season. Opinionated, multi-talented, stylish, indipendent and really easy on the eyes, these young stars show us what hitting the big time is all about.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Personally I would define success as the amount of joy or passion you have for what you are doing. If people are doing what they love or if it means a lot to them, then that really is successful and really blessed and lucky.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;B&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/B&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;BR /&gt;She has starred in three acclaimed TV series: &lt;U&gt;ER&lt;/U&gt;, &lt;U&gt;The West Wing&lt;/U&gt; and currently &lt;U&gt;CSI: Crime Scene Investigation&lt;/U&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;11 movies, including last year&amp;rsquo;s thriller, &lt;U&gt;Memento&lt;/U&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Composed song &amp;lsquo;Lullaby&amp;rsquo; for the 1998 movie &lt;U&gt;Traveling Companion&lt;/U&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Strong Magazine</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2001/strong-magazine/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2001/strong-magazine/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Actress Jorja Fox, star of CBS&amp;rsquo;s hit drama &lt;em&gt;CSI&lt;/em&gt;, spends a lot of time in bed - but not necessarily for the reason you&amp;rsquo;re thinking. &amp;ldquo;Sleep is key,&amp;rdquo; she says. &amp;ldquo;I try to get a full eight hours a night. On the weekends, it might even be 10 or 11 hours.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Us Weekly</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2001/us-weekly/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2001/us-weekly/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If [William] Petersen (who is divorced and not dating anyone seriously) is &amp;ldquo;the dad&amp;rdquo; of the cast, according to [Marg] Helgenberger, then the rest of the family hierarchy is as follows: &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m the mom,&amp;rdquo; she says, &amp;ldquo;Jorja [Fox, who playes Grissom prot&amp;eacute;g&amp;eacute;e Sara Sidle] and George [Eads] are the little sister and brother.&amp;rdquo; And [Gary] Dourdan? &amp;ldquo;Gary is the really hot guy that makes our flesh tingle when he walks by,&amp;rdquo; she says, laughing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even thought the cast members spend up to 50 hours working togeather during the week, they often hand out with one another during off hours &amp;#8212; barbecuing at Petersen&amp;rsquo;s Los Angeles house, going out to dinner or catching a movie.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;I know it sounds funny, but sometimes at the end of the week, when i go home, I think about these guys &amp;#8212; I miss them,&amp;rdquo; says Fox, 33, who moved to Los Angeles from New York in 1996 after being cast on &lt;em&gt;ER&lt;/em&gt;. In 1999, she left that show for a recurring role on &lt;em&gt;The West Wing&lt;/em&gt;, which she gave up when she landed her part on &lt;em&gt;CSI&lt;/em&gt;. When Fox, who is single and writes folks music in her spare time, joined &lt;em&gt;CSI&lt;/em&gt; for last season&amp;rsquo;s third episode, Petersen felt it was a good omen. &amp;ldquo;She&amp;rsquo;s the talisman of [hit] shows,&amp;rdquo; he says.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a tribute to the fictional crime victims, the cast came up with a rating system [&amp;hellip;] The all time winner [&amp;hellip;] was Jody Lynn Wilson, a stunt actor from last season who was covered with live bugs and didn&amp;rsquo;t move for at least two hours. It&amp;rsquo;s a notion that still makes Fox a little squeamish. &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m the wimp of the cast,&amp;rdquo; she admits. &amp;ldquo;But I&amp;rsquo;m getting getter. Last year, I couldn&amp;rsquo;t red the scripts before I went to bed. I couldn&amp;rsquo;t eat anything and watch the show at the same time. Now when I see something [gross] is coming up, I&amp;rsquo;m like, &amp;#8216;Yeah, cool.&amp;lsquo;&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s now late afternoon. Outside the soundstage, Eads, Petersen and Dourdan assemble under golf umbrellas for a brief cigarette break. Fox, who might normally join the guys, stays inside becuase &amp;ldquo;my hair will frizz out in this weather.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shape Magazine</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2001/shape-magazine/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2001/shape-magazine/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Jorja Fox admits she has trouble seeing herself as the beautiful woman she is today. &amp;ldquo;Up until the age of 17, I was an overweight kid,&amp;rdquo; she says. &amp;ldquo;So I still see my body that way sometimes. It stays with you.&amp;rdquo; Lately though, Fox has been feeling more comfortable in her own skin, having landed a coveted role as crime scene investigator Sara Sidle on last season&amp;rsquo;s top-rated freshman drama, &lt;em&gt;CSI&lt;/em&gt;. Fox, a self-admitted tomboy, says she prefers outdoor exercise to the confines of a gym. &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;ve never even had a membership!&amp;rdquo; - Alexis Iacone.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WORKOUT&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;ldquo;I try to work out every day. Of course, it ends up being like every other day. I do stuff outside. I grew up on the beach in Florida, and everything there involved some kind of outdoor activity: surfing or waterskiing or swimming or hiking. And in California, there&amp;rsquo;s always some kind of outdoor sport to do.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CARDIO&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;ldquo;Hiking, surfing and running. I also take my dog out for long walks, throw the ball with her for a while and then we run together.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;FUEL&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;ldquo;I really like to eat. Typically, I eat a lot early in the day, a big meal midday and a light meal at night. I&amp;rsquo;ve been a vegetarian for 12 years now, so I eat lots of soy products and fruits and vegetables. When I make bacon cheeseburgers, I&amp;rsquo;ll get all the ingredients from the health food store &amp;#8212; like soy cheese and fake bacon. Or I&amp;rsquo;ll barbecue ribs that aren&amp;rsquo;t really meat.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SLEEP&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;ldquo;Sleep is key. I try to get a full eight hours a night. On the weekends, it might even be 10 or 11 hours. I know they say it doesn&amp;rsquo;t work to play catch-up, but it feels better for me.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;INDULGENCE&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;ldquo;I love anything that&amp;rsquo;s home-baked.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PEAK MOMENT&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;ldquo;I just did a short film about dancers. There&amp;rsquo;s no nudity in it, but at one point, there were seven scantily clad women on the set doing a striptease. I had never done it before, so it felt really sexy and scandalous. I was free and vulnerable at the same time.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;IDOL&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;ldquo;I saw Benicio Del Toro at the Golden Globe Awards. Even from far away, he was still this gorgeous person. There&amp;rsquo;s a little extra charisma or energy going on with that guy.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;MIND/BODY/SPIRIT KEY&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;ldquo;I go to a spiritual center in Los Angeles. It&amp;rsquo;s not a particular religion; people of all religions are welcome. But I enjoy going someplace and experiencing other people. I find it balances my workout, which are more of a solo, almost meditative, time for myself.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SPIRITUAL RETREAT&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;ldquo;It&amp;rsquo;s all about being outdoors for me. Even when I was living in New York city, i would climb onto my rooftop to meditate.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Time Out New York</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2001/time-out-new-york/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2001/time-out-new-york/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CSI&amp;rsquo;s Jorja Fox is out for truth, justice and a steady job&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This week, Jorja Fox returns for a second season of the CBS drama CSI: Crime Scene Investigation as determined detective Sara Sidle. This is big news- her previous characters have had a habit of disappearing from top-rated shows.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Five years ago, on ER, Fox played Maggie Doyle, the lesbian pediatrician who pissed off nurses and colleagues, then wandered off the series when the writers couldn&amp;rsquo;t find anything more for her to do. &amp;ldquo;Maggie was like a ghost,&amp;rdquo; says Fox. &amp;ldquo;She just kind of poofed away.&amp;rdquo; Three years later, on The West Wing, Fox played Special Agent Gina Toscano, who survived an assassination attempt on the President (Martin Sheen) but might as well have taken the bullet herself. &amp;ldquo;I asked to leave,&amp;rdquo; says Fox. &amp;ldquo;I had [another possible show] I was excited about.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While that one never happened, Fox, 33, did find herself on CSI; last year, the freshman crime drama, which follows a group of crime scene detectives in Las Vegas, was second only to ER in the ratings. And Fox is staying put, even though she didn&amp;rsquo;t expect to be here at all. Asked if she thought the somewhat corny show would become a monster hit, she answers: &amp;ldquo;Um&amp;hellip; honestly?&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Born in New York City but raised in Melborne, Florida (her Canadian parents dreamed of living near the beach), Fox was discovered in a model search at age 16 at the local mall. Not conventionally beautiful?she was &amp;ldquo;a fat kid with new wave punk-rock hair&amp;rdquo;-she soon moved to New York and gravitated toward acting. After roles in straight-to-video movies and flops like The Jerky Boys, she scored an audition for ER. Since then, she&amp;rsquo;s played strong-willed characters who usually have attitude (although she did have a cameo in Memento as Guy Pierce&amp;rsquo;s loving wife). On CSI, her antisocial detective Sidle spends more time with dead bodies than real ones. &amp;ldquo;Friends and family always say, &amp;#8216;You never smile,&amp;rsquo; and I&amp;rsquo;m like, &amp;#8216;It&amp;rsquo;s really hard to smile. I&amp;rsquo;m standing over someone who&amp;rsquo;s met a horrific end!&amp;lsquo;&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To lighten up her life, last year, Fox founded Honeypot Productions, an acting troupe that puts on the comedic plays she writes. She says she finds the CSI scripts a little goofy in comparison (in one episode, a man is killed by his frat buddy because the latter&amp;rsquo;s girlfriend autographed the former&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;johnson&amp;rdquo;). &amp;ldquo;There&amp;rsquo;s always something funny and macabre, but we&amp;rsquo;re also dealing with this highly sensitive, dark material. So to meld that together is a great challenge.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She thinks this season&amp;rsquo;s scripts will continue to walk that line and prays last season&amp;rsquo;s success wasn&amp;rsquo;t a fluke. &amp;ldquo;We&amp;rsquo;re hoping people don&amp;rsquo;t get bored with it,&amp;rdquo; says Fox. &amp;ldquo;Every week, somebody&amp;rsquo;s dead and we try to figure out what happened to them. So you have to wonder if it will get stale.&amp;rdquo; Don&amp;rsquo;t expect her to stick around if it does.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The second season of CSI: Crime Scene Investigation begins September 27 at 9pm on CBS.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Houston Chronicle</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2001/houston-chronicle/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Sep 2001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2001/houston-chronicle/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Jorja Fox speaks for many of us trying to work while also worrying about current events.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;I go from moments where you don&amp;rsquo;t want to come to work, to being very focused and concentrating, knowing there is something I&amp;rsquo;ve got to do, to other moments when I can&amp;rsquo;t seem to get it together,&amp;rdquo; said Fox, who plays Sara Sidle on CBS&amp;rsquo; hot sophomore drama &lt;em&gt;CSI: Crime Scene Investigation&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the wake of the Sept. 11 attacks, *CSI *went dark for a week, and producers pulled an upcoming episode that didn&amp;rsquo;t involve terrorism but showed a small plane crashing into a casino.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When shooting resumed, Fox found comfort in &amp;ldquo;having a place where I had to go and something I&amp;rsquo;m supposed to do.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Clearly, Fox was ready for &lt;em&gt;CSI&lt;/em&gt;. But what about the rest of America?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;High ratings indicate that Americans are craving entertainment, both drama and comedy. CBS&amp;rsquo; &lt;em&gt;Everybody Loves Raymond,&lt;/em&gt; NBC&amp;rsquo;s *Crossing Jordan, *ABC&amp;rsquo;s *Philly *and Fox&amp;rsquo;s &lt;em&gt;Undeclared&lt;/em&gt; all received strong samplings this week, ratings show.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But forensic science may not be what the public wants to see right now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;We&amp;rsquo;re obviously concerned whether people are going to want to turn to that for entertainment right now,&amp;rdquo; Fox said. &amp;ldquo;We don&amp;rsquo;t know what&amp;rsquo;s going to happen.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On tonight&amp;rsquo;s season premiere (8 p.m., Channel 11), the son of an entrepreneur who helped build Las Vegas is found in his home, dead of an apparent drug overdose. But as the CSI team studies the scene, murder comes to be suspected, and every member of the forensic team is assigned to the case.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The episode was not available for preview, but if the show continues to exhibit hallmarks from its freshman series, it should go gangbusters again. As viewers have discovered, *CSI *is a mix of provocative plot lines, compelling performances by an ensemble cast and an irresistible Las Vegas locale.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fox&amp;rsquo;s character, Sara, is as straightforward and complex as any on the show. Her compulsion for her work strongly suggests trauma in her past.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But like another strong drama series, NBC&amp;rsquo;s &lt;em&gt;Law &amp;amp; Order&lt;/em&gt;, *CSI *does not dwell on the lives of the principal characters. It focuses instead on the cases. So we don&amp;rsquo;t know exactly what drives Sara.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even Fox is not clear about Sara&amp;rsquo;s past.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;I may have alluded to the fact that there may be things in her personal life that definitely directed her to the profession that she&amp;rsquo;s in,&amp;rdquo; Fox said. &amp;ldquo;It&amp;rsquo;s not necessarily that she was the victim of something, but perhaps she was very close to someone, a family member (who was a victim).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;One thing about us, we were very plot-driven last year, and I think we&amp;rsquo;re going to stay plot-driven. Certainly the first six shows of the year are all about plot. There are tiny, tiny pieces of character in the shows. Our hope is that people always want to know more about the characters (than is revealed). It&amp;rsquo;s fun that way. You keep an air of mystery about yourself. It&amp;rsquo;s fun to play.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fox (her first name is pronounced &amp;ldquo;Georgia;&amp;rdquo; it&amp;rsquo;s a shorter version Jorja-Ann, the name given her by her French Canadian mom) is the person you want to stand next to during a lightning storm. Her credits include three seasons as Dr. Maggie Doyle on *ER, *a stint as a Secret Service agent on &lt;em&gt;The West Wing&lt;/em&gt; and now a role on CBS&amp;rsquo; top drama. She was the murder victim in the much-heralded movie &lt;em&gt;Memento&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;I think it&amp;rsquo;s just been a series of personal miracles,&amp;rdquo; Fox said. &amp;ldquo;I do feel so very lucky about that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;The only thing I know is that if I feel really nervous about a decision I&amp;rsquo;m about to make, it usually means I should pursue that decision. And all three of those (TV) shows, there was something about them that made me really nervous.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Guide Canada</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2001/tv-guide-canada/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Sep 2001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2001/tv-guide-canada/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;She&amp;rsquo;s been on three hit TV series in as many years - &lt;em&gt;ER&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;The West Wing&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;CSI&lt;/em&gt; - so you can&amp;rsquo;t say Jorja Fox doesn&amp;rsquo;t know how to pick choice roles. But while the natures of her shows have been diverse, the characters she&amp;rsquo;s played have all had at least one thing in common: they are strong, independent women. On &lt;em&gt;ER&lt;/em&gt;, Fox played cranky medical intern Maggie Doyle, on &lt;em&gt;The West Wing&lt;/em&gt; she played the recurring role of Secret Service agent Gina Toscano. Now, on &lt;em&gt;CSI: Crime Scene Investigation&lt;/em&gt;, Fox is the new kid on the block as Sara Sidle, a crime-scene analyst who seems about as unfazed as Agent Scully while picking through blood and guts. As gross as that sounds, we have to admit there&amp;rsquo;s something sexy about a woman who can stomach the tough stuff &amp;hellip; and knows how to back a winner.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Find Law</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2001/find-law/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Aug 2001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2001/find-law/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;HOLLYWOOD (Variety) - It was difficult to conduct interviews with director Allison Anders and stars Kim Dickens and Gabriel Mann Thursday during Showtime&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Things Behind the Sun&amp;rdquo; premiere after-party at the Paramount Theater.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tearful guests could not stop coming up to these three, professing love and gratitude; one fan literally bowed to kiss Dickens&amp;rsquo; foot.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is the intense reaction a film about a 12-year-old&amp;rsquo;s gang rape will provoke in people. That the story is based on Anders&amp;rsquo; own experience and was filmed in the house where her rape took place many years ago did not do much to lighten the mood.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;I think I am pretty much done with this,&amp;rdquo; Anders said of her rape. &amp;ldquo;When I walked into that house, it was over for me, and I was exhilarated.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dickens portrays the grown-up victim, a singer, trying to come to terms with her traumatic past. She credits her performance to Anders: &amp;ldquo;I had her as my guide, so I felt really safe,&amp;rdquo; Dickens said. &amp;ldquo;By the time we started filming, she was relieved, and it was a joyful process.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The low-key party featured music by Anders&amp;rsquo; daughter, Tiffany, who was also featured on the film&amp;rsquo;s soundtrack.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Guests included thesps Mario Van Peebles, Mike Farrell, Jorja Fox and Ellen DeGeneres.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hollywood.com 24</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2001/hollywood.com-24/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Aug 2001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2001/hollywood.com-24/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Actress Jorja Fox has been everywhere on the tube-from a three-season stint on &lt;em&gt;ER&lt;/em&gt; to a guest role on &lt;em&gt;The West Wing&lt;/em&gt;-but she&amp;rsquo;s found a home on CBS&amp;rsquo; critically acclaimed series &lt;em&gt;C.S.I.&lt;/em&gt;, playing forensics expert Sara Sidle.&lt;br /&gt;
Fox, 33, spoke with Hollywood.com over the phone from her L.A. home to discuss her role on &lt;em&gt;C.S.I.&lt;/em&gt;, the upcoming Emmys ceremony, the success of &lt;em&gt;ER&lt;/em&gt; and the joys of nudity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja, you&amp;rsquo;re a busy girl these days. Thanks for taking some time off from that grueling damn schedule of yours to talk with us.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Fox&lt;/strong&gt;: Hey, I love these phone interviews. They&amp;rsquo;re so much more stream-of-consciousness, ya know?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;And more laid back.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Fox&lt;/strong&gt;: Oh yeah. I could be half naked right now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Yeah, me too. Well, that aside, tell me how early production&amp;rsquo;s going on the show.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Fox&lt;/strong&gt;: Great! I&amp;rsquo;m really excited. It&amp;rsquo;s good to be back.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Does the show seem to be going in any different directions this season?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Fox&lt;/strong&gt;: They&amp;rsquo;ve only shown me one script, so I&amp;rsquo;m not sure yet. But the first episode is great. There&amp;rsquo;s a big plot twist in there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Last season, your character, Sara, played a fairly supporting role on the show. Is she going to break out a bit more this season as a major player?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Fox&lt;/strong&gt;: [Sighs] I don&amp;rsquo;t even know. I hope so. But everything&amp;rsquo;s a secret right now, so&amp;hellip;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Well, one main character, Marg [Helgenberger], certainly received some recognition this year, snagging an Emmy nomination for best lead actress. What do you think of her chances?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Fox&lt;/strong&gt;: Oh, we&amp;rsquo;re all pretty giddy, that&amp;rsquo;s for sure. She deserves it. The show got three nominations, I believe. I think one was a tech nomination.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Regardless of whether or not you guys win, it&amp;rsquo;s still a damn good reason to get dressed up and schmooze.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Fox&lt;/strong&gt;: Yeah, and it&amp;rsquo;s good that Marg got the nomination because she&amp;rsquo;s definitely the best dresser of anyone on the show. Me-I&amp;rsquo;m more of a jeans and T-shirt kind of girl, ya know? Both me and George] [Eads, who plays Nick Stokes on the show] are like that. Man, we tie for last place in the best-dressed department.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;One show you used to work on, &lt;em&gt;ER&lt;/em&gt;, got a handful of nominations as well. Do you think the show is better or worse since you left in &amp;lsquo;99?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Fox&lt;/strong&gt;: I disagree with people who put down the show today. I mean, it&amp;rsquo;s the number-one show on TV, ya know? It has been for years. That&amp;rsquo;s such a challenge to stay on top, and they&amp;rsquo;ve done it every time. It&amp;rsquo;s still a great show.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ever miss it?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Fox&lt;/strong&gt;: Sometimes. But on &lt;em&gt;C.S.I.&lt;/em&gt;, the atmosphere&amp;rsquo;s not so different, ya know what I mean? The sets still have that metallic look. The labs and everything.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Very true. It&amp;rsquo;s not such a departure after all. And &lt;em&gt;C.S.I.&lt;/em&gt;&amp;#8216;s amassing quite a fan base, I hear.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Fox&lt;/strong&gt;: Oh, god yes. These fans are amazing. The show&amp;rsquo;s really developed a following with students-you know, forensic students. They&amp;rsquo;ve really latched on.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;**I guess most people still recognize you for &lt;em&gt;ER&lt;/em&gt;, but you recently made an appearance in one of the year&amp;rsquo;s best films, &lt;em&gt;Memento&lt;/em&gt;. Any further big-screen plans? **&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Fox&lt;/strong&gt;: That was fun, definitely. I love movies. There may be a project coming up with Josh Leonard-you know, the guy from &lt;em&gt;The Blair Witch Project&lt;/em&gt;? A short film. But right now it&amp;rsquo;s &lt;em&gt;C.S.I.&lt;/em&gt; all the way.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jezebel Magazine</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2001/jezebel-magazine/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Aug 2001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2001/jezebel-magazine/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Note: Jorja Fox&amp;rsquo;s answers were hand written, and spelling errors were not corrected.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;With a name like Georgia Fox&amp;hellip;er&amp;hellip;Jorja Fox, have you ever visted Altanta. If so, what did you like most about our city?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have family in Atlanta and I&amp;rsquo;ve been there many times. I have fantasies of living there, having a big old covered porch, and a little theater. I &lt;U&gt;love&lt;/u&gt; the Reverand, Doctor King museum!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What do you think of Southern men?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I &lt;U&gt;adore&lt;/U&gt; Southern men, simply adore &amp;hellip;.. As long as they&amp;rsquo;re very liberal.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You&amp;rsquo;ve starred in &lt;em&gt;ER&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;West Wing&lt;/em&gt;, and currently &lt;em&gt;CSI: Crime Scene Investigation&lt;/em&gt;, what is your secret for landing &lt;em&gt;gigs&lt;/em&gt; in such incredible series?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I really wish I had one. I do know if I feel nervous about a professional oppertunity it&amp;rsquo;s usually a good thing and I should explore it. I was obviously a little nervous about all three shows.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Which show have you enjoyed starring in most?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It would have to be CSI. It&amp;rsquo;s a fundemental leap into the &amp;ldquo;great unknown.&amp;rdquo; And that&amp;rsquo;s created an amazing, strange, wild, 150 member family.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Is &lt;em&gt;CSI&lt;/em&gt; ever based on real occurrences? Real Crimes?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sometimes. We try very hard to tell those stories with integrity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Which actors/actresses have you enjoyed working with most?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;it would be easier to try and hone in on who I&amp;rsquo;ve not enjoyed working with. I&amp;rsquo;ve been very lucky. I have a cerebrial crush on William Peterson. And certainly Martin Sheen and Allison Janey, are personal heros.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What would be your ultimate role?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I really just love getting to tell stories. I&amp;rsquo;d love to do a period peice, I&amp;rsquo;d love to play a revoluntionary, I&amp;rsquo;d love to explore mental illness.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Please tell our &lt;em&gt;JEZEBEL&lt;/em&gt; readers about Honeypot Productions and some of its upcoming projects.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Honeypot is a zaney theater compant I&amp;rsquo;m in. We do stuff we&amp;rsquo;ve always just wanted to do, and things people might not pay us to do - theater under the stars, musicals, we did a dance piece - So far all our projects have been internally written. We have a new musical in the works.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What do you enjoy doing on your &amp;ldquo;off&amp;rdquo; days?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Right now I&amp;rsquo;m trying to surf - and learn how to play the drums. I have a car in L.A. (which I never had in New York) and I like to drive around - the west is &lt;U&gt;big&lt;/U&gt; and new to me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This would not be a &lt;em&gt;JEZEBEL&lt;/em&gt; interview without referencing fashion. Describe your current style? Favorite designer?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Urban decay - I&amp;rsquo;ve always been underdressed - I try and I try - but I&amp;rsquo;m intrinsicly messy. I love Richard Tyler and Earl Jones.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Which is your favorite section of &lt;em&gt;JEZEBEL&lt;/em&gt; Magazine?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I love to imagine what my nephews might be up to, so I love your hot shots section.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Animal Planet Radio</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2001/animal-planet-radio/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jul 2001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2001/animal-planet-radio/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;introduction:056bed86c85c27270cb0cb969b710445&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;] TV star Jorja Fox of &amp;ldquo;Crime Scene Investigation: CSI&amp;rdquo; talked about how she plays with her pooch while she has time between scenes. She also talked about her roles on &amp;ldquo;The West Wing&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;E/R.&amp;rdquo; Jorja says her dream job would be appearing on TV on Animal Planet. Were the bosses listening that day?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;animal-planet-radio-10-min:056bed86c85c27270cb0cb969b710445&#34;&gt;Animal Planet Radio - (10 min)&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Steve Dale&lt;/strong&gt; We&amp;rsquo;ll be right back with Jorja Fox on Animal Planet Radio!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Theme to CSI: Who Are You?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Steve Dale&lt;/strong&gt; You&amp;rsquo;ve seen her on the West Wing and ER. Oh, remember that episode of Ellen? It was called the &amp;#8216;Puppy&amp;rsquo; Episode. We&amp;rsquo;ll talk about that in a second. Her name is Jorja Fox, and right now she&amp;rsquo;s the hottest thing on TV. Well no, I don&amp;rsquo;t mean it quite that way. Well, you know, maybe I do. You see her on CSI and she&amp;rsquo;s giggling. Hey, Jorja.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; Hello, Steve. How&amp;rsquo;s everything?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Steve Dale&lt;/strong&gt; Everything is great. You know, the reason why we wanted to have you on Animal Planet Radio was because I&amp;rsquo;ve got, right in my hand here, your bio. And it says your name, you know, and then the date of birth, which is interesting cause the year is actually on this. I don&amp;rsquo;t know any other actress that does that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; See, I&amp;rsquo;m not quite sure how that all slipped out. But it&amp;rsquo;s all out in the open.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Steve Dale&lt;/strong&gt; The place of birth, and then your pets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; No, it doesn&amp;rsquo;t!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Steve Dale&lt;/strong&gt; It does! Ali the dog, a boxer, Rumplestiltskin your cat, and Sidney Potier, your cat.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; Yes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Steve Dale&lt;/strong&gt; Well, we need to talk about this.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; Okay.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Steve Dale&lt;/strong&gt; I mean, you are a HUGE pet lover.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; Um .. I&amp;rsquo;m, I&amp;rsquo;m an extreme animal lover now. And I love you know all animals. Domestic largely, but I&amp;rsquo;m kind of an animal freak, I guess you could say.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Steve Dale&lt;/strong&gt; Well, I don&amp;rsquo;t think it&amp;rsquo;s a freaky thing, I think that&amp;rsquo;s a great thing. Lets, you know I understand that between takes, I don&amp;rsquo;t know many, you know, television scenes, exciting, and it kind of is, but you know, a lot of these shows especially those that are not sitcoms, they take a while. Yours is done in film style, movie style, and that means there&amp;rsquo;s time between these takes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; Yes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Steve Dale&lt;/strong&gt; Things have to be set up and especially with you show, because things are so specifically detailed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; Very visually oriented.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Steve Dale&lt;/strong&gt; Mm hm. What do you do with all that time?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;laughs&lt;/strong&gt; That&amp;rsquo;s a very good question. Well, we have all kinds of games on the set. Like chess and checkers and things like that. Match games like soccer and basketball break out. I have a big music collection in my trailer. And we&amp;rsquo;re actually really lucky because we shoot a little outside of LA and we&amp;rsquo;re allowed to bring our dogs to work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Steve Dale&lt;/strong&gt; Now &amp;ldquo;&amp;lsquo;that&amp;rsquo;s&amp;rdquo;&amp;rsquo; where I&amp;rsquo;m going.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; Yeah. Yes, exactly, so.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Steve Dale&lt;/strong&gt; So the really big game isn&amp;rsquo;t chess or checkers, it&amp;rsquo;s fetch.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; Mm hm. Yeah, Marg has a dog she brings sometimes. And George Eads brings his dog to work &amp;ldquo;&amp;lsquo;every&amp;rdquo;&amp;rsquo; day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Steve Dale&lt;/strong&gt; Ah, you&amp;rsquo;re talking about Marg Helgenberger.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; Yes, Marg Helgenberger is on the show.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Steve Dale&lt;/strong&gt; And?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; And George Eads. And his dog, Maverick, is there every day. If he&amp;rsquo;s there, Maverick&amp;rsquo;s there. And I bring my dog, I&amp;rsquo;d say, you know about once every couple of weeks. I- I bring her if I have a shorter day. Because I have two cats, she has company at home. So unless- If I&amp;rsquo;m there for a couple of hours or less, I have the time. If it gets to be a long day then &lt;strong&gt;laughs&lt;/strong&gt; she&amp;rsquo;s ready to come home, you know, before I am. That&amp;rsquo;s a lot of fun, and it&amp;rsquo;s a big gift too. That&amp;rsquo;s not often, I mean you see that on some sets sometimes, but it&amp;rsquo;s rare on a show that people are allowed to bring their pets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Steve Dale&lt;/strong&gt; Well, and those names of your pets intrigue me. Ali, named after the boxer?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; Mm hm.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Steve Dale&lt;/strong&gt; Really?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; All three of them, of my animals, came with their names. Sid Potier, actually was originally named Sid Vicious. And I quit calling him that, sort of altered that name, because he was inheriting his namesake a little bit, and I thought that maybe. And kind of the funny thing about that after he became Sid Potier, he did sort of relax. He&amp;rsquo;s very debonair now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Steve Dale&lt;/strong&gt; He&amp;rsquo;s a much better actor.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; He&amp;rsquo;s a perfect gentleman.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Steve Dale&lt;/strong&gt; Yeah.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; And, ah, Ali was named after the great Muhammad Ali.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Steve Dale&lt;/strong&gt; Mm hm.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; Who, who was I to change their names? And I actually love all of their names.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Steve Dale&lt;/strong&gt; Where did you get your dog, Ali, the Boxer, from?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; Ah, um. Ali was a personal rescue, actually. I had a friend who couldn&amp;rsquo;t keep her, and she was about ten months old. He had heard that I just moved out to LA and had a small yard and he called me and I said sure, that I would take her. She sort of came with an expiration date. That after six months, if I wasn&amp;rsquo;t completely satisfied, that he was moving out to LA, and he would take her. And, ah, you know, of course, I fell madly in love. I think it took all of about a week. Ali was one of the best decisions I ever made.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Steve Dale&lt;/strong&gt; You know, they say that. And I used to do a lot of celebrity interviews, and I would talk, eventually, because I&amp;rsquo;m me, with the celebrities, about their pets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; Right.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Steve Dale&lt;/strong&gt; And one of my favorite questions was-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; Even before Animal Planet?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Steve Dale&lt;/strong&gt; Yeah! Yeah.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; Which I&amp;rsquo;m a huge fan of, by the way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Steve Dale&lt;/strong&gt; Well, thank you! Thank you very much. Well I wanna know if your dog&amp;rsquo;s personality, in any way, reflects yours?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; Um &lt;strong&gt;laughs&lt;/strong&gt; Well. People say that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Steve Dale&lt;/strong&gt; Really?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; Definitely say that. And that&amp;rsquo;s the thing I&amp;rsquo;ve been intrigued with for a long time too, cause I notice dogs, I think in particular, that are with owners or human companions, or whatever you want to call them, you know, the two personalities definitely seem to blend. The question to me has always been &amp;#8216;has it been the dog the takes on the human personality, or the human takes on the dog personality.&amp;rsquo; &lt;strong&gt;laughs&lt;/strong&gt; And it&amp;rsquo;s kind of a brilliant thing. But yeah, so I&amp;rsquo;ve heard. I&amp;rsquo;ve heard that we look alike, I&amp;rsquo;ve heard that we have definitely similar personality traits.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Steve Dale&lt;/strong&gt; Mm hm. Have you always been this huge animal lover?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; Yeah, I mean, matter of fact, even as a kid, I grew up in a small, beach town in Florida, and there was more wildlife there than there probably were humans. At that time, things have changed, sort of a bit. My grandmother, who&amp;rsquo;s 98, is a huge environmentalist, and has always been very, ah, very sort of tuned in to the natural world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Steve Dale&lt;/strong&gt; Hmm.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; And I think, as a young kid, I, um I really wanted to be like a marine biologist, or work with wildlife, more than I wanted to do anything else. And as I got older, you know, my science skills are really weak, which is also sort of iran- ironic cause I&amp;rsquo;m playing a scientist &lt;strong&gt;laughs&lt;/strong&gt; right now on television!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Steve Dale&lt;/strong&gt; Yeah, now you weren&amp;rsquo;t supposed to tell me that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;laughs&lt;/strong&gt; Science and math. It sort of became clear to me, probably around Jr. High or High School, that I might not make it! You know? Like I would love to do it as a career, work with wildlife, but the actual mechanics of getting a degree might not really be in my future.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Steve Dale&lt;/strong&gt; You know what would really be cool? And you never know who&amp;rsquo;s listening to this show, wouldn&amp;rsquo;t it be great if you hosted a show on Animal Planet? Where you didn&amp;rsquo;t have to really know the science?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; Yeah!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Steve Dale&lt;/strong&gt; But you did have to use your ability, well you know, talk into that camera or that camera. And read off cue cards and do all the things that you can do. And- And and I don&amp;rsquo;t mean that in a bad way! And still be able to go out and do things, like, with dolphin show trainers. And go to, maybe, a rain forest somewhere. Wouldn&amp;rsquo;t that be great?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; Steve, you know, if that could be in my future, I would be absolutely thrilled. That would be amazing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Steve Dale&lt;/strong&gt; Okay! Let&amp;rsquo;s say, alright, this is your- remember &amp;#8216;I Dream of Jeanie&amp;rsquo;?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; Mm hm.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Steve Dale&lt;/strong&gt; Okay.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; Actually, I grew up ten minutes from the town where &amp;#8216;I Dream of Jeanie&amp;rsquo; took place, Coco Beach, Florida.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Steve Dale&lt;/strong&gt; Alright, so you are now Jeanie. And you can cross your arms like Barbara Eden used to do, and close your eyes and, and all and make a wish for a TV Show. I mean, after CSI runs its very long and healthy course. Which we want.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;laughs&lt;/strong&gt; Thank you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Steve Dale&lt;/strong&gt; What would that show be? Would it be a sitcom, would it be really a nature show?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; Um yeah, I mean I would love to go out into the world, and sort of, you know, meet animals where they live and where they are naturally. I think that would be the all time greatest job. That was my hope, you know, even if it was being a wildlife photographer or that, where I could go to the places where animals are. That would be good.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Steve Dale&lt;/strong&gt; You know, one thing I learned about this business: You say it, and it can happen. You do, you never know who&amp;rsquo;s listening. But the first job, or one of the first times that we became familiar with you, Jorja Fox, was on &amp;#8216;Ellen.&amp;rsquo; They call that last show, and you&amp;rsquo;ll have to explain something to me, and if it&amp;rsquo;s filthy, don&amp;rsquo;t explain it. Why is that last show refereed to, like on all the websites? As-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; As &amp;#8216;The Puppy Episode.&amp;rsquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Steve Dale&lt;/strong&gt; Yeah!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; I wish that I had a great answer to that question, and that&amp;rsquo;s something I&amp;rsquo;ve always wanted to personally ask Ellen myself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Steve Dale&lt;/strong&gt; Is it something you can say on the radio, do you think?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; I, well, I don&amp;rsquo;t even know the answer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Steve Dale&lt;/strong&gt; You have no idea.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; And I know that it is absolutely a term of endearment. That it&amp;rsquo;s an inside joke, that there&amp;rsquo;s an inside story to why it was called &amp;#8216;The Puppy Episode.&amp;rsquo; Obviously there&amp;rsquo;s no puppies in that episode. And there&amp;rsquo;s really, I don&amp;rsquo;t think there&amp;rsquo;s any reference to any type of animals at all. But, ah, it&amp;rsquo;s quite possibly, when Ellen was writing the show with the writers, you know, something that came, that was very personal to them, which you know at least that has in common with that episode. It was a show that was extremely personal to Ellen.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Steve Dale&lt;/strong&gt; I want to talk about CSI for a second. I mean, you are now probably being heard all over the nation, all over America, but I&amp;rsquo;m from Chicago and there&amp;rsquo;s a Chicago connection: William Petersen&amp;rsquo;s on the show.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; Yes, he is.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Steve Dale&lt;/strong&gt; And he has something in common with you, because you have roots in the theater and so does he, I know.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; Yes. Absolutely. William Petersen is maybe one of my all time heroes. And, ah, he is from Chicago, he spent most of his break in Chicago. We&amp;rsquo;ve just come off break. So we had six weeks to sort of go away and do whatever we wanted to do.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Steve Dale&lt;/strong&gt; You know, I&amp;rsquo;ve referred to him as, ah, er, others have referred to him as an actor&amp;rsquo;s actor. I don&amp;rsquo;t know quite ever what that means. Maybe you can explain it to me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;loud laughter&lt;/strong&gt; Oh, I think that&amp;rsquo;s very specific right now, because he&amp;rsquo;s producing [[CSI]] as well. So he&amp;rsquo;s wearing two hats and, ah, as a producer, um, probably his number one concern, I think, that he looks after, is the actors on the show. And, um, he kind of once said to me that he wouldn&amp;rsquo;t know how to work if it wasn&amp;rsquo;t a collaborative process. Which is something that is extremely common, coming out of theater. If you work, you know, working on plays, two months of rehearsing, it becomes very much this collective of what people want to do. So that&amp;rsquo;s how he works, and it&amp;rsquo;s kind of unique to television, and um, everybody supported that. I think that they knew when they got William Petersen and he would be involved, that that&amp;rsquo;s how the show would go. It&amp;rsquo;s a very, very special thing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Steve Dale&lt;/strong&gt; Well, CSI&amp;rsquo;s become a very special thing, a very successful show. Wouldn&amp;rsquo;t be that without you, Jorja Fox, thanks for sharing some time and talking about your best friends with four legs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;laughs&lt;/strong&gt; Thank you so much!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Theme to CSI: Who Are You?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Steve Dale&lt;/strong&gt; Jorja Fox promoting the Pounce Purr-fections, that&amp;rsquo;s a new cat treat, and Jorja was involved in a promotion to benefit the ASPCA. It was a treat talking to Jorja &amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;see-also:056bed86c85c27270cb0cb969b710445&#34;&gt;See Also&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.pouncepurrfections.heinzpetproducts.com/index.asp&#34;&gt;Pounce Purrfections&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.ascpa.org/&#34;&gt;ASPCA&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>In Style</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2001/in-style/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jul 2001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2001/in-style/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What is the strangest thing in your fridge?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Actress, &lt;em&gt;CSI&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;I have a cat ball in a plastic container with catnip and dog vitamins that look like sausages.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Entertainment Weekly</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2001/entertainment-weekly/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jul 2001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2001/entertainment-weekly/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One minute a poker-faced sleuth can be found intoning &amp;ldquo;We chase the lie till it leads to the truth&amp;rdquo;; the next they&amp;rsquo;ll be gesturing to an anatomical sketch, cracking &amp;ldquo;This is the vagina, and it does tell a monologue.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cold ones too, most likely, considering he and the rest of the crew are spending this nippy March night outdoors-lensing the opener to an upcoming episode in which a couple is found stabbed to death outside a restaurant. &amp;ldquo;These are the nights when I get a little freaked out&amp;hellip;.The crime scenes [are] always just a little spooky and sad,&amp;rdquo; says costar Jorja Fox, 31, who plays Grissom protege Sara Sidle, of tonight&amp;rsquo;s bloody scenario. But it&amp;rsquo;s the chillingly real, ripped-from-the-headlines tales that creep Fox out the most. &amp;ldquo;If something just falls out of the sky into someone&amp;rsquo;s imagination, it&amp;rsquo;s easier to just be like &amp;#8216;Wow, this is cool,&amp;lsquo;&amp;rdquo; she says. &amp;ldquo;But when you know that this is based on something that happened to somebody somewhere, there&amp;rsquo;s a weight to that that&amp;rsquo;s very real. I hope I don&amp;rsquo;t lose that.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>News Limited</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2001/news-limited/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jul 2001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2001/news-limited/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It started with Quincy M E. but now a new tea of dedicated experts are solving crimes using forensic science. SHARON RAINSBURY visited the set of Nine&amp;rsquo;s CSI and spoke to series&amp;rsquo; stars william Petersen and Jorja Fox. IT is 8.30am on Monday morning, but the Las Vegas criminalistics bureau is already a hive of activity. Uniformed police officers come and go through the front door as two cars pull up outside the grey building.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lead crime scene investigator Gil Grissom is climbing out of his car when colleagues Sara Sidle and Warrick Brown pull in next to him.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;How&amp;rsquo;d it go at the college?&amp;rdquo; Grissom asks, leaning in the open passenger window. &amp;ldquo;They&amp;rsquo;re not co-operating,&amp;rdquo; Sidle replies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;We didn&amp;rsquo;t have a warrant. Got kicked out,&amp;rdquo; Brown adds, before the conversation is cut short when a loud voice interjects from the sidelines.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From behind a mobile monitor, director Peter Markle is watching the action play out on the screen in front of him, and he is not happy with what he sees.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Let&amp;rsquo;s do it again,&amp;rdquo; he cries, as the actors return to their positions at the start of the scene. They run the lines once more before Markle calls for the &amp;ldquo; second team&amp;rdquo;, and actors William Petersen, Jorja Fox and Gary Dourdan disappear into their trailers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Their stand-ins run the scene again while camera angles are checked and marked on the road, and final preparations are made to shoot the scene.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Making the most of modern special effects, CSI viewers are often given a microscopic view of the clues that help Grissom (Petersen) and his team of crime scene investigators &amp;#8212; Catherine Willows (Marg Helgenberger), Nick Stokes (George Eads), Sara Sidle (Jorja Fox) and Warrick Brown (Gary Dourdan ) &amp;#8212; piece together the evidence and bring the perpetrators to justice.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jorja Fox, who plays Sara, also thought the show would appeal to viewers from the moment she joined the cast in the second episode.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Stereotypically, whenever you are pitching science it is a hard sell,&amp;rdquo; she says.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Audiences are really smart and if it is not a total escape sitcom then they want to feel like their intellect is being appreciated. And that&amp;rsquo;s one thing we work really hard at.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;I barely passed eighth-grade science, and it is so romantic to me that I get to play a scientist.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;It was sort of that elusive faraway thing that I would never be able to be any good at, and here I am playing a star scientist who went to Harvard. It is great.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>