<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Movies on Fans of Le Fox Library</title>
    <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/tags/movies/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Movies on Fans of Le Fox Library</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://jorjafox.net/library/tags/movies/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>3 Weeks to Daytona</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/actor/3-weeks-to-daytona/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/actor/3-weeks-to-daytona/</guid>
      <description>Recap Chuck Weber is a race car driver who is down on his luck and nothing has gone right in twenty years, which happens to be the last time he won a race. Divorced, struggling to pay for his car and the alimony for his son, Willy (aka Worm), the only bright spot in his life is racing at the Speedbowl, a lock stock-car track run by Sal.
After crashing into the wall and losing his sponsorship, Chuck fears his dreams are at an end when Sal loses his sponsorship from Rob&amp;rsquo;s furniture.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alchemy</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/actor/alchemy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/actor/alchemy/</guid>
      <description>This distinctly feminist drama chronicles three phases in the life of a young woman. The three phases are presented as distinct, titled vignettes, &amp;ldquo;Charity,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;Hope,&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Faith,&amp;rdquo; centered upon Louisa Garrison, a woman who translates folk tales. She is first seen working in a bookstore. Though involved with Ethan, she decides to break up with him because she strongly suspects that he is still in love with Kitty, his ex-girl friend.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dead Drunk: The Kevin Tunell Story</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/actor/dead-drunk/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/actor/dead-drunk/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Dead Drunk: The Kevin Tunell Story&amp;rdquo; was first aired on HBO in 1993. It is a compelling and cautionary tale of the choices and consequences of drinking and driving. On New Years Eve, 1981, Kevin Tunell went to a party to celebrate the coming new year and drank with his friends. He took his girlfriend home and although impaired, told her &amp;ldquo;nothing ever happens to me when I drink.&amp;rdquo; That might have been true, but that night Kevin&amp;rsquo;s life would change forever.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dead Funny</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/actor/dead-funny/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/actor/dead-funny/</guid>
      <description>Reggie has been skewered to the kitchen table with a Samurai sword, and Viv&amp;rsquo;s trying to remember what happened. After all, it was one hell of a party last night. Instead of calling the police, Louise, Viv&amp;rsquo;s best friend, takes charge, attempting to solve Reggie&amp;rsquo;s murder with the help of a list of suspects and a couple of bottles of champagne. Deep in memories of her last year with Reggie and continuously interrupted by a strange cast of characters, Viv wanders through her apartment in a daze.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Down With The Joneses</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/actor/down-with-the-joneses/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/actor/down-with-the-joneses/</guid>
      <description>While it is listed at IMDb as having been completed in 2003, this movie has no release information and there is no record of anyone having see the completed film.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Extinction Soup</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/producer/extinction-soup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/producer/extinction-soup/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Extinction Soup&amp;rdquo; follows documentary filmmaker Philip Waller on his quest for adventure as he sets out to tell the story of his larger-than-life friend and extreme sports legend, Jimmy Hall. The film quickly takes a surprise turn when Waller finds himself consumed with exposing to the world an environmental catastrophe in the making - the extinction of the oceans&amp;rsquo; shark population through the mass slaughter of these magnificent animals for their fins.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Filmography</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/filmography/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/filmography/</guid>
      <description>A filmography is, in essence, the resume of a performer, listing all their cinematic achievements. This filmography has been broken down by section, to aid in sorting her work.
Jorja is credited as Jorja Fox unless otherwise noted.
Actor    Title   Date(s)   CSI: Immortality (TV Movie) Sara Sidle  2015   CSI: Crime Scene Investigation (TV Series) Sara Sidle – 2000-07 (main cast)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Food for the Heart</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/actor/food-for-the-heart/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/actor/food-for-the-heart/</guid>
      <description>Jorja Fox plays Delmar Youngblood; a divorcee with an abundant love of cooking and family raising a young son in a small town in anywhere, USA. Her cherished dream is to open a restaurant, The Hungry Bachelors Club, but this reality is deterred by her uninteresting and low-paying job as an insurance adjuster.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Forever Fabulous</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/actor/forever-fabulous/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/actor/forever-fabulous/</guid>
      <description>Loreli Daly (Jean Smart), beauty pageant organizer and Former Miss Texas Gal 1969, was run out of Paris, Texas ten years ago on the heels of a tabloid sex scandal. Living somewhere in Arizona with her long-term boyfriend and washed-up pageant MC, Lyle (Robert Wagner), and her daughter Corinne (Jennifer Elise Cox), holder of over 200 pageant titles and tiaras, Loreli is invited back, to Paris, to host the Miss Texas Tiara Quest &amp;ndash; but she can&amp;rsquo;t face the shame.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Forever Fabulous Biography</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/biographies/forever-fabulous/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/biographies/forever-fabulous/</guid>
      <description>Jorja Fox (Liz) co-stars in the new CBS breakout series C.S.I.: CRIME SCENE INVESTIGATION. She has also been featured as a Secret Service agent on NBC&amp;rsquo;s popular, Emmy-winning series THE WEST WING. She played the recurring role of Doyle on the NBC&amp;rsquo;s long-running ER, where she happily appeared for a number of seasons. She has made several made-for-TV films and mini-series including HOUSE OF FRANKENSTEIN, DEAD DRUNK and SUMMER STORIES. Film credits include MEMENTO, THE JERKY BOYS, THE HUNGRY BACHELORS&amp;rsquo; CLUB, VELOCITY TRAP, HOW TO MAKE THE CRUELEST MONTH, ALCHEMY, DEAD FUNNY, HAPPY HELL NIGHT and KILL OFF.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gidget: The Accidental Icon</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/actor/gidget/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/actor/gidget/</guid>
      <description>Narrated by Jorja Fox and produced by Brian L. Gillogly and Robert Masters, ACCIDENTAL ICON explores the largely untold story of the real “Gidget,” Kathy Kohner Zuckerman. Kathy’s account of surfing Malibu in the mid-50’s became the basis for a best-selling novel by her father Frederick Kohner and the hit 1959 “Gidget” movie, which introduced the modern sport of surfing to a world-wide audience. Surf legends and present-day “surfer girls” set the stage and take the Gidget story full circle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happy Hell Night</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/actor/happy-hell-night/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/actor/happy-hell-night/</guid>
      <description>25 years ago at Winfield College, psycho-priest Zachary Malius murdered seven frat boys and was put away in the local asylum. Now, however, the same fraternity stages a prank from which Malius is inadvertently set free and returns to the house to repeat his crime&amp;hellip;
As a prank for Rush Week, a couple of frat boys go to an insane asylum to take some pictures of an inmate there who supposedly killed a group of frat guys from their fathers&amp;rsquo; generation at the same college.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>House of Frankenstein 1997</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/actor/house-frankenstein/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/actor/house-frankenstein/</guid>
      <description>Distinctly mutilated bodies are being dropped all over Los Angeles like so much arcane propaganda. No one, however, knows how to read the message. The police are secretly baffled while the press has made the only stab at profiling the killer, calling the perpetrator The Midnight Raptor. Grace Dawkins is the Raptor&amp;rsquo;s latest victim, and the only one to have survived an attack, but she&amp;rsquo;s little help to the investigation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How I Became an Elephant</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/producer/how-became-elephant/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/producer/how-became-elephant/</guid>
      <description>How I Became An Elephant is more than just a film. It&amp;rsquo;s one girl&amp;rsquo;s story&amp;hellip; which led to a movement, which led to a continuing plan, to save a species.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Make the Cruelest Month</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/actor/how-make-crueslest-month/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/actor/how-make-crueslest-month/</guid>
      <description>Kip Koenig wrote and directed this comedy, set in a small college town, about neurotic Bell Bryant (Clea DuVall) who explains her problems directly to the camera: her older sister Sarah (Jorja Fox) has a happy marriage plus a baby on the way. Her other sister, beautiful Dot (Amy Smart), is involved in an affair with Bell&amp;rsquo;s ex, Leonard (Gabriel Mann). In a remote location, Bell makes love to Leonard and then departs, abandoning the nude Leonard who makes his way to the house of a married couple (Dennis Haysbert, Marianne Jean-Baptiste).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hungry Bachelors Club Biography</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/biographies/hungry-bachelors-club/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/biographies/hungry-bachelors-club/</guid>
      <description>Note: This biography was released before The Hungry Bachelors Club was renamed.
Jorja Fox (Delmar Youngblood) is the lead in THE HUNGRY BACHELORS CLUB, playing a single mother with an unusual offer that may make her dreams come true. She had a recurring role as Dr. Maggie Doyle on NBC&amp;rsquo;s hit series ER. Her television credits also include guest leads on Law and Order and most recently, a pilot for Barry Levinson and Tom Fontana, Flesh and Blood.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lion Ark</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/producer/lion-ark/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/producer/lion-ark/</guid>
      <description>More action adventure than traditional documentary, Lion Ark follows the world’s most ambitious and daring animal rescue, with a narrative compiled from film, interviews, conversations and reactions as events unfolded. How attitudes to animals were changed in Bolivia, illegal circuses pursued and closed, and 25 lions airlifted to freedom.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Memento</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/actor/memento/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/actor/memento/</guid>
      <description>Memento is a movie starring Guy Pearce (&amp;lsquo;The Adventures of Priscilla, Queen of the Desert&amp;rsquo; and &amp;lsquo;L.A. Confidential&amp;rsquo;) and Carrie Anne-Moss (&amp;lsquo;The Matrix&amp;rsquo; and &amp;lsquo;Red Planet&amp;rsquo;). Jorja Fox plays Catherine Shelby, the wife of Leonard Shelby (Pearce), who was raped and murdered in the couple&amp;rsquo;s home.
Recap Around 2:00 AM (Nov. 1997) police were called to the home of Leonard and Catherine Shelby, after two neighbors reported hearing gunshots. The front door was open, and they found the Shelbys in serious condition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Next Exit</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/actor/next-exit/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/actor/next-exit/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Charles wants to become an actor and Jason wants to go only as far as Bakersfield, where he hopes to reunite with his estranged father. Upon arrival in Bakersfield, Charles gets sidetracked when he falls in love with Tracy Morris, a local teen, who is dating Jon Burroughs, a twenty something, small time drug dealer.
Jason finds his father, but the reunion is cut short when he realizes that his dad has moved on with a new family of his own and is not interested in making up for lost time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Jerky Boys</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/actor/jerky-boys/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/actor/jerky-boys/</guid>
      <description>When a former high school classmate brags about his mob connections, the Jerky Boys &amp;ndash; a pair of thirty-something slackers who pride themselves on devious prank phone calls &amp;ndash; decide to have a little fun in the Mafia underworld. However, when a cop mistakes the Jerky Boys for actual hit men, their innocent game causes more trouble than they would&amp;rsquo;ve ever imagined.
Character Jorja Fox plays Lazarro&amp;rsquo;s Young Lady. Lazarro works for the Mafia, and his Young Lady is basically a hired call girl.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Kill-Off</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/actor/kill-off/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/actor/kill-off/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis In a small coastal community in New Jersey, the only action in town is a run-down nightclub called Pavillion. The club&amp;rsquo;s owner, Pete (Jackson Sims), can barely make the payroll for Rags the bartender (William Russell), Myra the barmaid (Jorjan Fox) (who is also Pete&amp;rsquo;s daughter), and clean-up man Ralph (Steve Monroe). In a bid to bring in more customers, Pete hires a stripper, Danny Lee (Cathy Haase). Danny Lee&amp;rsquo;s act soon turns Ralph&amp;rsquo;s head, which is not good news for his wife Luanne (Loretta Gross).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Velocity Trap</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/actor/velocity-trap/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/actor/velocity-trap/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s high noon in deep space. It&amp;rsquo;s the year 2150, and electronic crime and interstellar piracy rule the galaxy. Facing unlawful murder charges, Police officer Raymond Stokes is reassigned to escort the Federal Banking Ship USF Atlantic and $40,000,000,000 through the Bermuda Triangle of space: The Velocity Run. With only Beth Sheffield, the ship&amp;rsquo;s navigator, to assist him, all his strength is put to the test when everything on board is threatened by an oncoming 600 million ton asteroid, and a well-armed team of thieves that have docked alongside the USF Atlantic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Velocity Trap Biography</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/biographies/velocity-trap/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/biographies/velocity-trap/</guid>
      <description>Jorja was born in New York City to French Canadian immigrant parents. When she was three, the family relocated to a small costal town in Florida. Raised on a narrow barrier island, Jorja has a deep affinity for all things oceanic, big skies, and Jimmy Buffet. Jorja began her acting career at the age of five, when she landed the coveted role of the &amp;#8216;Rooster&amp;rsquo; in the children&amp;rsquo;s classic &amp;ldquo;Chicken Little.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>