<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Mini Series on JFO Library</title>
    <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/tags/mini-series/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Mini Series on JFO Library</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="http://jorjafox.net/library/tags/mini-series/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>I Love the &#39;70s</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/self/i-love-the-70s/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/self/i-love-the-70s/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;I Love the 70s&lt;/em&gt; takes viewers on another fun-filled ride through the music, movies, TV shows, products, fashions, fads, trends and major events that defined pop culture each year of the decade. From Star Wars to Charlie&amp;rsquo;s Angels, leisure suits to underoos, mutton-chop sideburns to the Mod Squad&amp;hellip; we once again tap our collective memories to cover the sublime, the ridiculous, and everything in between.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Comics, rock stars, actors, writers and other celebs past and present weigh in on the 70s experience. They discuss the important questions of the decade: What the hell happened to Richie&amp;rsquo;s brother Chuck on Happy Days? Did Michael Myers use Ginsu knives in Halloween? And most important of all: Who sank my Battleship?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Viewers are treated to a barrage of retro clips from sitcoms, movies, network news, commercials and other sources. And it won&amp;rsquo;t be just TV, music and film. It&amp;rsquo;s be cars, junk food, fashion and everything else that went into making the delicious pop culture stew that was the 70s.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;appearances:816cae55cc983882b73d184ed07028d2&#34;&gt;Appearances&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jorja appeared in 5 episodes of the miniseries:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1970 &amp;#8211; Original Airdate 08.18.2003&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1973 &amp;#8211; Original Airdate 08.19.2003&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1974 &amp;#8211; Original Airdate 08.20.2003&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1976 &amp;#8211; Original Airdate 08.21.2003&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1977 &amp;#8211; Original Airdate 08.21.2003&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>