<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>2002 on Jorja Fox Library</title>
    <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/tags/2002/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 2002 on Jorja Fox Library</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2002 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://jorjafox.net/library/tags/2002/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Guide</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2002/tv-guide-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2002/tv-guide-5/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Showbiz Buzz + Celebrity Scoop&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; loves playing Sara Sidle, the lab rat on CBS&amp;rsquo;s &lt;em&gt;CSI: Crime Scene Investigation&lt;/em&gt;. &amp;ldquo;She&amp;rsquo;s brave, smart, obsessed with doing the right thing. I aspire to be this person,&amp;rdquo; Fox says. &amp;ldquo;Being a little less squeamish would be a good thing.&amp;rdquo; That won&amp;rsquo;t be easy. Some story lines are so &amp;ldquo;psycholigically horrifying,&amp;rdquo; Fox has nightmares if she reads scripts before going to bed. &amp;ldquo;I keep thinking they [bad dreams] are going away!&amp;rdquo; she says. She wards off the bogeymen by watching &amp;ldquo;something funny- Nickelodeon or infomercials.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About.com</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2002/about-com/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2002/about-com/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Are you surprised at the popularity of the show and the amount of young people who are going to college now to learn more about forensics?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;JORJA FOX: I&amp;rsquo;m enormously surprised at the success of ?C.S.I.? I think that even in all of our wildest dreams that we could have imagined as great a run as we are having and I&amp;rsquo;m just thrilled about it. I feel blessed every day. I&amp;rsquo;m also surprised that, yes, there seems to be an increase in kids wanting to study forensics.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I know that the big joke right now is with law enforcement, when they talk to people, everybody thinks that they can have their crime solved in 40 minutes or at least less than two days. Unfortunately, that&amp;rsquo;s the key to our show. We&amp;rsquo;re hearing about that right now and it&amp;rsquo;ll be interesting to see if the kids stick to it or if it&amp;rsquo;s something that looks more glossy than it is perhaps on a day-to-day basis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How has the reaction been within the law enforcement community? Do you hear mostly positive responses?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;JORJA FOX: Yes, for the most part everybody is very, very supportive. It&amp;rsquo;s really a great thing. We try very hard to make the show as real as we can. Time is the only place where we really take big cheats. We thought about opening a case in September and we&amp;rsquo;ll solve it in December - like real-life - but we thought we might lose some of our audience then.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What&amp;rsquo;s it like joining a show that&amp;rsquo;s so successful?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;ARCHIE KAYO: It&amp;rsquo;s so exciting.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Is it a little bit intimidating joining one of the highest rated shows on television?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;ARCHIE KAYO: Yes, there&amp;rsquo;s no question. I think it&amp;rsquo;s certainly a genuine privilege. Besides the show being so well done, everyone on the show is a class act. Everyone is realizing that it is kind of an extraordinary ride and they are all aware.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;JORJA FOX: Basically we are all loony and down-to-earth.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Is it really crazy behind-the-scenes? It&amp;rsquo;s such a serious drama.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;JORJA FOX: Yeah, we cut loose.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;ARCHIE KAYO: You couldn&amp;rsquo;t imagine.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Who is the practical joker?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;JORJA FOX: I think probably George Eads is the biggest practical joker. But everybody is fair game and everybody has jokes that they like to play on each other.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This movie tonight - &amp;ldquo;The Emperor&amp;rsquo;s Club&amp;rdquo; - is basically about teachers and the impact they have on their students. Did you have a teacher who made an impact on you?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;JORJA FOX: Yes, several. I am specifically thinking right now about a high school English teacher, Mrs. Williamson, and a high school Humanities teacher, Mrs. Asher.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Was it what they taught you or how they taught you?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;JORJA FOX: Both, I think. They were really accessible to all the kids in the school, for the most part. It didn&amp;rsquo;t matter if you were doing well in the class or if you were doing poorly in the class, they kept an eye on everybody in addition to just inspiring kids. For me, I never loved Shakespeare or traditional English studies; I like modern stuff. For a teacher to get me really excited about Shakespeare to a point where you are passionate about it - you can&amp;rsquo;t wait to read the next chapter - that shows dedication.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;ARCHIE KAYO: I had an English Composition teacher in college who I think I really, really looked up to. I thought so much of him as a professor, he was so inspirational, that I actually wanted to be him when I graduated. So I went to talk to him and I said, ?I want to teach.? He said, ?Archie, I really admire that, I think it&amp;rsquo;s noble, but I think you should go live your life and then come back and you&amp;rsquo;ll have more to teach.? At first I was offended, but now I realize how right he really was.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Have you called him since you started acting to let him know he was right?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;ARCHIE KAYO: (Laughing) I can&amp;rsquo;t find him. I&amp;rsquo;ve been looking for him but I don&amp;rsquo;t know where he&amp;rsquo;s gone.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ET Online</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2002/et-online-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2002/et-online-2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A permanent disappearance during a magic trick means it&amp;rsquo;s time to call in the &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; crew. Inhuman blood droplets and the discovery of a razor sharp knife just magnify the mystery for investigators. And as star JORJA FOX told ET, tonight&amp;rsquo;s episode on CBS is so realistic that it frightened her. Meanwhile, over at &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rsquo;s&amp;rdquo; sister show, &amp;ldquo;CSI: Miami,&amp;rdquo; a decision has been made regarding an episode that features a sniper. CBS has decided to now air the episode on November 18th as originally scheduled. The network had planned to withhold the sniper episode because of the Washington, D.C.-area shootings. The story was developed in August, several weeks before the attacks began.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Guide</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2002/tv-guide-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2002/tv-guide-4/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Question: I am a huge CSI fan. I was wondering if you have heard anything about if the show is going to put Grissom (William Petersen) and Sara (Jorja Fox) together? You can see that they&amp;rsquo;re attracted to each other! Do you think that Grissom and Sara should date despite their age difference? ? Karen&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Matt: I think dating would be a huge mistake for CSI, but not because I&amp;rsquo;m an ageist or anything. This isn&amp;rsquo;t (thankfully) NYPD Blue, where the entire office seems to be pairing off with each other. Keeping the attraction muted, as subtext, allows us to be fascinated by the possibilities. Both characters are pretty well defined as somewhat anti-social loners who occasionally pine for a fuller life. If they began a romantic relationship, I think it would diminish our interest in their interactions almost immediately. Best just to be left wondering.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ET Online</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2002/et-online-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2002/et-online-1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Not since &amp;#8216;The Wizard of Oz&amp;rsquo; have so many little people gathered together for a production, but this week&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; earns that distinction when the team investigates the death of one of the members attending the International Organization of Little People&amp;rsquo;s convention in Las Vegas.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;There are two storylines,&amp;rdquo; JORJA FOX tells ET about tonight&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;A Little Murder&amp;rdquo; episode of &amp;ldquo;CSI.&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;One of the them is very touching and affects Catherine Willows (MARG HELGENBERGER) and Warrick Brown (GARY DOURDAN). Our storyline is going to deal with a murder in the little people community.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;It&amp;rsquo;s very cool,&amp;rdquo; GEORGE EADS (Nick) adds, &amp;ldquo;because &amp;#8216;Under the Rainbow&amp;rsquo; is the last time I saw a group of little people together on film.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When Lawrence Ames (MICHAEL GILDEN) is found hanging on the stage where the convention will take place, Grissom (WILLIAM PETERSEN), Sara (Fox) and Nick (Eads) are called to the scene. At first it appears to be a suicide, but Grissom disputes that, and the team sets to work to track down the killer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;We&amp;rsquo;ve done a couple of shows in the past that have dealt with situations that hadn&amp;rsquo;t gotten much television coverage,&amp;rdquo; Petersen explains. &amp;ldquo;We always find it interesting to get into a milieu that is unfamiliar to regular network viewers. The value of television is to take you places you don&amp;rsquo;t normally get to be. These little people conventions are not something where &amp;#8216;average&amp;rsquo; people go.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Meanwhile, Catherine is attacked by an unknown assailant at a crime scene where she is collecting evidence.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For a sneak peek at the &amp;ldquo;A Little Murder&amp;rdquo; episode of &amp;ldquo;CSI,&amp;rdquo; watch tonight&amp;rsquo;s ET. Then tune in to CBS at 9 p.m. and catch the action!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Gal</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2002/tv-gal-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2002/tv-gal-3/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I know the big thing about &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; (Thursday, CBS, 9 p.m.) is that we don&amp;rsquo;t know much about the personal life of the characters, but I do love the subtle tension that is building between Grissom and Sara. He&amp;rsquo;s obviously fighting his attraction to her and she&amp;rsquo;s obviously angry about his announcement that she needs to get a life. The really amazing thing is how much more vibrant and interesting the characters on &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; are versus the characters on &amp;ldquo;CSI: Miami.&amp;rdquo; When I watch &amp;ldquo;CSI: Miami,&amp;rdquo; my biggest concern is if David Caruso is wearing enough sunscreen.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>People</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2002/people-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2002/people-2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;As crime-solving wizards on TV&amp;rsquo;s top-rated drama, the stars of CSI steep themselves in blood, bullet holes and (very) gross anatomy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This past summer the cast of CSI: Crime Scene Investigation did what you&amp;rsquo;d expect anyone from a major hit series to do. They kicked back and forgot about the inanimate parade of bruised, gouged, mutilated and (on one memorable occasion) liquefied corpses that form the dramatic center of the CBS show&amp;rsquo;s high-tech forensic sleuthing. Costars Jorja Fox, Eric Szmanda and Gary Dourdan all vacationed together in Paris. Evanston, Ill., native William Petersen took in a Chicago Cubs baseball game with six CSI grips from L.A.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Meanwhile Marg Helgenberger, 43, went on a busman&amp;rsquo;s holiday from hell: She&amp;rsquo;d been worried that the show&amp;rsquo;s phenomenal popularity &amp;#8212; signaled by its own new spinoff, CSI: Miami, teaming NYPD Blue alumni David Caruso and Kim Delaney &amp;#8212; might be taking the edge off her performance as intrepid detective (and ex-stripper) Catherine Willows. So she spent a night with Las Vegas&amp;rsquo;s own crime scene investigators, the inspiration for the series. The unit was called to a casino hotel to check out a corpse, male, in his 30s, dead of drugs and alcohol. &amp;ldquo;You get a sense of the fragility of life,&amp;rdquo; says Helgenberger, seated near a photo of her son Huey, 12, in her trailer on the set in Valencia, Calif. &amp;ldquo;But I also came away with a sense of what heroes these people are. They do a job most people couldn&amp;rsquo;t or wouldn&amp;rsquo;t do, and make a difference solving crimes.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As of July, Helgenberger was back on the set for CSI&amp;rsquo;s third season, which kicked off Sept. 26 with its best ratings ever. An audience of 30 million tuned in for the adventures of this savvy, cast-iron-stomached Vegas forensics unit led by the obsessive Gil Grissom (Petersen, 49), with an assist from a team that also includes Warrick Brown (Dourdan, 35), Nick Stokes (George Eads, 35) and Sara Sidle (Fox, 34). Their cases are peppered with grisly details &amp;#8212; an old lady devoured by her cats, a cheerleader disemboweled on a soccer field &amp;#8212; and discussed with such intimidating jargon as &amp;ldquo;phenolphthalein&amp;rdquo; (a chemical that detects blood) and &amp;ldquo;epithelial&amp;rdquo; (skin cells). &amp;ldquo;Most of these terms are in Latin,&amp;rdquo; says Petersen. &amp;ldquo;But we learn as we go along.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They learn fast. The show, which has supplanted ER as TV&amp;rsquo;s top-rated drama, is now famous enough that when Dourdan and Eads last year promoted CSI in Buenos Aires, where the show airs, local police decided to take the stars down a peg. &amp;ldquo;They showed us tapes of autopsies to see if we would crack,&amp;rdquo; Dourdan says. &amp;ldquo;We didn&amp;rsquo;t.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Far from being queasy, the cast seems genuinely curious about the show&amp;rsquo;s morbid matters. Petersen &amp;#8212; who is coexecutive producer and costar &amp;#8212; unwinds by plowing through the dense prose of The Future of Life by forensic entomologist Edward O. Wilson. One shelf of Helgenberger&amp;rsquo;s colorfully decorated trailer includes Practical Homicide Investigation. The set&amp;rsquo;s atmosphere is hardly funereal, though. Some days Fox, Dourdan, Eads and Robert David Hall (who plays coroner Albert Robbins) bring out guitars for an off-camera sing-along of folk and blues, and Paul Guilfoyle, 53 (police captain Jim Brass), is considered a reliable cutup. Helgenberger arrives already chilled out. &amp;ldquo;I did yoga at 4:45 a.m.,&amp;rdquo; she says.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All around them, however, is the presence of death. There&amp;rsquo;s the lab (stocked, for verisimilitude&amp;rsquo;s sake, with several million dollars&amp;rsquo; worth of equipment, including a $500,000 ballistics identifier) and Robbins&amp;rsquo;s morgue. &amp;ldquo;One of the treats for me,&amp;rdquo; says Hall, 55, &amp;ldquo;is what our special effects guy will do to the corpses.&amp;rdquo; The cadavers are actually actors, made up to look seriously dead and damaged. And all that blood? It&amp;rsquo;s Karo Syrup, &amp;ldquo;and it tastes like peppermint,&amp;rdquo; says Eads.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even though the gore is fake, Jorja Fox and Eric Szmanda, who plays DNA tech Greg Sanders, could do with a little less of it. They will never again make the mistake of eating pizza before a forensics scene. &amp;ldquo;I started feeling nauseous,&amp;rdquo; says Fox. &amp;ldquo;I don&amp;rsquo;t think I could ever be a CSI.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mantra Online</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2002/mantra-online/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2002/mantra-online/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Actress Jorja Fox poses as she arrives at the Macy&amp;rsquo;s and American Express Passport &lt;sup&gt;20&lt;/sup&gt;&amp;frasl;&lt;sub&gt;02&lt;/sub&gt; 20th anniversary HIV/AIDS fundraiser in Santa Monica, California, September 28, 2002. The annual event features a celebrity auction and fashion show.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>People</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2002/people-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2002/people-1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Someone must have forgotten to tell CSI: Crime Scene Investigation&amp;rsquo;s Jorja Fox that it&amp;rsquo;s still summer: The actress (whose show is an Emmy contender for outstanding drama series) opts to pair her spaghetti-strapped dress with calf-high leather boots.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Post Dispatch</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2002/post-dispatch/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2002/post-dispatch/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;CSI: Crime Scene Investigation CBS&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Last season ended with the revelation that Grissom (William Petersen) is losing his hearing. But producers say we shouldn&amp;rsquo;t expect his condition to dominate the season; instead, look for Sara (Jorja Fox) to strike up a romance with the cute guy she met last season who didn&amp;rsquo;t mind her smell.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Extra TV</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2002/extra-tv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2002/extra-tv/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Those crafty crime scene investigators of &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; are back on the case for another season of murder and mayhem, shifting into high gear for the third season of CBS? runaway hit. And only &amp;ldquo;Extra&amp;rdquo; was on location in Las Vegas with the ratings grabbing gumshoes as they shot an upcoming episode with a crime ripped from the headlines.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Star William Petersen and his team of criminalists are called in to investigate a young movie star accused of murder. And much like the infamous O.J. trial, co-star Gary Dourdan says for the first time viewers will see the &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; cast take the stand in court. Gary says, &amp;ldquo;It&amp;rsquo;s going to go into more of what C.S.I.&amp;rsquo;s really have to deal with in regards to court stuff and how they have to prove their evidence.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But the new season isn&amp;rsquo;t the only thing on the cast&amp;rsquo;s mind these days. With six Emmy nominations, including one for best drama series, they&amp;rsquo;re already making plans for Emmy night. Well, co-star Jorja Fox says that win or lose, the real party will be after the September 22nd ceremony. She says, &amp;ldquo;The cast has a reputation for partying a little bit after events that we get together at. We&amp;rsquo;re very bad.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But you can bet these party people know how to hide the evidence.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>In Style Magazine</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2002/in-style-magazine-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2002/in-style-magazine-2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;She&amp;rsquo;s a dressed-down, seriously smart cookie in &amp;#8216;CSI: Crime Scene Invesigation&amp;rsquo;, but off-screen, Jorja Fox loves to get glammed-up for big nights out in Hollywood.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Brains and beauty can mix. That&amp;rsquo;s if vivacious American actress Jorja Fox, 34, is anything to go by. The ex-model plays Sara Sidle, a bookishly sexy forensic scientist in Channel 5&amp;rsquo;s number-one show, &lt;em&gt;CSI: Crime Scene Invesigation&lt;/em&gt;, which also has the second biggest TV ratings in the US. But life on screen is more grit than glamour, with Sidle spending most of her time at Las Vegas murder scenes. &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m more into make-up than Sara would be; she&amp;rsquo;s practical, although she certainly flirts with the guys,&amp;rdquo; Fox laughs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;In &lt;em&gt;CSI&lt;/em&gt;, your character has very straight hair, yet yours is naturally curly. How come?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I associate her with action-figure qualities: sleekness and stelth and, for me, straight hair reflects that. I use Phillip B Straight Baume [&amp;pound;16 ; from Space NK, 0870 169 9999], and straightening irons every day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What do you do with your hair off duty?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mostly, I wear my hair curly, partly to give it a rest because I straighten it every day at work. So I&amp;rsquo;ll let it do it&amp;rsquo;s own thing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Your character is quite no-nonsense, but is she feminine? Does she like make-up?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The characters are almost always on the job, so you see her in work clothes. Sometimes she has to go to dark, creepy places - sewers, deserted roads, and under people&amp;rsquo;s houses - so she wears lots of jeans, boots and long coats. Crime scenes are dangerous places. Often criminals return to the crime scene, so she needs clothes she can run in! Make-up wise, she likes low-key lips and smoky, mysterious eyes to reflect the intense, brooding vibe of her character.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Now that &lt;em&gt;CSI&lt;/em&gt; is so successful, you must have to go to awards ceremonies and dress up.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yes, we have been invited to awards ceremonies, which is nice and it&amp;rsquo;s exciting to achieve the recognition. Getting ready to go is really fun and I enjoy havign my hair and make-up done. I always wear a classing gown and the full hair and make-up works.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Are you a beauty junkie?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yes, I love the natural beauty of women and I think make-up is fantastic when it&amp;rsquo;s work for fun, to feel different or to create characters. But if people feel they need to wear it before they can present themselves to the world, then I feel sad for them. All shapes and colours and sizes are beautiful.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What&amp;rsquo;s your favourite make-up look?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I love the dewy, healthy look. For me, it&amp;rsquo;s all about looking alive and fresh but, for going out in the evening, I love the old-school glamour look with vampy eye make-up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;So, what have you got in your make-up bag?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Christian Dio Teint Diorlift Concealer [&amp;pound;15 ; available nationwide], I normally don&amp;rsquo;t leave the house without putting some on, a MAC brown eyeliner [&amp;pound;9 ; 020 77534 9222] and brow pencil, although I wear black eyeliner if I&amp;rsquo;m going clubbing. On a night out I&amp;rsquo;ll also wear mascara and lipgloss. I love Stila Lip Glazes [&amp;pound;18 ; from Space NK], and Paula Dorf Lipsicle lipglosses [&amp;pound;13 ; from Dickins &amp;amp; Jones; 020 7734 707]. I keep it simple on skin as I wear power and foundation all day and I like to give my skin a break.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How do you cope with the punishing schedule on &lt;em&gt;CSI&lt;/em&gt;?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Normally it&amp;rsquo;s 12 to 15 hours a day, but we do get days off and three-day weekends occasionally. If I am especially tired, they&amp;rsquo;ll right me a lighter episode.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How do you keep up your energy?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Coffee, coffee and more coffee. Also, I try to get at least eight to 10 hours sleep. My social life has gone out the window. But I try to keep my energy up by eating well- lots of fruit, vegetables and protein. I eat a lot of those protien bars, too. I&amp;rsquo;m a vegetarian, not so much for health reasons but becuase I live in the big city, where there&amp;rsquo;s plenty of food, I don&amp;rsquo;t see the need to kill animals to eat.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What do you do to disguise tiredness?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We have genius make-up artists who put us back together, but I drink tons of water to prevent dehydration and puffy eyes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Do you have any beauty rituals?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Oh yes, I love the bath. I&amp;rsquo;ll put essential oils in the bath and play a little music.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How do you relax?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We get time to relax on set, so I go to my trailer and play guitar. The Winnebegos go everywhere with us and I take all my tapestries and games and cars, and I have a dog, so I take him with me. LA is very much an outdoor culture, so I go to the beach and to the mountains with my dog.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Self</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2002/self/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2002/self/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Love Match&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One advantage of tennis: it&amp;rsquo;s an amazing exercise. Just ask actress &lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When Jorja Fox isn&amp;rsquo;t busy playing a forensic scientist on the CBS Drama &lt;em&gt;CSI: Crime Scene Investigation&lt;/em&gt;, she&amp;rsquo;s sleuthing out new ways to stay fit. Her latest fitness foray: adding tennis to her repertoire, which already includes running, boogie boarding and hiking. Fox hadn&amp;rsquo;t played since her teens, so she started by having a coaching session with Sue Whiteside, tennis director at Rancho Valencia in Rancho Santa Fe, California. She recieved not only a skills brushup but also a terrific workout. &amp;ldquo;I don&amp;rsquo;t tone my arms as consistently as I do my legs,&amp;rdquo; Fox says, so Whiteside suggested practicing serves to build up arm strength and add curves &amp;ldquo;And don&amp;rsquo;t shy away from overheads!&amp;rdquo; Whiteside says- nailing them strengthens shoulders. To up the cardio factor, get to the ball on one bounce. &amp;ldquo;If you work hard, you can burn 500 calories in an hour,&amp;rdquo; says Whiteside. Fox has fallen in love with tennis: &amp;ldquo;My producers might kill me, but maybe I&amp;rsquo;ll start whacking balls against the side of the soundstage during downtime.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Entertainment Tonight</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2002/entertainment-tonight/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2002/entertainment-tonight/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; star JORJA FOX tells ET that even though she hasn&amp;rsquo;t received a script for the upcoming season of the CBS drama, she can guarantee it&amp;rsquo;s going to be scary. While Fox was enjoying her summer hiatus from show, she took time to help out a cause dear to her heart: the environment. Fox posed for the Environmental Communications Office&amp;rsquo;s educational campaign about global warming. Long an advocate of the cause, Fox hopes that the effort will help preserve the earth for generations to come.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CSI season 2 DVD extras</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2002/csi-season-2-dvd-extras/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2002/csi-season-2-dvd-extras/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;ldquo;(shot of the characters viewing a &amp;lsquo;corpse&amp;rsquo;; Jorja walks away holding her stomach)&amp;rdquo; Uh. It&amp;rsquo;s too early. &amp;ldquo;(to &amp;lsquo;corpse&amp;rsquo;)&amp;rdquo; I mean, I&amp;rsquo;m sure you&amp;rsquo;re a really nice guy&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>