<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>2008 on Fans of Le Fox Library</title>
    <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/tags/2008/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 2008 on Fans of Le Fox Library</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2008 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://jorjafox.net/library/tags/2008/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Contra Costa Times</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2008/contra-costa-times/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2008/contra-costa-times/</guid>
      <description>The City Council temporarily halted construction of a new $42 million elephant exhibit at the Los Angeles Zoo on Wednesday amid concerns over funding and a debate over whether the animals should be kept in zoos at all.
The vote came after the nonprofit Greater Los Angeles Zoo Association offered to pay an additional $14 million to finish the exhibit.
[&amp;hellip;]
At the council meeting, activists and celebrities including comedian Lily Tomlin and actress Jorja Fox said the zoo&amp;rsquo;s costly exhibit would do nothing to alleviate painful foot diseases that often lead to death among captive elephants.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Politico</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2008/politico/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2008/politico/</guid>
      <description>The Obama campaign is going to do wonders for the gang running Artists &amp;amp; Athletes, the nonprofit that has found its niche within the confines of Hollywood&amp;rsquo;s interest in and naiveté about Washington.
Last night the ballroom at the Four Seasons in L.A. was filled with 140 agents, publicists, managers, writers, producers, directors and actors who filed in to listen to Mark Halperin moderate a panel discussion about what to expect from Washington.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EasyVegan.info </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2008/easyvegan-info/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2008/easyvegan-info/</guid>
      <description>On yesterday&amp;rsquo;s episode of &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; (&amp;ldquo;Leave Out All the Rest&amp;rdquo;), recently departed CSI Sara Sidle sends Gil Grissom a .mov file -slash- Dear John &amp;ldquo;letter&amp;rdquo; over the internets. Look closely, and you can briefly see her email address flash across the screen: info@seashepherd.org. ZOMG! Sara is sailing with the crew of the Sea Shepherd Conservation Society!
Of her adventure with Captain Paul Watson and his band of anti-whaling pirates, Sara says,</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TVGuide.com - Ask Matt </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2008/tv-guide-07/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2008/tv-guide-07/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
Question: Have we really seen the last of Sara Sidle on &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo;? Last week&amp;rsquo;s ending of Episode 2 was heartbreaking. The creators have invested years hinting at, building up and finally revealing the relationship between Gil and Sara. I appreciate that it hasn&amp;rsquo;t been all hearts and flowers, but now that Petersen is leaving the show anyway, why not let these two tortured characters have a happy ending together? — Patrice</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Courier-Mail</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2008/the-courier-mail/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2008/the-courier-mail/</guid>
      <description>I WAS shocked at the amount of wrinkle-relaxing poison in the face of Jorja Fox when I watched CSI last week. There wasn&amp;rsquo;t any. She just looked like the rest of us, ie: a corrugated iron roof from some angles.
She was back for Warrick&amp;rsquo;s funeral, an episode that required some emotion to register on his colleagues&amp;rsquo; face. So it worked out well for her. Not so good for the other woman in the show, Marg Helgenberger, who didn&amp;rsquo;t look remotely upset, even though she said she was.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EW.com</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2008/ew-04/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2008/ew-04/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;] I wasn&amp;rsquo;t surprised to learn that so many of you got choked up at the gut-wrenching scenes from Warrick&amp;rsquo;s funeral, but I was taken aback by some commentary regarding Sara&amp;rsquo;s appearance &amp;ndash; namely, whether or not she was with child, and if her condition would eventually explain her abrupt decision to leave Las Vegas last season. All I can say is &amp;ndash; good God, no. Look, I hated her poofy dress (and the curls she wore with it) probably as much as the next fan, but never in my wildest dreams would I have considered she was trying to cover up a secret pregnancy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Denver Post</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2008/denver-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2008/denver-post/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
Soap star Deidre Hall at CNN Grill on Wednesday, along with &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rsquo;s&amp;rdquo; Jorja Fox&amp;hellip; .
[&amp;hellip;]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ausiello TV </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2008/ausiello-tv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2008/ausiello-tv/</guid>
      <description>Michael Ausiello: You&amp;rsquo;re back this season
Jorja Fox: Maybe. Maybe I am, maybe I&amp;rsquo;m not.
Ausiello: I&amp;rsquo;ve already seen the first episode, and you were there.
Fox: Yeah, yeah. I&amp;rsquo;m definitely there for that.
Ausiello: And a couple more there.
Fox: Yeah, I&amp;rsquo;m visiting for a little bit. I&amp;rsquo;ll be in and out, so that&amp;rsquo;s kind of fun. I knew that might happen, I didn&amp;rsquo;t know it was gonna happen so soon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Entertainment Weekly 6th Annual Pre-Emmy Party </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2008/ew/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Sep 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2008/ew/</guid>
      <description>*Jorja Fox:** I think it&amp;rsquo;s my second or my third year at this party. I&amp;rsquo;m not the biggest party person. Yeah, no it&amp;rsquo;s super fun, it&amp;rsquo;s been super fun. I&amp;rsquo;ve even had a friend come in from out of town and she&amp;rsquo;s so excited.
Interviewer: Unintelligible
Jorja Fox: I think it&amp;rsquo;s a convergence of a lot of different people who almost never get to see each other. That&amp;rsquo;s number one. And because so many people are coming out tomorrow night anywhere, they&amp;rsquo;re here, they&amp;rsquo;re getting ready, they&amp;rsquo;re excited, they&amp;rsquo;re adrenaline is high.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EW</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2008/ew-06/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2008/ew-06/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
Question: So, you are one of the lucky privileged people who got to see the premiere of &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; early. What is the deal with Grissom-Sara? All of these interviews and articles make it sound like their relationship is in huge amounts of trouble. &amp;#8212; Sarah
Ausiello: I didn&amp;rsquo;t see any signs of trouble in the first episode, but the hour isn&amp;rsquo;t really about them; it&amp;rsquo;s about Warrick. If anything, the one significant scene they &amp;ldquo;do&amp;rdquo; share in the Oct.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Antelope Valley Press (08 September 2008)</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2008/antelope-valley-press/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2008/antelope-valley-press/</guid>
      <description>The well-heeled wore their compassion on their designer threads as hundreds of animal lovers turned out Saturday evening for a star-studded gala at the Animal Acres farm animal sanctuary.
Celebrities such as actors James Cromwell, Jorja Fox, John Schneider, Marc Vann and Alicia Silverstone were among the approximately 300 people who mingled with the sanctuary&amp;rsquo;s 150 cows, pigs, goats, turkeys and chickens for an evening of vegan food, music and entertainment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EW.com</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2008/ew-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2008/ew-01/</guid>
      <description>Fall TV preview: &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; &amp;#8212; How the crime procedural will solve murders without its &amp;ldquo;King,&amp;rdquo; William Peterson
[&amp;hellip;]
Lauren Lee Smith (&amp;ldquo;The L Word&amp;rdquo;) will also join the cast in episode 3 as a young and sarcastic &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; named Riley Adams. But perhaps the most noteworthy season 9 addition is a blast from the past. Jorja Fox &amp;ndash; whose character, Sara Sidle, walked out on both her job and her engagement to Gil &amp;ndash; will return, just 11 months after quitting the show, to help solve the murder of Dourdan&amp;rsquo;s Warrick Brown.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Official CSI Magazine</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2008/csi-magazine-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2008/csi-magazine-2/</guid>
      <description>None of us wanted her to go, least of all Gil Grissom &amp;hellip; so it&amp;rsquo;s great news that Jorja Fox, aka CSI Sara Sidle, will return to reprise her role in season nine. Fox is expected to appear in the first three episodes of the year as the team lay Warrick Brown to rest.
Don&amp;rsquo;t bank on any resolution to the truncated love-story between Grissom and Sara, though. As Fox recently told &amp;ldquo;TV Guide&amp;rdquo;, talking about their feelings isn&amp;rsquo;t something the pair find easy: &amp;ldquo;As a couple, they are a little dysfunctional in some ways, but in other ways, they are fabulous.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Arkansas Tonight</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2008/arkansas-tonight/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2008/arkansas-tonight/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
The whole thing was simply huge, and security was unlike anything I&amp;rsquo;ve ever experienced, even when I visited Guantanamo Bay. Fencing, TSA, you name it, police were everywhere. And it was like walking into a television set. The celebrities were everywhere. Chevy Chase, Jorja Fox (late of CSI), guys from &amp;ldquo;The Daily Show&amp;rdquo; Rosey Grier (in a wheelchair and gray-haired now) Rep. Murtha, Spike Lee, Blizter, and so on and so forth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reed all about Tracie&#39;s Obama adventures</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2008/reed-all-about-tracie-s-obama-adventures/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2008/reed-all-about-tracie-s-obama-adventures/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
I was afraid that our celebration wouldn&amp;rsquo;t feel very intimate in such a huge venue but the architects who put the show together did an amazing job. I wandered around trading pins for the first couple of hours; got a picture taken with Roland Martin and saw Jessie Jackson. Our section was right behind California where Jorja Fox, who plays Sarah Sidle on CSI and the Mayor of San Francisco Gavin Newsom (I got pictures with both).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Erin in Denver </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2008/erin-in-denver/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2008/erin-in-denver/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
We could see all of the speakers w/o any trouble. Lots of celebrities walking up and down our aisle too. Patti and I both got our picture taken with Jorja Fox (Sarah from CSI) and lots of politicos.
[&amp;hellip;]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Guide - The Biz Blog</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2008/tv-guide-06/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2008/tv-guide-06/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
&amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rsquo;s&amp;rdquo; Jorja Fox stopped in for a cold one after she had just purchased a &amp;ldquo;Bark Obama&amp;rdquo; doggie bandana for her 12-year-old boxer. Fox said she&amp;rsquo;s been a Barack Obama fan since she watched his keynote address at the 2004 convention, the moment that sent his political career into the stratosphere. &amp;ldquo;I just feel blessed to be a part of it,&amp;rdquo; she said. &amp;ldquo;Every major historic event in history needs a devoted and excited audience and I get to be one of those people.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blue Hearts </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2008/blue-hearts/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2008/blue-hearts/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
Then, on the way back to the buses, I see actress Jorja Fox who played Sara Sidle on CSI. So fun. I heard there were numerous celebs leaving the CA delegation area, but I think they were probably in some VIP area.
[&amp;hellip;]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Leader-Telegram</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2008/leader-telegram/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2008/leader-telegram/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
We met actress Jorja Fox (Sara on &amp;ldquo;CSI: Crime Scene Investigation&amp;rdquo;), which was exciting. Then it was off to the hotel for just a few minutes of shuteye before we do it all over again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rocky Mountain News</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2008/rocky-mountain-news/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2008/rocky-mountain-news/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
[Nelly], who performed until nearly 2 a.m., drew a few notable celebrities, including Charlize Theron and a bleached-blond Cyndi Lauper, both of whom jived upstairs in the VIP balcony and CSI&amp;rsquo;s Jorja Fox, who looked skinnier than a straw and was smoking up a storm on the well-populated back patio.
[&amp;hellip;]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>43rd Ward Democrats</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2008/43rdwarddemocrats/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2008/43rdwarddemocrats/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
Day Four:
From the Precinct, to the Ward, to the Nation
[&amp;hellip;]
Mary and I stood in line behind State Rep. Barbara Flynn Currie and State Senator Julie Hamos, and it took us a long while to realize that we were standing behind actress Jorja Fox, who is on CSI and played Secret Service Agent Gina Toscano on the West Wing (you know, the one who protected Zoe Barlett). I had to take a picture.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EW</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2008/ew-05/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2008/ew-05/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
Question: Please set the record straight. Is Jorja Fox doing just the season premiere of CSI, or will she be in additional episodes? &amp;ndash; Shane
Ausiello: I don&amp;rsquo;t want to give away the exact number, so let&amp;rsquo;s just say she&amp;rsquo;s doing two more than Gary Dourdan and seven less than William Petersen.
[&amp;hellip;]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>After Ellen</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2008/after-ellen/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2008/after-ellen/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
This season of CSI &amp;ndash; the series&amp;rsquo; ninth &amp;ndash; starts off with a guest appearance by Jorja Fox in the conclusion of a cliffhanger that left Warrick dead. I had the opportunity to watch a screener of the season premiere, and though Jorja does show up, she has little to do with solving the crime, since she&amp;rsquo;s no longer working for the Las Vegas crime lab. The episode, which premieres Oct.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Austin Chronicle</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2008/the-austin-chronicle/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2008/the-austin-chronicle/</guid>
      <description>There was a Fox loose in City Hall last week: Jorja Fox, star of hit TV show CSI: Las Vegas, visited Austin on July 11 to highlight a new report on animal cruelty in traveling circuses.
[&amp;hellip;]
As part of a cross-country tour, ADI spokesperson Fox presented Council Member Lee Leffingwell with a copy of the report. Referring to &amp;ldquo;The ABCD&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ndash; acquisition, brutality, confinement, disposal&amp;rdquo; &amp;ndash; that are an inherent part of the circus industry, she highlighted the success of human-performer-only circuses like Cirque du Soleil and the Chinese State Circus.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EW</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2008/ew-03/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2008/ew-03/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
&amp;ldquo;This will be a year of transition for the show,&amp;rdquo; concedes Mendehlson. &amp;ldquo;We always knew it was coming, and I&amp;rsquo;m glad it didn&amp;rsquo;t come until now.&amp;rdquo; At this point, she&amp;rsquo;s confident that, like Law &amp;amp; Order and ER, CSI is a franchise that can weather such cast shifts. &amp;ldquo;There&amp;rsquo;s never going to be another William Petersen, and there will never be another Jorja Fox,&amp;rdquo; she hastens to add. &amp;ldquo;But we are not out to just replace those actors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Texan</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2008/daily-texan/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2008/daily-texan/</guid>
      <description>Circuses advertise a joyful, colorful form of entertainment, but for circus animals, the shows hold dark promises of horrible living conditions that force animals into miserable confinements, according to animal advocacy groups.
Circuses featuring exotic animals may be banned from Austin in the future after Animal Defenders International, an animal rights group, presented an abuse report to the Austin City Council Friday.
The London-based group asked Austin City Council to ban these circuses in the city of Austin as part of the group&amp;rsquo;s nationwide campaign.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>North Texas E-news</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2008/north-texas-e-news/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2008/north-texas-e-news/</guid>
      <description>This past week at Austin City Hall, councilor Lee Leffingwell met with CSI actress Jorja Fox at a press conference held by Animal Defenders International (ADI) and confirmed he would certainly look in to the issue of circus animal cruelty in Austin.
Leffingwell accepted a letter, report and DVD from Fox, on behalf of the campaigning group, which asks for the city council to consider a ban on animal circuses in light of the evidence presented by ADI&amp;rsquo;s report and undercover footage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AHN</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2008/ahn/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2008/ahn/</guid>
      <description>Jorja Fox&amp;rsquo;s character on &amp;ldquo;CSI: Crime Scene Investigation&amp;rdquo; is known for fighting crime. Now the actress is taking a stand against wrong-doers in real life, too.
Fox, well known for her prominent role as Sara Sidle on the CBS hit, is campaigning against the suffering of circus animals. She will hand deliver copies of a new scientific report on the circus animal abuse to officials at Austin&amp;rsquo;s City Hall on Friday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EW</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2008/ew-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2008/ew-02/</guid>
      <description>Pamela Anderson isn&amp;rsquo;t the only one crackin&amp;rsquo; jokes about Jessica Simpson&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Real Girls Eat Meat&amp;rdquo; T-shirt.
&amp;ldquo;But I think that [T-shirt] phrase can be interpreted in many different ways,&amp;rdquo; quipped CSI star and longtime animal-rights activist Jorja Fox. &amp;ldquo;We should ask Jessica what meat she was referring to, because there are several out there.&amp;rdquo;
But is Fox truly upset over the shirt?
&amp;ldquo;I think Jessica Simpson has every right to her opinion, but I&amp;rsquo;m not offended by it at all, because it was done in jest,&amp;rdquo; Fox assured me earlier today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MSN tv</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2008/msn-tv/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2008/msn-tv/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
Nerdiest Cop: Sara Sidle, &amp;ldquo;CSI: Crime Scene Investigation&amp;rdquo;
You gotta love her: She&amp;rsquo;s dry, supersmart, slightly damaged and obsessed with cadavers. The original &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; isn&amp;rsquo;t what you&amp;rsquo;d call a character-driven show, but Sara Sidle has more personality than all her co-workers combined. Too bad depression got the best of this geek guru. We can only hope for the surprise return of her character &amp;#8212; and, hopefully, no more lab explosions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Parade</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2008/parade/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jul 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2008/parade/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
Q Will actress Jorja Fox ever return to &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo;?&amp;ndash;Betty Rudder, Mascot, Tenn.
A We&amp;rsquo;ve received dozens of letters like yours since Fox left &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; in November and told us she needed a break from the daily grind. She then turned down several TV movies to focus on producing a musical about the late singer Dusty Springfield, which was staged in L.A. earlier this year. But Jorja, who&amp;rsquo;ll turn 40 this week, always hoped to return to &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo;, and fans will be thrilled to learn that she&amp;rsquo;ll be back on the season premiere this fall.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Buddy TV</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2008/buddy-tv-03/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2008/buddy-tv-03/</guid>
      <description>Jorja Fox left CSI last November, leaving fans with a promise that it wouldn&amp;rsquo;t be the last time they would see her character Sara Sidle.&amp;nbsp; For seven months now, the 39-year-old actress has savored the &amp;ldquo;break from the commitment of a weekly television series.&amp;rdquo;&amp;nbsp; Although not yet ready to do a new television show, she&amp;rsquo;s ready to hold up to the end of her bargain as she returns for the ninth season of CSI.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Guide Magazine</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2008/tv-guide-05/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2008/tv-guide-05/</guid>
      <description>1 EXCLUSIVE INTERVIEW!
Jorja&amp;rsquo;s Coming Back to &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo;
When Jorja Fox left &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; last fall, producers promised it wouldn&amp;rsquo;t be the last fans would see of her. They&amp;rsquo;ll hold up their end of the bargain when the actress&amp;rsquo; Sara returns to the crime drama for it&amp;rsquo;s third episode next season. &amp;ldquo;It involves an old friend of Sara&amp;rsquo;s who has to confront a [life or] death situation with his wife,&amp;rdquo; she teases.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Guide Magazine</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2008/tv-guide-04/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jun 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2008/tv-guide-04/</guid>
      <description>Inside sources reveal top secrets about the season&amp;rsquo;s biggest burning questions
[&amp;hellip;]
Why did CSI&amp;rsquo;s Warrick have to die (and was the story line influenced by Gary Dourdan&amp;rsquo;s real-life troubles)?
&amp;ldquo;Executive Producer Carol Mendelsohn says&amp;rdquo;: We thought that if we ever lost Warrick [Dourdan], this was the way he would go. Warrick&amp;rsquo;s a local guy. The only family he had was Grissom [William Petersen] and the team, so this was not a guy who was going to leave Las Vegas or CSI.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Buddy TV</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2008/buddy-tv-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2008/buddy-tv-02/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; fans have not seen the last of Sara Sidle. In fact, the time has come for fans to welcome one of the key players of the forensic drama, Jorja Fox, whose character left the series in the season 7 episode &amp;ldquo;Goodbye and Good Luck&amp;rdquo; where she had to go face the ghost of her past.
According to &amp;ldquo;TV Guide&amp;rdquo;, the 39-year-old actress has just inked a deal to return for &amp;ldquo;CSI**s ninth season premiere next fall.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Guide - Ausiello Report</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2008/tv-guide-03/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2008/tv-guide-03/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; boss Carol Mendelsohn wasn&amp;rsquo;t pulling my leg when she told me last October that we haven&amp;rsquo;t seen the last of Sara Sidle. Sources confirm that Jorja Fox has inked a deal to return for the show&amp;rsquo;s ninth-season premiere next fall.
Specifics of her comeback are being kept under lock and key, but my &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; mole assures me that she &amp;ldquo;won&amp;rsquo;t be appearing in a flashback.&amp;rdquo; The likely scenario has Sara returning to Vegas to shag Grissom mourn ex-colleague Warrick, who was shot (and presumably) killed in last week&amp;rsquo;s finale.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Squad</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2008/tv-squad/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2008/tv-squad/</guid>
      <description>When Sara left &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo;, driving out of Las Vegas on her way to who knows what, he left behind a brokenhearted Gil Grissom. The producers of &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; were wise to keep the door open for the character to return, and that&amp;rsquo;s just what&amp;rsquo;s happening &amp;#8212; at least for one show. According to &amp;ldquo;TV Guide**s Michael Ausiello, Jorja Fox will be in the season premiere of &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo;. Oh, and she won&amp;rsquo;t be the only former cast mate on the show; so will Gary Dourdan as Warrick.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Celebrity Cafe</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2008/the-celebrity-cafe/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2008/the-celebrity-cafe/</guid>
      <description>SPOILER ALERT
Jorja Fox, who plays Sara on the original &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo;, will return for at least the show&amp;rsquo;s ninth season premiere next fall, according to the show&amp;rsquo;s boss, Carol Mendelsohn.
The news comes via &amp;ldquo;TV Guide**s Michael Ausiello, who says that Fox&amp;rsquo;s character won&amp;rsquo;t be in a flashback, but the most likely scenario would be Sara returning to Vegas to mourn the death of ex-colleague Warrick. Who, of course, was shot and (presumably) killed in last week&amp;rsquo;s season finale.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Official CSI Magazine</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2008/csi-magazine-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2008/csi-magazine-1/</guid>
      <description>In her eight years working the Las Vegas graveyard shift, Sara Sidle faced more than her fair share of heartache, which eventually resulted in her leaving Sin City for good. Actress Jorja Fox recalls her time on CSI: Crime Scene Investigation, and reveals why it was the right moment for her to leave the show.
&amp;#8212;-
When it comes to Sara Sidle, it&amp;rsquo;s definitely a case of gone but not forgotten for the show&amp;rsquo;s millions of fans.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Access Hollywood </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2008/access-hollywood/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2008/access-hollywood/</guid>
      <description>Interviewer: What are some tips you have to going green?
Jorja Fox: Going green? Oh, wow, I love it. Well, you know, start with the simple stuff. There&amp;rsquo;s some very simple things you can do. Recycling, obviously, I think we&amp;rsquo;re all doing that in California. I&amp;rsquo;m amazed. I go visit some of my family members across the country, and they don&amp;rsquo;t have recycling centers yet. And most of them are doing it themselves anyway.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Orangutan Outreach</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2008/orangutan-outreach/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2008/orangutan-outreach/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
Public Service Announcements (PSAs)
We spent a few days this past January in sunny California filming our first set of Public Service Announcements (PSAs). We would like to personally thank the stars, Tatjana Patitz and Jorja Fox, who graciously volunteered their time and talents to our cause, as well as Jim Denault for offering to film the PSAs. We&amp;rsquo;d also like to thank Hayley Moss, without whom it never would have happened.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AFP Google News</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2008/afp-google-news/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2008/afp-google-news/</guid>
      <description>About 30 Hollywood celebrities will kick off a campaign Thursday to seek the release of Myanmar&amp;rsquo;s democracy icon Aung San Suu Kyi and push for freedom in the military-ruled nation.
[&amp;hellip;]
In another video clip, two stars from the popular CSI television show, Eric Szmanda and Jorja Fox, play a game called &amp;ldquo;forced labor&amp;rdquo; using cards with graphic pictures of alleged abuses in Myanmar.
[&amp;hellip;]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CSI: Crime Scene Investigatio News</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2008/sspeedlecsi/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2008/sspeedlecsi/</guid>
      <description>Jorja Fox, actress that played Sara Sidle and that said GoodBye of CSI in the episode &amp;ldquo;GoodBye &amp;amp; Good Luck&amp;rdquo; visit Guanacaste, Costa Rica in Central American, for a week. The actress stay in the hotel Cala Luna, in the beach Langosta of Tamarindo, when she share with the workers of the company and the rest of the people in the hotel, inform a comiunicate to press from Luis Castrillo, from Servicios Periodisticos Globales (SPG) S.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VIVA nacion.com</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2008/viva-nacion-com/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2008/viva-nacion-com/</guid>
      <description>Translated from Spanish
**In Guanacaste.&amp;rdquo; Jorja Fox, the actress who portrays Sara [Sidle] in the successful television series &amp;ldquo;CSI Las Vegas&amp;rdquo;, visited the beaches of Guanacaste for during one week.
This actress stayed in the hotel Cala Luna, along the beach Langosta de Tamarindo, where she spent time with the hotel&amp;rsquo;s concierge and with the rest of the guests, according to an official press notice from Luis Castrillo Marín, Global News Services (SPG) S.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Guide</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2008/tv-guide-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2008/tv-guide-01/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
Question: What happened to Catherine finding the picture of Grissom and Sara that was teased all week? That scene sure wasn&amp;rsquo;t in the &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; I watched on Thursday! — Kathy
Ausiello: Good question — let&amp;rsquo;s ask exec producer Carol Mendelsohn. &amp;ldquo;The scene where Catherine finds Sara&amp;rsquo;s picture on Grissom&amp;rsquo;s fridge is really fun. But the paradox of writing a procedural is that sometimes even our favorite scenes (scenes that show the personal lives of our CSIs) aren&amp;rsquo;t required by the narrative.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Guide</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2008/tv-guide-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2008/tv-guide-02/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;] Carita writes &amp;#8216;Is Jorja Fox returning to &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo;?&amp;rsquo; Well, let&amp;rsquo;s examine the evidence, Carita. Last fall, on the eve of Fox&amp;rsquo;s swan song, executive producer Carol Mendhelson said quote &amp;ldquo;Fans will not have seen the last of Sarah Sidle &amp;#8212; nor will Grissom.&amp;rdquo; unquote. Cut to last Thursday, Sara&amp;rsquo;s spirit loomed large in an episode that confirmed what we all knew: Grissom is far from over his ex-partner. Sure sounds like a Sara comeback is imminent right?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The TV Guide</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2008/the-tv-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2008/the-tv-guide/</guid>
      <description>For eight seasons of &amp;ldquo;CSI: Crime Scene Investigation&amp;rdquo;, William Petersen has played Gil Grissom [&amp;hellip;] The 55-year-old theater veteran talks to &amp;ldquo;TV Guide&amp;rdquo; about the hit show, his character and what happens now co-star Jorja Fox has left.
[&amp;hellip;]
What did you think of [Grissom&amp;rsquo;s] relationship with Sara (Jorja Fox)?
It&amp;rsquo;s really worked for Jorja Fox and me to play Sara Sidle and Grissom and have this sort of adult relationship.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creators.com</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2008/creators.com/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2008/creators.com/</guid>
      <description>Ask Stacy
DEAR STACY: Why did Jorja Fox leave her role as Sara Sidle on &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo;? This saddens many of us. &amp;ndash; Beverly L., North Bergen, N.J.
DEAR BEVERLY: Fox left the show last year, saying she wanted a break from the rigors of weekly TV production. Her departure came after years of drama over her status with the show. She and fellow costar George Eads were fired &amp;ndash; temporarily &amp;ndash; back in &amp;lsquo;04, when their contract renegotiations went sour.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Miami Herald</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2008/miami-herald/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2008/miami-herald/</guid>
      <description>The catholic tastes of TV audiences shouldn&amp;rsquo;t have come as a blinding epiphany to anyone, says Robert Thompson, who runs the Center for the Study of Popular Television at Syracuse University.
&amp;ldquo;We make a mistake when we think the only people we want to watch on TV or in movies are people in our own demographic,&amp;rdquo; Thompson says. &amp;ldquo;Think of all little kids&amp;rsquo; shows in the &amp;lsquo;50s and &amp;lsquo;60s that starred frazzled old miners or sailors or whatever&amp;hellip; .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pittsburgh Tribune-Review</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2008/pittsburgh-tribune-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2008/pittsburgh-tribune-review/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
But [Marg Helgenberger]&amp;rsquo;s not about to abandon her &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; team anytime soon, as former co-star Jorja Fox did last year. Of Fox&amp;rsquo;s decision to leave, Helgenberger says, &amp;ldquo;I know she considered not wanting to forget to have a baby. And I think she kind of wanted a break from the heinous crimes our show deals with.&amp;rdquo;
The women have maintained an off-screen friendship. Last month, the two caught up at L.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Showbuzz</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2008/the-showbuzz/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2008/the-showbuzz/</guid>
      <description>Networks Pull Out All The Stops To Entice Viewers Back To Their TV Sets
[&amp;hellip;]
Fans of &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; will also learn about why Sarah Sidle (Jorja Fox) departed.
People are intrigued,&amp;rdquo; said [Entertainment Weekly&amp;rsquo;s Dalton] Ross. &amp;ldquo;We&amp;rsquo;re going to get answers in the first episode back as to why she left the show.&amp;rdquo;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pride Source</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2008/pride-source/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Mar 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2008/pride-source/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
I didn&amp;rsquo;t get to tell you, but I recently went with Jenifer Lewis to LA&amp;rsquo;s Gay and Lesbian Center to see &amp;ldquo;Stay Forever: The Life and Music of Dusty Springfield,&amp;rdquo; which was co-produced by Jorja Fox. Due to the limitations of this presentation, certain aspects of the show couldn&amp;rsquo;t be fleshed out &amp;lt;&amp;gt; making it somewhat unclear whether this was an actual play or a very good lounge act. What is undeniable is that Kristen Holly Smith is a goldmine of talent and knowledge (she co-wrote the piece).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CSI Files</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2008/csi-files/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2008/csi-files/</guid>
      <description>Allen MacDonald has been with &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; since the show&amp;rsquo;s third season. He&amp;rsquo;s climbed the ranks from writers&amp;rsquo; assistant to staff writer and has had a hand in some of the most significant episodes of the last few seasons, including &amp;ldquo;Dead Doll&amp;rdquo; and Goodbye and Good Luck&amp;rdquo;, which saw the exit of the first regular character to leave the show, Sara Sidle. Though busy at work for an episode for the show&amp;rsquo;s eighth season following the hundred day WGA strike, MacDonald took the time to discuss the current season and his career at &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; with CSI Files.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creators Syndicate</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2008/creators-syndicate/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2008/creators-syndicate/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
DEAR STACY: Is Jorja Fox going to do a different series now that she&amp;rsquo;s no longer on &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo;? &amp;ndash; L.F., Westbury, N.Y.
DEAR L.F.: The actress has no such plans at this time and has said she&amp;rsquo;s not going to even think of more regular series work for a while &amp;ndash; though she is open to the idea of returning to &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; as a guest star.
[&amp;hellip;]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Defamer (7 March 2008)</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2008/defamer/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2008/defamer/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
*Last Saturday (Mar 2) saw Jorja Fox with 3 non-celeb friends (2 guys and a girl) buying wine a bit after 10pm at CapNCork on Hillhurst in Los Feliz. She was in jeans, green shirt and white vest, hair down, no makeup and looking very casual but easily recognizable.
[&amp;hellip;]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The UkuLady&#39;s UkulUniverse </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2008/the-ukulady-s-ukuluniverse/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2008/the-ukulady-s-ukuluniverse/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
t was quite the celebrity day in Hollywood today. I just barely saved myself from looking like a total jackass to CSI star, Jorja Fox. Here&amp;rsquo;s the scoop: Being &amp;ldquo;on deck&amp;rdquo; at my voiceover agency to audition, means lingering my the desks of the assistants, who are awesome. I enjoy chit chat with the Tallest-Assistant-In-The-World, Jeff, who is almost 7 feet and hilarious. On Jeff&amp;rsquo;s desk last week, was a notice for a show at the LBGT Center, produced by Jorja Fox.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mirror</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2008/mirror/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Feb 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2008/mirror/</guid>
      <description>If ever a TV couple shared some great chemistry it&amp;rsquo;s Sara Sidle and Gil Grissom.
But after years of successfully concealing their relationship from their colleagues - and from us - no sooner is the cat out of the bag, than Sara&amp;rsquo;s off.
So now I&amp;rsquo;m wondering if maybe it was just the secrecy that was the real attraction for Sara, and the thought of being able to hold hands with Gil in the CSI canteen and drive in to work together each day is just too mundane for words.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Buddy TV</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2008/buddy-tv-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Feb 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2008/buddy-tv-01/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
Speaking of &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo;, former regular cast member Jorja Fox is now able to enjoy doing the other things she was raring to sink her teeth into when she decided to leave the show earlier this season. Since quitting as CSI Sara Sidle, Fox has had the opportunity to work on one of her dream projects.
&amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m producing a musical about the life and music of Dusty Springfield called &amp;ldquo;Stay Forever&amp;rdquo; in Los Angeles at the Renberg theater,&amp;rdquo; Fox told Variety.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Variety</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2008/variety/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Feb 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2008/variety/</guid>
      <description>Jorja Fox, co-producer of &amp;ldquo;Stay Together: The Life and Music of Dusty Springfield,&amp;rdquo; which opens on Feb. 7
**Book I&amp;rsquo;m reading: **
&amp;ldquo;Blink&amp;rdquo; by Malcolm Gladwell. I&amp;rsquo;m reading it in a flash.
**Total number of books I own: **
I don&amp;rsquo;t really like to collect stuff. I try to pass them on. That line also hides the evidence that I don&amp;rsquo;t really read that much&amp;hellip;
**Last film I saw: **</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SpinDaily </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2008/spindaily/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Feb 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2008/spindaily/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
Jorja Fox: You get &amp;ndash; you come into the theater and you&amp;rsquo;re like &amp;ldquo;Ah, I know that one song, it&amp;rsquo;ll be great&amp;rsquo; Never mind what an amazing colorful story she had, in what an amazing colorful times. Then you get in there and you actually know the songs, and you&amp;rsquo;re like &amp;ldquo;Oh wow!&amp;rsquo;
[&amp;hellip;]
Jorja Fox: It&amp;rsquo;s amazing to me that this story hasn&amp;rsquo;t been told before, 500 times already.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lesbian News</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2008/lesbian-news/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2008/lesbian-news/</guid>
      <description>Jorja Fox and Kirsten Holly Smith talk about the life and music of Dusty Springfield.
For millions the music and life of Dusty Springfield has grand significance. More specifically, as a woman who was producing music in the man&amp;rsquo;s world of music making, a performer who professionally protested Apartheid (before it was de rigueur) and a household name who came out of the closet, Springfield&amp;rsquo;s music and life meant much more to specific groups such as women, blacks and gays.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Zealand TV Guide (February 2008)</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2008/new-zealand-tv-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2008/new-zealand-tv-guide/</guid>
      <description>[&amp;hellip;]
NZTVG: How did you feel about Jorja Fox (who plays Sara Sidle) leaving the show this season?
Marg Helgenberger: We only shot a couple of episodes more after she left but it was sad. Everybody reacted very differently and you don&amp;rsquo;t even really think about it until you have the party and it&amp;rsquo;s your last day and everyone shows up. Then it becomes the big, emotional thing. It hit some people really hard that day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KTLA Morning Show </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2008/ktla-morning-show/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jan 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2008/ktla-morning-show/</guid>
      <description>Interviewer: All right, we&amp;rsquo;re gonna talk all about this play and everything Jorja related, but you, you made sort of a conscious decision - you know, you&amp;rsquo;ve been on this very successful show, and then, you left. What, what, what &amp;ndash; was that a real soul search, or was it &amp;ldquo;gee, it&amp;rsquo;s time&amp;rdquo;?
Jorja Fox: Oh, yeah. Yes, yeah, very very much. It was harder to leave than it was to stay, for sure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ian Harvie Show </title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2008/ian-harvie-show/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jan 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2008/ian-harvie-show/</guid>
      <description>Jorja Fox: Ten and a half years of deaths -
Ian Harvie: Yes
Jorja Fox: - violence -
Ian Harvie: What is it with you -
Jorja Fox: I just had it of dead bodies -
Ian Harvie: Yeah, seriously!
Jorja Fox: I mean I&amp;rsquo;ve just had it.
Ian Harvie: Seriously, what is it with you and these roles, like these really hard, like, and the dialog is like really hard too!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LesbiaNataion</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2008/lesbianation/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2008/lesbianation/</guid>
      <description>Most Loved Women of 2007 [&amp;hellip;] Besides Hargitay and Morris, hot cops on our list for your voting pleasure include CSI&amp;rsquo;s natural beauty and PETA advocate Jorja Fox.
[&amp;hellip;]
 3 - Jorja Fox :List Veteran
:Last 5
:Best 3  Since she starred on ER as lesbian medical intern Maggie Doyle, we&amp;rsquo;ve had Jorja Fox on our minds. An outspoken vegetarian and PETA supporter, Jorja&amp;rsquo;s only upped her appeal as troubled investigator Sara Sidle on CSI: Crime Scene Investigation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>News Articles (2008)</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2008/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/news/2008/</guid>
      <description>Date Source    January 01 LesbiaNataion   February 01 Lesbian News   February 01 New Zealand TV Guide (February 2008)   February 06 Variety   February 14 Buddy TV   February 19 Mirror   February 28 The UkuLady&amp;#39;s UkulUniverse    March 07 Defamer (7 March 2008)   March 09 Creators Syndicate   March 10 CSI Files   March 20 Pride Source   March 24 The Showbuzz   March 26 Pittsburgh Tribune-Review   March 30 Miami Herald   April 04 Creators.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>