<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Biographies on Fans of Le Fox Library</title>
    <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/categories/biographies/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Biographies on Fans of Le Fox Library</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://jorjafox.net/library/categories/biographies/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>All Movie Guide Biography</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/biographies/allmovieguide/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/biographies/allmovieguide/</guid>
      <description>The lithe and attractive brunette American actress Jorja Fox entered the public eye in the late &amp;lsquo;90s and early 2000s, given her involvement as a recurrent cast member in three consecutive, top-ranked U.S. television series: ER (1994), The West Wing (1999), and CSI: Crime Scene Investigation (2000). Fox is perhaps most familiar to fans of CSI, appearing in well over 150 episodes and numerous seasons.
Born Jorja-An Fox on July 7, 1968, in New York, NY, but raised in Melbourne Beach, FL, Fox moved back to Manhattan in her teens and began a modeling career after winning a local modeling contest, then subsequently enrolled as a drama student at the Lee Strasberg Institute, where she studied acting under the aegis of legendary actor William Hickey (Prizzi&amp;rsquo;s Honor, Forget Paris).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Biography</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/biographies/main/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/biographies/main/</guid>
      <description> Jorja Fox is an actress, producer, humanitarian, activist and environmentalist. She has been seen on such hit TV shows as CSI: Crime Scene Investigation, ER, The West Wing and Law &amp;amp; Order, as well as indie movies like Memento and Food for the Heart. She has been in numerous other television shows and movies.
Vital Statistics  Birth Name: Jorja-An Fox Nicknames: Jorja, Jorj, Jorjan, Horha (the Spanish pronunciation of her name, used by her &amp;ldquo;CSI Miami&amp;rdquo; friend Emily Procter) Date of Birth: 07 July 1968 Place of Birth: New York City, NY (raised in Melbourne Beach, FL) Eye Color: Brown Hair Color: Brown Height: 5&amp;rsquo;9&amp;rdquo; Pets: Bexar (dog - adopted 2012)  Other Biographies </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CBS Biography</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/biographies/cbs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/biographies/cbs/</guid>
      <description>Fox&amp;rsquo;s television credits include &amp;ldquo;ER,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;West Wing,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;Law and Order,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;Ellen&amp;rdquo; and, most recently, &amp;ldquo;Drop Dead Diva.&amp;rdquo; In addition to television, her film work includes &amp;ldquo;Memento,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;How to Make the Cruelest Month,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;The Kill-Off,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;Forever Fabulous&amp;rdquo; and Down with the Joneses.&amp;rdquo;
A devoted wildlife advocate, Fox recently produced the documentary film &amp;ldquo;How I Became an Elephant.&amp;rdquo; The film is about one young girl&amp;rsquo;s mission to save the elephants, as she travels to south East Asia to work with her hero The Elephant Lady and shows how everyone can make a difference.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Forever Fabulous Biography</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/biographies/forever-fabulous/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/biographies/forever-fabulous/</guid>
      <description>Jorja Fox (Liz) co-stars in the new CBS breakout series C.S.I.: CRIME SCENE INVESTIGATION. She has also been featured as a Secret Service agent on NBC&amp;rsquo;s popular, Emmy-winning series THE WEST WING. She played the recurring role of Doyle on the NBC&amp;rsquo;s long-running ER, where she happily appeared for a number of seasons. She has made several made-for-TV films and mini-series including HOUSE OF FRANKENSTEIN, DEAD DRUNK and SUMMER STORIES. Film credits include MEMENTO, THE JERKY BOYS, THE HUNGRY BACHELORS&amp;rsquo; CLUB, VELOCITY TRAP, HOW TO MAKE THE CRUELEST MONTH, ALCHEMY, DEAD FUNNY, HAPPY HELL NIGHT and KILL OFF.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gist TV Biography</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/biographies/gist-tv/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/biographies/gist-tv/</guid>
      <description>Birthplace: Melbourne Beach, Florida Date of Birth: 07/07/1968  The Gist Sara Sidle on C.S.I.: Crime Scene Investigation Special Agent Gina Tuscano on The West Wing
Jorja Fox first began as a model. When she was sixteen, she had signed a modeling contract, and had moved to New York. Soon after, she was cast in her first film, The Kill Off.
A few small appearances here and there in films like The Jerky Boys led her to a full time position as Dr.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hollywood.com Biography</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/biographies/hollywood.com/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/biographies/hollywood.com/</guid>
      <description>Adept at playing smart, strong women, this former teen model segued to acting with guest spots in after-school specials and evening dramas. A comely, gap-toothed brunette whose good looks can&amp;rsquo;t obscure her intelligence or hard-nosed attitude, Fox became a small-screen star with a trio of plum prime-time parts. In the mid-&amp;lsquo;90s she had a recurring role as a blunt doctor on ER who turned out to be a lesbian and — like Fox — a vegetarian.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hungry Bachelors Club Biography</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/biographies/hungry-bachelors-club/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/biographies/hungry-bachelors-club/</guid>
      <description>Note: This biography was released before The Hungry Bachelors Club was renamed.
Jorja Fox (Delmar Youngblood) is the lead in THE HUNGRY BACHELORS CLUB, playing a single mother with an unusual offer that may make her dreams come true. She had a recurring role as Dr. Maggie Doyle on NBC&amp;rsquo;s hit series ER. Her television credits also include guest leads on Law and Order and most recently, a pilot for Barry Levinson and Tom Fontana, Flesh and Blood.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IMDb Biography</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/biographies/imdb/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/biographies/imdb/</guid>
      <description>Jorja Fox has become a familiar face by playing major roles in three of the most successful television dramas in history: ER (1994), The West Wing (1999) and CSI: Crime Scene Investigation (2000).
As a teenager, Fox had a career as a fashion model. She then turned to formal study of the acting craft at the Lee Strasberg Institute in New York, as well as under the tutelage of veteran actor William Hickey at HB Studios.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Official Biography</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/biographies/official/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/biographies/official/</guid>
      <description>With a variety of memorable roles filling up her resume, it would not be cliched for one to hum a few bars of &amp;ldquo;Jorja On My Mind.&amp;rdquo; Actress JORJA FOX currently stars on the highest-ranked drama of the new television season, CSI: Crime Scene Investigation for CBS. Fox stars as a member of the autopsy team who heads-up the gritty drama series that is executive produced by Jerry Bruckheimer.
No stranger to television, Fox also stared on NBC&amp;rsquo;s top-rated series ER as resident intern Dr.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TVGuide.com Biography</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/biographies/tvguide.com/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/biographies/tvguide.com/</guid>
      <description>Birth Name: Jorja-An Fox
 Birth Place: New York, NY
 Date of Birth / Zodiac Sign: 07/07/1968, Cancer
 Profession: Actor  A former teen model who segued to acting with guest spots in after-school specials and evening dramas, Fox became a small-screen star with a trio of plum prime-time parts. In the mid-&amp;lsquo;90s she had a recurring role as a blunt doctor on ER&amp;nbsp;who turned out to be a lesbian and â&amp;ndash; like Fox &amp;ndash; a vegetarian.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Velocity Trap Biography</title>
      <link>https://jorjafox.net/library/biographies/velocity-trap/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jorjafox.net/library/biographies/velocity-trap/</guid>
      <description>Jorja was born in New York City to French Canadian immigrant parents. When she was three, the family relocated to a small costal town in Florida. Raised on a narrow barrier island, Jorja has a deep affinity for all things oceanic, big skies, and Jimmy Buffet. Jorja began her acting career at the age of five, when she landed the coveted role of the &amp;#8216;Rooster&amp;rsquo; in the children&amp;rsquo;s classic &amp;ldquo;Chicken Little.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>