<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>2005 on JFO Library</title>
    <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/tags/2005/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 2005 on JFO Library</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2005 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://jorjafox.net/library/tags/2005/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Guide</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2005/tv-guide-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2005/tv-guide-4/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;D | Double-Ups&lt;/strong&gt; Ever find yourself puzzled (or elated) when a particular &lt;em&gt;CSI&lt;/em&gt; episode features, say, only Grissom (William Petersen) and Nick (George Eads), and is followed the next week by one about only Sara (Jorja Fox) and Catherine (Helgenberger)? Such character divisions occasionally happen because of a production double-up &amp;#8212; when the show&amp;rsquo;s scheduling demands require the series to shoot two episodes simultaneously.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;X | *X-Files, The&lt;/strong&gt;* How was the groundbreaking paranormal series &lt;em&gt;CSI&lt;/em&gt;&amp;rsquo;s most kindred stylistic spirit? It was a science-oriented procedural drama with high production values, a mordant sense of humor and a painfully repressed romance (Mulder and Scully, meet Grissom and Sara). Also remarkable is the number of actors who&amp;rsquo;ve guest-starred on both. To wit: Nicholas Lea, Doug Hutchinson, Nick Chinlund, Xander Berkley, Krista Allen, Jeremy Roberts, Timothy Carhary and Michael Silver, to name a few.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Z | Zamboni&lt;/strong&gt; The gliding, boxlike machine that clean and smooth ice-skating rinks. In Season 2&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Primum Non Nocere,&amp;rdquo; one Zamboni holds a key piece of evidence in the death of a hockey player. Ever the hopeless romantic, Grissom opines in an intimate moment with Sara: &amp;ldquo;There are three things people love to stare at: a rippling stream, a sunset and a Zamboni going around and around.&amp;rdquo; Sigh&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Zone</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2005/tv-zone/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2005/tv-zone/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;As CSI&amp;rsquo;s Sara Sidle, she has her hands full of blood, bugs and rotting parts &amp;#8212; but Fox&amp;rsquo;s passion for acting gives her the stomach to cope, as she explains to Jenny.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;O&lt;/strong&gt;ver the last five years, CSI has been responsible for some of TV&amp;rsquo;s goriest scenes. From bone cracking autopsies to flesh piercing special effects and horrific murders, there.s no holding back when it comes to blood and guts. Yet star Jorja Fox, who plays Sara Sidle, admits that after five years the realistic looking bodies can still ruin her stomach.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m especially queasy and weak and sensitive to it,&amp;rdquo; she says. &amp;ldquo;it&amp;rsquo;s not just how gross and graphic it is, but it&amp;rsquo;s the way in which it happened, that somebody horribly killed someone else. And God forbid we&amp;rsquo;re doing a case that&amp;rsquo;s based on a real story, that adds a whole other dimension to how bad I feel. It&amp;rsquo;s like the violence of the crime is more repulsive to me than the graphicness of whatever we&amp;rsquo;re showing. So it&amp;rsquo;s not just peeling a face back in a coroner&amp;rsquo;s office, far grosser to me is how the person got to be there.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If the blood isn&amp;rsquo;t bad enough then there&amp;rsquo;s always the bugs. When actors say never act with children or animals, no one mentions insects, but with the crucial clue of many of the show&amp;rsquo;s cases being the bugs at the crime scene the cast have had to cope with plenty of creepy crawly encounters.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;We&amp;rsquo;ve lost the evidence a lot,&amp;rdquo; says Fox. &amp;ldquo;Bugs are tough, they&amp;rsquo;re really hard to catch and you&amp;rsquo;re trying not to hurt them at the same time. And they come with their own wrangler so there&amp;rsquo;s no harming of insects on this show.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;T&lt;/strong&gt;he 37 year old actress was already a familiar face on TV when CSI gave her a job. She&amp;rsquo;d had a recurring role as Dr. Maggie Doyle on ER, then she&amp;rsquo;d become one of President Bartlet&amp;rsquo;s secret service bodyguards in The West Wing, while staring in the critically acclaimed movie, Memento. Fox had started off as a model after being talent spotted in a shopping mall near her Florida home, but her passion for acting and stature in the industry now means she can work with her own company, Honeypot Productions alongside CSI. &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m going to be finishing my ninth consecutive year on network television in the States and that&amp;rsquo;s a really, really good run for anyone.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But that run almost came to an end at the start of the last season, as she faced unemployment after being temporarily sacked from CSI.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At first I though it was kind of a joke but then, after four or five days, I started to realize it was serious,&amp;rdquo; she says. &amp;ldquo;I think I probably feel a lot less safe about anything having to do with a show, and I think that&amp;rsquo;s probably a good thing, I mean change is inevitable in life. But the rest of what happened was half of the cast was working with a pay raise, and half of the cast was not. I think that&amp;rsquo;s not necessarily good for anybody on the show.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;F&lt;/strong&gt;ox&amp;rsquo;s character has faced a tough time on the show as Sara has battled booze alongside a king-sized crush on her boss Gil Grissom. They are some of the few scant insights that have been allowed into her character&amp;rsquo;s personal life, but Fox believes part of the appeal of the show is based on the old fashioned idea of good against bad that&amp;rsquo;s the foundation of the storylines.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;The CSIs go out there and really try and make peace and make truth using their minds and their hearts, you know. It&amp;rsquo;s like an outlaw sort of gunslinger idea without the gun,&amp;rdquo; she muses.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;I think we will go back to very story-driven CSIs at the start of the new season because all the characters, almost everybody on the show, went through something deeply personal and sort of painful last year. So we&amp;rsquo;ll wipe that out for a while and probably do a lot of blowing things up and exciting chase scenes.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But that doesn&amp;rsquo;t mean the &amp;lsquo;Will they - won&amp;rsquo;t they?&amp;rsquo; romance between Sara and Grissom is off the agenda entirely. &amp;ldquo;I think the ball is in Grissom&amp;rsquo;s court at the moment,&amp;rdquo; says Fox. &amp;ldquo;I think that Sara&amp;rsquo;s made a decision that she&amp;rsquo;s gonna make. She chased him for about two seasons. I think there&amp;rsquo;s definitely a possibility that something might happen between the two of them before it&amp;rsquo;s all over. But she&amp;rsquo;s so smart, she&amp;rsquo;s so good at the job. But when it comes to matters of the heart, or of friends or personal life, she&amp;rsquo;s completely awkward and uneducated.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Like the other members of the original CSI cast, Fox admits she had reservations about the two spin-off series. With both Miami and New York competing for the viewers hears all the Las Vegas crew expressed doubts about the wisdom of created three rival CSIs. But Fox admits that, despite their fears, all the series seem to have found their own niche.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;I think if you offer somebody a really great piece of cake, they&amp;rsquo;re going to take it. But then if they&amp;rsquo;re offered cake every day, you might start to want ice cream. I may have wished, you know, that there weren&amp;rsquo;t any spin-offs of CSI but I think that the shows have been able to sort of find their own legs.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Newswire</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2005/u-s/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2005/u-s/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;On Nov. 19, Animal Acres, LA&amp;rsquo;s newly opened farm animal sanctuary, will celebrate Thanksgiving with a unique celebration called the &amp;ldquo;Feed A Turkey Ceremony&amp;rdquo; at the sanctuary in Acton, Calif.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At noon, special guests actresses Daryl Hannah and Jorja Fox (from the No. 1 hit television show CSI) will be helping feed the turkeys and speaking about the need to protect ALL animals from cruelty and neglect. Daryl and Jorja, who are vegetarians, are LA&amp;rsquo;s leading celebrity advocates for animals, and their support of Animal Acres is opening hearts and minds to the plight of turkeys and other farm animals.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From noon to 4 p.m., guests will be able to enjoy tours of the sanctuary featuring three newly rescued baby pigs alongside the children&amp;rsquo;s&amp;rsquo; favorite baby pig, Bagel. At 1:30 p.m. guests will gather to actually hand feed the turkeys. This will be followed by a delicious vegetarian thanksgiving meal created by LA restaurant Native Foods, one of LA&amp;rsquo;s favorite vegetarian restaurants, served in the sanctuaries gorgeous courtyard.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In addition to nine rescued turkeys, the Animal Acres sanctuary is also home to 25 chickens that were victims of Hurricane Katrina and traveled from Louisiana to find safe haven. Other adorable residents include two calves rescued from a Southern California stockyard, and over 50 sheep recently seized from a Los Angeles slaughterhouse by humane officers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Animal Acres &amp;ldquo;Feed A Turkey&amp;rdquo; celebration hopes to teach people that farm animals are living sentient animals who deserve protection, and kindness, too. Most states specifically exclude farm animals from anti-cruelty laws. There are no federal laws to protect farm animals from abuse. As a result, farm animals in the United States are raised, transported and slaughtered in conditions considered so cruel they have been banned in other countries.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The sanctuary is directed by Lorri Bauston who co-founded the nation&amp;rsquo;s first shelter for farm animals in 1986. Considered to be the pioneer of the farm animal sanctuary movement, Bauston has helped establish dozens of sanctuaries around the country and her efforts have been featured in several documentaries. For more information please visit &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.animalacres.org&#34;&gt;http://www.animalacres.org&lt;/a&gt; or call 661- 269-0986.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CBS News</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2005/cbs-news/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2005/cbs-news/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In Thursday night&amp;rsquo;s episode, the sexual tension also continues between Sara Sidle (Jorja Fox) and Gil Grissom (William Peterson).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;I don&amp;rsquo;t know if I&amp;rsquo;d throw him out of my bed,&amp;rdquo; Fox says. &amp;ldquo;But I&amp;rsquo;m certainly not chasing him anymore. I think Sara&amp;rsquo;s done with sort of actively trying to pursue Grissom. But, I still think that the window is open if he came to her in several episodes and said that he wanted to start something. I think she&amp;rsquo;d, she&amp;rsquo;d certainly not say no.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Early Show</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2005/the-early-show-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2005/the-early-show-2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Julie Chen:&lt;/strong&gt; After six seasons and a pair of spin-offs, &amp;ldquo;CSI:&amp;rdquo; remains a true original. It&amp;rsquo;s still a ratings powerhouse too with nearly 30 million viewers tuning in every week. I sat down with some of the show&amp;rsquo;s stars inside the CSI autopsy room to dissect the secret of their success.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Julie Chen:&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;ldquo;(voiceover)&amp;rdquo; In tonight&amp;rsquo;s episode, the sexual tension also continues between Sara and Grissom.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Julie Chen:&lt;/strong&gt; In season six you still kinda have a crush on Grissom, right?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; Well, I don&amp;rsquo;t know if I&amp;rsquo;d throw him out of my bed, &amp;ldquo;(laughter from Julie)&amp;rdquo; but I certainly not chasing him any more. I don&amp;rsquo;t, I think Sara&amp;rsquo;s done with sort of actively trying to pursue Grissom, but um, I, I think, y&amp;rsquo;know, I, I still think that the window is open if he came to her in several episodes and said that, you know, he wanted to start something, I think, I think she&amp;rsquo;d certainly not say no.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NEWS.com.au</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2005/news-com-au/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2005/news-com-au/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;em&gt;Reservoir Dogs&lt;/em&gt; creator may be known for his fondness for graphic violence, but co-star Jorja Fox says the change in pace under his direction only intensified the emotional stakes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;I was really surprised at how emotional it (the episode) was,&amp;rdquo; she says. &amp;ldquo;There were a couple of times I just had to sort of not cry and I didn&amp;rsquo;t ever imagine that I would get like that.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Guide</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2005/tv-guide-7/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2005/tv-guide-7/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;*&lt;strong&gt;CSI* PUTS SEX SCENE TO BED&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s not often that &lt;em&gt;CSI&lt;/em&gt; mixes business with pleasure, so when exec producer Carol Mendelsohn revealed in the September 25th issue of TV GUIDE that Grissom (&lt;strong&gt;William Petersen&lt;/strong&gt;) and Sara (&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt;) would &amp;ldquo;spend the night together&amp;rdquo; while out of town working on a possible quadruple-murder case, fans took notice. They also took notice when the episode aired on October 20, and there were three body bags but no naked bodies. In fact, there was very little Grissom, naked or otherwise. What gives? &amp;ldquo;Billy had a death in the family, and the script was rewritten to accommodate his absence,&amp;rdquo; Mendelsohn explains. &amp;ldquo;The stay tuned to see if the story line reemerges in a future episode.&amp;rdquo; Oh, Carol. Ya big tease.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Early Show</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2005/the-early-show/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2005/the-early-show/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Julie Chen:&lt;/strong&gt; If you can&amp;rsquo;t get enough of TV&amp;rsquo;s hottest drama, CSI:, then you&amp;rsquo;re in luck. Every Friday, we&amp;rsquo;re going to take you behind the scenes to show you how they make it happen. In last night&amp;rsquo;s episode, called &amp;ldquo;Secrets and Flies&amp;rdquo;, star Jorja Fox came face to face with an actor&amp;rsquo;s big challenge: working with a baby. Or did she?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; The camera comes in, you find a woman who&amp;rsquo;s obviously deceased, you don&amp;rsquo;t know what&amp;rsquo;s happened, there&amp;rsquo;s a pool of blood, and the only other sound in the house is of a baby crying. Well, first thing I wanted to say for the record, Moms and Dads, at home, don&amp;rsquo;t worry, no babies were traumatized in the making of &amp;ldquo;Secrets and Flies&amp;rdquo; that aired last night. &amp;ldquo;(Jorja brushes her hair back, grins)&amp;rdquo; It&amp;rsquo;s amazing how we can do these things, we&amp;rsquo;ll have a baby in a room by his self, and then the baby will leave the room and the actress will come in and do her part of the scene which really was fairly stagnant, as some of you might remember. So yeah, there&amp;rsquo;s tricks of the trade and so forth when you&amp;rsquo;re working with a baby. And often the Moms and Dads of those babies become pivotal in helping to, ah, create the mood for the baby that we&amp;rsquo;re looking for.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; It was, uh, a really fun scene we did in that show, yes, there was this woman representing this sort of baby bank, and how these babies find their way to mothers, and, ah, what&amp;rsquo;s sort of, ah, different for me in that respect is I&amp;rsquo;m, I&amp;rsquo;m the one who sort of got to keep my calm and watch all this happen while Marg Helgenberger, who of course plays Catherine Willows gets a little hot under the collar. And she does have a temper, we&amp;rsquo;ve seen that from time to time, but we rarely see her interacting, um, with anybody other than suspects that she&amp;rsquo;s almost positive are guilty of actually committing a crime.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;dl&gt;
&lt;dt&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; It was fun, it was really great to just sort of back Marg&amp;rsquo;s character up like that, and try and be the stoic one, you know, and get the information, and remain less emotional, cause that&amp;rsquo;s not really Sara&amp;rsquo;s forté.&lt;/dt&gt;
&lt;/dl&gt;

&lt;p&gt;:&lt;strong&gt;Julie Chen:&lt;/strong&gt; Now next week is &amp;ldquo;CSI Week&amp;rdquo; here on The Early Show; every day we&amp;rsquo;re going to have something special, including visits to the sets of &amp;ldquo;CSI: Miami&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;CSI: New York&amp;rdquo; and the original &amp;ldquo;CSI:&amp;ldquo;. Plus we&amp;rsquo;re going to get to hang out with the stars, so stay tuned for that.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Guide</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2005/tv-guide-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2005/tv-guide-6/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Question:&lt;/strong&gt; What happened to the Sara-Grissom motel scene that, according to TV Guide&amp;rsquo;s Oct. 1 cover story, was supposed to take place on last Thursday&amp;rsquo;s &lt;em&gt;CSI&lt;/em&gt;?! &lt;strong&gt;William Peterson&lt;/strong&gt; wasn&amp;rsquo;t even in that episode! &amp;#8212; Jennifer&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ausiello:&lt;/strong&gt; There&amp;rsquo;s a &lt;em&gt;really&lt;/em&gt; good explanation for this, and I&amp;rsquo;m going to let exec producer &lt;strong&gt;Carol Mendelsohn&lt;/strong&gt; give it to you. &amp;ldquo;Billy had a death in the family and the script was rewritten to accommodate his absence,&amp;rdquo; she says. &amp;ldquo;The scene itself was episode-specific, since the case being investigated took place several hours outside of Vegas, which placed Grissom and Sara in a hotel overnight. But stay tuned to see if the story line reemerges in a future episode!&amp;rdquo; I told you there was a &lt;em&gt;really&lt;/em&gt; good explanation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Guide</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2005/tv-guide-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2005/tv-guide-5/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Question:&lt;/strong&gt; Is it true that Grissom on CSI sleeps with someone on his team this season? If so, please tell me it&amp;rsquo;s &lt;em&gt;not&lt;/em&gt; Catherine. &amp;#8212; Susanne&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ausiello:&lt;/strong&gt; It&amp;rsquo;s not Catherine. At least I don&amp;rsquo;t think it is. It appears producers are heading toward a Sara-Grissom-Sofia triangle instead. Next month, Grissom and Sofia (new series regular &lt;strong&gt;Louise Lombard&lt;/strong&gt;) will share a heart-to-heart in his office, when Sara walks in and thinks she&amp;rsquo;s interrupting something more intimate. Cue flying sparks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MSNBC</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2005/msnbc-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2005/msnbc-3/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The ABCs of &amp;lsquo;CSI&amp;rsquo;: Who&amp;rsquo;s dead, who dun it and who solved it.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CSI: Grissom, you lead, we&amp;rsquo;ll follow&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sara, do you still work at CSI?&lt;/strong&gt; Sara is getting less and less screen time this season. Coroner&amp;rsquo;s assistant Super Dave seems to log more screen time than she does. Does a CSI have to get buried alive to rate a little more storyline? Or is it time for Sara to move on to a new lab?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Market Wire</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2005/market-wire/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2005/market-wire/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Boots are a fashion must-have this fall and Earth has styles to accompany the biggest fall fashion looks as reported by Style.com, the online home of Vogue and W. The &amp;ldquo;Summit&amp;rdquo; is an over-the-calf, butter-soft Nubuk leather design with fleece trim and full-length laces traveling from the top to the bottom of the boot, blending the Boho and the fur (or faux fur) looks that are all the rage. The &amp;ldquo;Alaska&amp;rdquo; also features fur trim with leather laces that wrap the boot to customize the fit and add style. &amp;ldquo;The Wrangler&amp;rdquo; follows the New Frontier trend in Earth&amp;rsquo;s version of the cowboy boot, which is accented with embroidered flowers. The versatile suede &amp;ldquo;Mirage&amp;rdquo; in Bark Brown, Beaver Tan, Lime green and Wine is also available in animal-friendly faux suede micro-fiber. The &amp;ldquo;Tofu,&amp;rdquo; another animal-friendly faux suede vegan style, is casual with plush fleece linings to keep toes toasty and comes in khaki, tan and pink. Earth boot styles feature elasticized stretch-gores or adjustable lacing systems to accommodate varying calf sizes, and so that you can tuck jeans into them, which is another great look this fall.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Celebrities such as Diane Lane, Salma Hayek, Marcia Cross, Amber Tamblyn, Jorja Fox and Tyra Banks have all put in their orders for the sought-after Earth boots this fall. [&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Media Post</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2005/media-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2005/media-post/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;IN AN ATTEMPT TO BUILD&lt;/strong&gt; a TV audience for its show about first-time home buyers, &amp;ldquo;My First Place,&amp;rdquo; Scripps Networks will Webcast the premiere episode on HGTV.com on Monday, Oct. 17, five days before the show airs on TV. Scripps also has arranged for Webcasts of the show to run on TVGuide.com, said Charity Curley, director of HGTV&amp;rsquo;s Web site.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The interviews are designed to &amp;ldquo;sex it up a little bit&amp;rdquo; Curley said, adding: &amp;ldquo;We&amp;rsquo;ve never done any celebrity programming online.&amp;rdquo; Other celebrities the network will feature on the Web include movie star Jamie Lee Curtis, movie and TV actor Natasha Henstridge, comedian Paul Reiser, Jorja Fox from &amp;ldquo;CSI,&amp;rdquo; and Persia White from &amp;ldquo;Girlfriends.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Matters of the Heart</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2005/matters-of-the-heart/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2005/matters-of-the-heart/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s kind of a funny thing about our show, &amp;lsquo;cause I say that the audience is almost split down the middle, where about 50% of the audience really just wants to, they want the stories. They don&amp;rsquo;t wanna get into the characters personal lives all that much. And then the whole other 50% of the audience wants always to know more about the characters. It&amp;rsquo;s a unique conundrum for the writers, and I think they handle it very gracefully and &amp;hellip; they&amp;rsquo;re always disappointing &lt;em&gt;someone&lt;/em&gt; and they&amp;rsquo;re always making someone happy. So they tend to follow their hearts a lot and just write what they feel, and, ah.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think this season we&amp;rsquo;re going to go back, at least in the beginning of the season, to a lot of the early CSIs. Should be very story driven, and ah, which will be fun! Cause it was kind of an emotional year. Character-wise, you know. All the characters, almost everybody on the show went through something deeply personal and sort of painful.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So we&amp;rsquo;ll wipe that out for a while, and probably do a lot of blowing things up and exciting chase scenes. And then get back again to the heart of the matter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;New direction&amp;hellip;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The episode that I did, Committed, with Richard Lewis, was one of the greatest working moments of my life. We had a lot of fun and it was dangerous. It felt kind of intense. And I&amp;rsquo;m really excited to see, you know, where Sara might go this year. She&amp;rsquo;s been so heavy for just a long time. There&amp;rsquo;ve been all these different things sort of working against her, and I have a &lt;em&gt;feeling&lt;/em&gt; that the hot air balloon that she&amp;rsquo;s been looking for is gonna sail this season. And, uh, she&amp;rsquo;ll lighten up a little bit and maybe we&amp;rsquo;ll return to some of those story-lines from time to time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja on SARA&amp;hellip;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think she&amp;rsquo;s almost, she&amp;rsquo;s a little social misfit, really. You know, I think her social skills are some of the weakest skills that she has. It&amp;rsquo;s awesome to play her, cause she&amp;rsquo;s so smart, she&amp;rsquo;s so good at her job. But when it comes to matters of the heart, or matters of friends or personally life, she&amp;rsquo;s completely awkward and uneducated. But sensitive to it. You know, I think she&amp;rsquo;s an emotional personal, and vulnerable, she&amp;rsquo;s just never quite comfortable in those areas of her life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;rdquo;&amp;lsquo;A romance with Grissom?&amp;ldquo;&amp;rsquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well I would definitely say &amp;ldquo;Never say never.&amp;rdquo; You know, I think the ball is in Grissom&amp;rsquo;s court at the moment. I think that Sara&amp;rsquo;s made a decision that she&amp;rsquo;s gonna move on. She chased him for about two seasons, I think, a year and a half, two seasons. I think there&amp;rsquo;s definitely a possibility that something might happen between the two of them before it&amp;rsquo;s all over. But who knows how long it&amp;rsquo;s going to be before it&amp;rsquo;s all over? Just keep my fingers crossed that it&amp;rsquo;ll be a while before it&amp;rsquo;s over &lt;em&gt;laughter&lt;/em&gt;. I don&amp;rsquo;t know.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Other projects&amp;hellip;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I produced this play in Los Angeles last year, and we just found out that it&amp;rsquo;s gonna go to London in March of 2006. I&amp;rsquo;m very excited about that. I guess there&amp;rsquo;ll be a trip abroad in my future.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;For the joy of it&amp;hellip;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I do play guitar. I don&amp;rsquo;t think I&amp;rsquo;ve ever played guitar well. But I&amp;rsquo;ve played guitar for a long time and I consistently play bad guitar. So I love it, yeah. And that&amp;rsquo;s something that&amp;rsquo;s always just been, sort of something to do for myself. I think it&amp;rsquo;s really nice to have things that you do, which is similar to the theater company that I&amp;rsquo;m involved with, that it&amp;rsquo;s really just for the joy of it and the adventure of it. Not really looking for any long term results or anything like that. It&amp;rsquo;s good for anybody to have that thing going on. So yeah, so I do. We jam, we play.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MSNBC</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2005/msnbc-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2005/msnbc-2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The ABCs of &amp;lsquo;CSI&amp;rsquo;: Who&amp;rsquo;s dead, who dun it and who solved it.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The crush rears its ugly head again:&lt;/strong&gt; When Grissom and Sara were processing the upstairs of the Lesters&amp;rsquo; house, there was an awkward moment when Sara said, &amp;ldquo;You don&amp;rsquo;t have to sleep in the same bed to have sex. Or to have romance.&amp;rdquo; Grissom couldn&amp;rsquo;t seem to get out of that room fast enough. Of course, this scene brings up another question I&amp;rsquo;ve had about &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; forever: Why do these guys always use their flashlights instead of just turning on the lights?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>