<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Career on Jorja Fox Library</title>
    <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/tags/career/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Career on Jorja Fox Library</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="http://jorjafox.net/library/tags/career/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>About Jorja Fox&#39;s Career</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/faq/career/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/faq/career/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-movies-and-tv-shows-has-she-been-in:7e6e72851422b97b7259805ca91208dc&#34;&gt;What movies and TV shows has she been in?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jorja Fox most recently starred in the CBS drama CSI. For a complete list, please check her &lt;a href=&#34;http://jorjafox.net/library/filmography/&#34;&gt;filmography&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-was-her-first-role:7e6e72851422b97b7259805ca91208dc&#34;&gt;What was her first role?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She first played the Rooster, in a children production of Chicken Little. Her first professional role was as Myra Pavlov in The Kill-Off.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;why-did-jorja-fox-leave-er:7e6e72851422b97b7259805ca91208dc&#34;&gt;Why did Jorja Fox leave ER?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since she wasn&amp;rsquo;t a main cast member, Jorja Fox had the freedom to film a pilot for a UPN series, The True Story. The pilot ep was reworked into The Beat, which was sans Fox and was canceled after a handful of episodes. She was then in two movies, The Hungry Bachelors Club and Velocity Trap, which accounts for her time between ER and The West Wing, which became her next TV project.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;why-did-jorja-fox-leave-the-west-wing:7e6e72851422b97b7259805ca91208dc&#34;&gt;Why did Jorja Fox leave the West Wing?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Her role on The West Wing was only a guest-starring role, so when she got the call for CSI, she was able to audition for it - twice. Originally it had been hoped that she would continue to be a guest star on The West Wing, however her commitment to CSI kept her too busy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;was-she-really-run-over-on-the-west-wing:7e6e72851422b97b7259805ca91208dc&#34;&gt;Was she really run over on The West Wing?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yes. During the filming of the final episode for the season, a limousine ran over her legs. Thankfully, there were no broken bones or other permanent damage, but when she auditioned for CSI she did so on crutches.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;does-jorja-fox-like-her-csi-co-stars-in-real-life:7e6e72851422b97b7259805ca91208dc&#34;&gt;Does Jorja Fox like her CSI co-stars in real life?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Off camera they&amp;rsquo;re all friends, though Jorja&amp;rsquo;s probably friendlier with Eric Szmanda, Gary Dourdan and George Eads, as they&amp;rsquo;re closer to her age. By all reports, Jorja&amp;rsquo;s friendly with everyone on the set, including William Peteresen and Marg Helgenberger.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;jorja-fox-makes-all-these-cute-innuendos-in-interviews-with-her-csi-co-stars-do-they-mean-anything:7e6e72851422b97b7259805ca91208dc&#34;&gt;Jorja Fox makes all these cute innuendos in interviews with her CSI co-stars. Do they mean anything?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Probably not, she&amp;rsquo;s just good friends with her co-stars. Go re-read the answer to &amp;lsquo;Is Jorja dating anyone?&amp;rsquo; She&amp;rsquo;s not dating Gary Dourdan, George Eads, or Eric Szmanda. I&amp;rsquo;m not going to dignify the questions of if she&amp;rsquo;s dating any of the co-stars who are happily married to other people. Please get your heads out of the gutter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;was-jorja-really-fired-from-csi:7e6e72851422b97b7259805ca91208dc&#34;&gt;Was Jorja really fired from CSI?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yes she was, for &amp;lsquo;breach of contract&amp;rsquo; on July 16, 2004. Basically, CBS sent her a letter, asking her to sign it, that stated she wouldn&amp;rsquo;t form a sick-out to bargain for the raise she asked for. Jorja sent the letter back via registered mail, while everyone else used a Fax. CBS claimed not to have received the letter, however the sign-for date on the registered mail supports otherwise. Jorja was hired back once this was resolved, however refused to return until CBS also re-hired George Eads, who had been fired at the same time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Of note, Jorja also did not agree to sign the contract extension (to remain on the show past season seven), which caused her not to receive a raise, like the rest of her co-workers. This may be related to why she chose to leave the show in season eight.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As of July 23, 2004 Jorja was officially rehired on CSI. If you want to follow the fun, go check the 2004 news section. There&amp;rsquo;s a lot to read.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;why-did-jorja-leave-csi:7e6e72851422b97b7259805ca91208dc&#34;&gt;Why did Jorja leave CSI?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are all these things I want to do. Some are personal. Some are professional. And I really need to do some of them before I get too old. If I thought the show were on its last legs, I would have tried harder to stay the course. But I feel like its going to be around for a while, so if I don’t want some of those dreams to pass me by, I have to get off the ride for a while.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;why-did-jorja-come-back-to-csi:7e6e72851422b97b7259805ca91208dc&#34;&gt;Why did Jorja come back to CSI?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In season nine, Jorja came back to give William Petersen a great send off when he left the show.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In season ten, she came back because CBS asked if she&amp;rsquo;d be interested in coming back part-time, and she said yes. She stuck around for season eleven as a part time main cast member, returning to the credits, and stayed till the end.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;has-she-been-nominated-for-any-awards:7e6e72851422b97b7259805ca91208dc&#34;&gt;Has she been nominated for any awards?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She was in the first round of nominations for the 2007 primetime Emmys in the category &amp;ldquo;Supporting Actress, Drama&amp;rdquo; (for her work in the CSI episode Empty Eyes). However, she was removed from subsequent rounds of the nomination process. CSI has been nominated (and has won) several times.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;where-can-i-find-her-movies-and-tv-shows:7e6e72851422b97b7259805ca91208dc&#34;&gt;Where can I find her movies and TV shows?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The TV shows ER, The West Wing and CSI have all been released on DVD. You can also find the movie Memento on DVD, however many of her other films are difficult to find on DVD or VHS. Her guest appearances on Ellen and Law &amp;amp; Order are both available on DVD.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;is-it-true-she-did-a-movie-for-free:7e6e72851422b97b7259805ca91208dc&#34;&gt;Is it true she did a movie for free?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The independent film Next Exit was looking to cast no-name actors for the small buget movie. Jorja knew the director and offered to play the role for no pay. The film aired at a Los Angeles area film festival in January 2005.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>