<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>2011 on Jorja Fox Library</title>
    <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/tags/2011/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 2011 on Jorja Fox Library</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2011 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://jorjafox.net/library/tags/2011/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>ET Online</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2011/et-online/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2011/et-online/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I like to think that I know Marg very well. And she&amp;rsquo;s one of the toughest, most stoic people &amp;lsquo; forget about woman or ladies &amp;lsquo; I mean one of the most stoic people I&amp;rsquo;ve ever met. And these moments where she&amp;rsquo;s kind of overcome are once in a blue moon. Probably the last time I ever saw that happen her dog died, probably six years ago. She&amp;rsquo;s got nerves of steel. So yeah, it&amp;rsquo;s really overwhelming. I lovingly call this job the &amp;lsquo;Hotel California&amp;rsquo;. There&amp;rsquo;s a line in the song that says that &amp;lsquo;You can check out anytime you like but you can never leave.&amp;lsquo; I&amp;rsquo;ve made that joke to her several times in the last couple of weeks. I&amp;rsquo;m like, &amp;lsquo;You&amp;rsquo;ll be back, don&amp;rsquo;t worry. You&amp;rsquo;re always a part of the team. You&amp;rsquo;re always part of the family.&amp;lsquo; And I think that, I mean, I believe in my heart I think it makes it easier to say goodbye to her right now because I believe in my heart she will be back at some point, some time. Obviously that will be Marg&amp;rsquo;s decision and that will be the writers&amp;rsquo; decision. And, you know, fate will prevail.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AP Celebrity Extra</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2011/ap-celebrity-extra/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2011/ap-celebrity-extra/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;When she&amp;rsquo;s not solving crimes on &amp;#8216;CSI,&amp;rsquo; you can find actress Jorja Fox on a surfboard. (Nov. 16)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I feel like I&amp;rsquo;m still learning to surf, you know? And that&amp;rsquo;s one of the things that I think makes it so fun, because it&amp;rsquo;s not really &amp;#8212; because I don&amp;rsquo;t do it competitively, I never feel like I&amp;rsquo;ve stopped learning. For me, it can lower my ambition, to go out and surf for a few hours, is so fulfilling and seems almost like an education. And you feel kind of completely at peace afterwards. I did notice how as my goal got smaller as I started surfing, my ambitions got smaller as I started surfing. But I don&amp;rsquo;t know if that&amp;rsquo;s a bad thing!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Probably the most recent amazing thing that happened &amp;#8212; I was out with a friend of mine, at a beach that we go to often. We have a pretty long whale season in California, and as we were paddling out, there was a whale making her way north, back towards Alaska. To be on a surfboard and to see that is almost hard to put into words.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily News</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/daily-news/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Nov 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/daily-news/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s a joke almost as old as show business itself. The aging actor - or, the more common stereotype, actress - who insists they can play characters decades younger than they are.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In our modern information age, though, it&amp;rsquo;s no laughing matter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In October, an actress filed suit against Amazon and its subsidiary, the Internet Movie Database, for posting her birth date on the latter website.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The world&amp;rsquo;s most comprehensive repository of information about films, television shows and just about everybody who&amp;rsquo;s ever worked on them, IMDb has become the standard reference for not only journalists and fans, but increasingly for folks in the industry who want to check out potential hires.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;In many ways, it is a privacy issue for artists, and it does tie their hands a little bit if there&amp;rsquo;s too much truth out there about them,&amp;rdquo; said Jorja Fox, who despite having her real age outed on the Internet when she was younger, went on to an impressive acting career in such popular shows as &amp;ldquo;ER,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;The West Wing&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;CSI.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Our ability to create characters and put a veil of believability around what we do - that&amp;rsquo;s the whole idea,&amp;rdquo; Fox continued. &amp;ldquo;The Internet&amp;rsquo;s been really amazing in a lot of ways, like getting people out there. But in other ways, it&amp;rsquo;s sort of made that job harder and harder to do over these years.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today, it&amp;rsquo;s character and everyday working actors - though much younger ones - who have the biggest problem with IMDb birth dates.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AP</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/ap/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/ap/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) &amp;#8212; There&amp;rsquo;s a feeling of dread on the set of &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; and it has nothing to do with a murder. Jorja Fox says they&amp;rsquo;re starting to shoot the episodes leading up to Marg Helgenberger&amp;rsquo;s departure after 12 years. She says they&amp;rsquo;ve been on &amp;ldquo;this really fun high&amp;rdquo; since Ted Danson joined the show, but now, they&amp;rsquo;re &amp;ldquo;about to be devastated.&amp;rdquo; She says it&amp;rsquo;s getting &amp;ldquo;pretty emotional&amp;rdquo; on the set. She says not a day goes by that someone doesn&amp;rsquo;t ask Helgenberger to stay.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jorja Fox says Marg Helgenberger is leaving just as &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; was getting to be fun again.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jorja Fox says the cast isn&amp;rsquo;t taking Marg Helgenberger&amp;rsquo;s departure well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jorja Fox says she and Marg Helgenberger talk about her departure, since Fox also left the show for a while when it got to be too much for her.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jorja Fox says if she could write an episode for her character Sara Sidle, she&amp;rsquo;d update fans on her relationship with William Petersen&amp;rsquo;s character Gil Grissom.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ecorazzi</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/ecorazzi/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/ecorazzi/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; spends her days investigating crimes on the TV show &amp;lsquo;CSI.&amp;rsquo; Now, she&amp;rsquo;s asking the public to do some investigating of their own. Not hair remnants or clothing fibers, but the way 10 billion farm animals are raised for food annually in the USA. She wants you to explore vegetarianism.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The actress debuted her new PETA ad at the vegan restaurant Sublime, and even helped with the cooking. They prepared spicy Singapore street noodles, &amp;ldquo;chicken picatta, and gourmet pizzas.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fox went vegetarian years ago right in the middle of eating a meat sandwich. She said, &amp;ldquo;I was having a meatball sub one day in Brooklyn, and it just clicked. I was in the middle of that sandwich, and I put it down, and I never had meat again.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Have you considered putting down the meatball sub and going veg?&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WFMY News 2</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/wfmy-news-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/wfmy-news-2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Washington, DC &amp;#8212; Ever wonder what&amp;rsquo;s happening with Sara and Gil and their long-distance, practically nonexistent relationship on &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo;? So does Jorja Fox. If she could write her own episode, she&amp;rsquo;d want to &amp;ldquo;look at her love affair more closely.&amp;rdquo; She says &amp;ldquo;it would be amazing if she traveled somewhere kind of exotic to see Grissom and see what he&amp;rsquo;s doing.&amp;rdquo; She says Sara may be happily married, but &amp;ldquo;she&amp;rsquo;s really lonely.&amp;rdquo; Fox says they&amp;rsquo;ve starting filming the episodes leading up to Marg Helgenberger&amp;rsquo;s departure after 12 seasons.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PETA</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/peta/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/peta/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; star Jorja Fox thinks that everyone should play detective and investigate how animals are killed for food. Jorja unveiled her pro-vegetarian PETA ad to an enthusiastic crowd Sunday at Fort Lauderdale&amp;rsquo;s gourmet vegan restaurant, Sublime.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She even got things cooking in the kitchen, helping the chefs with the evening&amp;rsquo;s delicious cruelty-free feast.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jorja went vegetarian years agoâhalfway through a sandwich. &amp;ldquo;I was having a meatball sub one day in Brooklyn, and it just clicked,&amp;rdquo; she explains. &amp;ldquo;I was in the middle of that sandwich, and I put it down, and I never had meat again.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; fans: Follow Jorja&amp;rsquo;s advice and do some sleuthing into the [&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.meat.org/&#34;&gt;http://www.meat.org/&lt;/a&gt; meat industry by clicking here].&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Boston Herald</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/boston-herald/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/boston-herald/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Animal activists and celebrities launched a new effort Wednesday to protect exotic animals by taking the &amp;ldquo;traveling&amp;rdquo; out of traveling circuses.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The proposed federal legislation would place sharp limits on the ability to transport lions, tigers and elephants around the country. Circuses say it would essentially shut down the animal portion of their shows.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Representatives from L.A.-based Animal Defenders International and Northern California&amp;rsquo;s Performing Animal Welfare Society, along with critter-friendly celebrities Bob Barker and Jorja Fox, held a press conference in Washington, D.C., Wednesday to introduce the new bill that amends the Animal Welfare Act.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;It&amp;rsquo;s called the Traveling Exotic Animal Protection Act, TEAPA for short,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; star Fox explained earlier in the week. &amp;ldquo;It will severely limit the traveling of exotic wildlife.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Narrowly aimed at preventing maltreatment of non-domesticated animals in traveling circuses, the bill, among other things, proposes severe restrictions on moving wildlife around the country in restrictive mobile accommodations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They claim animals suffer by being denied sufficient space to move around when traveling, and are forced to deal with unnatural groupings, such as incompatible species being kept near each other.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The bill does not address stationary zoos or other permanently sited animal attractions, animals used in film and television productions, domesticated species such as horses moved for rodeo or racing purposes, or circus horses.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Circus operators, of course, have issues with the proposed legislation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Ringling Bros. as well as other licensed, traveling exhibitors are inspected by federal, state and local authorities,&amp;rdquo; said Stephen Payne, vice president of corporate communications for Feld Entertainment, which produces the Ringling Bros. and Barnum &amp;amp; Bailey Circus. &amp;ldquo;This bill doesn&amp;rsquo;t do anything to improve animal care. We&amp;rsquo;re the experts on taking care of our animals; we&amp;rsquo;ve been doing it for over 140 years.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;We&amp;rsquo;ve looked at the way that the USDA has tried to inspect and license traveling circuses,&amp;rdquo; noted ADI President Jan Creamer. &amp;ldquo;The license fees that they charge only amount to about 13 percent of the cost of an inspection, so actually the taxpayer is paying for most of the cost of those inspections.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While Creamer is convinced that the bill will stop traveling wild animal shows in their tracks, Representative Jim Moran (D-Va.), the bill&amp;rsquo;s principal sponsor and chairman of the Congressional Animal Protection Caucus, suggested that circuses could conceivably avoid federal legislation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Right now, the situation is such that we feel the only way to address it is to restrict the traveling circuses,&amp;rdquo; Moran said. &amp;ldquo;If the circuses want to show us how the more egregious and unjustifiable conditions can be resolved, we would certainly be amenable to discussing that.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Payne countered that Moran rebuffed several earlier offers from Feld, whose corporate headquarters is in the congressman&amp;rsquo;s district, to meet with Ringling representatives who could explain the circus&amp;rsquo; animal care policies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Creamer said ADI has helped get similar legislation passed in a number of European and Latin American countries. She also noted that approximately 30 U.S. municipalities have enacted full or partial bans on animal use in circuses.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;The human-only circuses tend to thrive in places where animal acts have been banned,&amp;rdquo; Creamer claimed. &amp;ldquo;You get more jobs for people, and all of the workers who look after circus animals on a day-to-day basis also do other jobs.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;That&amp;rsquo;s patently absurd,&amp;rdquo; Payne said, noting Ringling has &lt;sup&gt;24&lt;/sup&gt;&amp;frasl;&lt;sub&gt;7&lt;/sub&gt; animal care and veterinary staffs. &amp;ldquo;If we are not able to present this vital part of The Greatest Show on Earth, really, it would have a dramatic economic impact.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;According to Creamer&amp;rsquo;s estimate, some 300 animals in 20 to 25 traveling circuses will benefit if the bill passes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not insignificant, but is it enough to satisfy animal rights advocates?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;If this were the last bill that ever got crafted to protect wild, exotic animals, I would be disappointed,&amp;rdquo; Fox said. &amp;ldquo;But I think it&amp;rsquo;s a really realistic start.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Inquisitr</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/inquisitr/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/inquisitr/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bob Barker&lt;/strong&gt;, the mythological horde of &amp;ldquo;Price is Right,&amp;rdquo; as well as &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; star Jorja Fox, assimilated with Animal Defenders International (ADI) as well as Performing Animal Welfare Society (PAWS) currently to deliver legislation to Congress to finish the pang as well as unsuitable conditions playground animals have been forced to endure.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Barker, the long-time animal rights romantic who late from the TV pricing diversion in 2006, trafficked to Washington to await the Traveling Exotic Animal Protection Act, which, once launched, will shorten the operate of outlandish as well as furious animals in roving circuses.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Exotic animals cannot be full of health as well as can&amp;rsquo;t even proceed being happy in the roving circus,&amp;rdquo; the 87-year-old diversion uncover idol explained during the Capitol Hill headlines conference, observant which roving circuses rest heavily upon animals which have been lerned to do tricks, which he pronounced is achieved with acts of cruelty. &amp;ldquo;They never know the day which is unequivocally pleasurable. We all have problems, though you all have great days. These animals don&amp;rsquo;t have great days.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fox, Barker&amp;rsquo;s luminary co-host, echoed the call for environment up some-more permanent residences for playground animals, as well as receiving them off the road.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Our kids demeanour to us for what is right as well as the kids demeanour to us for what is fun. â¦ If the kids knew how vicious as well as aroused these events were, we consider they&amp;rsquo;d essentially be really unhappy in us, for [going] to these places,&amp;rdquo; Fox said.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Supporters of the Traveling Exotic Animal Protection Act(TEAPA), indicate out which twenty countries &amp;ndash; enclosed Austria, Belgium, Czech Republic, Peru, Portugal, Denmark, Sweden as well as India between others &amp;ndash; have already upheld identical legislation, as well as supplement which some-more than the half-dozen countries have been shortly expected to follow suit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;It is time for the United States to stick upon this march of nations which is you do the right thing,&amp;rdquo; Bob Barker said.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For some-more report upon the Traveling Exotic Animal Protection Act conduct over to ADI&amp;rsquo;s website.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ADI International</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/adi-international/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/adi-international/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Congressman Rep. Jim Moran, Bob Barker, and Jorja Fox announce new Bill to end animal suffering.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Measures that could see an end to elephants, lions, tigers, monkeys and bears touring with circuses have been unveiled today at a press conference attended by Bob Barker, Jorja Fox, Animal Defenders International (ADI), and the Performing Animal Welfare Society (PAWS). The Travelling Exotic Animal Protection Act, introduced by Rep. Jim Moran (D-Va.), will restrict the use of exotic and non-domesticated animals in traveling circuses and exhibitions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;TV host Bob Barker and CSI&amp;rsquo;s Jorja Fox back the bill&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Known to 73 million CSI viewers as Sara Sidle, today &lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt; said: &lt;em&#34;It is time to say that elephants should not be kept in chains nor lions, tigers, bears and monkeys in small cages on the backs of trucks. This Bill has the potential to eradicate considerable animal suffering and I believe it will be embraced by Americans.&#34;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;n the coming months Members of Congress will be urged to sign the Bill. Jorja Fox concluded: &lt;em&gt;&amp;ldquo;Everyone now has a chance to end this suffering, people should contact their Member of Congress today urging them to sign the Bill. It&amp;rsquo;s a practical and reasonable measure to protect animals. Don&amp;rsquo;t take no for an answer.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ADI Jorja Fox Addresses Congress</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2011/adi-addresses-congress/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2011/adi-addresses-congress/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I do think that a question that some of you may be asking right now is &amp;ldquo;Well what about my kids? Can&amp;rsquo;t my kids have the same chance I did to go to these traveling circuses?&amp;rdquo; Or maybe these circuses your parents went to. And I thought about this at length, and I think the truth is that our kids look to us for what is right, and our kids look to us for what is fun.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And I think we can do more for our kids if we do the compassionate thing, the respectful thing. These animals do deserve our kindness, and they do deserve our respect. And I think that often our kids understand that better than us most of the time/&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If our kids knew how cruel and violent these events were, I think they&amp;rsquo;d be very disappointed in us, for bringing us to these places.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This bill is the right thing to do, and I urge you to let your congresspeople know that you support it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank you very much.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CNN</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/cnn/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/cnn/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Bob Barker, the former host of &amp;ldquo;The Price Is Right,&amp;rdquo; made an impassioned plea Wednesday for an end to what he described as an ugly side of entertainment: the mistreatment of exotic and wild animals in traveling circuses.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At a Capitol Hill news conference, Barker noted that traveling circuses rely heavily on animals that are trained to do tricks, which he said is accomplished with acts of cruelty.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;How do they train them? They have to dominate the animal,&amp;rdquo; Barker said. &amp;ldquo;How do they dominate the animal? They beat it, with clubs, fists, black jacks, ax handles, golf clubs. They shock it with all sorts of electric devices. They use bull hooks on them they even deprive them of food and even water in order to make them do these tricks.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Barker, who is well known for promoting the cause of animal protection, is championing the Traveling Exotic Animal Protection Act. The bill, which would amend the existing Animal Welfare Act, has attracted bipartisan support.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The bill would affect only traveling shows. It specifically exempts zoos, aquariums and research labs and rodeos.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rep. Jim Moran, D-Virginia, said that although the issue is not the most pressing concern of the day for Americans, &amp;ldquo;how we treat animals is a reflection of our nation&amp;rsquo;s moral character.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dr. Mel Richardson of Animal Defenders International lent his perspective from more than four decades of veterinary practice on the conditions of most, if not all, lions, tigers and elephants in traveling shows: &amp;ldquo;Imagine living all of your life on a queen-size or king-size bed.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But the concerns are not confined to their housing. Jan Creamer, president of ADI, said there is sufficient documented evidence &amp;#8212; gained from workers planted in some traveling circuses &amp;#8212; that many of the animals suffer from violent training and severe punishment.&lt;br /&gt;
Barker&amp;rsquo;s celebrity co-host was actress Jorga [sic.] Fox of &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;The West Wing,&amp;rdquo; who echoed the call for setting up more permanent residences for circus animals, and taking them off the road.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Our kids look to us for what is right and our kids look to us for what is fun. &amp;hellip; If our kids knew how cruel and violent these events were, I think they&amp;rsquo;d actually be very disappointed in us, for [going] to these places,&amp;rdquo; Fox said.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A recent incident in Ohio in which privately kept wild and exotic animals were released by their owner and ultimately killed by authorities, and a recent lawsuit against SeaWorld alleging the exploitation of orcas, have drawn attention to the mistreatment of show animals. Barker and his fellow advocates say the public is attuned to the nature of the proposed legislation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Similar measures have been passed in at least 20 countries, including Bolivia, Peru, Portugal and India. And, according to the panel, more than a half-dozen countries are soon likely to follow suit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;It is time for the United States to join this parade of nations that is doing the right thing,&amp;rdquo; Barker said.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FotoPeep</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/fotopeep/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/fotopeep/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bob Barker&lt;/strong&gt;, a well known animal enthusiast, and &lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox&lt;/strong&gt;, an animal advocate as well, had teamed up to help get three elephants moved to a sanctuary from a Toronto zoo where things were too cold.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And now they are in Washington, launching a bill called the Traveling Exotic Animal Protection Act.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The bill would:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;[â¦]restrict the use of exotic and wild animals in traveling circuses,&amp;rdquo; [and end the] &amp;lsquo;random cruelty and neglect&amp;rsquo; found in these circuses.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;About the bill, Bob Barker said:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Americans are becoming increasingly aware that circus animals suffer from violent training techniques and severe confinement.&lt;br /&gt;
Big, wild animals should not be part of the traveling circus and simply put, animal acts in circuses are antiquated and belong in the past, in a time when humans were ignorant about the needs of the other species who share our planet.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the bill, Jorja Fox said:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Congress has a responsibility to protect the welfare of animals and ensure public safety. A prohibition on the use of exotic and wild animals in traveling circuses is proportionate, responsible, the least expensive solution to this problem, and long overdue.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We call on Congress to bring to an end, once and for all, the abuse and suffering that has been exposed by ADI time and time again.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Similar bills have been passed in other countries and it seems strong that this bill will pass in the US.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Way to go!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Glittarazi</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2011/glittarazi/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/transcript/2011/glittarazi/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Glittarazi:&lt;/strong&gt; How does it feel to constantly be named one of PETA&amp;rsquo;s sexiest vegetarians?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; It feels amazing and embarrassing at the same time. I&amp;rsquo;m thrilled that I get on the list, and I don&amp;rsquo;t even know how that happens. It may have to do with the little bit of green that I slip them to put me on it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Glittarazi:&lt;/strong&gt; Oh! Okay! I guess my other question is how would you like to expand or take this cause one step further? What strategies do you have in place? Or what do you have going on right now?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; You mean me trying to be one of PETA&amp;rsquo;s sexiest vegetarians?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Glittarazi:&lt;/strong&gt; No, I think we&amp;rsquo;ve got that one pretty much well covered. No I think we&amp;rsquo;re talking about the one that you&amp;rsquo;re advocating for today.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; Yes! I&amp;rsquo;m here in Washington DC today and I get to be a part of this amazing group of people today. We&amp;rsquo;re launching a bill called TEAPA. It&amp;rsquo;s the &amp;ldquo;Traveling Exotic Animal Protection Act.&amp;rdquo; I&amp;rsquo;m over the moon, I&amp;rsquo;ve never been to congress before in this fashion. We&amp;rsquo;re going to meet a lot of representatives this afternoon. The bill&amp;rsquo;s out &amp;hellip; What can people do? People could get sort of involved. The biggest thing right now is to spread the message and spread the word. In order for any bill to have a chance in congress the public has to know about it, and they kind of have to get their congress-people excited about passing it. If what we came here today to talk about is popular and people agree with it, and I really think they do and they will, especially if they take some time to look at the information, then this bill will pass and .. These animals, these large land mammals that so many of us love and adore, I think really deserve better at this point. And I think that if we want to leave a planet for our kids and their kids, a good planet, the survival of these animals is absolutely imperative. We need them. We don&amp;rsquo;t just &amp;#8212; We think that maybe we won&amp;rsquo;t, but we actually do to survive.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Glittarazi:&lt;/strong&gt; Absolutely. So if you could star in a PSA with any politician, who would it be?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; Well! I&amp;rsquo;m going to just shoot for the stars and the moon because you&amp;rsquo;re asking me. It would have to be, you know, it would have to be the President, Obama.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Glittarazi:&lt;/strong&gt; I think you could probably arrange that &amp;hellip; slip a few greenbacks. So speaking of the President, seeing that we are in DC, is this your first time in the city?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; I&amp;rsquo;ve had the pleasure of being in DC many, many times throughout my life. I&amp;rsquo;m always excited when I come here. Usually when I come here, it&amp;rsquo;s for something really amazing, like this bill. I have yet to be to the Reverend Martin Luther King Jr. Monument. That&amp;rsquo;s on my list to try and do before I go home, it&amp;rsquo;s a short trip. I&amp;rsquo;m going to make it happen.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Glittarazi:&lt;/strong&gt; Okay. When you come into DC, where are some of the usual places you like to check out?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; Because it&amp;rsquo;s usually two to three years between visits for me, there&amp;rsquo;s very few places I go back to again and again, unlike the Lincoln Monument &amp;#8212; Memorial. I think I&amp;rsquo;ve seen it every single time I&amp;rsquo;ve been here. I love to walk in the park. But the restaurants &amp;hellip; It&amp;rsquo;s funny because &amp;#8212; I&amp;rsquo;m from New York City originally, and I would say about my own city what I would say, perhaps naively, about DC. And it&amp;rsquo;s that it seems to never ever change, and yet it&amp;rsquo;s completely different at the same time. I went to a really great restaurant last night that I&amp;rsquo;d never heard of and I&amp;rsquo;d never been to. I try to check out new stuff, I guess, when I come.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Glittarazi:&lt;/strong&gt; What was that restaurant called? Do you remember?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; Yeah it&amp;rsquo;s called The Science Club.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Glittarazi:&lt;/strong&gt; Science Club? Okay!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; Yeah, very good wine and beer. Vegan options. Lots of veggie stuff.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Glittarazi:&lt;/strong&gt; Awesome. Do you have any other upcoming projects that you&amp;rsquo;d like to tell us about?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; I&amp;rsquo;ll be working, fightin&amp;rsquo; crimes, I think for the next six or seven months. Also I have a little documentary that I&amp;rsquo;ve been working with a couple people on for a couple years. It&amp;rsquo;s about elephants in Thailand. Wild Animals are a passion of me. The story is really about a 14 year-old girl who travels to Thailand, learns about elephants, and brings that knowledge home with her.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Glittarazi:&lt;/strong&gt; Okay.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; That&amp;rsquo;s called &amp;ldquo;How I Became an Elephant.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Glittarazi:&lt;/strong&gt; Awesome.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; We submitted it to the festivals. So we&amp;rsquo;re waiting to hear. Wish us luck.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Glittarazi:&lt;/strong&gt; We&amp;rsquo;ll look out for that one. As a vegetarian, what are some of your favorite dishes or recipes you recommend?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; Well. I think that a good cookbook is imperative if you&amp;rsquo;re a vegetarian or vegan. Tal Ronnen has a terrific book out that I love. Baking is especially, I think, key. I think a lot of people think when it comes to cookies and cakes and stuff like that, you &lt;em&gt;have&lt;/em&gt; to have eggs and butter all over it. But there are some amazing alternatives right now. Definitely I&amp;rsquo;d start going on-line. PETA has some great cook books. They almost always have a couple of recipes on their website. Start there and get the book and you&amp;rsquo;ll have great food.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Glittarazi:&lt;/strong&gt; Okay, awesome. Well that you so much for taking the time to speak with us today. We hope that your new initiative goes well here.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; Yes, thank you so much.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Glittarazi:&lt;/strong&gt; We wish the best of luck.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jorja Fox:&lt;/strong&gt; Thank you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Glittarazi:&lt;/strong&gt; Thank you.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Washington Examiner</title>
      <link>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/washington-examiner/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jorjafox.net/library/news/2011/washington-examiner/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Former longtime &amp;ldquo;The Price Is Right&amp;rdquo; host Bob Barker joined &amp;ldquo;CSI&amp;rdquo; actress Jorja Fox and Rep. Jim Moran, D-Va., to introduce the &amp;ldquo;Traveling Exotic Animal Protection Act,&amp;rdquo; which will prohibit exotic animals from being able to travel with circuses.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Our kids look to us for what is right and our kids look to us for what is fun and I think we can do more for our kids by doing the compassionate thing and the respectful thing. If our kids knew how cruel and violent these events were, I think they would actually be very disappointed in us for bringing them to these places,&amp;rdquo; Fox said on the Hill Wednesday morning.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;I would like to see Ringling Brothers closed, It&amp;rsquo;s all animal exploitation,&amp;rdquo; Barker chimed in.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The 87 year-old animal advocate told Yeas &amp;amp; Nays the price is definitely wrong for animals who are forced into traveling circus shows.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;The price that these animals pay is that they live horrible lives, terrible lives. The day they die is probably the best day of their lives because then they escape the misery of the circus,&amp;rdquo; he said.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>